<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ab on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/ab/</link>
    <description>Recent content in ab on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2019 10:23:20 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/ab/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>work is going faster with tests</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/02/18/work-is-going-faster-with-tests/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2019 10:23:20 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/02/18/work-is-going-faster-with-tests/</guid>
      <description>10:23 Monday 18 February 2019 JST Although I have not gotten all the way to the part of MLAPHP that we are supposed to be adding tests, I am close enough that I can add some tests. They have helped a lot, like OMG how did I live without tests? It hasn&amp;rsquo;t been so long that I don&amp;rsquo;t remember what it was like, and I sure like this better.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>crontab -e as root vs sudo crontab -e [solved]</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/01/21/crontab-e-as-root-vs-sudo-crontab-e-solved/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jan 2019 21:10:29 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/01/21/crontab-e-as-root-vs-sudo-crontab-e-solved/</guid>
      <description>21:10 Monday 21 January 2019 JST I had a weird issue with crontab today.
If I editted the crontab while logged in as root, it did not work.
$# whoami root $# crontab -e ((( make edits ))) crontab: installing new crontab  But the changes did not work.
$# exit $ whoami ubuntu sudo crontab -e ((( make edits ))) crontab: installing new crontab  And the changes work just fine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>work and prep work</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/01/10/work-and-prep-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2019 13:55:38 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/01/10/work-and-prep-work/</guid>
      <description>13:55 Thursday 10 January 2019 JST One of the AB cronjobs has been throwing errors, but the job is still running.
I am in the middle of refactoring the code to use Dependency Injection; I don&amp;rsquo;t know how I broke something, but I cannot really go back to a previous version. Rather, I don&amp;rsquo;t know what version to go back to, and my local dev environment cannot recreate the error.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AB site progress</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/11/07/ab-site-progress/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2018 22:03:48 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/11/07/ab-site-progress/</guid>
      <description>22:03 Wednesday 07 November 2018 JST I have been upgrading AB&amp;rsquo;s PHP to the standards described in Paul Jones&amp;rsquo; Modernizing Legacy Applications in PHP. So far I am still in the Autoloading section, but have done nearly half of the classes. Almost all of the &amp;ldquo;data&amp;rdquo; classes are done, but none of the search or factory classes are done.
(I put data in quotes above because I think that is just a name we came up with .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>worked on AB</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/10/30/worked-on-ab/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 17:37:58 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/10/30/worked-on-ab/</guid>
      <description>17:37 Tuesday 30 October 2018 JST Still going through MLAPHP for the AB project. I guess I am about halfway through the step of naming all the class definition files so they can be loaded via the autoloader.
During this process I found Mabl which features a short domain name and some tools for automated testing. Pretty easy onboarding, and they are giving the site a good onceover every day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>work and work</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/10/18/work-and-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 17:35:28 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/10/18/work-and-work/</guid>
      <description>17:35 Thursday 18 October 2018 JST Today I got to hear about the production of silicone for the first time via Hitomi. Then about generating electricity with hydrogen (for the nth time) and then other ways to save energy for the nth time.
Just renamed class.translator.php to Translator.php so it can be autoloaded.
Falling asleep now as I write this while on the train headed to Akihabara. Nap now and hope I wake up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Confirmed no meeting</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/10/15/confirmed-no-meeting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2018 15:36:27 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/10/15/confirmed-no-meeting/</guid>
      <description>15:36 Monday 15 October 2018 JST I will work on MLAPHP AB instead.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>refactor</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/10/05/refactor/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 08:27:57 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/10/05/refactor/</guid>
      <description>08:27 Friday 05 October 2018 JST I found a solution to all my work woes.
I just had an interesting thought about my computer job, which I brought up in the meeting on Monday. My website client is AB. It is likely that I can find a company that can do the work I am doing for less money, but it&#39;s not possible to secretly act as a middle man and keep the money due to how payments are done now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>progress on multiple fronts</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/09/22/progress-on-multiple-fronts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Sep 2018 21:12:36 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/09/22/progress-on-multiple-fronts/</guid>
      <description>21:12 Saturday 22 September 2018 JST BH set up a Slack space for MKP Japan where we can discuss creating the organization and setting up some trainings.
I got a multi-month fix done for AB; now users can use the same filter on their custom list page as they can on the main list. I don&amp;rsquo;t recall why it was set up this weird way before, but it is better now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>moe joe work</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/07/16/moe-joe-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2018 22:39:03 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/07/16/moe-joe-work/</guid>
      <description>22:39 Monday 16 July 2018 JST Bah. I&amp;rsquo;ve been working for like 12 or 16 hours trying to figure out how to keep a button visible, but I cannot figure out this spaghetti of code, domains, css, and browsers to figure out what is hiding it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>work</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/06/20/work/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jun 2018 15:14:48 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/06/20/work/</guid>
      <description>15:14 Wednesday 20 June 2018 JST Lunched with Tomoko and Yukiko (first time to meet her) at SCC, talking about movies and fears (acrophobia, claustrophobia, arachnophobia) and then lesson with Midori, talking about spot AC units which do not need ducts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>work</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/06/06/work/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2018 21:33:07 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/06/06/work/</guid>
      <description>21:33 Wednesday 06 June 2018 JST I worked for JB at three different locations around Kawasaki Station today, as I do every Wednesday, at Solid Square, SSC, and JB main office. Solid Square lesson went pretty well; we drew mind maps of our favorite places and then said a few sentences about them. Then I had a break during which I Marco Poloed with Richard from ae911truth a bit and then worked on AB, nearly finishing this ticket since it received a bit higher priority at our last meeting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>worked on AB</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/28/worked-on-ab/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Apr 2018 20:35:11 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/28/worked-on-ab/</guid>
      <description>20:35 Saturday 28 April 2018 JST Good some good shiz done for AB today. Ran a DB update last night, and this evening added some calculated fields to a page. That was easy enough, but adding them to the output reports will take a bit more time to figure out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Got some AB done today</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/26/got-some-ab-done-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 22:38:42 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/26/got-some-ab-done-today/</guid>
      <description>18:18 Thursday 26 April 2018 JST 22:39 Thursday 26 April 2018 JST haha I forgot to write anything.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting https working on AB</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/19/getting-https-working-on-ab/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Mar 2018 15:43:36 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/19/getting-https-working-on-ab/</guid>
      <description>15:43 Monday 19 March 2018 JST Nice to see setting up SSL certificates for Apache 2 on Ubuntu is pretty easy. They even automagically set up a cron job to renew the certificate after two months. See /etc/cron.d/certbot
I had a problem for a minute because one .conf file had a domain and an alias in it. I ran certbot for the aliased domain and told it to go ahead and force https, but then that broke the main domain (which was the main domain) by forcing SSL and using the certificates for the test domain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>work work work all day</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/02/23/work-work-work-all-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 22:47:27 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/02/23/work-work-work-all-day/</guid>
      <description>22:47 Friday 23 February 2018 JST Sigh. Worked on AB all morning and then they were essentially like &amp;ldquo;yeah we don&amp;rsquo;t like it. Go back to the version that didn&amp;rsquo;t function, but looked pretty.&amp;rdquo;
I don&amp;rsquo;t understand their priorities, but I switched it back.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>work day</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/02/13/work-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2018 16:21:31 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/02/13/work-day/</guid>
      <description>16:21 Tuesday 13 February 2018 JST Worked at IL for ist today, and then with CE for MR, and then talked to Chika at B for JB.
Now going to AB to talk to T and S-san.
Tired, I would rather go home.
Oh, but I got past the tween issue I had with Godot 3
Yay!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>work</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/02/02/work/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 19:51:52 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/02/02/work/</guid>
      <description>19:51 Friday 02 February 2018 JST Yikes my previously-used JQuery CDN isn&amp;rsquo;t responding so I replaced it and now the main page of the site breaks. When did that start happening? What do I do? How do I find someone to take over this site? (that is my real question / I do not want to maintain it forever)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AB work</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/29/ab-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2018 17:23:51 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/29/ab-work/</guid>
      <description>17:23 Monday 29 January 2018 JST Had a good meeting with T at AB today. Nate got me the information I needed before the meeting and everything went well. Got them a new account set up and on Wednesday night I will transfer their server from our account to theirs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ab work</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/09/14/ab-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2017 13:52:29 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/09/14/ab-work/</guid>
      <description>13:52 Thursday 14 September 2017 JST AB said something changed suddenly. git blame says in changed in April 2014. AB conceded but asked that I change it back to the way it was.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>project management</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/09/01/project-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2017 16:41:09 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/09/01/project-management/</guid>
      <description>16:41 Friday 01 September 2017 JST One of my work projects has been in maintenance mode for years.
https://www.beargroup.com/ideas/agile-web-development-our-approach-project-management mentions &amp;ldquo;wing it&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;agile&amp;rdquo; as two methodologies. We are definitely in the &amp;ldquo;wing it&amp;rdquo; column.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>need to figure out email issue</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/08/28/need-to-figure-out-email-issue/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2017 17:14:05 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/08/28/need-to-figure-out-email-issue/</guid>
      <description>17:14 Monday 28 August 2017 JST aight I am going to dig in to why AB is not getting their email.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>work</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/12/28/work/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2016 14:28:39 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/12/28/work/</guid>
      <description>14:28 Wednesday 28 December 2016 JST Gotta work on AB more. I did a bit of CB work, then bought Fred&amp;rsquo;s 2017 calendar and mailed it. He likes the calendars from Japan because weekends and evenings get the same amount of space as workday hours.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yay AB defined_report thing works for a few different reports</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/12/06/yay-ab-defined_report-thing-works-for-a-few-different-reports/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Dec 2015 16:11:09 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/12/06/yay-ab-defined_report-thing-works-for-a-few-different-reports/</guid>
      <description>16:11 Sunday 06 December 2015 JST I need to make (sure) it work(s) for reports with JOINs in the query, but at least it&amp;rsquo;s better than what it was earlier today!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Good coding on AB site</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/12/02/good-coding-on-ab-site/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2015 21:44:02 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/12/02/good-coding-on-ab-site/</guid>
      <description>21:44 Wednesday 02 December 2015 JST Actually I don&amp;rsquo;t know if the code is good, but I&amp;rsquo;m having fun, and the new part of the site is doing 90% (and counting) of the things I want it to.
Basically there&amp;rsquo;s a report system which I made so they can create reports without danger of destroying data. There are some reports they cannot create with my interface, so I created another report system where I hardcoded the query and just let them run it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AB meeting</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/11/30/ab-meeting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2015 14:15:17 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/11/30/ab-meeting/</guid>
      <description>14:15 Monday 30 November 2015 JST Headed to meeting with AB.
17:21 Super great meeting!
Have lots of fun new things to write and a much better sense of what we need to write for the new user-type who will be able to log in to the system.
And finally Nate sent the invoice for the year. So they had a bunch of questions which I was fortunately able to answer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working on AB site</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/11/13/working-on-ab-site/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2015 11:23:06 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/11/13/working-on-ab-site/</guid>
      <description>11:23 Friday 13 November 2015 JST Been working on AB site this morning. Trying to sort out how to sort out some records with duplicate entries. Plus explain that I can add certain data, but it&amp;rsquo;s certain to be wrong in some cases, but hopefully those will be a small minority..
But they&amp;rsquo;ll be impossible to detect with code.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AB site updates</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/06/29/ab-site-updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2015 21:20:32 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/06/29/ab-site-updates/</guid>
      <description>21:20 Monday 29 June 2015 JST Yesterday or maybe this morning I finished a relatively significant change to the AB site. Now they can edit some records which were never meant to be edited, just logged&amp;hellip; but the logs are of human-driven changes and sometimes they have errors which need to be fixed, so they need to be fixed in the log as well. Fair enough!
Then got another request to log one more thing in that log.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AB site testing</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/02/19/ab-site-testing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2015 17:44:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/02/19/ab-site-testing/</guid>
      <description>##16:44 Thursday 19 February 2015 JST##
Spent 6 hours working on AB site, planning for how to migrate them to their new server(s) (web + DB). That was while emailing S about some problem with server running out of memory. That ain&amp;rsquo;t good. I boosted the allowed memory in config file, but would love to figure out what the actual problem is (more precisely than there&amp;rsquo;s a lotta records!)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>juggling data</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/02/11/juggling-data/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/02/11/juggling-data/</guid>
      <description>##09:33 Thursday 12 February 2015 JST##
Yesterday I worked several hours trying to get my AWS instance to talk to an RDS instance on a VPC. I set &amp;ldquo;Publically accessable&amp;rdquo; to true, set the Security group to (wide open/allow the AWS instance security group), but I still couldn&amp;rsquo;t connect.
My great idea now is to create an AMI based on the AWS instance, then spin up a new instance of the AMI in the same VPC as the RDS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fixed AB site issue that got delayed</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/21/fixed-ab-site-issue-that-got-delayed/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/21/fixed-ab-site-issue-that-got-delayed/</guid>
      <description>##12:16 Friday 21 November 2014 JST##
I finished the request that was made in August. It took close to 12 hours + 3 months. Oops.
Though the repo is currently private, the git hash is 04d5f55b8f0fcb3508920331858df0f89dee745e, in case someone comes across it later.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Started Phase 3 of AB website</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/01/29/started-phase-3-of-ab-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/01/29/started-phase-3-of-ab-website/</guid>
      <description>##4pm Wednesday 29 Jan 2014 JST##
Just finished meeting with Tomomi and Sho about phase three of their website. I&amp;rsquo;m thankful that Tomomi took into consideration the existing technologies we&amp;rsquo;ve used on the site when planning how to do the next steps. My next steps are to create some rough mockups and estimate time required to make the changes.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>