<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>train on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/train/</link>
    <description>Recent content in train on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2019 07:50:24 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/train/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Early morning snooze before work</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/09/04/early-morning-snooze-before-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2019 07:50:24 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/09/04/early-morning-snooze-before-work/</guid>
      <description>I slept on 南武 line from 登戸 to 川崎 station today. Nice to get a 57 minute sleep on a 30 minute trip. (The train sits in Noborito for 27 minutes before departing.)
Early morning lessons on Wednesday are back after the summer break. I&amp;rsquo;ve been teaching here for some years, &amp;ldquo;wouldn&amp;rsquo;t mind&amp;rdquo; if the lessons were taken over by someone else.
&amp;ldquo;Wouldn&amp;rsquo;t mind&amp;rdquo; in quotes because that was the phrase Eriko doublechecked with me to be true regarding the lesson.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream: Unstoppable Trains</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/08/30/dream-unstoppable-trains/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 16:53:14 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/08/30/dream-unstoppable-trains/</guid>
      <description>16:53 Friday 30 August 2019 JST One train came and slammed through the car on the tracks. Another train came on the adjacent tracks and slammed through the car on those tracks. A third train came through and I knew it must be a dream so I threw the garbage of the KKK uniforms under the train and watched it be carried away relentlessly by the wheels unstopping and then noticed the train was not that long so they could see it was me and I thought good thing it&#39;s a dream and then an old black man came by laughing and we laughed our asses off as they train curved its way slowly around the whole valley as I started to make up straight lies &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>headed home</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/07/11/headed-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2019 23:35:43 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/07/11/headed-home/</guid>
      <description>23:35 Thursday 11 July 2019 JST I&amp;rsquo;m on a local train in Shinjuku which will leave in less than a minute from now. I could have taken an express train which would get to our station faster, but would not have afforded me a seat to write.
23:59 Thursday 11 July 2019 JST Just woke up in Kyodo. Soshigaya-Okura now. Super tired. Too tired to write kanji.
00:02 Friday 12 July 2019 JST Express train.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I got a seat on the train</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/06/17/i-got-a-seat-on-the-train/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2019 06:17:53 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/06/17/i-got-a-seat-on-the-train/</guid>
      <description>06:17 Monday 17 June 2019 JST I got a seat on my preferred train. I arrived in just enough time, though it&amp;rsquo;s reasonable to say I could have ridden more slowly to be safer (down the big-ass whooo-hooo hill).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>great timing to catch the train</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/06/11/great-timing-to-catch-the-train/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2019 15:45:05 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/06/11/great-timing-to-catch-the-train/</guid>
      <description>15:45 Tuesday 11 June 2019 JST I walked gently toward our station while repeating the lesson for today. I included &amp;ldquo;I am determined to see time differently&amp;rdquo; an was intrigued as I walked past a man who was walking slowly; it felt right / fine to do so.
Arrived at the train station and just missed the local train, but whatdya know the next train was a Hakone Limited Express (or something) and the next stop is Shinjuku, and I got a seat (for 410 yen).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>hugged a woman on the train</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/06/26/hugged-a-woman-on-the-train/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2018 23:26:52 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/06/26/hugged-a-woman-on-the-train/</guid>
      <description>23:26 Tuesday 26 June 2018 JST Tonight in Noborito station, I got off the train to try to figure out which train would be fastest to my station. A woman saw me barefoot and asked where I was going. She kindly looked up my station and confirmed my hunch that the next train was fastest to Shin Yurigaoka.
While riding on the train together, she asked me why I was barefoot, and then what I was doing in Japan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>woke up in Noborito</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/04/woke-up-in-noborito/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Apr 2018 07:05:45 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/04/woke-up-in-noborito/</guid>
      <description>07:05 Wednesday 04 April 2018 JST This morning I woke up with a start in Noborito, where I transfer between lines from Odakyu main line to JR Nambu line.
&amp;ldquo;Oh snap my stop!&amp;rdquo; and bounced out of my seat, got off the train and was confused about how far down the platform I was.
&amp;ldquo;Where am I? This is&amp;hellip; ohhhh&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo; and went back in the train and sat back down in my seat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>free bus ride with babychan</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/02/17/free-bus-ride-with-babychan/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2018 21:17:27 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/02/17/free-bus-ride-with-babychan/</guid>
      <description>21:17 Saturday 17 February 2018 JST After work today, Lin and I met at the station and as a little &amp;ldquo;romantic&amp;rdquo; gift, I bought reserved seats so we could take Romance Car to our station. It was nice to just be able to relax all the way home. Curiously, when Lin tried to pay for my bus fare, it wouldn&amp;rsquo;t go through so the driver just let us on the bus free.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>morning train</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/11/13/morning-train/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2017 06:39:52 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/11/13/morning-train/</guid>
      <description>06:39 Monday 13 November 2017 JST A local train leaves my station at 6:15 or so. It takes 45 minutes to get to Shinjuku. It seems to always have all of its seats taken, but today I found a seat in the very last car. Only downside is I barely have room to get out my computer, and I am currently typing with one hand. There is dfinitely not enough room to have my elbows at my sides and type with good posture.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>caught express train</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/10/30/caught-express-train/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2017 06:30:38 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/10/30/caught-express-train/</guid>
      <description>06:30 Monday 30 October 2017 JST Wow interesting! Today I thought I had completely missed the express train to Shinjuku (non-stop from my station), misremembering that it leaves at 6:14. But it leaves at 6:21.
The train and I arrived at the station at the same time, but from past experience, not only will all the seats be sold out, there will be a queue of people hoping to buy tickets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>typhoony morning but trains were fine</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/10/23/typhoony-morning-but-trains-were-fine/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2017 14:40:25 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/10/23/typhoony-morning-but-trains-were-fine/</guid>
      <description>14:40 Monday 23 October 2017 JST When I took the train this morning at 6:24am, it was running on time no worries. However, apparently trains started running late soon thereafter. One of my students happens to live near my same station (新百合ヶ丘) and she said the trains were late, which caused her to arrive late. I am thankful for my policy of arriving 20+ minutes early.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>headed to work</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/10/11/headed-to-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2017 07:27:29 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/10/11/headed-to-work/</guid>
      <description>07:27 Wednesday 11 October 2017 JST I just had a nap on the train while headed to Kawasaki. I&amp;rsquo;m barefoot on the train, with my computer in my lap. I will put on my shoes once I reach the building where the lesson is.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>headed home from Osaka</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/09/16/headed-home-from-osaka/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2017 21:10:06 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/09/16/headed-home-from-osaka/</guid>
      <description>21:10 Saturday 16 September 2017 JST Simon drove me to Shin Osaka station so we could chat an hour longer. The last train for me to get home tonight leaves at 9:23pm, but I was able to get the 9:03pm train. Yay!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>working on (shinkansen)</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/09/15/working-on-shinkansen/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2017 06:51:37 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/09/15/working-on-shinkansen/</guid>
      <description>06:51 Friday 15 September 2017 JST On the shinkansen from Shin Yokohama to Shin Osaka. First stop is Nagoya (I think), 72(?) minutes away.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>guaranteed seat to Shinjuku</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/09/04/guaranteed-seat-to-shinjuku/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2017 05:26:33 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/09/04/guaranteed-seat-to-shinjuku/</guid>
      <description>05:26 Monday 04 September 2017 JST I have taken to takin&amp;rsquo; the super express train to work on Monday mornings. I get a guaranteed seat for a 20 minute snooze instead of guaranteed standing room only for 30 minutes. Only problem is the schedule: I end up arriving 45 minutes early.
However, I have never been late to this class, given that I attempt to arrive at least 20 minutes early.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Met B and R, headed to Hakone</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/07/03/met-b-and-r-headed-to-hakone/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2017 12:10:53 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/07/03/met-b-and-r-headed-to-hakone/</guid>
      <description>12:10 Monday 03 July 2017 JST Met R and B (Rhythm and Blues?) B and R (Banana Republic?) in Shinjuku today. I hope I helped them get to Hakone easily and quickly enough. We rode the fastest train that would stop at my station on its way to Odawara.
They have been studying in Taiwan, and came to Japan to check things out. They&amp;rsquo;ve been to pretty much all the good spots on the metro map of Tokyo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>train</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/10/05/train/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2016 15:31:03 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/10/05/train/</guid>
      <description>15:31 Wednesday 05 October 2016 JST I took the KQ line from Shinagawa to YRP Nobi, and then back to Kanazawa-hakkei, because I had loads of time between Paola&amp;rsquo;s and work. Still have loads of time, so I&amp;rsquo;ll probably walk to Fukuura now. Hopefully it won&amp;rsquo;t rain! (About 10 percent of people I can see now are carrying umbrellas.)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>nearly home</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/09/13/nearly-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Sep 2015 18:07:32 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/09/13/nearly-home/</guid>
      <description>18:07 Sunday 13 September 2015 JST On Keihin Tohoku line now approaching Oimachi. Will arrive in Kawasaki in about 12 minutes, at which point I&amp;rsquo;ll go to Wired Cafe to drink up some addictive internet, on which I plan to email Lin that I&amp;rsquo;m back, and look for a guy to fix my phone. I&amp;rsquo;m sure it can be fixed; just the chargin&amp;rsquo; parts are borked.
And maybe I&amp;rsquo;ll try to find a toot for integrating Soomla into a Unity app.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fast train to Fukuura</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/12/17/fast-train-to-fukuura/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/12/17/fast-train-to-fukuura/</guid>
      <description>##15:56 Wednesday 17 December 2014 JST##
Sweet this Limited Express train is fun to ride as it whizzes past like 7 stations between KQ Kawasaki and Yokohama (sorry, Travis). I might try to ride in the very front (passenger) seat next time. It features big windows to see out front.
To be honest, I&amp;rsquo;ve never really liked riding trains from KQ Kawasaki; there are several lines which use the same set of platforms so I can&amp;rsquo;t just jump on any train that comes by.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>meeting delayed</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/27/meeting-delayed/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/27/meeting-delayed/</guid>
      <description>##15:26 Thursday 27 November 2014 JST##
Was planning to meet T and M at 3:30 but M&amp;rsquo;s grandfather died and T forgot to tell me the meeting was therefore canceled. So we&amp;rsquo;re going to meet in about an hour from now. While waiting, I&amp;rsquo;m seated on Yamanote Line, traveling from Tokyo to Shinagawa, the long way around.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>heading home</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/23/heading-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/23/heading-home/</guid>
      <description>##15:17 Sunday 23 November 2014 JST##
We were gonna take the express from 西武秩父駅 to 池袋駅, but the seats were all sold out for the next train. So we&amp;rsquo;re on the local train that terminates at a station halfway to Ikebukuro from Seibu-Chichibu station.
I was willing to wait an hour (while eating ice cream) until the next train, but the others wanted to get going.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chigasaki bound</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/14/chigasaki-bound/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/14/chigasaki-bound/</guid>
      <description>##11:15 Friday 14 November 2014 JST##
I&amp;rsquo;m on the train headed to Soness&amp;rsquo;s house in Chigaski. She&amp;rsquo;s going to help me with ideas for teaching kids class on Wednesdays, and I&amp;rsquo;m going to help her with computer stuff. And we&amp;rsquo;ll get to catch up on life and hugs!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>