<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>oops on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/oops/</link>
    <description>Recent content in oops on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2019 20:26:14 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/oops/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Turns out I am *not* eligible for AWS free tier</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/04/18/turns-out-i-am-not-eligible-for-aws-free-tier/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2019 20:26:14 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/04/18/turns-out-i-am-not-eligible-for-aws-free-tier/</guid>
      <description>20:26 Thursday 18 April 2019 JST It turns out I am not eligible for AWS free tier.. Thank goodness for their billing alarms. It went off at $3 and I was like whhaaa??
It turns out free tier is only for new customers less than a year old. I have had my account for ages.. Why would their interface say free tier next to anything while I am logged in?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>walked from Nishi-Azabu to Yotsuya by way of Yoyogi Park oops</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/10/22/walked-from-nishi-azabu-to-yotsuya-by-way-of-yoyogi-park-oops/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Oct 2018 16:27:28 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/10/22/walked-from-nishi-azabu-to-yotsuya-by-way-of-yoyogi-park-oops/</guid>
      <description> 16:27 Monday 22 October 2018 JST １３時３０分に西麻布の授業後、４時１５分に飯田橋駅行く予定でした。 二時間４５分暇時間があったから歩く方がいいと思った。 マップを見たとほと んど分かりましたからマップ見えずに代々木公園の反対側まで歩きました。 あっ。表参道で右曲がりよかった。 戻りながら、ミミズただ見ました。ミミズが乾いた道頑張れましたから、彼を 強く太陽の光ないの植物の下で持ってきました。 彼が行きテラレったら、よかったです。 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>fixed my site</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/09/14/fixed-my-site/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 16:12:02 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/09/14/fixed-my-site/</guid>
      <description>16:12 Friday 14 September 2018 JST I broke my upload process, but I think it is fixed now.
Yep. It took 65 seconds to process and upload to my server, but it works.
When trying to get that number down, to a few seconds, I mis-remembered how it was set up and destroyed the public/ directory of my Hugo-controlled site thinking Hugo can rebuild it, but since the Hugo directory is already a Git repo, it was conflating the two, and things got really confuzzed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>accidentally skipped Skype</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/09/02/accidentally-skipped-skype/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Sep 2018 08:54:50 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/09/02/accidentally-skipped-skype/</guid>
      <description>08:54 Sunday 02 September 2018 JST 毎週末、母とスカイプで喋る。　I talk to my mom each weekend via Skype.
今朝、スカイプを始める予定の時間に「日本語も勉強しないと」と思ったから、母に英語で 「今日、日本語の宿題しないと」と書いた。 When it came time to Skype, I remembered I also need to study Japanese. I wrote as much to my mom in English.
母のため日本語の文字もじが面白そう思っ たから日本語で「今、日本語の宿題をしないと多分たぶんやらないかも」と書いた。 I thought she might enjoy seeing some Japanese characters, so I wrote in Japanese, &amp;ldquo;If I don&amp;rsquo;t do Japanese homework now, I probably won&amp;rsquo;t do it.&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>drops app price confusion</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/08/03/drops-app-price-confusion/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Aug 2018 21:45:05 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/08/03/drops-app-price-confusion/</guid>
      <description>21:45 Friday 03 August 2018 JST Apparently there is a big sale on Drops.

From me to Drops via their in-game help
Pricing is incorrect in Japanese yen 0.367 yen is like US$0.00367 I can do with that price! ;-)  I was impressed with how quickly I got a reply!
Hi, Thanks for playing Drops and contacting us! We&#39;re really sorry about any confusion and inconvenience! What you see in the app is the price for one month in your currency, but the total for the yearly subscription is billed as one up-front payment for the full year at the time of subscribing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>poor planning</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/07/29/poor-planning/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jul 2018 19:22:24 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/07/29/poor-planning/</guid>
      <description>19:22 Sunday 29 July 2018 JST We ordered some refrigerated food before heading to Niigata. For some reason it was not labeled as needing refrigeration so it sat on the counter for a day until just now when we got home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mt3: retested large marble</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/05/02/mt3-retested-large-marble/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2018 10:12:52 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/05/02/mt3-retested-large-marble/</guid>
      <description>09:05 Wednesday 02 May 2018 JST Yesterday I glued a piece onto the track which was designed to catch small marbles as they fall through the not parallel bamboo chopstick marble splitter.
Now it&amp;rsquo;s time to see if it worked!
Woohoooo it worked!!
     
09:18 Wednesday 02 May 2018 JST Uh oh.
After I tested the fix today, while setting up for the next frame, I noticed the large marbles could not roll past the piece.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>minecraft undersea monster room</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/22/minecraft-undersea-monster-room/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Apr 2018 20:07:04 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/22/minecraft-undersea-monster-room/</guid>
      <description>20:07 Sunday 22 April 2018 JST I decided to recreate this reverse fishtank in Minecraft, but for some reason it is all dark when I view it from the outside. Not sure how to make the underwater view look lighter.
I created the tank using a fill command, decided to expand it, and made a huge area&amp;hellip;
I think the command was something like this
/fill 4000 46 -5000 4050 50 -4800 glass_blocks 0 hollow  Then I carpeted the area with grass using something like this</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>git out</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/19/git-out/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2018 00:15:53 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/19/git-out/</guid>
      <description>00:15 Thursday 19 April 2018 JST  39c7bfa recent entries 17a339c removed : from titles 70ec6d3 TEMPoRARY commit, not including all years, and not cleaned up filenames 6086901 Added README 354c77e (bitbucket/master) p 1fbcd35 s c385ebb colon 492f2fc slash 3b91dec slash 40ba10c w ce5271f w 8be74d2 w afebd29 dot  The above shows a weird thing that happened to my git repo while I was messing with Fossil. The commit 6086901 is the first, and the commit 354c77e is the last, but it was shown right in a row.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>missed Mutsumi lesson</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/02/18/missed-mutsumi-lesson/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2018 20:48:43 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/02/18/missed-mutsumi-lesson/</guid>
      <description>20:38 Sunday 18 February 2018 JST Well crap. I am sorry to say I missed the lesson time as Mutsumi understood it. She was thinking 8pm every week, whereas I thought it was just for last week.
Sorry, Sarumama.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dirk Gently and the focused binge</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/13/dirk-gently-and-the-focused-binge/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2018 02:29:22 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/13/dirk-gently-and-the-focused-binge/</guid>
      <description>02:29 Saturday 13 January 2018 JST Heh. Well, it was pretty great. Dirk Gently&amp;rsquo;s Holistic Detective Agency was good enough that I just watched the last four (4) episodes in a row. At 40+ minutes each that&amp;rsquo;s 160+ minutes or about oh my god I have to go to bed.
https://news.newonnetflix.info/news/dirk-gentlys-holistic-detective-agency-season-2-date-for-netflix-uk/
Now it is apparently canceled, but I hope not. https://variety.com/2017/tv/news/dirk-gently-2-1202644035/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>party like it&#39;s 2017</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/01/party-like-its-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2018 04:25:22 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/01/party-like-its-2017/</guid>
      <description>17:18 Sunday 31 December 2017 -02 (São Paulo - Brazil) 23:19 Sunday 31 December 2017 +04 (Dubai - United Arab Emirates) 04:20 Monday 01 January 2018 JST (Tokyo - Japan) We arrived and went to the baggage claim but, fortunately thanks to Lin checking first, we discovered we could not get our checked baggage in Dubai when staying in hotels in the airport.
But what&amp;rsquo;s awesome: the guy was like beep beep beep and said our baggage would be redirected to Haneda just like that boom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>haha glass door</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/30/haha-glass-door/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2017 11:09:32 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/30/haha-glass-door/</guid>
      <description>11:09 Saturday 30 December 2017 -02 There is at least one downside to having glass doors. I walked right into one while it was closed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Note to self: do not bite cashew shells</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/20/note-to-self-do-not-bite-cashew-shells/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2017 09:14:33 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/20/note-to-self-do-not-bite-cashew-shells/</guid>
      <description>09:14 Wednesday 20 December 2017 -03 Here is Brazil, cashew fruit are available at any fruit stand.
I tried the fruit. So much water spilling out I think it should be called watermelon. Very stringy and not so delicious, but edible.
Once I finished the fruit, I looked at the stem looking thing.
Wait, so you&amp;rsquo;re telling me there&amp;rsquo;s a cashew nut in here? That&amp;rsquo;s awesome!
It was too hard to crack with my fingers, so I used my teeth to try to crack it open.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>oops schedule</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/07/oops-schedule/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2017 18:15:23 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/07/oops-schedule/</guid>
      <description>14:30 Thursday 07 December 2017 JST (written 18:15 Thursday 07 December 2017 JST)
While on the phone with BoA credit card to close my account, I got a call from JB: &amp;ldquo;hey yeah why aren&amp;rsquo;t you at work?&amp;rdquo;
Stomach sank link oh damn are you kidding me?
Turns out they hadn&amp;rsquo;t sent me the schedule for December, but I certainly could have been more proactive to check. I have set a reminder for the 28th of each month to make sure I have the dates in my calendar for the subsequent month.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>prevent unauthorized root access in OS X High Sierra</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/01/prevent-unauthorized-root-access-in-os-x-high-sierra/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2017 23:18:55 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/01/prevent-unauthorized-root-access-in-os-x-high-sierra/</guid>
      <description>23:18 Friday 01 December 2017 JST Oops. https://www.macrumors.com/2017/11/28/macos-high-sierra-bug-admin-access/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>forgot my wallet</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/01/forgot-my-wallet/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2017 13:16:38 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/01/forgot-my-wallet/</guid>
      <description>13:16 Friday 01 December 2017 JST Well! I discovered something new about Tokyo trains. If I promise to pay at the other end, it&amp;rsquo;s possible to get a free entry ticket. I did not think to take a picture of the ticket, but its kanji started with 無 and may have started with 無理 but I am not sure I can readily identify the second kanji.
Anyway, I called Ty and he met me at his station to let me out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>missed lesson</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/01/26/missed-lesson/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2017 12:33:35 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/01/26/missed-lesson/</guid>
      <description>12:33 Thursday 26 January 2017 JST Today was the day that I woke up with the sinking feeling of &amp;ldquo;oops; I wasn&amp;rsquo;t planning to get a good night&amp;rsquo;s sleep last night&amp;rdquo;
Xoxox to Lin for driving me to the station. I was only 50 minutes late for an hour lesson.
I&amp;rsquo;m going to buy an analog alarm clock.
22:41 Thursday 26 January 2017 JST 
I&amp;rsquo;ve named him Noisy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>stop fuckin around (and get on the bus)</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/12/23/stop-fuckin-around-and-get-on-the-bus/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2016 10:03:51 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/12/23/stop-fuckin-around-and-get-on-the-bus/</guid>
      <description>10:03 Friday 23 December 2016 JST We stopped in a rest stop at 9:47, and the driver was like &amp;ldquo;gonna leave at 10 sharp so&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo;
So I bought a drink and headed back to the bus, and honestly got a bit panicked when I couldn&amp;rsquo;t find it (because I hadn&amp;rsquo;t carefully noted its location based on immobile surroundings. (okay okay I didn&amp;rsquo;t really note the location based on anything but a vague angle toward the rest area entrance)).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>transcription</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/12/01/transcription/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2016 13:19:23 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/12/01/transcription/</guid>
      <description>13:19 Thursday 01 December 2016 JST I seem to have lost the
13:42 Thursday 01 December 2016 JST Oh, it was on my other phone.
Okay, here&amp;rsquo;s a transcription (maybe)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>panic pack</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/10/10/panic-pack/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2016 17:51:28 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/10/10/panic-pack/</guid>
      <description>17:51 Monday 10 October 2016 JST Oh man I&amp;rsquo;m leaving tomorrow! Today is a holiday so I thought it was Sunday and I&amp;rsquo;d be leaving in 2 days, but I&amp;rsquo;m leaving in about 24 hours, after a day of work, during which I&amp;rsquo;m supposed to buy some stuff for the trip. D&amp;rsquo;oh!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>forgot my keys</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/10/06/forgot-my-keys/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2016 21:28:12 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/10/06/forgot-my-keys/</guid>
      <description>21:28 Thursday 06 October 2016 JST I forgot my keys today, so I&amp;rsquo;m chillin&amp;rsquo; in a bakery in our station waiting for Lin to arrive so we can go home together.
21:30 Ah crap the bakery is closing now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>aw man</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/07/27/aw-man/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2016 12:38:29 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/07/27/aw-man/</guid>
      <description>12:38 Wednesday 27 July 2016 JST My online journal is facked. new.robnugen.com shows the about page but I want it to show the journal like it does when I test the site. wth is going on with it?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>nerve blister</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/06/20/nerve-blister/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2016 11:16:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/06/20/nerve-blister/</guid>
      <description>11:16 Monday 20 June 2016 JST You&amp;rsquo;ve probably hear of blood blisters. I have one on my thumb, a result of clipping some thick twigs with scissor-sized loppers a couple weeks ago. The skin of my thumb got caught between the handles as they thunked together and boom instant blood blister. Yay!
A couple days earlier I had done the same thing to my index finger. Scissor-sized loppers and oops blood blister on my finger!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>how to kill an external hard drive for only a few dollars</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/12/01/how-to-kill-an-external-hard-drive-for-only-a-few-dollars/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2015 12:31:54 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/12/01/how-to-kill-an-external-hard-drive-for-only-a-few-dollars/</guid>
      <description>12:31 Tuesday 01 December 2015 JST Step 1 buy neodymium magnets
Step 2 Put the hard drive on them</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yikes stripes I found an old bug</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/11/11/yikes-stripes-i-found-an-old-bug/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2015 15:45:40 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/11/11/yikes-stripes-i-found-an-old-bug/</guid>
      <description>15:45 Wednesday 11 November 2015 JST Man oh man I&amp;rsquo;m lucky there aren&amp;rsquo;t that many affected rows, but when AB client requested that four fields in their main table allow DECIMAL values and not just INTegers, I didn&amp;rsquo;t change the summary-of-main-table in the same way. So each time a record was saved to main table, its summary was saved with truncated values in those fields.
Dang.
Fortunately, there aren&amp;rsquo;t many times that decimal values are needed in those fields.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fun with physics</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/10/14/fun-with-physics/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2015 12:55:33 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/10/14/fun-with-physics/</guid>
      <description>12:55 Wednesday 14 October 2015 JST After a nice lunch, and a nice nap, I decided to break out the art supplies and draw some art!
I brought four blank paperboard panels (I think they&amp;rsquo;re called shikishi in Japanese), some pastel colored markers, and some bright colored markers.
Hmmm what to do, oh what to do. This is always my question when starting a new piece. I decided to go with bright green.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>my redmine question on superuser</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/07/11/my-redmine-question-on-superuser/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jul 2015 19:48:24 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/07/11/my-redmine-question-on-superuser/</guid>
      <description>19:48 Saturday 11 July 2015 JST Redmine Q on superuser took more time to research and write than to just rewrite all the time entries (there are 9), but fuckit; what if I had a million entries? or a quadrillion? (*)
I logged several time entries to an issue in project A, but they should have been logged to an issue in project B.
I tried using Redmine GUI to edit the time entries to be associated with the correct issue, but (because they&amp;rsquo;re in different projects?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Errorin</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/07/01/errorin/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2015 15:42:56 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/07/01/errorin/</guid>
      <description>15:42 Wednesday 01 July 2015 JST I learned something about CB site after pushing a change to live server: I need to test the mobile (and touch) sites locally as well. I had tested the main site but not the others, so the usability team tested them for me.
Errors poured in over night, but my phone was in quiet mode cause I wanted to sleep so I didn&amp;rsquo;t notice until morning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>late walkin</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/05/30/late-walkin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 May 2015 19:11:08 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/05/30/late-walkin/</guid>
      <description>19:11 Saturday 30 May 2015 JST Great lovely walk from Shimotakaido to Shibuya but now I&amp;rdquo;m late for drinks with Muchan and Sarupapa at The Pink Cow!
Along the way, I met Mat from England but from OZ for past 7 years or so. He&amp;rsquo;s on a week long jaunt through Japan on his way back home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>forgot my paper at toy store</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/05/12/forgot-my-paper-at-toy-store/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2015 18:41:24 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/05/12/forgot-my-paper-at-toy-store/</guid>
      <description>18:41 Tuesday 12 May 2015 JST Today I found a little computer touch screen terminal in Ebisu station: &amp;ldquo;Route Finder&amp;rdquo;
Hmm! Well in time for the olympics! I decided to test the machine by entering the two farthest cities I could think of at the moment: Wakkanai and Nagasaki. Now I realized Kagoshima would be further than Nagasaki.
Next week, machine, be ready!
I showed it to the guy at the toy store, but then forgot to grab it on my way out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>logistical oops</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/04/06/logistical-oops/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2015 18:47:13 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/04/06/logistical-oops/</guid>
      <description>18:47 Monday 06 April 2015 JST Gotta make an hour phone call tonight, but I don&amp;rsquo;t have my phone charger with me. D&amp;rsquo;oh! Bought one at the conveni.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Haha oops forgot White Day</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/03/15/haha-oops-forgot-white-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Mar 2015 10:01:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/03/15/haha-oops-forgot-white-day/</guid>
      <description>##10:01 Sunday 15 March 2015 JST##
I didn&amp;rsquo;t go outside yesterday and thereby completely forgot White Day. I think I&amp;rsquo;ll add it to my calendar for next year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apparently, U.S. Government Has a Secret System for Stalling Patents</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/12/07/apparently-u.s.-government-has-a-secret-system-for-stalling-patents/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/12/07/apparently-u.s.-government-has-a-secret-system-for-stalling-patents/</guid>
      <description>##14:33 Sunday 07 December 2014 JST##
From Yahoo https://www.yahoo.com/tech/the-u-s-government-has-a-secret-system-for-104249688314.html
Plus archive.today version https://archive.today/rBLww</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>meeting delayed</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/27/meeting-delayed/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/27/meeting-delayed/</guid>
      <description>##15:26 Thursday 27 November 2014 JST##
Was planning to meet T and M at 3:30 but M&amp;rsquo;s grandfather died and T forgot to tell me the meeting was therefore canceled. So we&amp;rsquo;re going to meet in about an hour from now. While waiting, I&amp;rsquo;m seated on Yamanote Line, traveling from Tokyo to Shinagawa, the long way around.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Did some coding for AB site</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/10/did-some-coding-for-ab-site/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/10/did-some-coding-for-ab-site/</guid>
      <description>##Monday 10 November 2014 JST##
(written 10:24 Tuesday 11 November 2014 JST)
I&amp;rsquo;m late writing this entry, but really late with the code. It was around the time that I was leaving the language school in Ebisu that AB client requested a change. The paper on which the request was made got moved by over-eager cleaning and I just found it on Sunday, whereas I think I had the meeting in August.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KTRU</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/06/22/ktru/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/06/22/ktru/</guid>
      <description>1:10am CDT Thursday 22 June 2000
 From: ktru Tue 16:36 Subject: Forgot to sign off To: Rob Nugen OPERATOR REPORT ERROR NOTICE This is to inform you of a problem in your entry on the operator report (log) for 6/17/00. You forgot to include the time when you signed off on the log. Please fix your entry the next time you are at the station. Thanks, If you have any questions please ask your Program Director or reply to this e-mail.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>gymnastics crunch</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/10/21/gymnastics-crunch/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/10/21/gymnastics-crunch/</guid>
      <description>Gymnastics
Wednesday 21 October 1998
Yesterday was big fun at gymnastics. I&#39;ve stopped practicing my round off back flips, and toned them down to round off back handsprings. Why? So I can do round off back handspring back flip, of course! I&#39;ve got to lower the angle/height/energy etc to get the back flip down to a back handspring. I&#39;ve also got to overcome my fear of bonking my head on back handsprings!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>