<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>bridge on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/bridge/</link>
    <description>Recent content in bridge on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 21:34:24 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/bridge/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>met Jon for dinner and bridge spotting</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/27/met-jon-for-dinner-and-bridge-spotting/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 21:34:24 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/27/met-jon-for-dinner-and-bridge-spotting/</guid>
      <description>21:34 Friday 27 April 2018 JST Jon and I ate burgers after we did a bit of a code review and MySQL discussion. Short answer: it&amp;rsquo;s better to loop through via code than do group+sort+filter+etc in MySQL.
After discussion, he showed me a lovely bridge across a river. It connects a building to a parking area with 15 bicycle parking spots on the far side of a river. 15 bicycle parking spots is a joke compared to the size of the building, and even the bridge itself, which features glass elevators on each side.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>headed to BRIDGE</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/02/06/headed-to-bridge/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2018 13:49:03 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/02/06/headed-to-bridge/</guid>
      <description>13:49 Tuesday 06 February 2018 JST This is the fourth to last lesson at BRIDGE. They started off strong, but then started to get busy quite quickly last summer. Two hours of lessons went down to 1 hour which sucked considering it took 3 hours round trip travel. But I kept at it. During December they cancelled January saying they will be too busy. So I had a nice break during January, during which they said the will end at the end of February.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>pics of Toshiba Muza bridge</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/16/pics-of-toshiba-muza-bridge/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2018 09:22:05 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/16/pics-of-toshiba-muza-bridge/</guid>
      <description>09:22 Tuesday 16 January 2018 JST These are from May and July 2017</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>