<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>nrt on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/nrt/</link>
    <description>Recent content in nrt on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2019 13:06:44 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/nrt/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>I&#39;m on a bus</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/10/03/im-on-a-bus/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2019 13:06:44 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/10/03/im-on-a-bus/</guid>
      <description>(written 13:06 Thursday 03 October 2019 JST)
I&amp;rsquo;m on a bus! I&amp;rsquo;m on a bus! Everyone, look at me; I&amp;rsquo;m on a nearly empty bus, headed to Narita, headed to Seattle to see Colleenie Bean Dawg for a day doing touristy things in the city and then having pizza at their crib.
(The bus is now waiting at a light like 5 minutes from my house. So funny how transit works on this planet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Delta Flight 166</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/03/13/delta-flight-166/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2019 20:57:13 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/03/13/delta-flight-166/</guid>
      <description>21:00 Wednesday 13 March 2019 JST 05:00 Wednesday 13 March 2019 PDT I am on the non-infamous Delta flight 166 from Narita to Seattle on which nothing of consequence happened&amp;hellip;. except I got a Bailey&amp;rsquo;s Irish Cream because it had the word cream in it and I thought I might like it.
It&amp;rsquo;s good!
I watched Christopher Robin movie which was cute. I considered watching Bohemian Rhapsody again but my first viewing last month or so caused the music to rattle around in my head for weeks afterward, and it is even back now as I write about it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>At airport on time</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/10/14/at-airport-on-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2015 07:55:11 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/10/14/at-airport-on-time/</guid>
      <description>07:55 Wednesday 14 October 2015 JST Near my gate there are two tables featuring four electric outlets, each next to a USB charging outlet. I wonder how much power they can provide. I can charge my computer, but could I bring a rice maker and make rice here? What about an oven to roast a chicken?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>