<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>scc on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/scc/</link>
    <description>Recent content in scc on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 16:58:02 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/scc/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>scc lesson with Lily</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/08/29/scc-lesson-with-lily/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 16:58:02 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/08/29/scc-lesson-with-lily/</guid>
      <description>16:58 Thursday 29 August 2019 JST Lily had not seen the (silent) video snippets for Marble Track 3, so I sent her a link on LINE after we finished looking at her study material. I told her about cases of normally countable words used as adjectives, (e.g. &amp;ldquo;He has a 3 year old.&amp;rdquo; vs &amp;ldquo;His kid is 3 years old.&amp;rdquo;)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>worked at SCC</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/07/18/worked-at-scc/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2019 16:58:39 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/07/18/worked-at-scc/</guid>
      <description>16:58 Thursday 18 July 2019 JST Today Naoko worked on introducing the history zone, including teacup carrying dolls, perpetual clock, and the early days of electricity in Japan.
What was it like back in the day when a simple thing like a few candle power light bulb could be so impressive?
Yasu talked about the Meissner effect and flux pinning. I would like to do an experiment.. will the Meissner effect keep a thing suspended above the magnetic table or is that only do to flux pinning?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>lessons at SCC</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/07/11/lessons-at-scc/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2019 16:58:41 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/07/11/lessons-at-scc/</guid>
      <description>16:58 Thursday 11 July 2019 JST Interesting to talk about the Meisner effect and flux pinning at SCC today. I have always assumed I understand the meaning based on the English presentation, but I felt a bit unsure when I was breaking it down in detail for Yasu as he was practicing his explanation of the same.
My understanding: when a superconductor is below its critical temperature it pushes (almost) all magnetic flux out of itself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>great lessons at SCC</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/05/09/great-lessons-at-scc/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2019 17:19:56 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/05/09/great-lessons-at-scc/</guid>
      <description>17:19 Thursday 09 May 2019 JST Four lessons at SCC today. One was shorter than expected due to a (hopefully small) medical emergency. Third lesson on the third floor featured discussions of the other three lessons and hearing they students really enjoy my passion for the topics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Work at SCC</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/04/18/work-at-scc/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2019 20:34:39 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/04/18/work-at-scc/</guid>
      <description>20:34 Thursday 18 April 2019 JST Back at SCC today with four student for 30 minutes each. Hitomi came in for Lily, who could not come.
I bought Cast Arrows, a new Hanayama puzzle because I could not solve it in 20 minutes. (not that I can solve most of them in 20 minutes, but this one looked like I could solve it and then I was like &amp;ldquo;woah that&amp;rsquo;s not going to work?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>last lesson with Sweets Party Attendants</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/03/06/last-lesson-with-sweets-party-attendants/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2019 21:33:17 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/03/06/last-lesson-with-sweets-party-attendants/</guid>
      <description>21:33 Wednesday 06 March 2019 JST Today was the last lesson with Sweets Attendants. (Their office is being shut down at the end of this month, but I am leaving next week for three weeks overseas.)
I met Tomoko at CPK at 11am and helped her carry pizza to their office where we had a party, including candy I bought from the conveni ond 3F.
The party was fun, but afterward I unfortunately let myself get sidetracked into dealing with some work related Excel spreadsheet crap, but got it sorted out by moving the spreadsheet into Google Sheets, where I can use the =FILTER() function.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>lessons at SCC</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/02/21/lessons-at-scc/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Feb 2019 17:29:51 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/02/21/lessons-at-scc/</guid>
      <description>17:29 Thursday 21 February 2019 JST Today (and most Thursdays) I taught at SCC in Kawasaki. Naoko reviewed for her test next week. Yasu reviewed the same material for his test sometime in the future. Azusa did much better with her fluency and intonation for her presentation. Liliko asked about the brochure that has to change soon to accomodate new opening times.
After the lessons I went to say HI to Tomoko and Midori, but Midori had the day off.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>work and work</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/10/18/work-and-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 17:35:28 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/10/18/work-and-work/</guid>
      <description>17:35 Thursday 18 October 2018 JST Today I got to hear about the production of silicone for the first time via Hitomi. Then about generating electricity with hydrogen (for the nth time) and then other ways to save energy for the nth time.
Just renamed class.translator.php to Translator.php so it can be autoloaded.
Falling asleep now as I write this while on the train headed to Akihabara. Nap now and hope I wake up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>work</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/06/20/work/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jun 2018 15:14:48 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/06/20/work/</guid>
      <description>15:14 Wednesday 20 June 2018 JST Lunched with Tomoko and Yukiko (first time to meet her) at SCC, talking about movies and fears (acrophobia, claustrophobia, arachnophobia) and then lesson with Midori, talking about spot AC units which do not need ducts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>work</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/22/work/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2018 13:31:04 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/22/work/</guid>
      <description>13:31 Thursday 22 March 2018 JST Right now I am in a coffee shop in Lazona, and about to go to SCC lessons for 3 hours, and then GG lesson for 1 hour.
18:02 Thursday 22 March 2018 JST Tears were apparently shed by one of the students at SCC; she is scheduled to present tomorrow and found out today that her presentation is going to be different than what she expected/practiced for.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>work work work</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/02/28/work-work-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2018 18:36:47 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/02/28/work-work-work/</guid>
      <description>18:36 Wednesday 28 February 2018 JST I&amp;rsquo;m on break now at JB, listening to the other class, where the teacher&amp;rsquo;s Japanesey English always kinda bugs me. But the students seem happy and have been in the class for a long time.
This morning thinking about C who apparently took my investment advice before bitcoin blew up. She quit her job and is overseas now. hahahah nice!
Then working on AB, getting three alleged issues sorted.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>headed to work at SCC</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/26/headed-to-work-at-scc/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2018 12:55:17 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/26/headed-to-work-at-scc/</guid>
      <description>12:55 Friday 26 January 2018 JST Three hours of lessons in SCC today; looking forward to it!
On the way there, I hope to figure out why my local version of mypowercircle.org will not compile with Hugo. bah. it was supposed to be easy!!
Ah. I had gotten stuck trying to add Japanese language version of the site, but never got it working. It&amp;rsquo;s better to just have an actual Japanese speaker make the Japanese site, so I cut out the Japanese content from the site and now it&amp;rsquo;s working again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>work yesterday</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/16/work-yesterday/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2018 08:39:06 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/16/work-yesterday/</guid>
      <description>08:39 Tuesday 16 January 2018 JST I worked for four companies yesterday. First was my lesson in Akabanebashi for Tariq. Then walked to Nishi Azabu for MR Laboratories client (company DNE yet). Then walked across the Nishi Azabu intersection to a lesson for TESS. Then bus and train to Kawasaki for 2 hours of lessons at my favorite, SCC. Came home and had one more lesson for MR Laboratories.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>five hours of work at SCC</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/13/five-hours-of-work-at-scc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2018 02:33:31 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/13/five-hours-of-work-at-scc/</guid>
      <description>02:33 Saturday 13 January 2018 JST Today was the first time I worked five hours at SCC. Due to a schedule snafu, 1.5 hours with Liliko chatting about her trip to Sydney and my trip to OZ, then Rick and Morty and Lucifer. I didn&amp;rsquo;t think of Dirk Gently, but she considered getting Netflix to see the others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>two hour lesson with Tomoko</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/11/two-hour-lesson-with-tomoko/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2018 17:59:27 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/11/two-hour-lesson-with-tomoko/</guid>
      <description>17:59 Thursday 11 January 2018 JST Today was the first of five 2-hour lessons this month at SCC. Today I helped Tomoko by making corrections to her written English. She plans to present the features of some of her company&amp;rsquo;s products. Pretty cool stuff like elevators and batteries, and elevators that run on batteries. We studied up in their cafeteria on the 4th floor, and then I went down the escalator to the third floor and went out the exit I had never gone out before (but had seen many times).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>