<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>books on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/books/</link>
    <description>Recent content in books on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2013 22:12:23 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/books/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Theodore and Cindy, another story that won&#39;t go far</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2013/03/28/theodore-and-cindy-another-story-that-wont-go-far/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2013 22:12:23 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2013/03/28/theodore-and-cindy-another-story-that-wont-go-far/</guid>
      <description>##22:12 Thursday 28 March 2013
10:09pm Thursday 28 March 2013
Theodore the Crow was hungry. It was cold and he had no where to go. Then he saw a light in the window of a cabin far way. He flew toward it and landed outside the window, wondering how he could get inside. He pecked on the window to get the attention of the man sleeping inside, but the man had just finished another flagon of ale and wouldn&amp;rsquo;t stir until nature called in the morning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jeff and Harriet, a kids&#39; story that didn&#39;t pass</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2013/03/28/jeff-and-harriet-a-kids-story-that-didnt-pass/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2013 21:49:57 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2013/03/28/jeff-and-harriet-a-kids-story-that-didnt-pass/</guid>
      <description>##21:49 Thursday 28 March 2013
9:45pm Thursday 28 March 2013
A snake named Jeff was sleeping outside in the sun. He enjoyed the nice breeze and white clouds floating softly in the sky. Then he saw a cloud that looked just like an angel! He followed it as far as he could, but then reached the sea and could travel no further. &amp;ldquo;Oh no! How will i catch the angel?&amp;rdquo; he cried.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Life of Pi</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2005/11/08/life-of-pi/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2005 07:42:14 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2005/11/08/life-of-pi/</guid>
      <description>##07:42 Tuesday 08 November 2005
Completely wonderful story.
I loved the ironies in narration, like, &amp;ldquo;the experience itself was different than that of our imaginations, where we sunned ourselves with fat bellies after the picnic like lions on the Savannah, then tottered home under the glorious painting presented by the Heavens in the evening. We died.&amp;rdquo;
I laughed several times.
I want so much for the story to be true. It truly does prove the courage of life can overcome astonishing adversity.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>