<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>disclosure on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/disclosure/</link>
    <description>Recent content in disclosure on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/disclosure/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Disclosure message from Dr Steven Greer</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/01/02/disclosure-message-from-dr-steven-greer/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/01/02/disclosure-message-from-dr-steven-greer/</guid>
      <description>##12:30 Friday 02 January 2015 JST##
I got an email from Dr Steven Greer, and am taking the liberty of copying the bottom half:
I am often asked about Disclosure and &amp;quot;when&amp;quot; it will happen: It already has. A majority of people already believe we are not alone in the cosmos and that we are being visited by advanced ET civilizations. More than 14 [countries have opened their UFO files and acknowledge this reality](https://www.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>saw Sirius movie</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2013/05/13/saw-sirius-movie/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2013 01:07:24 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2013/05/13/saw-sirius-movie/</guid>
      <description>##01:07 Monday 13 May 2013
12:45am Monday 13 May 2013
Thanks to Rohini and Movies That Matter Tokyo crew for presenting Sirius and Q&amp;A; by Greg Sullivan of jceti.org (Japan Center for Extraterrestrial Intelligence)
The movie presents four phenomena: many people have information about UFOs and are beginning to talk about it, free energy has been available for some time, there&amp;rsquo;s a coverup of this information from the secret government, and a small humanoid body was recovered in Acatama, Chile.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>disclosure dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2013/05/09/disclosure-dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2013 06:53:58 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2013/05/09/disclosure-dream/</guid>
      <description>##06:53 Thursday 09 May 2013
6:42am Thursday 9 May 2013
I was in a small room, controlled by the government that was a bit like prison but not completely terrible conditions and it was time for alien disclosure but they were doing it in a very specific way. Some spider webs were in my room in the corner, and there was a pillow but nothing else. I was asked to lie face down with pillow ofer my head and to cover my ears as the aliens were revealed and each person could be shwon the aliens under supeision and not get freaked out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ET come home</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2008/03/02/et-come-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2008 13:29:44 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2008/03/02/et-come-home/</guid>
      <description>##13:29 Sunday 02 March 2008
Exopolitics: The Study of the Politics of Extraterrestrial Contact: Local ET Contact Activity
 A recent increase of ET activity worldwide seems to back up this assertion as well as what seems to be a corresponding increase in world government disclosure.
 About a year ago I asked my friends at work, &amp;ldquo;have you guys been seeing more reports of UFO sightings recently?&amp;rdquo;
They were like &amp;ldquo;no,&amp;rdquo; and I didn&amp;rsquo;t bring it up again, but the thought remained in the back of my mind.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>not 2013... 2017!</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2008/02/22/not-2013...-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2008 03:45:30 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2008/02/22/not-2013...-2017/</guid>
      <description>##03:45 Friday 22 February 2008
Confirmation &amp;amp; Update on Secret UFO Meeting at UN
 They pointed out that the “unambiguous showing up” of extraterrestrial life – sitting over major cities - would occur in 2017, rather than 2013 as described in the earlier article.
 D&amp;rsquo;oh! This is getting out of hand! 4 years back in just one day! ;-)
I&amp;rsquo;m still pretty excited.
Powered by ScribeFire.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>woohoo!!  UFOs in 2013</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2008/02/21/woohoo-ufos-in-2013/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Feb 2008 17:25:36 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2008/02/21/woohoo-ufos-in-2013/</guid>
      <description>##17:25 Thursday 21 February 2008
Source Reveals Secret UFO Meeting at U.N.
 A date of 2013 was given as the time for official disclosure and/or when extraterrestrials show up in an unambiguous way. In the interim there will be acclimation related releases of information. Importantly, the source revealed that the events leading up to official disclosure will involve more ethically oriented extraterrestrials, and they will not pose a military threat to the world.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>