<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>geocache on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/geocache/</link>
    <description>Recent content in geocache on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 May 2018 21:57:19 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/geocache/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>All day in park</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/05/20/all-day-in-park/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 May 2018 21:57:19 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/05/20/all-day-in-park/</guid>
      <description>21:57 Sunday 20 May 2018 JST Great day at a park, but there were briars in the grass. Got to talk to Aaron for quite a bit and catch up with Francine who invited him. My student Misato attended and joined our little outing to find a nearby geocache which she was actually the one to find.
I napped for 30 minutes in the tent that went largely unused.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>foot massage and geocaching with Lin</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/05/02/foot-massage-and-geocaching-with-lin/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2018 18:41:57 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/05/02/foot-massage-and-geocaching-with-lin/</guid>
      <description>18:41 Wednesday 02 May 2018 JST Lin and I went to Giwado in Kanda, a foot massage shop I like, and got 45 minute foot massages! Ate lunch with Charu after that and then headed back home because we were tired and the weather planned to rain.
Ate ice cream at BR31 after I found my third geocache, the geocache in 新百合ヶ丘駅.
Lin joined me to find my fourth, but we could not find it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>today</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/22/today/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Apr 2018 00:06:34 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/22/today/</guid>
      <description>00:06 Sunday 22 April 2018 JST oops it is tomorrow already, but today Lin and I had neighbors Richard and Mai over for lunch, and then went for a walk with them and Fitz. We found a geocache.
https://coord.info/GLVJHGHK

I got a sharp flake of plastic splintered into my foot on the way home. Thankfully Lin was able to get it out relatively easily.
Today was the last day for Build Your Speaker Bio course; I will miss everyone and am really thankful for how much Soness helped with my speaker sheet.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>