<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>excited on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/excited/</link>
    <description>Recent content in excited on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2019 23:59:59 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/excited/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>I performed stand up comedy!</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/09/13/i-performed-stand-up-comedy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2019 23:59:59 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/09/13/i-performed-stand-up-comedy/</guid>
      <description>(adapted from my note last night to Mark)
I went to a stand-up comedy open mic tonight and ended up doing a set (my first ever!)
Several jokes went well, a couple did not; one of those is not recoverable in any way I can think of.
Soness said it was really good that I used contents of the room for several of my bits.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Remembering Past Lives workshop today</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/09/07/remembering-past-lives-workshop-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2019 12:54:45 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/09/07/remembering-past-lives-workshop-today/</guid>
      <description>I am excited about Remembering Past Lives workshop today
(written 17:13 Thursday 12 September 2019 JST:)
Two people in attendance and had a good time! Great to hear their questions at the beginning. One was &amp;ldquo;What&amp;rsquo;s the process?&amp;rdquo;
Each participant gets into a relaxed position, usually either sitting in a chair, or laying down, or otherwise sitting against something comfortable. I will spend a few minutes leading you through a relaxation process, whereby you let your body relax and keep your mind awake.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yomiuriland with Lin and Mikarin</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/04/13/yomiuriland-with-lin-and-mikarin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2019 09:13:16 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/04/13/yomiuriland-with-lin-and-mikarin/</guid>
      <description> 09:13 Saturday 13 April 2019 JST Excited to go to Yomiuriland with Lin and Mikarin today!
21:22 Saturday 13 April 2019 JST Just got back home, though we left Yomiuriland around 5pm. Pretty early from my point of view, but they were both tired.
Good times.
       
Francois on Bandit:
  Squealing on waterslide:
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>met with Paul about The Men&#39;s Work</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/10/05/met-with-paul-about-the-mens-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 19:53:05 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/10/05/met-with-paul-about-the-mens-work/</guid>
      <description>19:53 Friday 05 October 2018 JST Exciting MKP Tokyo news!
I sent this to my online Integration Group.
I just got confirmation: I will be co-facilitating a 3-week online MKP introduction called The Men&#39;s Work https://mkpusa.org/themenswork/ with Paul Newell, who is currently co-facilitating it in the US. On Fridays, 7pm - 8:30pm (Japan time), November 3rd, 10th, and 17th, we will do this online training for men in Tokyo. Once we run this 3 week series of meetings a couple of times, I will create a new men&#39;s circle in Gotanda (Tokyo) on Fridays for men who are interested.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Excited (and scared)</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/09/06/excited-and-scared/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Sep 2018 20:31:29 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/09/06/excited-and-scared/</guid>
      <description>20:31 Thursday 06 September 2018 JST I&amp;rsquo;m excited when I think about my vision, and I&amp;rsquo;m scared what I think about implementing it.
I have been leading Tokyo men&amp;rsquo;s Circle for three years, And my vision is to create more circles that are empowered to continue doing their own emotional growth work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Giant Post Hole Digger!</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/07/29/giant-post-hole-digger/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jul 2015 16:17:20 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/07/29/giant-post-hole-digger/</guid>
      <description>16:17 Wednesday 29 July 2015 JST Oh my gosh wow!!! I like watching construction so I often take pictures of construction sites. Today I was having a gander at new building construction near 金沢八景駅 and I noticed a big digger thing suspended over a large vertical tube. Then I noticed the tube was slowly rotating!
I started taking video with Periscope (so it&amp;rsquo;s online now, even before this message is written) and stepped over a fence, which gained the attention from an English speaking security guard!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yay Travis and Yumi are staying in Tokyo!</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/06/yay-travis-and-yumi-are-staying-in-tokyo/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/06/yay-travis-and-yumi-are-staying-in-tokyo/</guid>
      <description>##11:58 Thursday 06 November 2014 JST##
Yay! Travis and Yumi are staying in Tokyo!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thanks to Travis for refactoring the code!</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/01/thanks-to-travis-for-refactoring-the-code/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/01/thanks-to-travis-for-refactoring-the-code/</guid>
      <description>##02:12 Sunday 02 November 2014 JST##
Got an email from Travis today indicating that he refactored my Hakyll installation. Whoohoo!!
The refactorization he&amp;rsquo;s done so far is visible here.
The biggest changes (in terms of me not understanding them well) are in one file. https://github.com/TravisCardwell/hakyll-journal/commit/05416e71fbbf0f910bcc19717ee88d7ae810c9bd.
I&amp;rsquo;m going to put all his changes into the &amp;lsquo;master&amp;rsquo; branch, merge them into my recently created &amp;lsquo;rob&amp;rsquo; branch, then replace my personalized content in master with some generic stuff so it&amp;rsquo;s easier for people to use this repo for their own Hakyll installations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Got Inbox invite from Genkiman Dan!!</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/10/31/got-inbox-invite-from-genkiman-dan/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/10/31/got-inbox-invite-from-genkiman-dan/</guid>
      <description>##11:12 Friday 31 October 2014 JST##
Hooray!
I apparently have some invitations to hand out, so email me if you want one.
##11:30##
In the first 3 minutes of using it (from my desktop), I archived ~200 messages quite easily.
Thanks you Inbox team!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>my image is on the cover of New Mind!</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2012/11/23/my-image-is-on-the-cover-of-new-mind/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2012 11:45:44 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2012/11/23/my-image-is-on-the-cover-of-new-mind/</guid>
      <description>##11:45 Friday 23 November 2012
 Special thanks to Paola for suggesting the idea of a cover for his book! Special thanks to Y V Chawla for putting my cover on his book!!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>yippee!!</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2001/02/11/yippee/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2001/02/11/yippee/</guid>
      <description>12:25am Monday 12 February 2001
In about 24 hours we will be on a 747 in Los Angeles going, &#34;oh my god! We&#39;re on a seven forty seven!!!&#34;
I have just been using my new Handspring Visor after exchanging my old one for a new one because my old one was draining batteries at a ridiculously fast clip. My thankful intention is that I&#39;ll be able to write tons and tons of great stuff and move it to my website once I get home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>laura!</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/08/31/laura/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/08/31/laura/</guid>
      <description>4:05pm Thursday 31 August 2000
Cute Wende is sleeping on the couch here at work. She now has Thursdays off from work. She brought lunch for us from (guess where?) James Coney Island and then she was lookin&amp;rsquo; pretty sleepy and I encouraged her to sleep. She was thinking 20 minutes, but it&amp;rsquo;s been longer than that now and I don&amp;rsquo;t think she has stirred.
I&amp;rsquo;ve been chatting over AIM with a few youth and all are excited about Tulsa Rally this weekend!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>keyboard!!</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/07/06/keyboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/07/06/keyboard/</guid>
      <description>1:10pm Thursday 06 July 2000
Wow!!!
This is pretty frikkin&amp;rsquo; fly! I just received my stowaway keyboard for my Handspring Visor! I can now write journal entries so crazy super fast anywhere I go! It fold into fourths and fits into my pocket!
It&amp;rsquo;s a bit weird to have the keyboard slightly flexing when I hit keys on the near the ends of the keyboard, like backspace and shift, but I totally love it!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yay!!!</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/04/25/yay/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/04/25/yay/</guid>
      <description>6:50pm CDT Tuesday 25 April 2000
We have a dial tone at home!!! I have just moved all my journal entries online from my computer. Look for names that start with PP up above.
From our house, I called Wende on her cell phone.
&amp;ldquo;Hey Wende, do you hear that noise?&amp;rdquo; I was walking on the squeaky part of our floor between our bedroom and bathroom.
&amp;ldquo;Yeah, what is it?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior!</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1987/05/31/senior/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 May 1987 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1987/05/31/senior/</guid>
      <description>(transcribed 9:15am CST Friday 31 January 2003)
1:00AM Sunday May 31, 1987
I am out of school. I am a senior! I passed Spanish final with a 72. I got an 86 in History for the last 6 weeks. That&#39;s great! I thought I failed. Maybe we will grab that room in church today. Good Night.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>