<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>todo on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/todo/</link>
    <description>Recent content in todo on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2018 13:41:38 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/todo/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>to do today</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/10/11/to-do-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2018 13:41:38 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/10/11/to-do-today/</guid>
      <description> 13:41 Thursday 11 October 2018 JST  contact BH about MKP local site write MT3 entry go to SCC update Redmine for AB work done recently teach at SCC go to Akihabara teach in Akihabara go home eat Japanese homework Japanese lesson check emails from TY update MT3 site to have latest video on top page  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>plans for today and forever</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/08/12/plans-for-today-and-forever/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Aug 2018 08:25:50 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/08/12/plans-for-today-and-forever/</guid>
      <description>08:25 Sunday 12 August 2018 JST After watching &amp;ldquo;A Journey Towards Inner Beauty,&amp;rdquo; Shirley Liu being interviewed on The Happy Mindset,
  I have been thinking about my morning routine. Today I came upon a grand idea to exercise each morning by walking around my local area for perhaps 20 or 30 minutes on days that I do not have to leave at 5:45 in the morning.
Lin walked with me today, and we saw some interesting old (and not as interesting new) houses in our neighborhood on streets I had never previously used.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>todo book</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/08/10/todo-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Aug 2018 09:46:31 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/08/10/todo-book/</guid>
      <description>09:46 Friday 10 August 2018 JST I bought a book that has become my todo book. It&amp;rsquo;s as portable as my phone and even more reliable in terms of battery power. I bought it on Tuesday and have used it daily since then. Wow four days in total.
So far I have used a single page per day. (It&amp;rsquo;s 91mm x 160mm x 6mm, featuring 96 pages and two covers within the 6mm thickness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>things to do</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/05/25/things-to-do/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2018 23:12:54 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/05/25/things-to-do/</guid>
      <description>23:12 Friday 25 May 2018 JST  Ask for help. Imagine that we live in a world of abundance. Create more time for heart space. The team can be bigger than you think. Focus on PITs and ST1s and IGFTs. Reach out to men. Building relationship as a bridge to teambuilding. Find the sprouts and water the sprouts. Use the corporate structure to keep things moving correctly, but don&amp;rsquo;t get lost in the corporate structure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>complice staleness</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/05/13/complice-staleness/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 May 2018 12:53:38 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/05/13/complice-staleness/</guid>
      <description>12:53 Sunday 13 May 2018 JST I wrote this:
 I have been using Complice for a while and I am at a stage where I am reminded to do a few things that I might not have remembered, but I am not excited to craft my things to do.
I think part of the problem is I have a bunch of stuff coming in from Workflowy, which includes little reminders (wear a belt, which I sometimes forget) and (do not eat after 9pm, which I sometimes ignore)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>productive day</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/17/productive-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Mar 2018 11:21:11 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/17/productive-day/</guid>
      <description>11:21 Saturday 17 March 2018 JST St Patrick&amp;rsquo;s Day today and I wrote a letter to Ma, and all of these so far
2) eat well 2) brush teeth in morning 2) do ten pushups 2) do 40 second plank 2) do 45 kettlebell lifts &amp;amp;) write quick letter to Ma 6) write Ma&#39;s address on envelope &amp;amp;) target complete above by 10am 3) one pomo try to run on hardware 2) do ten more pushups 2) do 40 second plank again 3) one pomo try to run on hardware &amp;amp;) target complete above by 11:30am 0) do two pomos of hypnotherapy &amp;amp;) target complete above by 12:30pm  Plus started the laundry and spent some time with babychan, who is also getting her stuff done.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>things to do</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/13/things-to-do/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Mar 2018 01:31:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/13/things-to-do/</guid>
      <description>01:31 Tuesday 13 March 2018 JST Chillin at airport now in Portland, about to go home. Sad that I did not connect with Colleen or anyone else who may be here.
Ecstatic about deep transformational work and experience I had.
But that&amp;rsquo;s not why I am writing.
Here&amp;rsquo;s my things to do:
1) copy things to do here 2) add new Complice Goal of Connect with Babychan 3) copy my things to do back onto Complice</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>on track to finish entire list</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/01/on-track-to-finish-entire-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Mar 2018 14:18:34 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/01/on-track-to-finish-entire-list/</guid>
      <description>14:18 Thursday 01 March 2018 JST I am on track to finish my todo list today on Complice. I got my AB work complete, though there is the possibility they will want one more change on it. I am prepared for work tomorrow and now just gotta write this journal entry, studying Japanese, work tonight, Japanese lesson tonight with Mel, ..
I watched episode 6(?) of Kakegurui. They did not have the subtitles added yet, but I could understand the overall meaning because the acting is so over-the-top, plus explained visually (given that it&amp;rsquo;s a tv show)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>things to do</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/06/19/things-to-do/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2017 12:12:12 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/06/19/things-to-do/</guid>
      <description>12:12 Monday 19 June 2017 JST  make a to-do list remember you already have a list look for the other list  12:22 Monday 19 June 2017 JST JUST as I got ready to do one thing after waiting for an answer to do a different thing, the answer came back to do the different thing instead of one thing. bah multi-tasking is dumb.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>today</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/01/17/today/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2017 10:29:30 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/01/17/today/</guid>
      <description>10:29 Tuesday 17 January 2017 JST Go teach GG in Akiba
Go lunch with E in Ueno
Go to the dentist to get my teeth cleaned (a first for me!) I&amp;rsquo;m curious if the difference will be noticeable.
13:00 Tuesday 17 January 2017 JST At the GG lesson I learned a couple interesting things about Japanese school system.
According to my students, there is a strict rule about how birthdates correspond to what year of school a student is in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>do today</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/11/30/do-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2016 22:19:06 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/11/30/do-today/</guid>
      <description> 22:19 Wednesday 30 November 2016 JST ✔ Write card to Paul ✔ Put it in envelope ✔ Address it Add stamp ✔ Set alarm to remind me to send it tomorrow ✔ Email dentist link to PK presentation ✔ Add file to Krimms.com ✔ Ask for image for Krimms.com ✔ Run elastic beanstalk creation script Get support if needed Point nosedowns source to new eb instance See if they go through to mlab ✔ Ask Fred about diary ✔ Write in diary ✔ Praise babychan for job well done </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Today</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/09/30/today/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2016 08:52:55 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/09/30/today/</guid>
      <description> 08:52 Friday 30 September 2016 JST  continue work on ansible practice writing kanji email Matt email Ken work on Charu&amp;rsquo;s painting Look up OZ visa requirments apply for OZ visa Sign up for Goremit  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>people to email</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/09/29/people-to-email/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2016 18:02:54 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/09/29/people-to-email/</guid>
      <description> 18:02 Thursday 29 September 2016 JST Tonight I need to email
 Ken to tell him how Matt&amp;rsquo;s lesson was Matt to tell him where to get his books Yuji to tell him what page my Wed class should do  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>to do today</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/08/20/to-do-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2016 07:58:10 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/08/20/to-do-today/</guid>
      <description> 07:58 Saturday 20 August 2016 JST  give Jennie her medicine do laundry Play with vagrant and ansible via https://sysadmincasts.com/episodes/45-learning-ansible-with-vagrant-part-2-4 take Jennie to vet (9800 yen moe joe) MOOV log time on Redmine  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>to do today</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/08/06/to-do-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2016 08:03:07 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/08/06/to-do-today/</guid>
      <description>08:03 Saturday 06 August 2016 JST MOOV laundry take Jennie to vet spin up AWS RDS for AB on public accessible subnet try to get Amazon Quicksight connected.
9:00 Laundry is started
Turns out I can&amp;rsquo;t connect to Quicksight during the preview because my data is not in a US region.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>to do today</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/08/01/to-do-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2016 10:50:03 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/08/01/to-do-today/</guid>
      <description>10:50 Monday 01 August 2016 JST  confirm lunch time with Alfonzo create invoice for Nate Make mockup for AB and send to T email I-group about MOOV read something for Japanese draw + scan art work dawg work  15:59 oops I watched 4 episodes of Comedians In Cars Getting Coffee.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>things to dooooo</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/02/03/things-to-dooooo/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Feb 2016 13:39:48 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/02/03/things-to-dooooo/</guid>
      <description>13:39 Wednesday 03 February 2016 JST We&amp;rsquo;re about an hour from Narita, and apparently receiving one more meal.
Things to do:
 eat arrive brush teeth get three bags go through customs be interviewed by Tokyo TV guys get some monies out of ATM (nm; I got paid by JB) take Narita Express SMS Tariq email Ma, Jon, Fred email Dad and Karen post on FB we arrived get images from Lin&amp;rsquo;s phone import images from my phone pet Jennie pet Ted&amp;hellip; he came back!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>to do today</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/11/16/to-do-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2015 07:36:20 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/11/16/to-do-today/</guid>
      <description> 07:36 Monday 16 November 2015 JST  upload new cb site to demo write email to have &amp;lsquo;em check it proofread protocol for I-group print protocol for I-group add audio to Apple TV app upload new cb site to live work on Summer Vacation work on AB site read PIT protocol go to I-group  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>things done did and to do today</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/11/09/things-done-did-and-to-do-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2015 16:29:23 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/11/09/things-done-did-and-to-do-today/</guid>
      <description> 16:29 Monday 09 November 2015 JST  get definition for AB request update code to change 4 kanji to 1 kanji (for Contact types) rejoice in how quickly Hugo updates my website move CB new header online email S move AB new report thing online update class for a few top pages on CB site email S update redmine update eom spreadsheet work on Apple TV app find an article for tomorrow&amp;rsquo;s lesson  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>To Do Soon</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/10/21/to-do-soon/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2015 19:17:11 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/10/21/to-do-soon/</guid>
      <description>19:17 Wednesday 21 October 2015 JST  Put The Brain in my bag Invite Lin to go for a walk each morning at 5am Email Malik to determine a good time to call him Get caught up on email that came during OZ trip Add image to center of game screen for tvOS app Try to send some money from bank to my PayPal account Post some more images on Patreon site Find some open I-group protocols online Take おみやげ to Ken Do some tickets for AB site Do some tickets for CB site Hmm maybe do some tickets for my own site Create tickets for my site on bitbucket or github Convert json word list to mysql wow https://sqlizer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>to do at work today</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/05/26/to-do-at-work-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2015 10:42:29 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/05/26/to-do-at-work-today/</guid>
      <description>10:42 Tuesday 26 May 2015 JST  Figure out why proposed fix to 2613 ain&amp;rsquo;t working (and fix it) meet with S and Y get new subdomains into DNS  11:15 Finished #1 above. It turns out it was working, oops, nevermind.
15:39 actually #3 isn&amp;rsquo;t done yet, but I&amp;rsquo;ve done as much as possible for now. It&amp;rsquo;s weird. There&amp;rsquo;s a website which exists at t.example.com but it&amp;rsquo;s not shown in the list of DNS records at the example.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>to do to day</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/05/22/to-do-to-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 May 2015 18:56:30 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/05/22/to-do-to-day/</guid>
      <description>12:00 Friday 22 May 2015 JST To do today:
 upload journal entries burn copy of Debian iso to DVD burn copy of SystemRescueCd to DVD work on tickets while those are running install new HD in new old PC see if I can install Debian on new computer write to Mutsumi work on Unity proofread Mt Mitake CSETI event notes temp staff Chris  18:56 Friday 22 May 2015 JST Middle of installing Debian now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>to do today</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/05/16/to-do-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 May 2015 10:31:12 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/05/16/to-do-today/</guid>
      <description>10:31 Saturday 16 May 2015 JST  study Japanese for an hour look at CB tickets for an hour Check Chika&amp;rsquo;s transcript for an hour look at AB tickets for an hour add menus to pong game for an hour plan AB server update do not stay up until 1 million o&amp;rsquo;clock  reality:
 texted Nate til 10:42 studied Japanese til 10:47 5 mins texted Alfonzo til 10:52 studied Japanese prefectures til 11:11 15 mins did 27 pushups til 11:14 (total 255 in two days yay) studied Japanese adjectives til 11:24 (著しい!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>todo today</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/04/15/todo-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2015 10:10:01 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/04/15/todo-today/</guid>
      <description>10:10 Wednesday 15 April 2015 JST study send fiverr postcard finish two fiverr orders reply email from yesterday meet Tariq ask for fix to 瞑想がんばれ sound email Sho about 1568 100 pushups</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Plan to do today</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/03/29/plan-to-do-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2015 10:42:31 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/03/29/plan-to-do-today/</guid>
      <description> 10:42 Sunday 29 March 2015 JST  fast all day (in progress) meditate (34 minutes woo!) upload latest journal entries (not inc. this one because Middleman is too slow) reboot my computer study Japanese post daily meditation thread to bittippers seven minute workout 80 more pushups (20 are inc. in 7 min workout) post about 80s cafe Japanese class schedule appt at Apple Store go for a bike ride with Lin begin to convert date formats of old journal entries try hugo instead of middleman for website do tetris unity tutorial meet Tariq  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do Today</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/03/05/do-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2015 07:36:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/03/05/do-today/</guid>
      <description>##07:36 Thursday 05 March 2015 JST##
 Add to Sunday prep for AB server update Check textbook (1 hour) pushups * 15 Clean kitty litter (5 mins) post daily meditation thread to bittippers Redo work on #2401 after having received new set of images (1 hour hopefully) pushups * 15 Tell Lin to check her schedule (at noon) Study Japanese (1 hour) pushups * 20  ##10:20
Well checking the textbook took nearly 3 hours, but ま, it&amp;rsquo;s a textbook and needs to be perfect.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do Today</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/03/03/do-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2015 10:43:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/03/03/do-today/</guid>
      <description>##10:43 Tuesday 03 March 2015 JST##
Slightly different than other todo lists I&amp;rsquo;ve made, I will put time limits on items today, during which I currently have 6 hours available:
 check illustrations (1 hour) get Redmine to send emails (1 hour) create invoice from Redmine (1 hour) try to fix journal entries so unadulterated Middleman can use them (1 hour)  If I had a tomato timer, I&amp;rsquo;d count off 15 minute increments with it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>