<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>bysb on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/bysb/</link>
    <description>Recent content in bysb on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2018 10:23:14 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/bysb/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>how to get photos while building my speaker bio</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/27/how-to-get-photos-while-building-my-speaker-bio/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2018 10:23:14 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/27/how-to-get-photos-while-building-my-speaker-bio/</guid>
      <description>10:23 Saturday 27 January 2018 JST I am taking Soness&amp;rsquo;s Build Your Speaker Bio course, learning techniques for how to get great photos for my bios. She brought in branding photographer Heidi Hapanowicz who is giving great tips on how to find a great photographer and what to expect from them. Expect to pay minimum of a few hundred bucks, but you should not have to micromanage nor dig through hundreds of photos.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>speaker bio draft</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/17/speaker-bio-draft/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2018 13:14:08 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/17/speaker-bio-draft/</guid>
      <description>13:14 Wednesday 17 January 2018 JST Often seen walking barefoot around Tokyo, Rob likes baring his soles as well as his soul. &amp;ldquo;The long term goal is to reduce the suicide rate in Tokyo&amp;rdquo; he says with a wistful gaze. &amp;ldquo;It just seems like such a waste of human potential for someone to kill themselves instead of talk about their problems.&amp;rdquo;
To facilitate talking about problems, he leads peer counseling circles in Tokyo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Office Hours with Soness</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/13/office-hours-with-soness/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2018 14:23:37 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/13/office-hours-with-soness/</guid>
      <description>14:23 Saturday 13 January 2018 JST Build Your Speaker Bio is Soness&amp;rsquo;s most recent course. It solves the problem of having something to give to TEDx organizers when they ask for a speaker bio which they can use in marketing materials.
Prior to starting this course I did not see myself as a speaker, so why should I write a bio? I still cannot honestly say I see myself as having something worth speaking about, but I can see huge value in the course.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>