<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>plans on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/plans/</link>
    <description>Recent content in plans on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2019 18:51:29 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/plans/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>plans</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/08/31/plans/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2019 18:51:29 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/08/31/plans/</guid>
      <description>I have often wondered about ways to write journal entries on some small device and incorporate them into my online journal.
I used to use a Handspring Visor, until the foldable keyboard folded for the last time and the Visor perhaps got replaced with a laptop? It had some way to sync, probably USB.
Anyway, I&amp;rsquo;ve got a handheld screen here with Swype keyboard, and I am writing this as an email to myself which I hope to remember to cut and paste into a full on my local file system and incorporate into my git repository for journal entries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>prepping to talk to F</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/02/21/prepping-to-talk-to-f/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Feb 2019 07:35:38 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/02/21/prepping-to-talk-to-f/</guid>
      <description>07:35 Thursday 21 February 2019 JST Marble Track 3 is not my #1 priority; I am happy to work on it slowly.
*) Rewriting in Gatsby / React makes sense if I can learn along the path to creating it. How do you feel about going slowly, to help an old newbie learn along the way?
Basically, I do the work, learning along the way, you get a per month retainer, for minimum 5 months?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Busy prepping for MKP trip</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/01/30/busy-prepping-for-mkp-trip/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jan 2019 22:10:31 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/01/30/busy-prepping-for-mkp-trip/</guid>
      <description>22:10 Wednesday 30 January 2019 JST Just a couple days ago I got my tickets all sorted to staff two different NWTA weekends and also attend the MKP USA Face to Face weekend in Texas.
After pretty much settling on the plans, it was pointed out that attending an IGFT might give me more of the training I am looking for, but I trust this is the training / trip I need.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Plans for marbletrack3.com Marble Track 3</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/12/20/plans-for-marbletrack3.com-marble-track-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Dec 2018 20:59:31 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/12/20/plans-for-marbletrack3.com-marble-track-3/</guid>
      <description>20:59 Thursday 20 December 2018 JST Though I have not figured out how to present it, I want to have some pages that give a complete rundown of how the workers have made Marble Track 3.
At this point, under /snippets, it starts like this:
Squarehead leads Rabby onto the set as Rabby drags a round circular plate behind him. Squarehead unties the ropes from Rabby. Rabby squishes Squarehead as he heads toward the camera, knocking it off its stand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mt3 plans</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/05/09/mt3-plans/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2018 10:25:02 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/05/09/mt3-plans/</guid>
      <description>10:25 Wednesday 09 May 2018 JST I am in the middle of making the marble splitter work for small marbles.
The manager has just glued one rail into place and will glue the inner rail next.
Next, the manager will:
 glue inner rail for small track test the too small marble (which will fail) eject too small marble test a correctly-sized small marble  At the same time, Reversable Guy (RG) will place the other splitter top rail.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>today</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/03/today/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Mar 2018 08:23:35 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/03/today/</guid>
      <description>08:23 Saturday 03 March 2018 JST In Complice I added 22 Intentions for today ranging from online courses to programming, to fixing the ugg boot which Bryn bought me back in the day. Also, gotta leave at 10:30am to TY today, which is two hours from now, so I am tempted to work on MT3 in this time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Plan to see Kai at Kawasaki Pecha Kucha tonight</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/06/21/plan-to-see-kai-at-kawasaki-pecha-kucha-tonight/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2017 18:57:11 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/06/21/plan-to-see-kai-at-kawasaki-pecha-kucha-tonight/</guid>
      <description>18:57 Wednesday 21 June 2017 JST Two more lessons tonight and then zoom past Kawasaki station to Rockwest(?) to see Kai after she speaks at Pecha Kucha in Kawasaki. Unfortunately (if my students come), I won&amp;rsquo;t be able to see her speech. The students always come though, so yeah. Speaking of whom.. gotta work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>plans for tomorrow</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/04/05/plans-for-tomorrow/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Apr 2015 19:45:06 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/04/05/plans-for-tomorrow/</guid>
      <description>19:45 Sunday 05 April 2015 JST In addition to catching up on pushups, (assuming I can&amp;rsquo;t do 100 tonight,) (my goal is 100 per day this month,) and catching up on Japanese study, I hope to retool the bejeweled game so the pieces move slower than light speed. Oh, and try to find the light speed game for Travis, who had a dream about my having created a game that included relativistic effects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chigasaki bound</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/12/05/chigasaki-bound/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/12/05/chigasaki-bound/</guid>
      <description>##12:09 Friday 05 December 2014 JST##
On the train now headed for Chigasaki to hang out with Soness! I helped organize some of her paperwork so I&amp;rsquo;m bringing that back now. She&amp;rsquo;s making yummy lunch!
The weather is lovely though cold; I&amp;rsquo;m barefoot. :-)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>move out</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/06/30/move-out/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/06/30/move-out/</guid>
      <description>1:33pm CDT Tuesday 25 June 2002
Things to do before I go:
thingfinished? Get membership with Youth Hostel Association Find a home for Spot Brainstorm minimum, but adequate set of expenses per month while I&#39;m on the roadcell, gas, repair, insurance, food, hotel, contingency fund ($2500),  Notice my amount of Peace Ask Dad, Ma, Wende, Maggie if they have dibs on furnitureDad, Maggie Figure out what to take and what to sell and what to archivestarted Find a place to put stuff resolve GenXchange responsibilities Build spiritual space into my life, like a hobby.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>optimal environment</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/03/27/optimal-environment/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/03/27/optimal-environment/</guid>
      <description>8:13 pm 27-3-02
This is my optimal environment, or aspects of environment that I would love and feel energized living within.
My bedroom is only accessible via a ladder or a rope swing, and a small portal of some sort. The hand holds are just the right size for me to use. Any guests have to be determined to enter before they&#39;ll be willing to go to such extremes.
In my room there is no phone unless I take my cell pone with me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>trip planning</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1997/09/25/trip-planning/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 1997 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1997/09/25/trip-planning/</guid>
      <description>As of earlier this month, I became totally debt free. Well, except for a $4000 medical bill that I still owe as a result of Wild Skating Adventure Six, totally debt free.  I&amp;rsquo;m a financial anomaly in this society!  As for the 4 grand, I&amp;rsquo;m probably not going to pay it off really fast- just pay several dollars per month to keep &amp;lsquo;em off my back. Instead, I&amp;rsquo;m saving up all my dollars for my Extended Remix Roadtrip that will begin in about August 1998.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>