<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2018 on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/2018/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2018 on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Dec 2018 20:22:58 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/2018/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>last Akihabara lesson this year</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/12/20/last-akihabara-lesson-this-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Dec 2018 20:22:58 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/12/20/last-akihabara-lesson-this-year/</guid>
      <description>20:22 Thursday 20 December 2018 JST We had our last lesson of the year in Akihabara today. This is also Toshie&amp;rsquo;s last lesson so we had a party in her honor with all her favorite snack foods.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>state of my life address</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/12/07/state-of-my-life-address/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 22:12:16 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/12/07/state-of-my-life-address/</guid>
      <description>22:12 Friday 07 December 2018 JST  Marble Track 3 has its own domain, https://www.marbletrack3.com/ hosted as a static site on Netlify ConSwi is open source under GNU copyleft. Several outstanding issues, the biggest of which are #25 disallow dragged pieces to go through other pieces and #23 Make piece keep up with mouse when dragging I created a Patreon page for MT3 and have my first patron, Jimmy! I recently got the fans and battery replaced on my MacBook, but it still conks out when the battery is at 65%.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>State of My Life Address</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/07/05/state-of-my-life-address/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2018 00:13:46 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/07/05/state-of-my-life-address/</guid>
      <description>00:13 Thursday 05 July 2018 JST  Dreamhost has decided to stop supporting catch-all emails so I am looking for a new provider. The encrypted versions cannot search nor test for spam very well so I may not be happy with any of those I am too tired to write this right now so I should go to bed. For AB, I have started adding arc_cycles, which should save them a decent amount of time when creating historical reports.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>State of My Life Address</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/06/02/state-of-my-life-address/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jun 2018 00:55:37 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/06/02/state-of-my-life-address/</guid>
      <description>00:55 Saturday 02 June 2018 JST  I just got home from Apocrypha #15  09:13 Saturday 02 June 2018 JST  Was up too late last night and did not do much good for myself (porn), but I on the productive side I read some of MJG&amp;rsquo;s new book The Rot&amp;rsquo;s War Ignifer Cycle Book 2 co-gender circle seems to have come back to meeting after a significant dip in attendance over winter holidays men&amp;rsquo;s circle has had pretty solid attendance, often with 7 men.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It snowed today</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/22/it-snowed-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2018 00:34:16 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/22/it-snowed-today/</guid>
      <description>00:34 Thursday 22 March 2018 JST It snowed &amp;ldquo;today&amp;rdquo; and was 2 degrees C all day long. It&amp;rsquo;s apparently going up to 16 or 18 degrees C tomorrow.
I chatted with Delayna who I&amp;rsquo;ve known since our mutual YRUU days back in late 1980s, culminating with ConCon 1988. Looking forward to seeing her herb business grow!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>getting back to work in 2018</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/10/getting-back-to-work-in-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2018 08:44:46 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/10/getting-back-to-work-in-2018/</guid>
      <description>08:44 Wednesday 10 January 2018 JST I worked yesterday for the first time in 2018. Monday was a holiday, and my
13:41 Wednesday 10 January 2018 JST I am on the train and the above is as far as I got before sidetracking myself with something before having a meeting with TY at 9am then lunch with Lin.
Today:
 I got my AWS account switched to JPY instead of USD so I can pay more efficiently.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>past week</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/08/past-week/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2018 13:27:14 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/08/past-week/</guid>
      <description>13:27 Monday 08 January 2018 JST Today is the last day of winter holiday for me. Lin and I have been back home for a week, during which I have mostly worked on Godot, read The Power of Now, watched movies with Lin, and worked a bit on MT3.
This past Saturday, we went to see her family for Happy New Year, and I have been chatting with her niece in English on LINE since then.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>