<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>jennie on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/jennie/</link>
    <description>Recent content in jennie on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 21:37:57 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/jennie/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>pics</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/10/31/pics/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 21:37:57 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/10/31/pics/</guid>
      <description>21:37 Wednesday 31 October 2018 JST Hanging out with Michael Shell in Midtown and found the egg.

Hanging out with Lin at home and found this cat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>cat paw</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/12/cat-paw/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2017 13:59:06 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/12/cat-paw/</guid>
      <description>13:59 Tuesday 12 December 2017 JST Giving Jennie some cuddles today, I noticed an extra pad on her foot. Hmmm. That&amp;rsquo;s not a pad, that&amp;rsquo;s a swollen something something. fortunately Lin still had time to take her to the clinic; I am headed to work now. Hopefully and presumably she will be okay!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jennie has a new door</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/10/27/jennie-has-a-new-door/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 15:12:39 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/10/27/jennie-has-a-new-door/</guid>
      <description>15:12 Friday 27 October 2017 JST Jennie has a pet door in our room now so she can go in and out. The door has a lock so that it can work both directions, neither direction, or this xor that direction.
The guy cut a hole in the glass and it was not like on Mission Impossible. He used a diamond tip to make a circle and then a smaller circle, and then a grid of cuts in the middle of the small circle, then tap tap tapped with a metal rod.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jennie got out and it was pretty much my fault</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/04/17/jennie-got-out-and-it-was-pretty-much-my-fault/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2015 12:10:36 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/04/17/jennie-got-out-and-it-was-pretty-much-my-fault/</guid>
      <description>12:10 Friday 17 April 2015 JST As Lin left this morning, she was like, &amp;ldquo;don&amp;rsquo;t let Jennie out!&amp;rdquo; and I was like, &amp;ldquo;of course!&amp;rdquo; and I noticed that I could put the chain on the door so it only opens this much she wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be able to get out. That way she&amp;rsquo;ll be safe and happy!
oh shit she getting out! I tried to close the door to carefully hold her without crushing her (cats hate that!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ted got out, and Jennie too..</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/04/06/ted-got-out-and-jennie-too../</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2015 22:19:55 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/04/06/ted-got-out-and-jennie-too../</guid>
      <description>22:19 Monday 06 April 2015 JST I apparently left the sliding glass door unlocked yesterday; Ted opened it and got outside. He hasn&amp;rsquo;t come back, though we&amp;rsquo;ve seen him on the balcony opposite ours.
Jennie and Ted usually sleep in the bed with Lin, and sometimes with me, but last night Jennie slept in the bed reserved for cats.
And today when ママ came home, Jennie bolted out the door, looking for Ted, I&amp;rsquo;m sure!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>