<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>morning on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/morning/</link>
    <description>Recent content in morning on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2019 06:17:53 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/morning/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>I got a seat on the train</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/06/17/i-got-a-seat-on-the-train/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2019 06:17:53 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/06/17/i-got-a-seat-on-the-train/</guid>
      <description>06:17 Monday 17 June 2019 JST I got a seat on my preferred train. I arrived in just enough time, though it&amp;rsquo;s reasonable to say I could have ridden more slowly to be safer (down the big-ass whooo-hooo hill).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>met Tariq and Dipendra</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/09/21/met-tariq-and-dipendra/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2018 09:24:08 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/09/21/met-tariq-and-dipendra/</guid>
      <description>09:24 Friday 21 September 2018 JST I met Dipendra today, a young man with design chops that far exceed my own, and even Tariq&amp;rsquo;s. He is interested in doing the images for ConSwi, our swipe game we are making in Godot.
We met in a room that used to be a car showroom, but now features a coffee shop because the car showroom was not making enough money.
I showed Dipendra how to get started with Godot and git.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>thirteenth walk, a week late</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/09/07/thirteenth-walk-a-week-late/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Sep 2018 07:46:21 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/09/07/thirteenth-walk-a-week-late/</guid>
      <description>07:46 Friday 07 September 2018 JST Walked this morning for the first time in a week or so oops. Good times, including meeting the guy who I usually meet on Wednesdays while he is on his exercise route. Oh, and nodded to the kid who runs around the neighborhood as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>fun fourth walk</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/08/17/fun-fourth-walk/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Aug 2018 07:21:12 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/08/17/fun-fourth-walk/</guid>
      <description>07:21 Friday 17 August 2018 JST I have been writing in Japanese about the walk.
Behind our house there are some houses under construction. There are no gates blocking entry so I went inside to have a look.
(English translations from my Japanese:)
Outside the houses there was scaffolding wrapped in blue fabric. On the first floor the fabric kept anyone outside from seeing me inside, but on the second floor, the fabric had gaps so I was nervous at times.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>break up cat fight before walk (3)</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/08/16/break-up-cat-fight-before-walk-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2018 06:25:47 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/08/16/break-up-cat-fight-before-walk-3/</guid>
      <description>06:25 Thursday 16 August 2018 JST Just before 5am, Lin let Jennie outside for her morning adventures. Soon thereafter we could hear her catching up with another cat. I woke up for my walk and headed toward the altercation. Unfortunately my approach was a catalyst for amplification of the catastrophe. They catapulted away from each other and Jennie ran under a car before I could catch her.
I continued walking and went 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>fantastic first walk (1)</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/08/14/fantastic-first-walk-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Aug 2018 11:05:38 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/08/14/fantastic-first-walk-1/</guid>
      <description>11:05 Tuesday 14 August 2018 JST I have decided to wake up at 5am each day, and on the five days I do not have to immediately go to work (for which I have already been waking up at 5am), I will go for a brisk walk around the neighborhood.
Today I went up the hill and along the ridge and up left on a street I had never walked before, then up a hill into a park and then omg down a spooky mossy staircase with spiderweb strands hitting my face and cicadas buzzing my ears and mosquitoes chomping my legs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>typhoony morning but trains were fine</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/10/23/typhoony-morning-but-trains-were-fine/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2017 14:40:25 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/10/23/typhoony-morning-but-trains-were-fine/</guid>
      <description>14:40 Monday 23 October 2017 JST When I took the train this morning at 6:24am, it was running on time no worries. However, apparently trains started running late soon thereafter. One of my students happens to live near my same station (新百合ヶ丘) and she said the trains were late, which caused her to arrive late. I am thankful for my policy of arriving 20+ minutes early.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>am</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/07/27/am/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/07/27/am/</guid>
      <description>9:58am CDT Saturday 27 July 2002
Awake. Unpacking and repacking my car to go visit the Bibby&#39;s for a few days. Ironically, Sean is in Utah now, so I can&#39;t hang out with him exactly yet.
4:52pm
Been chillin&#39; with Janette, Sean and Joey&#39;s mom. Joey just woke up a bit ago. Janette has been cooking all day (&#34;20 hours&#34; she says) and I&#39;ve helped a tiny bit by cutting parsley (I think) and jalepenos and mixing tabouli.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ConCon first am</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/08/04/concon-first-am/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Aug 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/08/04/concon-first-am/</guid>
      <description>Con Con
11:30am Tuesday 4 August 1998

transcribed from my diary
Woke up and read part of Shield and talked to Torger and Galen and others on staff out on our cabin porch. Then breakfast and sat at the same table with mostly the same group as dinner last night. We talked and chilled a bit and bounced a plastic ring from a coke bottle plastic cap. At the Spirt Circle I sat between Carol and Jeremy who sang &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>