<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>kids on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/kids/</link>
    <description>Recent content in kids on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Sep 2018 22:13:58 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/kids/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>family day</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/09/23/family-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Sep 2018 22:13:58 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/09/23/family-day/</guid>
      <description>22:13 Sunday 23 September 2018 JST Been a pretty good day today despite the 6-year-old driving me a bit crazy. He seems to be a bit entitled and petulant, but maybe that is my projection. We played with the vertical labyrinth game, kids blocks marble track, jenga, and tried to play pictionary, but his version of the game was to write the words instead of draw them. Make sense!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>easy lessons</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/18/easy-lessons/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2018 17:37:46 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/18/easy-lessons/</guid>
      <description>17:37 Wednesday 18 April 2018 JST Easy lessons today because Patrick was out. After combining the 4:30 classes, we played a game with target language &amp;ldquo;May I have a card, please?,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m ＿＿＿＿-ing,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;We&amp;rsquo;re ＿＿＿＿-ing,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Hey ＿＿＿＿, let&amp;rsquo;s go ＿＿＿-ing,&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Sorry I can&amp;rsquo;t. I&amp;rsquo;m busy.&amp;rdquo;
Matt is also out today, so I&amp;rsquo;ll teach his 6pm lesson.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>three lessons</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/10/11/three-lessons/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2017 17:37:38 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/10/11/three-lessons/</guid>
      <description>17:37 Wednesday 11 October 2017 JST The kids lessons were pretty good today. The two new students (one in each of my first two classes) are still not speaking, and I can&amp;rsquo;t tell if they are acting shy or don&amp;rsquo;t understand.. anytime they speak, they get the right answer, but getting them to speak is a stretch. esp with the other kids being so chatty. I ain&amp;rsquo;t sure how to handle it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Good small group lesson</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/01/14/good-small-group-lesson/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/01/14/good-small-group-lesson/</guid>
      <description>##10:32 Wednesday 14 January 2015 JST##
So great to have only 9 students in the second class today, especially after the first class was 20 kids of chaos. The 9 kids were so good that we had tons of time to do stuff!! No time wasted wondering why who was wailing with whom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kids class</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/12/03/kids-class/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/12/03/kids-class/</guid>
      <description>##14:48 Wednesday 03 December 2014 JST##
We had some older kids in the kids class today. I&amp;rsquo;m not sure why they were there, but they supported and some were enthusiastic / unafraid to do the dance/song/etc that I presented.
The second class got cut short for some reason; basically a woman came up and was like, &amp;ldquo;okay, please tell them thank you (and goodbye)&amp;rdquo; so I confirmed it with the normal staff and yep, so finished up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>a bit repetitive kids class</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/26/a-bit-repetitive-kids-class/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/26/a-bit-repetitive-kids-class/</guid>
      <description>##10:30am Wednesday 26 Nov 2014
(written 07:14 Thursday 27 November 2014 JST)
The first kids class yesterday included the song &amp;ldquo;Walking Walking&amp;rdquo; about 20 times; I brought Johnny (the bear I bought in Thailand) and had him join in the circle as we sang Walking Walking. All the kids wanted a chance to hold his hand, thought at first I tried to skip a few kids to save time. Not that I normally try to save time when it comes to play, but I felt a sense that I was suppose to do something productive during the class.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>And the kids class was fine</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/19/and-the-kids-class-was-fine/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/19/and-the-kids-class-was-fine/</guid>
      <description>##10:19 Wednesday 19 November 2014 JST##
Thanks to Soness helping me prepare, I was well enough prepared for the kids lesson even though I felt crazy afraid before the lesson. I believed I wasn&amp;rsquo;t prepared; I had forgotten to bring Johnny (the stuffed bear) who I planned to use as a teaching assistant; I didn&amp;rsquo;t have a way to play music in the class, and I was just a frazzled nut before the lesson.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Great help from Soness!</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/14/great-help-from-soness/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/14/great-help-from-soness/</guid>
      <description>##17:33 Friday 14 November 2014 JST##
I feel a lot more confident that I can present something fun and enjoyable for the kindergarten classes on Wednesday! Thanks to Soness for sharing from her years of experience!
She agrees that Dream English Kis is a great resource, and said Matt is a great person for me to model because he&amp;rsquo;s got good gestures and (like me,) isn&amp;rsquo;t over-the-top exuberant (like Soness).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A quick cry before kids lesson</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/12/a-quick-cry-before-kids-lesson/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/12/a-quick-cry-before-kids-lesson/</guid>
      <description>##08:37 Wednesday 12 November 2014 JST##
I&amp;rsquo;m prepping for the kids lesson today, and just had a good cry regarding fear of standing and performing in front of groups!
I&amp;rsquo;m planning to use this Goodbye song each day, and as I&amp;rsquo;m here in front of my computer trying to learn it, I just felt this surge of fear like OH FUCK! and just cried for a bit.
Fuck this; I can&amp;rsquo;t do it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best kids lessons so far</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/12/best-kids-lessons-so-far/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/12/best-kids-lessons-so-far/</guid>
      <description>##11:12 Wednesday 12 November 2014 JST##
And by &amp;ldquo;best&amp;rdquo; I mean, &amp;ldquo;well, I survived&amp;rdquo; though I&amp;rsquo;m mentally drained and have no idea how I can do it next week. I read the book &amp;ldquo;Go, Dog, Go&amp;rdquo; which they seemed to enjoy, but I didn&amp;rsquo;t see any other English books at the school.
I have no good way to start the lesson. I&amp;rsquo;ve just done a crappy Hello call and repeat thing but it&amp;rsquo;s kind of shite.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kids classes (a.k.a. O_o)</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/05/kids-classes-a.k.a.-o_o/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/05/kids-classes-a.k.a.-o_o/</guid>
      <description>##10:58 Wednesday 05 November 2014 JST##
Wow. Well, I survived the first day teaching a group of kids, they seemed to have fun overall, and there was some semblence of learning involved.
To be more specific, I just &amp;ldquo;taught&amp;rdquo; two classes of around 20 kids each, the first group being a bit younger than the second; I&amp;rsquo;d guess 5 and 6 years old, but I heard they were 4 and 5 years old respectively.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>