<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>tv on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/tv/</link>
    <description>Recent content in tv on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2018 02:29:22 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/tv/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Dirk Gently and the focused binge</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/13/dirk-gently-and-the-focused-binge/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2018 02:29:22 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/13/dirk-gently-and-the-focused-binge/</guid>
      <description>02:29 Saturday 13 January 2018 JST Heh. Well, it was pretty great. Dirk Gently&amp;rsquo;s Holistic Detective Agency was good enough that I just watched the last four (4) episodes in a row. At 40+ minutes each that&amp;rsquo;s 160+ minutes or about oh my god I have to go to bed.
https://news.newonnetflix.info/news/dirk-gentlys-holistic-detective-agency-season-2-date-for-netflix-uk/
Now it is apparently canceled, but I hope not. https://variety.com/2017/tv/news/dirk-gently-2-1202644035/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>the defenders</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/08/28/the-defenders/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2017 17:12:30 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/08/28/the-defenders/</guid>
      <description>17:12 Monday 28 August 2017 JST I watched episodes 2 and 3 of The Defenders today, some kinda expanded world offshoot from Danny Rand the Iron Fist. It&amp;rsquo;s good, but to quote Alfonzo, c&amp;rsquo;mon Iron Fist, let me sleep.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tall man in Ueno station</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/07/27/tall-man-in-ueno-station/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2017 17:58:13 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/07/27/tall-man-in-ueno-station/</guid>
      <description>17:58 Thursday 27 July 2017 JST While I was walking out of Ueno station, a tall man and I did the foreigner nod and then he said he had seen me on TV (for being barefoot). We shook hands and talked for a bit about the importance of doing one&amp;rsquo;s own thing.
He said, &amp;ldquo;I respect you,&amp;rdquo; and I should have said if he sees respectability in me, that means it&amp;rsquo;s in him, too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>end of year special YOUは何しに日本へ</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/12/13/end-of-year-special-you%E3%81%AF%E4%BD%95%E3%81%97%E3%81%AB%E6%97%A5%E6%9C%AC%E3%81%B8/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2016 20:47:12 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/12/13/end-of-year-special-you%E3%81%AF%E4%BD%95%E3%81%97%E3%81%AB%E6%97%A5%E6%9C%AC%E3%81%B8/</guid>
      <description>20:47 Tuesday 13 December 2016 JST Last night I met a whole lot of beautiful people who have been YOUs on the TV show &amp;ldquo;What are YOU doing in Japan?&amp;rdquo;
I connected most with Cyrus the wild man, who loves onsen and apparently lives off grid.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>just signed up for Netflix</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/10/18/just-signed-up-for-netflix/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2016 01:14:06 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/10/18/just-signed-up-for-netflix/</guid>
      <description>01:14 Tuesday 18 October 2016 JST The TV mysteriously broke while I was in OZ and Lin got a new one that supports Netflix, not just Hulu which we&amp;rsquo;ve liked for a long while, (and others we never used).
Netflix is hella better than Hulu.
 can pause movies for a while without the stream being disconnected can fast forward and reverse with great control can see thumbnails larger than a postage stamp can see titles and descriptions in English can rate movies can get movie recommendations per different profile seems like a lot more variety of things to watch 5% less expensive  Just turned on Lock Stock and Two Smoking Barrels, and realize I&amp;rsquo;ve never seen it before!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Plan for today</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/02/27/plan-for-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Feb 2016 08:00:57 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/02/27/plan-for-today/</guid>
      <description>08:00 Saturday 27 February 2016 JST  9am - meet you barefoot at Kawasaki station 9am - 9:30am walk barefoot with you to my house 9:30am to 10:30am buy toilet paper wash laundry show computer working sign art for Gary hang laundry feed cats 10:30am to 11:30am go shopping at local shops I often visit buy bananas buy milk 11:30 - 12pm noon play barefoot in a park across the street from our house (there is no grass, but lots of gravel and some equipment I like to climb barefoot) 12:noon - 12:20pm quickly shower (you can film and see lots of dirt washing off my feet in the shower!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>interviewed again for Tokyo TV</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/02/03/interviewed-again-for-tokyo-tv/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Feb 2016 16:03:32 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/02/03/interviewed-again-for-tokyo-tv/</guid>
      <description>16:03 Wednesday 03 February 2016 JST Yay! Upon our arrival in Narita, though Lin declined to be on camera, the guys from Tokyo TV interviewed me again! Fun! I wonder if they&amp;rsquo;ll actually follow me around at some point.. I imagine that would be a really interesting experience!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Barefoot me on TV</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/12/29/barefoot-me-on-tv/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Dec 2015 15:12:20 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/12/29/barefoot-me-on-tv/</guid>
      <description>15:12 Tuesday 29 December 2015 JST Okay so when I got back from OZ, upon arrival in Narita, I was approached by a TV crew who asked why I was barefoot and why I was coming to Japan.
I wish I had just been honest, but I told them what I wished I was doing: traveling barefoot around the country for 3+ months. They were like, &amp;ldquo;wow so can we follow you around?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>