<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>travel on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/travel/</link>
    <description>Recent content in travel on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2019 13:06:44 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/travel/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>I&#39;m on a bus</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/10/03/im-on-a-bus/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2019 13:06:44 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/10/03/im-on-a-bus/</guid>
      <description>(written 13:06 Thursday 03 October 2019 JST)
I&amp;rsquo;m on a bus! I&amp;rsquo;m on a bus! Everyone, look at me; I&amp;rsquo;m on a nearly empty bus, headed to Narita, headed to Seattle to see Colleenie Bean Dawg for a day doing touristy things in the city and then having pizza at their crib.
(The bus is now waiting at a light like 5 minutes from my house. So funny how transit works on this planet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>souvenir plan</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/10/02/souvenir-plan/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2019 18:21:23 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/10/02/souvenir-plan/</guid>
      <description>(written 15:21 Wednesday 02 October 2019 JST)
Heading out on October 3rd with a list of souvenirs to bring back
 Very hot sauce for Babychan Texas Boof jerky for Babychan 🍒 Lifesavers for Ami Hawaii snacks and Texas jerky for Daidoh black,white,silver,gold,red travel stickers for Tomoko Pineapple cookie for Aika Shukoh Coffee for Ayano shukoh Macadamia nuts for Toki shukoh Pineapple cookies for Shukoh Various sweets Skittles for Khiet Baking powder Colgate for Eriko and Khiet English games book for Kazu Eucerin for Kazu Small and medium funny shirts for Khiet Rocket for Yuji  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>benefits of leaving an airport at 00:01</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/05/09/benefits-of-leaving-an-airport-at-0001/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2019 22:00:16 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/05/09/benefits-of-leaving-an-airport-at-0001/</guid>
      <description>22:00 Thursday 09 May 2019 JST My friend wanted to buy a ticket to leave on Saturday and accidentally bought a ticket that leaves at 00:01am (one minute after midnight) Saturday morning. (26 hours from now as I write this)
I challenged him to write 25 benefits of such a situation. Here are mine:
 have a funny story be awake with nothing to do but watch digital clock turn from 23:59:59 to 00:00:00 arrive at airport when it&amp;rsquo;s relatively quiet get a chance to see behind-the-scenes stuff they only do at night at airports not have to wake up early for a flight have already halfway solved the jetlag issue get to really ponder the human construct of tracking time have a chance to put a smile on face of staff working late save time shopping for souvenirs save money on buying souvenirs have moving walkway all to yourself get to wonder if other passengers made the same mistake get to joke about how early the flight is easy chance to sleep late on Saturday no worries about a large choice of food vendors in airport immediate night mode on plane so can sleep quickly &amp;ldquo;I leave tonight&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;I leave tomorrow&amp;rdquo; are both true passport stamps says you left the day before you actually leave opportunity for taking nighttime photos at airport can play in kids zone because no kids will be there can say &amp;ldquo;good evening&amp;rdquo; to one seatmate immediately before &amp;ldquo;good morning&amp;rdquo; to next seatmate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pictures from big island Hawaii</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/04/01/pictures-from-big-island-hawaii/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 15:08:44 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/04/01/pictures-from-big-island-hawaii/</guid>
      <description>15:08 Monday 01 April 2019 HST The NWTA was held in Hawaiian Sanctuary, which featured lots of animals
      
Francois sitting on a dome covered in blankets

Francois sitting on bunches of apple bananas

From Bruce&amp;rsquo;s yard
    
Pics after 2018 lower Puna eruption riddled the area with lava flows</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rough final draft of video for GoFundme</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/01/16/rough-final-draft-of-video-for-gofundme/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2019 21:54:54 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/01/16/rough-final-draft-of-video-for-gofundme/</guid>
      <description>21:54 Wednesday 16 January 2019 JST The GoFundme text is not finished yet, but I plan to finish it up tonight or tomorrow.
It took a while to get this version complete, including breaking a pen and crying my eyes out with Mark at the Jonathan&amp;rsquo;s near 向ヶ 丘遊園駅むこうがおかゆうえんえき mukogaokayuen station.
Between working for TY and AB, I got this version complete in one take, after about 30 takes over a period of a week or so.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Met Dipika</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/04/met-dipika/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Apr 2018 12:45:01 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/04/met-dipika/</guid>
      <description>12:45 Wednesday 04 April 2018 JST Today while I was in the cafe below Muza, a woman came up and asked if I could speak English. I drew her a map to a bank on the other side of the station, but had a slightly bad feeling about sending her on a possible wild goose chase. Her name is Dipika, and she&amp;rsquo;s been in Japan just a little bit and will be here for 2 more weeks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Headed to Portland</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/09/headed-to-portland/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2018 12:16:24 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/09/headed-to-portland/</guid>
      <description>12:16 Friday 09 March 2018 JST I&amp;rsquo;m leaving in about an hour for a weekend in Portland. It&amp;rsquo;s for a training called The Container of Leadership. I will be challenged to look deeply at myself, really digging down into my -isms and other thoughts which unconsiously underly my perception of the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>party like it&#39;s 2017</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/01/party-like-its-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2018 04:25:22 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/01/party-like-its-2017/</guid>
      <description>17:18 Sunday 31 December 2017 -02 (São Paulo - Brazil) 23:19 Sunday 31 December 2017 +04 (Dubai - United Arab Emirates) 04:20 Monday 01 January 2018 JST (Tokyo - Japan) We arrived and went to the baggage claim but, fortunately thanks to Lin checking first, we discovered we could not get our checked baggage in Dubai when staying in hotels in the airport.
But what&amp;rsquo;s awesome: the guy was like beep beep beep and said our baggage would be redirected to Haneda just like that boom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>42 minutes to Dubai</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/31/42-minutes-to-dubai/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2017 14:45:15 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/31/42-minutes-to-dubai/</guid>
      <description>14:45 Sunday 31 December 2017 -02 I am certainly getting tired. I did not sleep the last 4 hours of the flight as planned. I kept working on Godot and then watched the last couple or three episodes of Lucifer season 2.
The flight was scheduled to be 14 hours, so I have been awake about 17 hours since my last entry.
Okay, yes I woke up at 20:47 and it is now 14:49 the next day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>chillin at the airport in Sao Paulo</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/30/chillin-at-the-airport-in-sao-paulo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2017 23:16:11 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/30/chillin-at-the-airport-in-sao-paulo/</guid>
      <description>23:16 Saturday 30 December 2017 -02 I think we thought the flight leaves at 00:15, in which case we would begin boarding in 20 minutes or so. But it&amp;rsquo;s at 01:15 so we have 80 minutes or so.
Lin is shopping for souvenirs though our bags are overweight, and will apparently cost $100 in Dubai because *they are very strict there&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>swapping A and P</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/30/swapping-a-and-p/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2017 16:40:49 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/30/swapping-a-and-p/</guid>
      <description>16:40 Saturday 30 December 2017 -02 We are going to get on the flight in several hours from now. I wonder when I will start to reverse my sleep schedule. We are 11 hours behind Tokyo, so not as far away as possible, but close.
I have just gotten out my computer (to work on ConSwi) when I realized I should be sleeping.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>pre jetlag?</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/29/pre-jetlag/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2017 05:37:12 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/29/pre-jetlag/</guid>
      <description> 05:37 Friday 29 December 2017 I woke up at 5am today; did we go to sleep too early?
07:50 Friday 29 December 2017 I don&amp;rsquo;t know, but I used the time to finish a big step in ConSwi. Now the player can win levels.
commit b550b45e7a225c13f206c257f6176fef91aea80a Author: Rob Nugen Date: Fri Dec 29 07:44:51 2017 Tell player if the level is won Fixes #22  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ate churascos</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/23/ate-churascos/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2017 14:19:30 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/23/ate-churascos/</guid>
      <description>14:19 Saturday 23 December 2017 -03 Lin and I just walked along the beach from the restaurante de churrascos (sp) after pretty much gorging on all the offerings.
I saw some really neat rivulets on the beach (but forgot to take a picture) where water seems to just spring from the beach. I guess that is exactly what&amp;rsquo;s happening; water within the sand works its way out and then comes down to the ocean.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>my first flight in an Airbus A-380</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/16/my-first-flight-in-an-airbus-a-380/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2017 07:37:40 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/16/my-first-flight-in-an-airbus-a-380/</guid>
      <description>07:37 Saturday 16 December 2017 -02 Last night was my (and Lin&amp;rsquo;s) first time to travel in an Airbus A380. Our flight was around 15 hours from Dubai to São Paulo on Emirates, which is apparently Airbus&amp;rsquo; largest A380 customer.
I was impressed with how relatively quiet the plane was during the entire flight. (I had a window seat just at the trailing edge of the wings.)
We had a hard landing with a bounce, but the aircraft came to a stop very quickly and smoothly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>long flight to Dubai</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/15/long-flight-to-dubai/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2017 08:40:50 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/15/long-flight-to-dubai/</guid>
      <description>08:40 Friday 15 December 2017 JST Wow we arrive in just 4 hours. I tried to stay up longer by watching a movie, but maybe I should have gotten out my computer. I had had a headache from being up so late so I didn&amp;rsquo;t think I could program well.
I slept most of the flight already, it seems. 11 hour flight, 7 hours down.
It is basically 8pm in our final destination, so I want to sleep again soon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A bit cramped haha</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/10/14/a-bit-cramped-haha/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2015 10:36:16 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/10/14/a-bit-cramped-haha/</guid>
      <description>10:36 Wednesday 14 October 2015 JST Though amazingly, we each have AC power available at each seat, it&amp;rsquo;s a bit cramped to have my computer on the tray table in front of me. As I type this, I&amp;rsquo;m actually using my USB keyboard while it&amp;rsquo;s on my legs under the tray table.
Mouse motion is a bit cramped as well, so it&amp;rsquo;s not a very good environment for computin&amp;rsquo;, but I figured I&amp;rsquo;d give it a shot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>late late final night before Ma and Fred go home</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2013/01/10/late-late-final-night-before-ma-and-fred-go-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2013 03:03:14 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2013/01/10/late-late-final-night-before-ma-and-fred-go-home/</guid>
      <description>##03:03 Thursday 10 January 2013
2:51am Thursday 10 January 2013 as I write this. Just now about to go to bed after chatting with Lin a bit about the best way to get Ma and Fred to Shinagawa station. She wanted to rent a car to Shinagawa, but I think a simple taxi ride one way to Kawasaki will be faster and cheaper overall.
Chatted with Fred at the monthly apartment while he packed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>super proud of Lin!</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2012/12/10/super-proud-of-lin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Dec 2012 22:57:16 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2012/12/10/super-proud-of-lin/</guid>
      <description>##22:57 Monday 10 December 2012
She&amp;rsquo;s making some small and big stretches in her life&amp;hellip; This Christmas she&amp;rsquo;s making some gifts for family (instead of just buying stuff). (that&amp;rsquo;s what I&amp;rsquo;m calling the small stretch.)
The big thing about which I&amp;rsquo;m super impressed: she just applied for a new job &amp;hellip;. in Thailand!! Wow! She&amp;rsquo;s always wanted to travel, and I&amp;rsquo;ve always said, &amp;ldquo;so when are you going to do it?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Carla Biked Africa</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2012/08/29/carla-biked-africa/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Aug 2012 15:00:08 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2012/08/29/carla-biked-africa/</guid>
      <description>##15:00 Wednesday 29 August 2012
OMG!!! This is my friend Carla!!!
https://www.carlabikesafrica.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best picture of Johnny in SF</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2012/01/31/best-picture-of-johnny-in-sf/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2012 07:56:05 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2012/01/31/best-picture-of-johnny-in-sf/</guid>
      <description>##07:56 Tuesday 31 January 2012

Over our Christmas holidays, Lin and I went to San Francisco to see her uncle, and then to Texas to see my family and have a wedding ceremony on 30 December at Northwoods UU which was my church while I was in Texas growing up.
I hope to write more about the ceremony, but for now I want to archive this awesome picture of Johnny flying over the ________ in San Francisco.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>wheels?  who needs &#39;em?</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2008/11/17/wheels-who-needs-em/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2008 12:50:26 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2008/11/17/wheels-who-needs-em/</guid>
      <description>##12:50 Monday 17 November 2008
U.S. Air Plane Lands Without Front Wheels, No Injuries In Philadelphia As Landing Gear Fails To Deploy - CBS News
 Before the scheduled landing at Philadelphia, the crew got an indication that the landing gear was not down and did a flyover to confirm that the nose wheels had not deployed, airport spokeswoman Victoria Lupica said.
 Sweet!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>From Suzy xx in Palestine</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2008/03/07/from-suzy-xx-in-palestine/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2008 18:08:18 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2008/03/07/from-suzy-xx-in-palestine/</guid>
      <description>##18:08 Friday 07 March 2008
This was actually sent to me a long time ago, but I&amp;rsquo;m just now getting it posted
 Hi All, it&amp;rsquo;s been a while I know! Partly my lack of emails is because i&amp;rsquo;m not very good at keeping in touch (as pointed out very clearly by my sister last week!) and partly because I didn&amp;rsquo;t think I had that much to report. I&amp;rsquo;m settled here now and my life has it&amp;rsquo;s routine just like it did in the UK.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brief thoughts on Virtual Prison, I mean Fence</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2008/03/01/brief-thoughts-on-virtual-prison-i-mean-fence/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2008 21:19:04 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2008/03/01/brief-thoughts-on-virtual-prison-i-mean-fence/</guid>
      <description>##21:19 Saturday 01 March 2008
&amp;lsquo;Virtual Fence&amp;rsquo; Along Border To Be Delayed - washingtonpost.com
 Boeing has already been paid $20.6 million for the pilot project, and in December, the DHS gave the firm another $65 million to replace the software with military-style, battle management software.
 This, for some reason, seems shocking to me. Okay, so this is for a virtual fence 28 miles long. The $20.6 million price works out to almost $140 / foot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>chomp!</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2008/02/26/chomp/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2008 17:22:35 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2008/02/26/chomp/</guid>
      <description>##17:22 Tuesday 26 February 2008
Hammerhead Shark Diving by Shark Diver
 To insure[sic] the best results we will be “chumming” the water with fish and fish parts. Consequently, there will be food in the water while divers are in the water. To insure your safety, we will usually have one or two crewmembers in the water as safety. Please be aware that these are NOT “cage” dives, they are open water experiences.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>some guy lying on the sidewalk</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2007/11/06/some-guy-lying-on-the-sidewalk/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2007 14:49:03 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2007/11/06/some-guy-lying-on-the-sidewalk/</guid>
      <description>##14:49 Tuesday 06 November 2007
 cellie-0095.jpg
Originally uploaded by thunderrabbit
Not sure the story here, but as I was walking to lunch, I saw this guy on the main street of Dogenzaka. I thought he was on the phone, but as I walked by, he didn&amp;rsquo;t seem conscious enough to talk.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rob, Francois, Hello Kitty</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2007/11/04/rob-francois-hello-kitty/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Nov 2007 14:02:56 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2007/11/04/rob-francois-hello-kitty/</guid>
      <description>##14:02 Sunday 04 November 2007
 cellie-0094
Originally uploaded by thunderrabbit
Rob, Francois, and Kittie.
Ami took this picture in Nihon O-dori station</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rochelle in Oaxaca</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2006/08/13/rochelle-in-oaxaca/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2006 21:43:25 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2006/08/13/rochelle-in-oaxaca/</guid>
      <description>##21:43 Sunday 13 August 2006
Hello all…
So things in Oaxaca are intensifying and fast.
Last week there was a 2000+ womens&amp;rsquo; march of the Popular Assembly of the
State of Oaxaca (APPO). A quick recap, this is the organization that
formed after the June 14th police repression of the striking teachers
union SNTE Section 22. APPO is made up of the teachers as well as a huge
variety of social organizations who support the teachers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Good ol&#39; Tokyo</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2006/08/07/good-ol-tokyo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2006 18:47:10 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2006/08/07/good-ol-tokyo/</guid>
      <description>##18:47 Monday 07 August 2006
 Yoshio Kushida, a scientist who grew up in Tokyo said: &amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s the most dangerous city in the world. There is just no way I would live there.&amp;rdquo;
 Belfast Telegraph
Article about the horrific nightmare that Tokyo will become when it is leveled by a monster earthquake sometime between now and the next 70 years.
Of course no one considers it a real threat: these things happen elsewhere, and only to other people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rob&#39;s Palestine Summary</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2005/12/16/robs-palestine-summary/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2005 11:35:56 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2005/12/16/robs-palestine-summary/</guid>
      <description>##11:35 Friday 16 December 2005
I have been agonizing over this document for weeks. My basic task is to write about my experiences in the occupied territories of Palestine, but I find it impossible to actually put to paper anything that could get across the idea of the reality there.
My friends have asked me questions, and I find the answers difficult because I have to keep &amp;ldquo;backing up&amp;rdquo; to give context before anything can make sense.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rafah Crossing by Serena</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2005/11/28/rafah-crossing-by-serena/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2005 11:34:47 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2005/11/28/rafah-crossing-by-serena/</guid>
      <description>##11:34 Monday 28 November 2005
Below (save for the AP quote) was written by Serena, serene@riseup.net
 RAFAH TERMINAL, Gaza Strip - It was a smooth debut Saturday for the first Palestinian-run border crossing. Hundreds of travelers zipped through passport control without having to submit to Israeli security checks, savoring their new freedom after 38 years of military occupation.
  (Written [27 November 2005 By Ibrahim Barzak, Associated Press](https://www.google.com/custom?domains=robnugen.com&amp;amp;q=%22Palestinian-run+border+crossing.+Hundreds+of+travelers%22&amp;amp;sa=Search&amp;amp;sitesearch=&amp;amp;client=pub-8968158139273573&amp;amp;forid=1&amp;amp;channel=5817411192&amp;amp;ie=ISO-8859-1&amp;amp;oe=ISO-8859-1&amp;amp;cof=GALT%3A%23008000%3BGL%3A1%3BDIV%3A%23336699%3BVLC%3A663399%3BAH%3Acenter%3BBGC%3AFFFFFF%3BLBGC%3A336699%3BALC%3A0000FF%3BLC%3A0000FF%3BT%3A000000%3BGFNT%3A0000FF%3BGIMP%3A0000FF%3BFORID%3A1%3B&amp;amp;hl=en))  Reading the headline news on Rafah Crossing one would conclude that Palestinians are free to come and go as they please with minimal control by Israel over Gaza in general, nothing significantly impeding them from creating a prosperous economy, controlling their borders, air space and sea ports.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leaving Palestine tomorrow...</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2005/11/20/leaving-palestine-tomorrow.../</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2005 19:02:43 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2005/11/20/leaving-palestine-tomorrow.../</guid>
      <description>##19:02 Sunday 20 November 2005
Hello world!
In the past couple weeks, I&amp;rsquo;ve witnessed two and a half particularly interesting things.
1) One was the anti-climatic detonation of what turned out to be a fake grenade found by a Palestinian farmer near the olive trees we were helping him harvest.
He showed us the grenade, which looked real enough to warrant concern. It had been partially buried with its pin removed, and two stones covering it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jerusalem Update!</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2005/10/29/jerusalem-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2005 04:53:42 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2005/10/29/jerusalem-update/</guid>
      <description>##04:53 Saturday 29 October 2005
I&amp;rsquo;ve decided to write a few lines about what I&amp;rsquo;ve seen in the West Bank, though I have not actually picked olives yet.
I have a feeling this will be a long message, so I&amp;rsquo;m going to write it in sections, and may follow up with other sections soon.
======================= Section One: Vocabulary
When I first arrived here, I did not know the meaning / differences between &amp;ldquo;West Bank&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Gaza.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jerusalem</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2005/10/09/jerusalem/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2005 05:10:55 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2005/10/09/jerusalem/</guid>
      <description>##05:10 Sunday 09 October 2005
I&amp;rsquo;m in Jerusalem!
I haven&amp;rsquo;t really seen anything undeniably inappropriate, but there is definitely a distinction between areas for Palestinians and areas for Israelis, and definitely some weird stuff going on.
For the past two days, I&amp;rsquo;ve been staying in Faisal Hostel, basically across the street from Damascus Gate, a portal between the Old City of Jerusalem, and the rest of Jerusalem. The Old City is where a lot of biblical stories took place, including where Jesus was tortured and paraded through town, if I understand correctly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Life onboard</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2005/07/19/life-onboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2005 02:18:15 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2005/07/19/life-onboard/</guid>
      <description>##02:18 Tuesday 19 July 2005
We 16 GET Teachers (GET stands for Global English/Espanol Training) all teach two classes a day on 35 days of the voyage. During our free time we have the option of being quite busy with lectures and myriad activities on the ship. (( One of the biggest &amp;ldquo;problems&amp;rdquo; on the ship is deciding what to do next! Every room usually teems with activity. )) Somewhere during all that (usually at night when we&amp;rsquo;ve got several hours before classes) we plan lessons, with each teacher designing his or her own curriculum to fit the students and hopefully coordinate with the ports we&amp;rsquo;re visiting, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Le Havre, France</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2005/07/02/le-havre-france/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2005 05:33:46 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2005/07/02/le-havre-france/</guid>
      <description>##05:33 Saturday 02 July 2005
Hello from Le Havre, France! This city of 100,000 features some museums and gardens, and old architecture that I can&amp;rsquo;t name, but reminds me of old paintings. I&amp;rsquo;ve written more detail about our Le Havre wanderings in my journal dated July 2nd.
I think the last time I wrote was in Egypt (Port Said) after we saw the three Great Pyramids and Sphinx in Cairo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sri Lanka</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2005/06/06/sri-lanka/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2005 05:45:52 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2005/06/06/sri-lanka/</guid>
      <description>##05:45 Monday 06 June 2005
Not just Sri Lanka, but Columbo, which is the largest city (though not the capital) in this beautiful friendly country. The people are as friendly as in Vietnam, and the traffic is about as crazy, but with more trucks and 3-wheelers (little three wheel trucks they use as taxis).
The homes here are often covered in corrugated sheet metal, with patchwork quilt appearance from above. We got a tour through a university (possibly named Kabilla) and it started raining (we&amp;rsquo;re in monsoon season now) so little red muddy rivers formed between the trees.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Viet Nam</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2005/06/01/viet-nam/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2005 05:40:09 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2005/06/01/viet-nam/</guid>
      <description>##05:40 Wednesday 01 June 2005
Vietnam has been the best stop so far (Hong Kong, Danang, Singapore). People were friendly, roads were bumpy and chaotic, little 8 to 12 year old kids hardselling postcards, silk things, tiger balm, .. anything they could carry around. I must say they were quite well practiced with quick lines and little pouty faces that could wrench money from the coldest heart.
I bought custom made sandals for 95,000 d.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Costa Rica</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1999/11/11/costa-rica/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 1999 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1999/11/11/costa-rica/</guid>
      <description>Costa Rica 20:53 Thursday 11 November 1999
Oh I keep forgetting!!!
A few days ago, I got the following email:
 From: Roni Kahn Subject: Your Site and the Tabacon page To: thunderrabbitATcheerfulDOTcom Dear Rob, I visited your web site regarding Costa Rica and stapled upon a page about Tabacon. My name is Roni Kahn and I&#39;m the assistant marketing director of Tabacon, I was really impressed from your impression of Tabacon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spring Break Science Trip</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1987/03/22/spring-break-science-trip/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Mar 1987 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1987/03/22/spring-break-science-trip/</guid>
      <description>(transcribed 5:50pm CST Monday 20 January 2003 - 11:ish Wednesday 22 January 2003)
(reformatted for Hugo 20 October 2017)
Mr. Hamm Mr. Cowan Beth Ahlborn Renae Ahlborn Pam Tacquard Julia Eckhardt Trace&#39; Dutson David Osborne Kevin Hollenshead Wade Johnson Barry Nelson Robert Nugen David Osborne Gary Picou Eric Shafer Brian Thigpen Allen Torgesen Carl Torgesen Charles Mike Hurt Glen Wilson Eric Likins John Tim Oestrich Doug ITINERARY Spring Trip Sunday-March 22: 11:00 AM-leave Tomball 2:00 PM-snack-roadside park near Bastrop 4:00 PM-supper in Austin 5:30 PM-arrive Inks Lake State Park.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>