<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>noborito on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/noborito/</link>
    <description>Recent content in noborito on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2017 00:07:06 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/noborito/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>noborito construction</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/10/06/noborito-construction/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2017 00:07:06 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/10/06/noborito-construction/</guid>
      <description>00:07 Friday 06 October 2017 JST I just discovered I uploaded these, but it seems I did not add them to my journal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>hung out with Michael near Noborito</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/09/09/hung-out-with-michael-near-noborito/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2017 00:08:05 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/09/09/hung-out-with-michael-near-noborito/</guid>
      <description>00:08 Saturday 09 September 2017 JST First time to hang out with Michael one on one. We ate at a cafe in the station and then went barefoot out on a balcony where we talked to a mom waiting for her kid to come back from school. Michael chatted with her a bit, introducing us.. I was kinda amazed because even though my Japanese is better, I&amp;rsquo;m not as willing to break the ice with people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Noborito station is getting a new southbound line</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/08/27/noborito-station-is-getting-a-new-southbound-line/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2017 18:34:19 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/08/27/noborito-station-is-getting-a-new-southbound-line/</guid>
      <description>18:34 Sunday 27 August 2017 JST I have been taking (but not really posting) pictures of the new train line in Noborito station. I guess it&amp;rsquo;s part of the campaign Odakyu has been announcing that they will reduce the congestion on the line, and even decrease the time required to go to Shinjuku.
Anyway, they did something which surprised me: put down the rails, locked them down, then took them back up before laying them down again.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>