<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>mika on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/mika/</link>
    <description>Recent content in mika on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 May 2018 08:06:12 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/mika/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>with Kai and Mika met Mike at The Pink Cow</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/05/18/with-kai-and-mika-met-mike-at-the-pink-cow/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2018 08:06:12 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/05/18/with-kai-and-mika-met-mike-at-the-pink-cow/</guid>
      <description>08:06 Friday 18 May 2018 JST 昨日ピンクカウ美佳さんと佳依さんと会って楽しみました。　Had a good time chilling with Kai and Mika at The Pink Cow last night.
マイケルさんも会った。彼が世界の1番よくなバーテンダーでしたって。We also met Michael. He said he&amp;rsquo;s the worlds best bartender.
そうでもそうでもないわからないけど、彼と面白い話できた。I don&amp;rsquo;t know if that&amp;rsquo;s true, but we had a good time talking to him.
美佳さんと佳依さんと日本語でも英語でも喋りました。I spoke in Japanese and English with Kai and Mika.
戸からピンポン音はピッザヂリベリかたが来た。みんながびっくりした。笑 Everyone was surprised when we heard a knock at the door; it was a pizza delivery guy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kai and Mika tonight</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/11/25/kai-and-mika-tonight/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Nov 2017 00:42:59 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/11/25/kai-and-mika-tonight/</guid>
      <description>00:42 Saturday 25 November 2017 JST Hung out with Kai and Mika near Mika&amp;rsquo;s work tonight. They gave me a stack of flyers to hand out for a show that Mika and Kai will be staffing on Monday. Thanks to Mika for sending my medium rare burger back to be recooked to well done as I had ordered! Thanks to Mama for snacks she brought back today from her trip.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mika bye bye party</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/03/19/mika-bye-bye-party/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2015 23:14:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/03/19/mika-bye-bye-party/</guid>
      <description>##23:14 Thursday 19 March 2015 JST##
On the train now after hanging out with Mika and Kai for nearly 3 hours around Tokyo station. French restaurant Gabo and then Mary&amp;rsquo;s (chocolate) Cafe where customers can self-serve white chocolate shavings on drinks!
Mika is moving to a new company, so this was our bye-bye party for her. We talked about their kanji, which I forgot, and Lin&amp;rsquo;s kanji, which I remember. Kai showed pictures of their trip to Europe and we compared our experiences in Paris; Kai saw Versaille, which sounds really big and beautiful!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>