<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>list on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/list/</link>
    <description>Recent content in list on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2016 11:41:52 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/list/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The List</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/09/15/the-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2016 11:41:52 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/09/15/the-list/</guid>
      <description>11:41 Thursday 15 September 2016 JST The List by Michael John Grist is now available! This is the fifth book in his Zombie series starting with The Last, and it&amp;rsquo;s possibly The Best!
This book really drives the characters forward, facing their greatest fears head-on as they leaving loved ones behind, stepping into a fight for their survival.
I love the care Grist puts into little details, bringing the characters to life in the real world, with great subtle foreshadowing!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Things to do soon</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/02/04/things-to-do-soon/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2015 19:07:37 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/02/04/things-to-do-soon/</guid>
      <description> 19:26 Wednesday 04 February 2015 JST  walk home with Lin write to JB list of students&amp;rsquo; names process recent emails ask Nate about CB tickets make maze for book write Fiverr card send Fiverr card write plans for 18 Feb class evaluate Pelican for static site submit medical receipts to insurance call Soness look at AB tickets move all www.robnugen.com content to static site move ridiculous wiki stuff to static site  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>buying Minecraft for Fred</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/12/04/buying-minecraft-for-fred/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/12/04/buying-minecraft-for-fred/</guid>
      <description>##14:08 Thursday 04 December 2014 JST##
After I said / hinted to Fred that I&amp;rsquo;d love to play Minecraft with him on a world that I&amp;rsquo;ve been tweaking for months over the past couple years, he said he knew what he wanted for Christmas.
So today, I did a big step towards buying Minecraft for Fred: update my beneficiary bank account in the US with GoLloyds GoRemit.
That way I can pay off my credit card (most of which was due to my having bought a follower on Twitter), so I can feel less dumb about charging MC to my MC.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>