<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>rant on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/rant/</link>
    <description>Recent content in rant on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2019 21:42:22 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/rant/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>I can choose to do anything (and no one really cares)</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/blog/2019/09/18/i-can-choose-to-do-anything-and-no-one-really-cares/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2019 21:42:22 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/blog/2019/09/18/i-can-choose-to-do-anything-and-no-one-really-cares/</guid>
      <description>So long as I do stuff within a normalized range, no one really cares what I do.
I can spend all day trying to figure out one bug, or ignore it. No one will know the difference. I could even quit my job, and just a few people will notice. (some people very much so, but 99+% will not)
Re-reading the above sounds like I am suicidal, but I am not.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>XCode do you hate me</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/08/11/xcode-do-you-hate-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2017 19:27:53 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/08/11/xcode-do-you-hate-me/</guid>
      <description>19:27 Friday 11 August 2017 JST Oh XCode, you&amp;rsquo;re so quirky.
You automatically change Images.xcassets, automatically add the changes to git, AND automatically restore the changes after I revert them. This might be helpful if you did not also refuse to build the app due to missing images. I hate building iOS apps. Utterly shit experience all the fucking time.
Why do sandboxed users have to have difficult passwords? I don&amp;rsquo;t mind good passwords for real users, but not for sandboxed users.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>stupid Finder</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/03/29/stupid-finder/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2015 10:15:43 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/03/29/stupid-finder/</guid>
      <description>10:15 Sunday 29 March 2015 JST Mail.app wouldn&amp;rsquo;t respond after Finder.app isn&amp;rsquo;t loading. I forced relaunch of Finder, but it hasn&amp;rsquo;t relaunched yet.
Here&amp;rsquo;s what I wrote to Apple when the dialog said &amp;ldquo;oh you killed Mail app; do you want to report it?&amp;rdquo;
Finder won’t start. I don’t know if that’s affecting Mail, but I had to kill finder because its one (1) single window couldn’t display ten (10) ten little (less than 1MB each) images.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apple, please get your shit straight</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2013/04/23/apple-please-get-your-shit-straight/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2013 20:49:26 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2013/04/23/apple-please-get-your-shit-straight/</guid>
      <description>##20:49 Tuesday 23 April 2013
8:44pm Tuesday 23 April 2013
I&amp;rsquo;m trying to create a test account. It&amp;rsquo;s a test account, about which I do not care. It cannot spend any real money; it&amp;rsquo;s a test account. BUT it has to have to have a real password, a birthdate, a first and last name, the last three of which are not used ANYWHERE.
But that&amp;rsquo;s not why I&amp;rsquo;m bitching.
When creating the test account, I tried to use the email address c at robnugen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apple, please get your shit straight</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2013/04/22/apple-please-get-your-shit-straight/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2013 07:25:16 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2013/04/22/apple-please-get-your-shit-straight/</guid>
      <description>##07:25 Monday 22 April 2013
6:52am Monday 22 April 2013
A couple days ago I renewed my iOS developer account because our apps made just enough money to cover the cost of the developer account.
EVEN THOUGH the email address on my account has not changed, Apple sent me an email &amp;ldquo;to complete my purchase&amp;rdquo; (wtf does that even mean? My credit card was charged; the purchase has been completed!)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apple, please get your shit straight</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2013/04/21/apple-please-get-your-shit-straight/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2013 22:31:26 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2013/04/21/apple-please-get-your-shit-straight/</guid>
      <description>##22:31 Sunday 21 April 2013
10:26pm Sunday 21 April 2013
I apparently received an email on my iPhone. When I unlock my phone, I have a screen that says so. When I press the big green Dismiss button at the bottom, the screen persists.
So, either I have received 50+ messages (and have to press Dismiss for each one), or my iPhone is stuck in a loop out of which I cannot break without turning off my phone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Xcode, what are you doing?</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2013/02/01/xcode-what-are-you-doing/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2013 20:46:16 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2013/02/01/xcode-what-are-you-doing/</guid>
      <description>##20:46 Friday 01 February 2013
I&amp;rsquo;m trying to get some work done; I&amp;rsquo;m trying to give my time and money to Apple so I have a chance to make a nickel.
Why is the provisioning process so obtuse? Am I just an idiot who can&amp;rsquo;t figure it out?
Why does Xcode have so many bugs? Did I write it?
As I write this, Xcode is locked up. Apparently I&amp;rsquo;m going to have to force close it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>terrible GUI on Chase.com</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2012/04/05/terrible-gui-on-chase.com/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Apr 2012 09:47:17 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2012/04/05/terrible-gui-on-chase.com/</guid>
      <description>09:47 Thursday 05 April 2012 I may sound like Grampa on The Simpsons, but the interface to provide feedback to chase.com can be improved with just a few obvious tweaks.
Tweak 1) the form doesn&amp;rsquo;t need to ask for my name, much less make it a required field; I&amp;rsquo;m logged in ffs, so you have my name.
Tweak 2) fix the CSS; when I expand the textarea (thank you very much for that), the absolutely positioned line below it should move out of the way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>US society is coming apart at the seams</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2008/01/10/us-society-is-coming-apart-at-the-seams/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2008 17:08:05 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2008/01/10/us-society-is-coming-apart-at-the-seams/</guid>
      <description>##17:08 Thursday 10 January 2008
 Whether it is the loss of a decent job, impossible conditions at work, rising prices, the threat of foreclosure or bankruptcy, the promise of endless war in Iraq and elsewhere, crumbling infrastructure, the elimination or slashing of social services and programs—US society is coming apart at the seams. None of the presidential candidates of the two big business parties is either willing or able to address these burning problems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Muslim Astronaut&#39;s Dilemma: How to Face Mecca From Space</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2007/10/10/a-muslim-astronauts-dilemma-how-to-face-mecca-from-space/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2007 12:40:48 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2007/10/10/a-muslim-astronauts-dilemma-how-to-face-mecca-from-space/</guid>
      <description>##12:40 Wednesday 10 October 2007
 Questions like these will continue as more and more religious astronauts travel into space. When is sunset in low Earth orbit if you&amp;rsquo;re experiencing a dozen sunrises and sunsets in every 24-hour period? When does Sabbath begin on the moon, where the sun sets once a month? When is the first sighting of the crescent moon if you&amp;rsquo;re on Mars? Religious councils of all faiths will have plenty to keep them busy for years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Worcester Telegram &amp; Gazette News</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2007/07/15/worcester-telegram-gazette-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jul 2007 14:05:19 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2007/07/15/worcester-telegram-gazette-news/</guid>
      <description>##14:05 Sunday 15 July 2007
Worcester Telegram &amp;amp; Gazette News
 All regions of the world will change, with the risk that nearly a third of the Earth’s species will vanish if global temperatures rise just 3.6 degrees above the average temperature in the 1980s-90s, the new report says. Areas that now have too little rain will become drier.
 Yet that grim and still preventable future is a toned-down prediction,</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>