<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>shell on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/shell/</link>
    <description>Recent content in shell on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Mar 2018 20:56:47 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/shell/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Great day</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/04/great-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Mar 2018 20:56:47 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/04/great-day/</guid>
      <description>20:56 Sunday 04 March 2018 JST Went to SOGO for workout with about 50 people in attendance. Great weather and great workout. I met Shell, Koji, Tyler, and others, but cannot remember now.
Went to lunch with Lisa at Laska and chatted with her a bit, and got to see a video of the type of dancing she is doing.
Went down to Tsujido for karaoke after recording video at karaoke with Kai, Mitsue, and Soness as the stars.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mens group</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/11/05/mens-group/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2017 21:50:40 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/11/05/mens-group/</guid>
      <description>21:50 Sunday 05 November 2017 JST We are building a peer support group of committed men who help each other meet their full potential. We meet twice a month
We build conflict resolution skills, create a personal mission statement, and create great friendships.
Would you be interested in hearing more about it? Come to one of our open sessions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>shell scripting</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/02/24/shell-scripting/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2015 18:31:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/02/24/shell-scripting/</guid>
      <description>##18:31 Tuesday 24 February 2015 JST##
I made the md5 cheater script, and want to augment it a bit to do something entirely different. I have never really programmed shell scripts, so we&amp;rsquo;ll see how it goes.
I wonder if I should search for Bash scripting tutorials or stay with more fundamental *nix code? I think I&amp;rsquo;ll go for Bash; this project ain&amp;rsquo;t very important, and I just want to get it done, plus I&amp;rsquo;m probably the only person who will use it, and I only use Bash.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>