<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>video on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/video/</link>
    <description>Recent content in video on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2019 12:49:16 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/video/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>my focus matters</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/blog/2019/07/08/my-focus-matters/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2019 12:49:16 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/blog/2019/07/08/my-focus-matters/</guid>
      <description>Where I place the focus my attention makes a difference in how I experienced my life.
Have you seen the basketball video? If not, have a look:
  If I&amp;rsquo;m in a bad mood I tend to see things that are likewise bad. If I&amp;rsquo;m in a good mood I tend to see things that are likewise good.
This causes a natural feedback loop that tends to amplify itself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>tail flip mystery</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/07/20/tail-flip-mystery/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2018 23:11:51 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/07/20/tail-flip-mystery/</guid>
      <description>In this livestream, I added 1 second of video to the 6th snippet.
In the background, the reversible guy has just gotten the bridge cut and is about to place it when he (and I, ahem) realized it was flipped around the wrong way.
In the foreground, the snake began climbing up the ramp to the triple ball splitter while the manager tries to work out how to get the small ball to fall at the right place.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mt3 gotcha</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/07/14/mt3-gotcha/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jul 2018 12:58:18 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/07/14/mt3-gotcha/</guid>
      <description>12:58 Saturday 14 July 2018 JST Working on MT3 today I had a funny idea. There were two marbles ready to roll off the track and I realized it would be great for the spoonhead guy to catch them. So I had to erase eight frames, but they were not too hard to recreate, and the end result is great.
  The frames are shown in the last second of the video above.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mt3: ready to test</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/07/12/mt3-ready-to-test/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jul 2018 22:32:22 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/07/12/mt3-ready-to-test/</guid>
      <description> 22:32 Thursday 12 July 2018 JST   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mt3: snake powered fall</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/06/24/mt3-snake-powered-fall/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jun 2018 13:53:59 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/06/24/mt3-snake-powered-fall/</guid>
      <description>13:53 Sunday 24 June 2018 JST Added about 3 seconds worth of frames, so about 36 frames today. Pretty good! One of the snakes has finished his first task and is now snaking around to meet up with his friend who will soon be able to snake around. Not sure if I will have them leave&amp;hellip; oh, maybe they should curl up and wait somewhere.
Pinky fell off the stage and hit the switch, so the stage is rotating again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mt3: yoi sho</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/06/15/mt3-yoi-sho/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 12:55:05 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/06/15/mt3-yoi-sho/</guid>
      <description>12:55 Friday 15 June 2018 JST よいしょ is the audio I want to add right at the end of this video. In this case, it is the equivalent of &amp;ldquo;3. 2. 1. lift!&amp;rdquo;
Spoonhead is adept at getting the marbles onto the stage because he&amp;rsquo;s the right height for that. I gave him long arms as well to help lift marbles (and knock the switch around accidentally).
  Speaking of accidents, while trying to film the frame after they lifted the marble, it fell and knocked everything askew.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mt3: adding small curve</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/06/08/mt3-adding-small-curve/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2018 15:16:58 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/06/08/mt3-adding-small-curve/</guid>
      <description> 15:16 Friday 08 June 2018 JST In addition to creating frames for the movie itself, I have been creating a curved track to be the stand-in track for the large marble to spiral around the whole stage.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mt3: introducing spoonhead</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/05/30/mt3-introducing-spoonhead/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 May 2018 05:15:44 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/05/30/mt3-introducing-spoonhead/</guid>
      <description> 05:15 Wednesday 30 May 2018 JST I spent a couple hours on MT3 yesterday, culminating in introducing a new character whose job is to carry marbles onto the stage. On his way out, he hit the switch to reverse the stage rotation, so Squarehead will fall because he is just about to jump off the stage onto the ramp, but the stage is just about to reverse direction.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MT3 Fancy Footwork</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/05/22/mt3-fancy-footwork/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 May 2018 12:44:56 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/05/22/mt3-fancy-footwork/</guid>
      <description> 12:44 Tuesday 22 May 2018 JST Only a couple of characters to move around, and no big disasters of things moving without authorization, so I was able to add five seconds of video today in just 1.25 hours.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mt3 helpful snakes</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/05/15/mt3-helpful-snakes/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 May 2018 14:36:10 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/05/15/mt3-helpful-snakes/</guid>
      <description> 14:36 Tuesday 15 May 2018 JST Today I livestreamed more of The Making of The Construction of Marble Track 3
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mt3 snakes</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/05/13/mt3-snakes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 May 2018 19:15:18 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/05/13/mt3-snakes/</guid>
      <description>19:15 Sunday 13 May 2018 JST Hahaha I am really entertained by this next portion of the video. Didn&amp;rsquo;t even really see it coming until just the other day when I needed a way to hold up a rail while it gets glued into place.
  Since June 2017, I have spent 7.5+ days on Marble Track 3.
The resulting video snippets, available via https://mt3s.robnugen.com/, total approximately 9 minutes 39 seconds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mt3 whats on the ramp</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/05/10/mt3-whats-on-the-ramp/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2018 09:34:25 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/05/10/mt3-whats-on-the-ramp/</guid>
      <description> 09:34 Thursday 10 May 2018 JST Neat neat neat I just discovered some new characters who should prove to be pretty useful as well as squirmy and maybe giving heebee jeebees!
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mt3: retested large marble</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/05/02/mt3-retested-large-marble/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2018 10:12:52 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/05/02/mt3-retested-large-marble/</guid>
      <description>09:05 Wednesday 02 May 2018 JST Yesterday I glued a piece onto the track which was designed to catch small marbles as they fall through the not parallel bamboo chopstick marble splitter.
Now it&amp;rsquo;s time to see if it worked!
Woohoooo it worked!!
     
09:18 Wednesday 02 May 2018 JST Uh oh.
After I tested the fix today, while setting up for the next frame, I noticed the large marbles could not roll past the piece.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mt3: brotherly spat</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/24/mt3-brotherly-spat/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2018 13:32:35 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/24/mt3-brotherly-spat/</guid>
      <description>13:32 Tuesday 24 April 2018 JST   Curiously, I do not see the live stream that I broadcast today. Usually they are visible on Marble Track 3 YouTube channel immediately after upload.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mt3: moving chopstick</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/17/mt3-moving-chopstick/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Apr 2018 13:53:29 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/17/mt3-moving-chopstick/</guid>
      <description>13:53 Tuesday 17 April 2018 JST I did only about 56 minutes of MT3 today before I glued a piece and had to pause. The large sized marble has been lifted up onto the track; the little brother has gotten back onto the stage and is fighting the big brother; the manager has just placed a little toothpick rail on the small marble track that meanders down from the ball splitter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mt3: ready to glue u turn</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/10/mt3-ready-to-glue-u-turn/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Apr 2018 16:55:36 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/10/mt3-ready-to-glue-u-turn/</guid>
      <description> 16:55 Tuesday 10 April 2018 JST   At the time I am posting this, I actually already glued and tested the U turn.
Here is the video I streamed during the test:
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mt3: stopped the madness</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/04/mt3-stopped-the-madness/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Apr 2018 09:58:02 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/04/mt3-stopped-the-madness/</guid>
      <description>09:58 Wednesday 04 April 2018 JST I added lots of frames yesterday to Marble Track 3 video. There was a long section with just 2 or 3, or even just 1 character moving at a time. I added 20 seconds to the video, which destroys any previous day expect maybe the first couple days when I just had the manager walking around.
I did not exactly predict the current situation; I just knew the chopstick poking off the edge of the track should do something.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mt3: lil brother hitches a ride</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/29/mt3-lil-brother-hitches-a-ride/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Mar 2018 15:41:11 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/29/mt3-lil-brother-hitches-a-ride/</guid>
      <description>15:41 Thursday 29 March 2018 JST I worked for 90 minutes today and nearly 60 minutes the other day (but did not put up a new video then). The latest:
  While the Reversable Guy went to see what happened, the little brother grabbed onto the chopstick which had kept the stage from rotating properly. Before crashing into the ramps, he jumped off; he is fine.
Soon RG will go back to the switch and perhaps find the ramp knocked over, or maybe the ramp will turn the switch on full blast which could be fun.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mt3: glued dual track rail</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/24/mt3-glued-dual-track-rail/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Mar 2018 11:15:41 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/24/mt3-glued-dual-track-rail/</guid>
      <description>11:15 Saturday 24 March 2018 JST   I have two sets of notes descrbing what characters should do. The Reversable Guy is trying to figure out why the stage is not rotating. The green head guy is about to glue a small stick under the ball splitter.
Meanwhile, Candycane Mom has just put the dual track rail in place down at another ball split point. It will hold medium-sized and small-sized marbles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mt3: hmm is the stage slowing down?</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/20/mt3-hmm-is-the-stage-slowing-down/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Mar 2018 15:22:32 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/20/mt3-hmm-is-the-stage-slowing-down/</guid>
      <description>15:22 Tuesday 20 March 2018 JST (written 09:25 Wednesday 21 March 2018 JST)
In a single day, I can take maybe 20 or 30 frames, which adds a couple of seconds to the final movie.
Yesterday, I worked 2 hours on Marble Track 3, including adding a new dimension of planning to the project:
  
I wrote notes to script out the next 5 weeks (or so) for the Reversable Guy (character whose head looks largely the same when facing forward or backward) as he debugs why the stage is slowing down.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mt3: progressing nicely</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/18/mt3-progressing-nicely/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Mar 2018 16:40:52 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/18/mt3-progressing-nicely/</guid>
      <description>16:40 Sunday 18 March 2018 JST An interesting thing is happening with the stage rotation. Last week I noticed a chopstick was sticking out too far for the stage to turn all the way around, and this time it has hit the wall and begun to hamper the rotation of the stage.
  I think the cutter guy might cut the offending chopstick and have the stage spring forward, which I may do in slow motion again, like when the manager got yanked by the spinning bearing while they tried to wrangle it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mt3 glued three pieces</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/17/mt3-glued-three-pieces/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Mar 2018 15:33:38 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/17/mt3-glued-three-pieces/</guid>
      <description>15:33 Saturday 17 March 2018 JST I think I added four seconds of video today in about an hour and a half. Pretty speedy because at some points only two characters were moving.
  Since June 2017, I have spent 6.3+ days on Marble Track 3.
The resulting videos available via https://mt3s.robnugen.com/ are like 8 minutes 32 seconds long.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mt3: back to work</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/06/mt3-back-to-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Mar 2018 16:36:21 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/06/mt3-back-to-work/</guid>
      <description>16:36 Tuesday 06 March 2018 JST Now that the little brother has been found to be alive and kicking, it&amp;rsquo;s time to get back to work.
  I will be out of town during the weekend, so not able to work on this until next week, probably Thursday or Friday.
Since June 2017, I have spent 6.3+ days on Marble Track 3.
The resulting videos available via https://mt3s.robnugen.com/ are like 8 minutes 28 seconds long.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mt3: look at me!</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/02/27/mt3-look-at-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2018 12:07:40 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/02/27/mt3-look-at-me/</guid>
      <description>12:07 Tuesday 27 February 2018 JST I finished the 5th snippet today. The little brother has been found, and did a little dance on the topmost track, much to everyone&amp;rsquo;s consternation because they had just spent several seconds looking for him.
This clip has 1400 frames in it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mt3: found little brother</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/02/20/mt3-found-little-brother/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2018 11:27:37 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/02/20/mt3-found-little-brother/</guid>
      <description>11:27 Tuesday 20 February 2018 JST I had previously thought of having the little brother come running up to see what all the fuss was about, and knock everyone off the stage. But I have done that once, and it wastes a bunch of time, and the timing didn&amp;rsquo;t work out anyway.
So in the end, the characters who were looking for him all turn around one by one. Candycane mom will put her hands on her hips after she fully turns around.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mt3: calling for help</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/02/12/mt3-calling-for-help/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2018 12:03:22 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/02/12/mt3-calling-for-help/</guid>
      <description>14:03 Friday 09 February 2018 JST
{&amp;lt; youtube s-KCwA27wjA &amp;gt;}
12:03 Monday 12 February 2018 JST On Feb 5th and Feb 8th I finished the final 5 seconds of video uploaded as &amp;ldquo;squiggle squiggle&amp;rdquo; on Friday, and then three seconds of &amp;ldquo;squiggle squiggle squiggle&amp;rdquo; on Saturday(?) and now after filming 2 seconds of video in 60 minutes, he is nearly out from between the plates, and they are nearly in full force looking for him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>nearly 8 minutes of mt3</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/02/03/nearly-8-minutes-of-mt3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2018 12:13:15 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/02/03/nearly-8-minutes-of-mt3/</guid>
      <description> 12:13 Saturday 03 February 2018 JST I spent an hour or more figuring out how to get Blender to import images and output video. This video is all of the frames I have so far. (5500 or so)
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mt3</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/02/01/mt3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2018 16:35:39 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/02/01/mt3/</guid>
      <description>16:35 Thursday 01 February 2018 JST Today I did 1.5 hours of live stream to get about 1 second of new video added to Dragonframe&amp;rsquo;s ongoing take.
In the foreground on the left, the cutter cut a piece (I decided to redo about 7 frames to get his cut lined up properly) which the gluer glued into place. In the foreground on the right, the 8th rib is being put into place.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mt3: just before gluing 7th rib</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/30/mt3-just-before-gluing-7th-rib/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2018 10:54:48 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/30/mt3-just-before-gluing-7th-rib/</guid>
      <description>10:54 Tuesday 30 January 2018 JST Recorded 2 seconds of video today, including having the little brother spin around and fall off the top end of the track splitter. The big brother started to run down to the area to look for his little brother but he won&amp;rsquo;t find him&amp;hellip; I have decided to have the little brother crawl out from between the stages in about 6 movie-seconds from now, which may be in 2 months from now?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mt3: spinning again while adding 6th rib</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/28/mt3-spinning-again-while-adding-6th-rib/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2018 21:53:25 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/28/mt3-spinning-again-while-adding-6th-rib/</guid>
      <description>21:53 Sunday 28 January 2018 JST I spent nearly 3 hours on Marble Track 3 today, but over an hour of it was trying to figure out how to make Blackmagic Fusion import multiple sequences of images to put them into one movie.
I was not able to figure it out.
  I have a sneaking suspicion that BM Fusion is not designed to do this. Most of its output options were images, so.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mt3: curving ribs 4 and 5</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/19/mt3-curving-ribs-4-and-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2018 15:55:02 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/19/mt3-curving-ribs-4-and-5/</guid>
      <description>15:55 Friday 19 January 2018 JST This clip includes 1066 frames. I didn&amp;rsquo;t upload clips the past 2 or 3 times I worked on the track because it took a long time to add the first three ribs to the edge of the largest marble&amp;rsquo;s track.
Now I am in the process of getting some characters off the set because they are just じゃま and wasting time during filming. I already have the brothers wasting enough time, plus the guy in the back trying to make his way around the currently-highest point of the largest marble&amp;rsquo;s track.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mt3: pics and toothpicks</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/09/mt3-pics-and-toothpicks/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2018 15:59:39 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/09/mt3-pics-and-toothpicks/</guid>
      <description>15:59 Tuesday 09 January 2018 JST I have worked on MT3 a few times since getting back. A couple days ago, progress was super slow and I did not even export a video clip, much less upload one. Today I got much further, after having figured out a way to lift the bridge, and then I had the green cutter guy make some curved toothpicks which will be used for rail supports to keep the large marbles on track during the 2nd to last U-turn.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mt3: recovery after big marble mishap</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/12/mt3-recovery-after-big-marble-mishap/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2017 09:51:29 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/12/mt3-recovery-after-big-marble-mishap/</guid>
      <description>09:51 Tuesday 12 December 2017 JST I added a record 7 seconds of video in just 2 hours. Part of that was certainly due to fewer disparate things going on, not the least of which being that the stage was stopped from turning!
At this point:
 the cutter is just about to cut the excess support off the ramp base, after which the gluer will lift the base and glue the pieces to it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>oops characters reacted too quickly</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/07/oops-characters-reacted-too-quickly/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2017 20:56:11 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/07/oops-characters-reacted-too-quickly/</guid>
      <description>20:56 Thursday 07 December 2017 JST I am quite happy with at least half of the frames I shot today. Fortunately, I am happy with the difficult ones! They were the frames in which the big marble rolled down the M Splitter and then slammed against the wall, driving the white pole all the way into the wall.
After the ball hit the floor, I had the other characters react to the &amp;ldquo;sound&amp;rdquo;, but upon playback, they react too quickly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mt3: before releasing the big marble</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/05/mt3-before-releasing-the-big-marble/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2017 13:46:08 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/05/mt3-before-releasing-the-big-marble/</guid>
      <description>13:46 Tuesday 05 December 2017 JST I worked on MT3 in two parts today. Right around 2 hours total, I think, not including letting glue dry (during which I ate lunch and had a nice nap). I found a pretty good technique for keeping the large marble in place: using a twist tie looped around the track seems to do the trick. If I had taken the time to figure that out before I had the guy push the big marble up the M Splitter, he would have been able to walk up on both rails.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mt3: guy fell off stage after ramp was overturned</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/11/29/mt3-guy-fell-off-stage-after-ramp-was-overturned/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2017 15:39:28 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/11/29/mt3-guy-fell-off-stage-after-ramp-was-overturned/</guid>
      <description>15:39 Wednesday 29 November 2017 JST I finally glued the last piece of the M Splitter.. and it works! Marbles roll down it faster than I had hoped, so I considered lowering it.. but there is just enough room for the small marbles to roll under that track and onto the small marble track which has walls on it, if I lower one of the walls.
Unfortunately, that wall is also the support for the track, so it will be tricky to cut.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mt3: Fully glued half of M splitter</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/11/25/mt3-fully-glued-half-of-m-splitter/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Nov 2017 12:07:59 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/11/25/mt3-fully-glued-half-of-m-splitter/</guid>
      <description>12:07 Saturday 25 November 2017 JST Only one hour so far today on Marble Track 3.
 
The images above show the track before and after having glued the second support on the first half of what I am calling the M Dropper or M Splitter. It will split the medium sized marbles off the large marble track by being too wide for the medium sized marbles to touch both sides of the track.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mt3: glue half M dropper</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/11/24/mt3-glue-half-m-dropper/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2017 14:17:52 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/11/24/mt3-glue-half-m-dropper/</guid>
      <description>14:17 Friday 24 November 2017 JST Today I glued the first half of the track which will separate the medium sized marbles from the large marbles. I am reasonably sure I can get it to work without too much undo/redo, but it has taken some time to get it to look like the characters put it all in place.
One slight mistake: I need to cut the end of the sticks because they stick out beyond the edge of the circle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mt3: cut vertical piece</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/11/24/mt3-cut-vertical-piece/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2017 08:37:43 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/11/24/mt3-cut-vertical-piece/</guid>
      <description>08:37 Friday 24 November 2017 JST I just uploaded the video that I took yesterday. At this moment, the vertical bar is cut, but I have not taken the photo for that cut. The green guy has swiped his sword, and I cut the bar, but.. let&amp;rsquo;s just say they are not poised for the shot.
 
  Since June 2017, I have spent 4.444 4.4+ days so far on Marble Track 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mt3: dual chopsticks arriving</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/11/21/mt3-dual-chopsticks-arriving/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 13:01:35 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/11/21/mt3-dual-chopsticks-arriving/</guid>
      <description>13:01 Tuesday 21 November 2017 JST I added about 2 seconds of footage today in 1.5 hours. Fast because a lot of it was just moving some characters around. Slow because Jennie came to sit in my lap for a bit. (I have come to accept the idea of letting her walk onto the scene; I will just take pictures of her entry&amp;hellip; but she chose not to walk on the desk.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mt3: mt3.robnugen.com</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/11/18/mt3-mt3.robnugen.com/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Nov 2017 15:00:18 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/11/18/mt3-mt3.robnugen.com/</guid>
      <description>15:00 Saturday 18 November 2017 JST During the livestream today, I watched the (5) clips so far to see which characters have had the ability to pass through tracks. Basically it&amp;rsquo;s easier to let characters pass through tracks, but I think it would be a good subtle thing if some characters (consistently) can, and some (consistently) cannot.
Anyway, I took notes and pinned them to the blue fabric which makes the floor of the set.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mt3: three angled walls</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/11/17/mt3-three-angled-walls/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2017 10:46:29 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/11/17/mt3-three-angled-walls/</guid>
      <description>10:46 Friday 17 November 2017 JST   Today I glued the third of three angled walls along the small marble track which will eventually catch marbles which will have rolled over the medium sized track that ends with the toothpick lock.
I have spent 4.2+ days ) so far on Marble Track 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mt3: 1.5 hours to add three pieces</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/11/14/mt3-1.5-hours-to-add-three-pieces/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2017 14:08:06 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/11/14/mt3-1.5-hours-to-add-three-pieces/</guid>
      <description>14:08 Tuesday 14 November 2017 JST Funny to put it that way, but yeah today about 30 minutes per glued piece, if I recall correctly. I went to bed early last night and woke up early to get started on MT3.
Right now I am on the train so don&amp;rsquo;t have the clip ID handy.. oh but Chrome remembered it.
  And here is the livestream https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=H3jQqWMIZFA
I am optimistic that the pieces I glued in place will prove to have been glued in correct enough places to stay put.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mt3: added stairs in back</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/11/10/mt3-added-stairs-in-back/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2017 16:40:56 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/11/10/mt3-added-stairs-in-back/</guid>
      <description>16:40 Friday 10 November 2017 JST   I have spent 4.1+ days on MT3 so far.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mt3: knocked off the stage by the big ball</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/11/09/mt3-knocked-off-the-stage-by-the-big-ball/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2017 15:43:34 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/11/09/mt3-knocked-off-the-stage-by-the-big-ball/</guid>
      <description>15:43 Thursday 09 November 2017 JST   I added 4 seconds of video during three.75 hours of livestreaming today; thanks to Jimmy for watching the last two!
I have spent 4+ days on MT3 so far.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mt3 started last track</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/11/07/mt3-started-last-track/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2017 22:57:34 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/11/07/mt3-started-last-track/</guid>
      <description>22:57 Tuesday 07 November 2017 JST   I have spent 3.8+ days on MT3 so far.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mt3: started other small tracks</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/11/06/mt3-started-other-small-tracks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2017 22:30:56 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/11/06/mt3-started-other-small-tracks/</guid>
      <description>22:30 Monday 06 November 2017 JST   I have spent 3.7+ days on MT3 so far.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mt3: big curve ball</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/11/03/mt3-big-curve-ball/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2017 16:29:43 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/11/03/mt3-big-curve-ball/</guid>
      <description>16:29 Friday 03 November 2017 JST I added 13 seconds of video in 2.25 hours today!
  I have spent 3.6 days on MT3 so far.
Thanks to Jimmy for watchin 2 hours today!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mt3 brought first bamboo</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/10/26/mt3-brought-first-bamboo/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2017 15:09:17 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/10/26/mt3-brought-first-bamboo/</guid>
      <description>15:09 Thursday 26 October 2017 JST Here is the latest video in my marble track construction series. I added about 4 or 5 seconds to the end of the video today.
  I have spent 3.5 days on MT3 so far.
22:26 grun1.com is working again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mt3 got another track glued down</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/10/20/mt3-got-another-track-glued-down/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2017 15:43:16 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/10/20/mt3-got-another-track-glued-down/</guid>
      <description>15:43 Friday 20 October 2017 JST I bought an AC adapter to use with my camera. Today I had been able to use the battery for about 90 minutes before it conked out. The adapter was 2000 yen from Amazon, but between 6000 and 8000 yen at Bic Camera and Yodobashi Camera. How will this play out in the long term? Bic Camera connect with Amazon Buy Now inside their store?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mt3 glued some small track</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/10/17/mt3-glued-some-small-track/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 12:38:59 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/10/17/mt3-glued-some-small-track/</guid>
      <description>12:38 Tuesday 17 October 2017 JST   I have spent 77+ hours on MT3 so far.
Special thanks to Jimmy for watching the Live stream nearly 3 hours today https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9V9_JSesKSo</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mt3 two more rolls</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/10/14/mt3-two-more-rolls/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2017 20:19:45 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/10/14/mt3-two-more-rolls/</guid>
      <description> 20:19 Saturday 14 October 2017 JST   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mt3 first roll celebration</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/10/10/mt3-first-roll-celebration/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2017 13:11:43 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/10/10/mt3-first-roll-celebration/</guid>
      <description>13:11 Tuesday 10 October 2017 JST   yay they rolled a marble!
Live stream in two parts today.
 Up to the first roll https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BjtpiRxoxvU The first roll https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=i9gCFg5TpqQ  I have spent 73 hours on MT3 so far.
10:23 Wednesday 11 October 2017 JST Oh wow I really love it. The characters manically run around for a bit and it&amp;rsquo;s hard to tell what&amp;rsquo;s going on, but then they all line up for the first roll; I think it looks pretty good.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mt3 nearly ready to glue</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/09/30/mt3-nearly-ready-to-glue/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2017 20:02:01 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/09/30/mt3-nearly-ready-to-glue/</guid>
      <description>20:02 Saturday 30 September 2017 JST To be honest, this is taking longer than even I expected. I need to plan ahead a bit better to put characters where the need to be to glue stuff down, etc.
  I have spent 70+ hours on MT3 so far.
Two livestreams today https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=EeY85MnK_y4 and https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tZAxfzXo63I</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mt3： first rails and marbles</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/09/28/mt3-first-rails-and-marbles/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2017 15:41:47 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/09/28/mt3-first-rails-and-marbles/</guid>
      <description>15:41 Thursday 28 September 2017 JST   I have spent 68+ hours on MT3 so far.
Today&amp;rsquo;s livestream https://youtu.be/FRIBcPa6nRI
Playlist https://mt3s.robnugen.com/ mt3s stands for Marble Track 3 Snippets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mt3： first rolling marble</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/09/27/mt3-first-rolling-marble/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2017 00:06:51 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/09/27/mt3-first-rolling-marble/</guid>
      <description>00:06 Wednesday 27 September 2017 JST   It does not honestly make a lot of sense, but the marble rolled on the stage and the guys ran around while it spun.
Livestream is here https://youtu.be/UAhlgQTAN4U
I have spent 66 hours on MT3 so far.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mt3 Francois kicked the stage into place</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/09/23/mt3-francois-kicked-the-stage-into-place/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2017 21:43:13 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/09/23/mt3-francois-kicked-the-stage-into-place/</guid>
      <description>21:43 Saturday 23 September 2017 JST It isn&amp;rsquo;t as smooth as I&amp;rsquo;d like, but the moment Francois kicks the stage represents about 1 hour of time spent during which I attached the upper stage to the lower stage. Connecting the upper stage was challenging enough for me, so it would have taken a silly amount of time to create footage of the pipe cleaner guys doing it.
  Here are today&amp;rsquo;s livestreams:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mt3 Attached bearing to stage</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/09/22/mt3-attached-bearing-to-stage/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2017 20:35:13 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/09/22/mt3-attached-bearing-to-stage/</guid>
      <description>17:44 Friday 22 September 2017 JST   Once I got the screwdriver upright, it went quite quickly to get all the screws in. Even so, it took two hours to do the screwdriver part in the video above.
Here is the livestream: https://youtu.be/UCiYZ17Yhe4</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mt3 Francois arrives</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/09/22/mt3-francois-arrives/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2017 20:35:13 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/09/22/mt3-francois-arrives/</guid>
      <description>17:44 Friday 22 September 2017 JST The playlist for Marble Track 3 now has four videos.
20:35 Friday 22 September 2017 JST   Get the helicopter up to super high speed and hovered the stage over to the right then started bringing the new stage with Francois.
Here is the livestream: https://youtu.be/VaOK-BXbmmU
I have spent 60+ hours on MT3 so far.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mt3 finished drilling holes</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/09/18/mt3-finished-drilling-holes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2017 18:12:55 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/09/18/mt3-finished-drilling-holes/</guid>
      <description>18:12 Monday 18 September 2017 JST   Pretty sure I finished the
05:20 Tuesday 19 September 2017 JST haha I don&amp;rsquo;t remember what I was going to write. I am pretty sure I did not finish the sentence.
I finished drilling the holes, but they may not be deep enough; yup that was it.
Livestream was split in two parts.
https://youtu.be/o5jzoI51LC0 https://youtu.be/5ygVtSrDhJk
I have spent 56+ hours on MT3 so far.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mt3 wrong direction</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/09/14/mt3-wrong-direction/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2017 16:04:39 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/09/14/mt3-wrong-direction/</guid>
      <description>16:04 Thursday 14 September 2017 JST I livestreamed for just about an hour today, and added a gag related to the direction of motion. Standing on opposite sides of the circle, the direction of rotation was miscommunicated between two characters.
  Here is a link to MT3 snippets playlist
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fWNuuGVUCgQ livestream for today.
I have spent 54+ hours on MT3 so far.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mt3 drilled one hole</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/09/12/mt3-drilled-one-hole/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2017 11:58:07 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/09/12/mt3-drilled-one-hole/</guid>
      <description>11:58 Tuesday 12 September 2017 JST It was a bit challenging to use the screwdriver and drillbit which are pretty heavy compared to the pipe cleaners, but I was able to get the first hole drilled, and I think I have a good system to drill the other holes in just the right places. I have glued the drillbit holder (yellow and green pipe cleaner guy) to the top of the bearing in such a way that he will hold the drillbit in the right spot for each hole simply by rotating the bearing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mt3 screeching the bearing</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/09/11/mt3-screeching-the-bearing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2017 18:35:25 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/09/11/mt3-screeching-the-bearing/</guid>
      <description>18:35 Monday 11 September 2017 JST   Because I needed to get the bearing aligned, I did a little trope of the scratching fingernails variety as one of the characters simply pulled the bearing into place. He was not one of the characters who tried to wrangle it, but the sorta-joke is that apparently he could have done it without all the trouble of making it float, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mt3 rewind before Matrix</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/09/09/mt3-rewind-before-matrix/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2017 20:25:13 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/09/09/mt3-rewind-before-matrix/</guid>
      <description>20:25 Saturday 09 September 2017 JST   Two livestreams from today, the second one being of me trying to figure out how to copy / reverse some frames in Dragonframe, plus messing with OBS a bit. I need to add 20 minutes to the total count because I forgot to start the second live stream on time..
https://youtu.be/N_9ocOflC9I
https://youtu.be/6YlM3UT467E
Before compressing month information, I had spent 50 hours on MT3 so far.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mt3 slow motion flip</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/09/08/mt3-slow-motion-flip/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2017 11:28:11 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/09/08/mt3-slow-motion-flip/</guid>
      <description>11:28 Friday 08 September 2017 JST I am really happy with this bit of the sequence. Thank you, Wachowski siblings.
  Here is the live stream from today https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zCqvXIN_G1k
I have spent 45.75 hours on MT3 so far.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mt3 beginning to wrangle</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/09/05/mt3-beginning-to-wrangle/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2017 07:14:09 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/09/05/mt3-beginning-to-wrangle/</guid>
      <description>07:14 Tuesday 05 September 2017 JST Starting livestream now. I think this is my channel so you can follow along https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCHiQhB8J_KI2LYQ7dsexfLw
09:47 Tuesday 05 September 2017 JST   I have spent 44 hours on MT3 so far.
Livestream for today https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WUpkQGOFpoI</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mt3 let&#39;s get ready to wrangle</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/09/02/mt3-lets-get-ready-to-wrangle/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2017 00:15:51 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/09/02/mt3-lets-get-ready-to-wrangle/</guid>
      <description>00:15 Saturday 02 September 2017 JST I have spent 42 hours on MT3 so far.
Livestream for today https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=owMCXdK-fC0
Latest segment as of today:
  They are preparing to center the spinning bearing over the stage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>before / during Harvey flood on Cypresswood</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/08/29/before-/-during-harvey-flood-on-cypresswood/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2017 08:46:06 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/08/29/before-/-during-harvey-flood-on-cypresswood/</guid>
      <description>08:46 Tuesday 29 August 2017 JST</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mt3 finished drawing circle</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/08/28/mt3-finished-drawing-circle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2017 19:37:20 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/08/28/mt3-finished-drawing-circle/</guid>
      <description> 19:37 Monday 28 August 2017 JST ⁂ Two videos and three or four livestreams today (and tonight).
https://youtu.be/i1mLycv9TwE
https://youtu.be/to4mS_4E-d0
12:22 Thursday 31 August 2017 JST begin centering bearing hasn&amp;rsquo;t finished processing, but I uploaded the video:
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mt3 finished drawing circle</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/08/26/mt3-finished-drawing-circle/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2017 11:13:16 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/08/26/mt3-finished-drawing-circle/</guid>
      <description>11:13 Saturday 26 August 2017 JST   Last night in the middle of drawing the circle which will help me center the bearing on the stage, I had to reglue the guide which I used to show where the pen should draw along the edge, so I paused the livestream while it dried.
17:27 livestream: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=J6wzdFQO2II started drawing the circle
1:31:35 livestream: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Vo_ysqq0VXc finished drawing the circle
I have spent 1 day 14 hours on MT3 so far.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mt3 getting to work</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/08/24/mt3-getting-to-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2017 16:46:25 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/08/24/mt3-getting-to-work/</guid>
      <description>16:46 Thursday 24 August 2017 JST   I have spent 1 day 8 hours on MT3 so far.
Plus whatever I spent today (4 or 5 hours across two livestreams, including the first one where I replied to Jimmy&amp;rsquo;s chats).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mt3 while ma watched</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/08/22/mt3-while-ma-watched/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2017 08:14:13 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/08/22/mt3-while-ma-watched/</guid>
      <description>08:14 Tuesday 22 August 2017 JST   Ma watched while I added about 100 frames to the video.
00:58 Wednesday 23 August 2017 JST   I have spent 1 day 8 hours on MT3 so far.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mt3 playlist MT3 movie so far</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/08/16/mt3-playlist-mt3-movie-so-far/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2017 22:49:51 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/08/16/mt3-playlist-mt3-movie-so-far/</guid>
      <description> 22:49 Wednesday 16 August 2017 JST  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mt3： curiosity</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/08/15/mt3-curiosity/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2017 11:09:19 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/08/15/mt3-curiosity/</guid>
      <description>11:09 Tuesday 15 August 2017 JST   Turned on the rotating bearing to test it, and one character nearly came too close.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The helicopter has landed</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/08/12/the-helicopter-has-landed/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2017 03:24:42 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/08/12/the-helicopter-has-landed/</guid>
      <description>03:24 Saturday 12 August 2017 JST This 20 second clip took 6 hours to make.
  According to the durations listed on the livestreams, I have spent 1 day 1 hour on MT3 so far.
Today&amp;rsquo;s livestream is here https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LnMk9D6lhgA
https://www.stopmotionanimation.com/profiles/blogs/my-first-flying-object
Using thread, I suspended a bearing plate from a broom over my set. I did not have a good way to adjust the length of the thread, so I used several layers of thick cloth (socks) on one side of the broom to allow the plate to descend toward the stage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mt3：skeleton arrives</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/08/08/mt3skeleton-arrives/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2017 11:33:46 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/08/08/mt3skeleton-arrives/</guid>
      <description>11:33 Tuesday 08 August 2017 JST   This is the first time the skeleton has been seen in a scene of Marble Track 3.
The livestream was 3 hours; it got split in the middle
https://youtu.be/9mEeIYsISLk
https://youtu.be/AALQGwA44Gc
video time: 68 seconds so far
video making time: 69001 seconds ( 19 hours) so far.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mt3： finished making skeleton</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/08/07/mt3-finished-making-skeleton/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2017 05:26:56 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/08/07/mt3-finished-making-skeleton/</guid>
      <description>05:26 Monday 07 August 2017 JST Interesting to see the sun start to stream through the window at the end.
  Livestream is here https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_25n-AKfa4E
16 hours so far.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>skeleton escapades</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/08/01/skeleton-escapades/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2017 11:52:05 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/08/01/skeleton-escapades/</guid>
      <description>11:52 Tuesday 01 August 2017 JST   Most of the live stream is here
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vcZYH25RMO8
14.5 hours so far.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MT3： begin assembling the characters</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/07/22/mt3-begin-assembling-the-characters/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2017 22:09:08 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/07/22/mt3-begin-assembling-the-characters/</guid>
      <description>22:09 Saturday 22 July 2017 JST   I added 200 frames in 2 hours 41 minutes (which included some prep time for future frames)
Livestream for today is here https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LCPFtlDrWkM
12.5 hours so far</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Added two frames</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/07/21/added-two-frames/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2017 19:11:26 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/07/21/added-two-frames/</guid>
      <description>19:11 Friday 21 July 2017 JST I added two frames to the video today. Now when the camera is knocked backward, it takes a bit of time to move.
  Here is the livestream from today https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WUL94mRtWYs</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>first stage moving first stage into place</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/07/11/first-stage-moving-first-stage-into-place/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2017 14:14:22 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/07/11/first-stage-moving-first-stage-into-place/</guid>
      <description>14:14 Tuesday 11 July 2017 JST   Here is the livestream from today.
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hOC9B5sx6v4
9 hours 24 minutes so far in livestreams for this thing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>got my Dragonframe bluetooth keypad</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/07/07/got-my-dragonframe-bluetooth-keypad/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 10:51:23 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/07/07/got-my-dragonframe-bluetooth-keypad/</guid>
      <description>10:51 Friday 07 July 2017 JST Nice.
It came with some little cards that can be used to focus, and some pages that can be used to plan scenes.. maybe I will sketch some out now.
08:11 Saturday 08 July 2017 JST Yesterday I ended up with about 80 frames of completed video.
  I might redo them from a different camera angle, but that would mean (starting over and) making a new shelf (or something) to hold the camera.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mt3： Have a plan for the base</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/07/04/mt3-have-a-plan-for-the-base/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2017 13:00:06 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/07/04/mt3-have-a-plan-for-the-base/</guid>
      <description>13:00 Tuesday 04 July 2017 JST Here is the video of just the frames of characters moving around. Red/white guy escapes the stage:
  Here are all the still frames taken:
  Here is the livestream https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bgxiGkFJhYs which features some audio pops and stuff at the beginning so watch your ears.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>303 frames of video</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/06/27/303-frames-of-video/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2017 19:42:35 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/06/27/303-frames-of-video/</guid>
      <description>19:42 Tuesday 27 June 2017 JST I am pretty happy with this video.
  I livestreamed its creation.
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PzBBKzArGKk</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cops Dashboard Videos Show Racial Slur, Fleeing Suspects Hit By Cruisers</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2008/03/21/cops-dashboard-videos-show-racial-slur-fleeing-suspects-hit-by-cruisers/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2008 16:23:39 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2008/03/21/cops-dashboard-videos-show-racial-slur-fleeing-suspects-hit-by-cruisers/</guid>
      <description>##16:23 Friday 21 March 2008
Videos Show S.C. Troopers Behaving Badly, Feds Launch Probe After Dashboard Videos Show Racial Slur, Fleeing Suspects Hit By Cruisers - CBS News
 A federal investigation was launched into the South Carolina Highway Patrol after dashboard camera videos showed a trooper using a racial slur and two others ramming their cruisers into fleeing suspects, a prosecutor said Thursday.
 Oh my god. What is happening to the world?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>it all started here</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2007/06/27/it-all-started-here/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2007 10:07:34 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2007/06/27/it-all-started-here/</guid>
      <description>27 June 2007 JST (written 10:11 Monday 25 September 2017 JST)
Okay so it all started ten years ago. I made Marble Track 2 during my free time at work and then made this video.
  People asked how I made the marble track. It&amp;rsquo;s a simple question without a simple answer. &amp;ldquo;I glued sticks together..&amp;rdquo;
I decided I should answer by showing the pipe cleaner characters making the track.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>