<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>bryn on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/bryn/</link>
    <description>Recent content in bryn on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2002 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/bryn/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>bryn</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/04/13/bryn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/04/13/bryn/</guid>
      <description>9pm ish
Bryn and I were sitting next to one another looking at her pictures of London and Paris when the lights went out as we were beckoned to the mass wedding.
Not an *actual* wedding, but an invitation for each person to honor others in friendship - these incredible bonds that YRUU makes possible.
This activity started in Plano a few years ago, and they had an anniversary each year afterward.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>bryn</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/03/27/bryn/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/03/27/bryn/</guid>
      <description>Brynsies! So great that you got your flight; thanks for letting me know. :-) I hear ya about being super busy; I have been AS well, and after two days of not a lot of work, I&#39;m about to get movin and groovin to get some stuff done around here. I have mostly gotten my sleep back inline with this timezone. Lee-eh was so funny last night, she said I have to &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>from bryn</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2001/12/23/from-bryn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Dec 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2001/12/23/from-bryn/</guid>
      <description>Date: Sun, 23 Dec 2001 19:39:12 -0800 (PST) From: Bryn Subject: California. To: thunderrabbit
Hey Rob!
I finished &amp;ldquo;Way of the Peaceful Warrior&amp;rdquo; yesterday with tears in my eyes on a plane en route to California. So i am here now visiting my mother&amp;rsquo;s parents and my aunt. good fun. But i have an amazing story to tell you!
So tonight my mom, sister, aunt, and I all went to eat sea food at our favorite seafood spot in So.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bryn</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2001/10/27/bryn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Oct 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2001/10/27/bryn/</guid>
      <description>Remember the loving feeling of wanting so much for Bryn to feel comfortable with her decision about whether or not to attend ACT class tomorrow in the AM (in 3 hours or so) maybe 5 hours. Hug hug hug and just so much love expressed for her. I Love You sign as I said bye to her. She was on the phone in the kitchen and I left for bed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>chat with Bryn</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2001/02/17/chat-with-bryn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2001/02/17/chat-with-bryn/</guid>
      <description>10:24 pm sat 17 feb 2001
Hello Rob. We are at Irene and Nick&#39;s wedding reception. i can&#39;t remember the last one of these i attended but it must have beAn quite some time ago. it is super dark in here. anyways, i love nick&#39;s smile (as i have expressed and wish for you to remeber) and irene is so beautiful and their happiness in an odd way definitely inspires me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>note from Bryn</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/06/04/note-from-bryn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/06/04/note-from-bryn/</guid>
      <description>Rob, OKC rally Sat 4 June 2000
Over the past three-ish years, i have met many people and done many things unlike any of my dreams. through all of these things, one person has always suported me, always comforted me, and always brought so much light to my life. rob, you&amp;rsquo;ve beAn so incredible. thank you for being my friend. when i think of not seeing you for VERY long times, it&amp;rsquo;s super sad.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>