<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>day on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/day/</link>
    <description>Recent content in day on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2019 00:07:01 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/day/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Super great day with Colleen</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/10/04/super-great-day-with-colleen/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2019 00:07:01 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/10/04/super-great-day-with-colleen/</guid>
      <description>(written 00:07 Friday 04 October 2019 PDT)
Colleen had to wait an extra hour for me to go through immigration and customs in Seattle. Once we hung out, though, it was like no time had passed!
                          
Lively laughy fun dinner with Colleen and Ryan at their house while eating pizza.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Friday</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/07/26/friday/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2019 10:22:29 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/07/26/friday/</guid>
      <description>10:22 Friday 26 July 2019 JST Nice meditation this morning and just finished an online group meeting for Integration Group Coordinators. It went well, though some &amp;ldquo;summaries&amp;rdquo; from small groups seemed like they may be as long as the originals.
I wanna do some work for AB, ConSwi, TEDx, and meditation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Great day so far</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/06/18/great-day-so-far/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2019 15:29:01 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/06/18/great-day-so-far/</guid>
      <description>15:29 Tuesday 18 June 2019 JST I got 1.5 hours of livestream done on MT3 and about an equal amount of work done on AB. Plus spent time ostensibly studying Japanese by watching Kakegurui in Japanese. (Season 2 now has subtitles in English.)
Anndd had a nice nap.
Rode TJ Bike to the station and am now on my way to 麻布十番 for my third session with Rin.
We are going to work on my first workshop together as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>today</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/04/26/today/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 13:53:19 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/04/26/today/</guid>
      <description>13:53 Friday 26 April 2019 JST Today has seemed busy; my brain was spinning with what to do next for a while this morning. I ended up creating a new Part entry for Marble Track 3 (tssfobls) before attending men&amp;rsquo;s group meeting (Integration Group Council).
Now I am on the way back from Tokyo station where I met Tariq and Jon (for different reasons). Tariq about ConSwi, and Jon to give him a bag he left at our house.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Great day today</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/04/21/great-day-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2019 20:00:22 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/04/21/great-day-today/</guid>
      <description>20:00 Sunday 21 April 2019 JST Lin and I enjoyed a great productive day today, starting with a romp after calling my mom on voip.
Main things for me: work on AB, fix bicycles. Lin wanted to clean the house a bit so she did that while I worked on AB.
We walked our decrepit bicycles to a local shop. Mine had to get a new chain; Lin&amp;rsquo;s bicycle needed a new valve stem and new seat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>productent</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/10/09/productent/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2018 23:25:22 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/10/09/productent/</guid>
      <description>23:25 Tuesday 09 October 2018 JST Today wasn&amp;rsquo;t as productive as I had planned, but I got some good stuff done.
4:30am meeting with Boysen, and should have a landing page for The Men&amp;rsquo;s Work soon.
8:00am IL lesson in which we talked about Tsukiji and 2020 Olympics https://the-japan-news.com/news/article/0004879769
came home to work on MT3, but ended up just sleeping
7:00pm Tokyo Men&amp;rsquo;s Circle https://tokyo.mypowercircle.org/
8:06pm someone killed themselves in Seijogakuenmae (a station along my train line)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>day</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/04/06/day/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2017 17:20:29 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/04/06/day/</guid>
      <description>17:20 Thursday 06 April 2017 JST work work work tired tired tired but fun talking about science-related topics. Before the lessons started at 2pm I was watching videos on Youtube and like snapped out of a reverie like oh-shit-what-timeisit? and thank goodness I still had ample time to make it to the lesson but dannnng that was spooky. I set an alarm on my phone to alert me 30 minutes beforehand.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>