<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>japan on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/japan/</link>
    <description>Recent content in japan on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2019 09:17:27 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/japan/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>great fear and great meeting</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/06/07/great-fear-and-great-meeting/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2019 09:17:27 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/06/07/great-fear-and-great-meeting/</guid>
      <description> 09:17 Friday 07 June 2019 JST Had a great meeting this morning where I was able to express my fear and feelings of inadequacy about being a leader.
Next steps, I will:
 Ask men &amp;ldquo;who do you want to sit in circle with you?&amp;rdquo; send English version to Zumi write my experience online send Doodle regarding next meeting time contact 3 men to invite  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>automatic gate immigration</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/10/06/automatic-gate-immigration/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2017 08:29:14 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/10/06/automatic-gate-immigration/</guid>
      <description>08:29 Friday 06 October 2017 JST Here is my QR code which apparently lets me through the immigration gate in a breeze. So nice that they have this service! On my way out of Narita, the lines to go through the human powered checkpoints were quite long compared to the lack of lines in the automated gates. Hmmm&amp;hellip; so I went over there and they helped me get registered free of charge!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>noborito construction</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/10/06/noborito-construction/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2017 00:07:06 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/10/06/noborito-construction/</guid>
      <description>00:07 Friday 06 October 2017 JST I just discovered I uploaded these, but it seems I did not add them to my journal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Noborito station is getting a new southbound line</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/08/27/noborito-station-is-getting-a-new-southbound-line/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2017 18:34:19 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/08/27/noborito-station-is-getting-a-new-southbound-line/</guid>
      <description>18:34 Sunday 27 August 2017 JST I have been taking (but not really posting) pictures of the new train line in Noborito station. I guess it&amp;rsquo;s part of the campaign Odakyu has been announcing that they will reduce the congestion on the line, and even decrease the time required to go to Shinjuku.
Anyway, they did something which surprised me: put down the rails, locked them down, then took them back up before laying them down again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>made pottery</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/08/19/made-pottery/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2017 11:04:24 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/08/19/made-pottery/</guid>
      <description>11:04 Saturday 19 August 2017 JST We just made some pottery with an chill old man sensei. I made a mobius strip for Fred, an upside-down plate for me, a dice shaker and two dice for my students.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>went to Lake Motosu</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/08/12/went-to-lake-motosu/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2017 15:51:36 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/08/12/went-to-lake-motosu/</guid>
      <description>15:51 Saturday 12 August 2017 JST Lin drove Ma and me to Lake Motosu. Super great to have a perfect break in the rainy weather on the way there and at the lake! Now on the way back, it is slightly foggy. (500m visibility)
Before laking, we ate next to four pugs whose owners had outfitted them with vests with ice pouches on their chests. While we ate, several bicyclists arrived (after we had passed them on the road on the way up).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>whiskey vending machine</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/12/26/whiskey-vending-machine/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Dec 2015 23:13:44 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/12/26/whiskey-vending-machine/</guid>
      <description>23:13 Saturday 26 December 2015 JST On the way home we saw a soft drink machine next to an alcohol machine which offered beer and two types of liquor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Customer service win</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/02/04/customer-service-win/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2015 15:07:37 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/02/04/customer-service-win/</guid>
      <description>15:46 Wednesday 04 February 2015 JST Last night I realized I must have left my computer power supply in Ebisu.
Today I went to Yodobashi Camera and specified I wanted a power supply for this computer (which they had on display). Upon arrival at home I discovered the power supply they gave me was not the power supply I requested.
I immediately blamed the sales guy mother fucker frackin smackin waste my time fricken asshole pendejo piece of s</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lost my phone</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/02/lost-my-phone/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/02/lost-my-phone/</guid>
      <description>##11:37am Sunday 2 November 2014##
Got off the train, felt no cellphone in my front pocket!
Crap!
I turned around and (stupidly) started angling back toward the train door where we had gotten off, instead of straight back to the train and got on before the doors closed.
D&amp;rsquo;oh!
Went to the lost and found to report it. I was like, &amp;ldquo;so where does that train stop?&amp;rdquo; thinking they could look up that the train that left at 11:37am and know when and where it was scheduled to stop for the day (probably 大崎).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New house in Kawasaki!</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/03/04/new-house-in-kawasaki/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/03/04/new-house-in-kawasaki/</guid>
      <description>##6:20am Tuesday 4 March 2014 JST##
We moved! Our new house is great, though a bit farther from the station. However, that gives me a chance to take a walk each morning and evening. I allocate 30 minutes walking time each direction. Not sure how far it actually is, but probably around 2km. 2.6km according to Google.
The key words for this house are big and nice. Oh, and cats (surrounding).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Years lunch with Ma and Fred in Japan 3 Jan 2013</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2013/01/03/new-years-lunch-with-ma-and-fred-in-japan-3-jan-2013/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2013/01/03/new-years-lunch-with-ma-and-fred-in-japan-3-jan-2013/</guid>
      <description>##family lunch in Japan 03 Jan 2013
(written 01:28 Monday 24 November 2014 JST)
Nice day!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>State of My Life Address</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2012/10/21/state-of-my-life-address/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Oct 2012 00:37:05 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2012/10/21/state-of-my-life-address/</guid>
      <description>##00:37 Sunday 21 October 2012
 I haven&amp;rsquo;t written a SoML in a while.
 Fred and Ma are coming to Japan in December!!
 Lin and I have been going to yoga class every Saturday morning at Yogasan.
 I&amp;rsquo;ve been working at sbstrm for going on 3 years now, not counting my Thailand adventure and chilling in Chigasaki.
 My long-running project at sbstrm is for AB, for whom Lin used to work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>got my visa extended</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2012/08/29/got-my-visa-extended/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Aug 2012 14:13:51 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2012/08/29/got-my-visa-extended/</guid>
      <description>##14:13 Wednesday 29 August 2012
Being married has its perks. One is free kisses. Another is permission to stay in Japan. I got my new visa today, and due to Japan&amp;rsquo;s new system, it&amp;rsquo;s not a sticker in my passport. It&amp;rsquo;s in a chip in my new card. And it expires in only a year. Gah. I wonder why it expires so soon; I used to get three year visas by being a programmer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>some guy lying on the sidewalk</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2007/11/06/some-guy-lying-on-the-sidewalk/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2007 14:49:03 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2007/11/06/some-guy-lying-on-the-sidewalk/</guid>
      <description>##14:49 Tuesday 06 November 2007
 cellie-0095.jpg
Originally uploaded by thunderrabbit
Not sure the story here, but as I was walking to lunch, I saw this guy on the main street of Dogenzaka. I thought he was on the phone, but as I walked by, he didn&amp;rsquo;t seem conscious enough to talk.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>