<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>joy on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/joy/</link>
    <description>Recent content in joy on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2019 21:22:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/joy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>What do emotions tell us</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/blog/2019/06/18/what-do-emotions-tell-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2019 21:22:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/blog/2019/06/18/what-do-emotions-tell-us/</guid>
      <description>Sticking with the basics, we have joy and fear.
Joy is how I feel when I have what I want, or I don&amp;rsquo;t want what I don&amp;rsquo;t have. I am aligned with what is, and have no need or desire to change it.
Fear is the emotion which says I don&amp;rsquo;t have enough information. This is usually about an unknown future. I come to a proverbial fork in the road and could simply choose arbitrarily, but if there is a part of me that wants to choose the &amp;ldquo;right&amp;rdquo; option, I may feel fear about choosing the &amp;ldquo;wrong&amp;rdquo; option.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Godot coding</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/12/godot-coding/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2017 17:16:29 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/12/godot-coding/</guid>
      <description>17:16 Tuesday 12 December 2017 JST I may be speaking too soon, but programming in Godot is so easy I could just cry. (in terms of memory managment, auto completion, and things just working)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gunma weekend</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/07/30/gunma-weekend/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2017 18:47:31 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/07/30/gunma-weekend/</guid>
      <description>18:47 Sunday 30 July 2017 JST Thanks to Rohini for inviting all the beautiful people who joined the Gunma adventure staying at Renee&amp;rsquo;s place.
Yesteray morning Lisa led yoga and later in the day she played an instrument with four strings. We tried doing some chanting with it, but no one knew the chants.
We went to the caves apparently dug by hand with a bunch of different statues (33?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>