<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>christmas on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/christmas/</link>
    <description>Recent content in christmas on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/christmas/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Harrod&#39;s bear for Lin</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/12/24/harrods-bear-for-lin/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/12/24/harrods-bear-for-lin/</guid>
      <description>##16:15 Wednesday 24 December 2014 JST##
I got Lin the 2014 Harrod&amp;rsquo;s bear, &amp;ldquo;Jasper&amp;rdquo; (I think). I&amp;rsquo;ve essentially promised her one each year, but each year I try to convince her that she doesn&amp;rsquo;t need another so she won&amp;rsquo;t expect it when she receives it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>great 2012 Christmas!</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2012/12/30/great-2012-christmas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Dec 2012 22:55:56 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2012/12/30/great-2012-christmas/</guid>
      <description>##22:55 Sunday 30 December 2012
No pics yet but they might be on my mom&amp;rsquo;s FB wall already.
Ma, Mama, Lin, Fred, and I shared gifts and laughter. I had the most fun watching Lin unwrap her teddy bear. The outer box was apparently mailed from Fred to me, the next inner box was from me to Fred; the next inner box was from Fred to Lin; the next inner box was from Lin to Lin; the next inner box was from Lin to Ma; the next inner bag was from Ma to Mama; the next inner box was from Mama to me, but that box was actually for Lin, which she could see very clearly from its branding.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>post Christmas</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1999/12/27/post-christmas/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Dec 1999 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1999/12/27/post-christmas/</guid>
      <description>pm Monday 27 December 1999
(transcribed from my diary)
Yesterday Fred and I rode his unicycle around more and tossed my new frisbee-ish thing (collapseable hinged ring) and then I went home. My butt hurts from unicycling.
Today Channing IMed me and asked about KTRU. After I told him all our music types, he was all, &amp;ldquo;what&amp;rsquo;s Navrang?&amp;rdquo; I told him it was music from India (but I&amp;rsquo;m afraid even that might be wrong), and that&amp;rsquo;s all I know.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>christmas</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1999/12/25/christmas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Dec 1999 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1999/12/25/christmas/</guid>
      <description>late pm Christmas Day 1999
(transcribed from my diary)
Presents and cookies at Ma&amp;rsquo;s in College Station then I surprised everyone by arriving at Dad&amp;rsquo;s in Magnolia. Fred was there; he had decided at the last minute to fly in to town (his plans at Berkeley fell through). I am so glad to have seen him unwrap the crazy gift! He required 1.3 hours to unwrap it. Really. That time does not include a break for dinner.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>pre-christmas</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1999/12/24/pre-christmas/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 1999 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1999/12/24/pre-christmas/</guid>
      <description>9:15pm Friday 24 December 1999
(transcribed from my diary)
I&amp;rsquo;m in College Station now after a candle light service at church. (My mom is a UU minister) The service was full of carols and candles, but I didn&amp;rsquo;t feel much like participating; my nose was all snuffly and stuff. It&amp;rsquo;s not the same here without Fred. Also conspicuously missing is Karina, me an&amp;rsquo; Fred&amp;rsquo;s step sister, although Alicia is here (our other step-sis), but she is not a boistrous as Karina.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1991/12/25/christmas/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 1991 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1991/12/25/christmas/</guid>
      <description>12:05AM Christmas Day, 1991
(transcribed from Book Two of my diary)
The zoo was cool. We went to every exhibit, except that I noticed we did not see girraffes. The reptiles were cool. This will all be written haphazardly, since I want to write about what just happened. At the zoo, we saw a huge ass green moray. It was in a tank with a nurse shark and a lemon shark.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>