<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>fortaleza on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/fortaleza/</link>
    <description>Recent content in fortaleza on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2017 09:02:15 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/fortaleza/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>in airport with NO WIFI OMG</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/24/in-airport-with-no-wifi-omg/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2017 09:02:15 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/24/in-airport-with-no-wifi-omg/</guid>
      <description>09:02 Sunday 24 December 2017 -03 Hafta give up phone number or Facebook credentials in order to get (free) wifi in Fortaleza airport, so I have no wifi now. Kinda stucks because I want to send an email to Fred and reply to Kai&amp;rsquo;s email to me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>leaving Fortaleza soon</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/24/leaving-fortaleza-soon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2017 06:17:54 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/24/leaving-fortaleza-soon/</guid>
      <description>06:17 Sunday 24 December 2017 -03 Leaving Fortaleza today (and my glasses, unless I happen to find them on last scan of the beach)
06:58 Sunday 24 December 2017 -03 Didn&amp;rsquo;t find my glasses during a quick walk along the beach near where I lost them. We did find breakfast buffet quite lovely, and I can make do with Lin&amp;rsquo;s glasses.
Headed to the airport now to fly to Presidente Prudente via Sao Paulo (to see our friends R&amp;amp;D).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ate churascos</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/23/ate-churascos/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2017 14:19:30 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/23/ate-churascos/</guid>
      <description>14:19 Saturday 23 December 2017 -03 Lin and I just walked along the beach from the restaurante de churrascos (sp) after pretty much gorging on all the offerings.
I saw some really neat rivulets on the beach (but forgot to take a picture) where water seems to just spring from the beach. I guess that is exactly what&amp;rsquo;s happening; water within the sand works its way out and then comes down to the ocean.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>beach day</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/21/beach-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2017 22:12:06 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/21/beach-day/</guid>
      <description>(transcribed 22:12 Monday 01 January 2018 JST)
evening 21 December 2017 Great view of semi-fragile sand dunes, but not safe to climb ざんねん. Hot girls including one with braces. OMG why do so many adults have braces here?
Finished algorithm for the app (LeSwipe / ConSwi) to deal with linking swipes to shapes while chilling in a self made hole in the beach.
(pictures coming soon?)
Quite interesting to see the waves coming in over the very-flat beach, so it came up significantly farther and farther with each passing unit of time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Relaxing on the beach in Fortaleza</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/20/relaxing-on-the-beach-in-fortaleza/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2017 14:46:04 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/20/relaxing-on-the-beach-in-fortaleza/</guid>
      <description>14:46 Wednesday 20 December 2017 -03 Relaxing on the beach, we got some delicious drinks: manga con leche (sp) for me and acerola for Lin. Mine was sweeet and muito deliciouso (sp).
A man came by with a young boy in his arms, and we ended up giving him R10 $3. Then other guys selling shirts, cashews, art, and maybe one more before we ended up just leaving instead of saying no no no no.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>