<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>gymnastics on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/gymnastics/</link>
    <description>Recent content in gymnastics on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Nov 1998 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/gymnastics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>gymnastics beanie babies</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/11/03/gymnastics-beanie-babies/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Nov 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/11/03/gymnastics-beanie-babies/</guid>
      <description>Bouncing Beanie Babies
Tuesday 3 November 1998
Last week I didn&#39;t go to gymnastics because I hurt my ankle jumping over Maggie&#39;s couch. I did go this week, but my ankle wasn&#39;t happy enough to do round off back handsprings on the floor. Today my heart just wasn&#39;t into tumbling. I did several russians (russian style front flips) and 1 back hand spring. However, on the trampoline, I did a lot of fun stuff!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>gymnastics crunch</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/10/21/gymnastics-crunch/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/10/21/gymnastics-crunch/</guid>
      <description>Gymnastics
Wednesday 21 October 1998
Yesterday was big fun at gymnastics. I&#39;ve stopped practicing my round off back flips, and toned them down to round off back handsprings. Why? So I can do round off back handspring back flip, of course! I&#39;ve got to lower the angle/height/energy etc to get the back flip down to a back handspring. I&#39;ve also got to overcome my fear of bonking my head on back handsprings!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>gymnastics closer layout</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/07/14/gymnastics-closer-layout/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jul 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/07/14/gymnastics-closer-layout/</guid>
      <description>Almost did layouts!
14 July 1998
Today after seeing Armageddon, but before gymnastics, I stopped by Smoothie King to get a smoothie. I told the guy they should have a smoothie flavor called &#34;groovy juice.&#34; &#34;Groovy juice, eh?&#34; &#34;Yeah.. let me tell you what&#39;s in it.&#34; I looked up at the ingredients list. &#34;Um, wheat germ, bananas, soy protein, turbinado and honey.&#34; &#34;That&#39;s it?&#34; &#34;Yeah. This time.&#34; &#34;do you want any fruit juices?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>almost arabians</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/05/05/almost-arabians/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 May 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/05/05/almost-arabians/</guid>
      <description>Journal
5 May 1998
Tonight in gymnastics I did some pretty cool stuff. I did round off back flips but did not get them as layouts very well at all. We were on a different floor which seemed softer than the other. I don&#39;t know if that really made a difference or not. But I did do a few russian front flips. &#34;Russian&#34; in that case is the style of motion used to power the flip.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>gymnastics almost layout</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/04/12/gymnastics-almost-layout/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Apr 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/04/12/gymnastics-almost-layout/</guid>
      <description>Layouts! almost
21 April 1998
 Today in gymnastics after I did some stretching, but before we really got started, I did two standing back flips onto a big fat mat. Each time, I almost got all the way over. Cool. I haven&#39;t done those in years!  During our tumbling passes I was doing my round off back flips when BB said, &#34;try doing layouts.&#34;  I was all, &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>gymnastics bluh</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/03/31/gymnastics-bluh/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/03/31/gymnastics-bluh/</guid>
      <description>Gymnastics and maybe a new new gym?
Tuesday 31 March 1998
 Today in gymnastics, I did back handsprings again, and my standing ones were better than those I did last week! (Plus I didn&#39;t rip my abs.)  I did some round off back handsprings, and they got better and better as I kept practicing and then they got crappy. My arms forgot to land or they were all spread out or whatever.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>gymnastics back handsprings</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/03/24/gymnastics-back-handsprings/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/03/24/gymnastics-back-handsprings/</guid>
      <description>More Gymnastics
Tuesday 24 March 1998
 Today I got to attend gymnastics again after the gym was closed for 2 weeks. During those two weeks the moved to a larger facility and I love it! The new place is way bigger and has two floors, two runway trampolines, two big trampolines, a vault, 1 high bar, 3 uneven bars, several low bars, and plenty of room for more stuff that hasn&#39;t been installed yet!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gymnastics!</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/02/19/gymnastics/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/02/19/gymnastics/</guid>
      <description>Journal
19 Feb
On Tuesday, I went to gymnastics class for the first time in probably 3.5 to 4 years ??!!!!  Wow how wonderful it was to be back on that big bouncy blue carpet!
 We started with some walking handstands and then cartwheels then roundoffs then after a bit I was doing roundoff back flips!! Big big tall high back flips and I felt glorious and joyful! After the hour of class, I went to the runway trampoline and did some front flips and even was able to get a proper front layout flip once.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Long Entry</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1993/12/03/long-entry/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 1993 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1993/12/03/long-entry/</guid>
      <description>(transcribed from Book Six 1:54pm JST Sunday 28 June 2009 (day 14340))
7:50PM Friday 3 December 1993 Day (Page44)
I have decided to not keep track of exactly what day I&#39;m on each day. I&#39;ll keep this pointer back to page 44 that will tell me the last recorded day count so I can recalculate it. The only reason for this is that maybe the days will go by faster, not that they are going slowly now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>finals gymnastics</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1987/05/19/finals-gymnastics/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 May 1987 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1987/05/19/finals-gymnastics/</guid>
      <description>(transcribed 8:26am CST Friday 31 January 2003)
May 19 1987 Tuesday
Mrs. Sherman liked the movie. I finished my Algebra II final except for the parabola. Rob and Neil stayed up all night working. Literally. They slept all day until 6th period (Algebra) when they came to school. Tomorrow I have a meeting to go to for rifles. We will get measured for our outfits. I talked to Heather Lakatos some in Algebra today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Candie gymnastics</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1987/05/05/candie-gymnastics/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 May 1987 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1987/05/05/candie-gymnastics/</guid>
      <description>(transcribed 12:05am CST Friday 31 January 2003)
May 5
Candie Downy knows the dude who recorded &#34;I be Elliot&#34; for 93Q. I may have a chance to meet the dude. He is totally cool and a real good friend from what I have heard from Candie. I&#39;m thinking about quitting gymnastics. I don&#39;t have the interest like I used to. Bryan said if I quit, he would too. I wonder how bad that would be for Jim?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>