<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>soml on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/soml/</link>
    <description>Recent content in soml on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2019 11:11:44 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/soml/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>State of My Life Address</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/09/04/state-of-my-life-address/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2019 11:11:44 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/09/04/state-of-my-life-address/</guid>
      <description>11:11 Wednesday 04 September 2019 JST  Yesterday I walked from Shinjuku to Hiroo, from the men&amp;rsquo;s group new meeting location to our old one. Last night we met for the last time at Takeshi&amp;rsquo;s office, and next week we will be in Shinjuku, at a place I have not yet seen. I have booked it for all of September and October, and trust we can get it for longer if we like it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>State of My Life Address</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/08/08/state-of-my-life-address/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2019 17:22:04 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/08/08/state-of-my-life-address/</guid>
      <description>17:22 Thursday 08 August 2019 JST  My old thunderrabbit router conked out so now we are using a new one with three antennas and mutiple channels and all that good stuff. The conking coincided with new printer disallowing login so I reset the networking and therefore lost the few scan-to-ssh profiles I had set up. I have half of them restored and a few new ones planned. This allows me to scan A4 pages and upload to my b.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Life in a Post as of July 2019</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/07/22/life-in-a-post-as-of-july-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2019 10:03:25 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/07/22/life-in-a-post-as-of-july-2019/</guid>
      <description>I wrote this to Dean Ramsden
10:03 Monday 22 July 2019 JST  In the meantime, maybe write up your personal history and your goals for the work you want done, and I’ll study it ahead of time, so we can jump right in.
 When I was a child, my dad showed me how to use coat hangers as divining sticks to find water. At the time, I thought it was strange.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>State of My Life Address</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/06/01/state-of-my-life-address/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2019 20:29:45 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/06/01/state-of-my-life-address/</guid>
      <description>20:29 Saturday 01 June 2019 JST  I met Yuri Logo today to talk about making a logo for my brand. She was recommended by Rin so I was like yay! She asked lots of questions and said she had good ideas for it. I could see in her smile the excitement and I felt good about that. I will be working with Rin in a life coaching capacity. I look forward to an accountability partner and learning some new facilitation techniques.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>lately</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/04/26/lately/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 14:01:38 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/04/26/lately/</guid>
      <description>14:01 Friday 26 April 2019 JST  Lately I&amp;rsquo;ve been saying &amp;ldquo;see you next era&amp;rdquo; in Japanese just do draw attention to the fact that the era is going to change on May 1st.  We&amp;rsquo;ve got a big pack of days off coming this Golden Week: 10! Most of my students are glad, but there are some people who are like wtf because schools and day care will be closed, but the parents (in service sector jobs) have to work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>State of My Life Address</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/03/03/state-of-my-life-address/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2019 21:46:31 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/03/03/state-of-my-life-address/</guid>
      <description>21:46 Sunday 03 March 2019 JST  I will be traveling to the US for 22 days starting March 13th. Not packed yet, but have it planned for next week. I have just sent a list of workshops to Tokyo Men&amp;rsquo;s Circle
Men, my stretch was to find workshops that we can do in Tokyo.
I have led #1 and #3 below. As a group, we did #2 in August 2018 for ourselves, and then again in November 2018 for new men.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>State of My Life Address</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/02/06/state-of-my-life-address/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2019 07:44:19 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/02/06/state-of-my-life-address/</guid>
      <description>07:44 Wednesday 06 February 2019 JST  Lin and I still have our cat Jennie, still keep her in at night, still live in Asao-ku near the bottom of a hill. I&amp;rsquo;m still working on Marble Track 3, trying to do at least 2 hours of livestream per week. I have been working on AB, getting tests added to cover the important parts of the codebase. I do not have a lot covered, but 10 tests is an order of magnitude more than 0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>state of my life address</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/01/21/state-of-my-life-address/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jan 2019 21:19:53 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/01/21/state-of-my-life-address/</guid>
      <description>21:19 Monday 21 January 2019 JST Lots of changes since just three weeks ago.
 I created a Gofundme with a target of $46,000 to kick off Mankind Project Japan. $525 so far! I created a 2.5 minute demo as a TEDx audition vid. Safely expressing emotions makes life better. Pinky has placed most of the decorative blocks along the Decorative Walls after the Lowest Small-Medium Splitter, although I have not taken a new picture that shows all of them so far.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>State of my life address</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/01/05/state-of-my-life-address/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jan 2019 20:27:25 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/01/05/state-of-my-life-address/</guid>
      <description>20:27 Saturday 05 January 2019 JST  I have not been writing in my journal a lot recently.. But I have been writing a lot on https://www.marbletrack3.com/ Been working a lot for AB, JB, TY, IST For AB, I have been going through https://mlaphp.com. Middle of step 5 now, trying to untangle class dependencies. Been working on game app with Tariq and recently Dipendra Very likely to go to US in late March and April for men&amp;rsquo;s group weekends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>state of my life address</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/12/07/state-of-my-life-address/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 22:12:16 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/12/07/state-of-my-life-address/</guid>
      <description>22:12 Friday 07 December 2018 JST  Marble Track 3 has its own domain, https://www.marbletrack3.com/ hosted as a static site on Netlify ConSwi is open source under GNU copyleft. Several outstanding issues, the biggest of which are #25 disallow dragged pieces to go through other pieces and #23 Make piece keep up with mouse when dragging I created a Patreon page for MT3 and have my first patron, Jimmy! I recently got the fans and battery replaced on my MacBook, but it still conks out when the battery is at 65%.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vision</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/09/06/vision/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Sep 2018 06:35:43 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/09/06/vision/</guid>
      <description>06:35 Thursday 06 September 2018 JST A man has two lives. The second one begins when he realized he only has one life.
My second life has begun. I am feeling the fire in my gut, mixed with the fear of rejection and failure. But as I have learned through experience, if I follow my fear I will be headed in the right direction in life.
For me these fears result in me dying alone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>state of my life address</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/09/03/state-of-my-life-address/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Sep 2018 06:12:06 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/09/03/state-of-my-life-address/</guid>
      <description>I have just removed the ## 06:12 Monday 03 September 2018 JST date from the top of this journal. Marking them in h2 tags makes them a bit too big for this theme. I hate to modify my source code to fit a theme, but that happened.
 I recently got the website for Mable Track 3 (nearly) up to date. It now has all the entries that had been in my journal at https://new.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>State of My Life Address</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/08/02/state-of-my-life-address/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Aug 2018 09:42:21 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/08/02/state-of-my-life-address/</guid>
      <description>09:42 Thursday 02 August 2018 JST  It&amp;rsquo;s hotter in Tokyo this summer than summers in my memory. It&amp;rsquo;s been getting up to 34 - 35 degrees Celcius as the high, with some hot spots in the 40s I bought https://www.marbletrack3.com/ and have got a reasonable start on how to display each livestream as an episode. I started making a page for each character, calling them workers, and even got some translation support from Tomoko at Showspace in SCC.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>State of My Life Address</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/07/05/state-of-my-life-address/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2018 00:13:46 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/07/05/state-of-my-life-address/</guid>
      <description>00:13 Thursday 05 July 2018 JST  Dreamhost has decided to stop supporting catch-all emails so I am looking for a new provider. The encrypted versions cannot search nor test for spam very well so I may not be happy with any of those I am too tired to write this right now so I should go to bed. For AB, I have started adding arc_cycles, which should save them a decent amount of time when creating historical reports.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>State of My Life Address</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/06/02/state-of-my-life-address/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jun 2018 00:55:37 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/06/02/state-of-my-life-address/</guid>
      <description>00:55 Saturday 02 June 2018 JST  I just got home from Apocrypha #15  09:13 Saturday 02 June 2018 JST  Was up too late last night and did not do much good for myself (porn), but I on the productive side I read some of MJG&amp;rsquo;s new book The Rot&amp;rsquo;s War Ignifer Cycle Book 2 co-gender circle seems to have come back to meeting after a significant dip in attendance over winter holidays men&amp;rsquo;s circle has had pretty solid attendance, often with 7 men.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>State of My Life Address</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/05/01/state-of-my-life-address/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2018 15:50:57 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/05/01/state-of-my-life-address/</guid>
      <description>15:50 Tuesday 01 May 2018 JST  I sent my invoice to Nate on time this month. He&amp;rsquo;s trying to cut costs by moving our Redmine server to a new server Nate: &amp;ldquo;This is an internal work and I don’t feel it’s fair for me to pay the cost to figure out how to move to amazon don’t U thjnk?&amp;rdquo; I am paid hourly, not a salary. Tariq and I have been working on ConSwi.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>State of My Life Address</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/01/state-of-my-life-address/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Apr 2018 15:25:24 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/01/state-of-my-life-address/</guid>
      <description>15:25 Sunday 01 April 2018 JST  I started a Meetup group ManKind Project Tokyo which will soon be linked to the Mankind Project Pro Meetup account. Men&amp;rsquo;s group meetings are now every Tuesday (since March). We had been meeting twice a month since about August 2015. The group has slowly grown and now twice a month is not enough for every man to do his work. SOGO is still going, although the leadership is changing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>最近の僕の世界</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/10/%E6%9C%80%E8%BF%91%E3%81%AE%E5%83%95%E3%81%AE%E4%B8%96%E7%95%8C/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2018 21:31:41 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/10/%E6%9C%80%E8%BF%91%E3%81%AE%E5%83%95%E3%81%AE%E4%B8%96%E7%95%8C/</guid>
      <description>21:31 Wednesday 10 January 2018 JST I can&amp;rsquo;t remember what Mel suggested about this title besides use the correct kanji for 僕
I just finished work and cannot quite bear to think in Japanese.
仕事がおわったばっかりだからまだ日本語であまり書きたくない。
電車乗りますので寝ちゃうかも知れない。
I am on the train so I will probably fall asleep.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>saikin (recently)</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/03/saikin-recently/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2017 15:06:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/03/saikin-recently/</guid>
      <description>15:06 Sunday 03 December 2017 JST There are likely myriad errors in the Japanese below! 俺の最近の世界  これは初めの「俺の最近の世界」と言う日記の文書です。 パソコンで書けますけど、今度読めますか？ 今日十時間ぐらい仕事できました。 メル先生から優しいメールをもらいました。 最近じゃないけど、毎日裸足で歩きます。 さっき、あんの人は私の裸足にさせて、微笑んだ。私「裸足」言うって、 彼は「なぜ」言うった。「気持ちから」言うった。彼がまた微笑んだ。 それはフォンで、只今電車に座りながら、書きます。 新宿まで乗るけどローマンスカーは２０分しかかからない。 日本語を喋りたいけど、「マットリクス」と言う映画見たい勉強しないすむがいいと思う。 まだ毎年新しものを勉強しますかな。 メーロを書く年あるし これは私のメーロのサイートです。 https://www.amazeaweek.net/ たくさんビットコインの記事を読んだし ３５分後、英語のレッスンが始まります。その前に２５版までを終わらせちゃう。 今日もっと寒かったけど裸足で歩きました。 妻にごぼうもらった。美味しいです。 食べたいけどもう歯を磨きました。 明日またMT3の作る事を続きたいです。 MT3のサイトは https://mt3.robnugen.com です。 友達の　ジェニファーから取って、うちの猫をジェニーと名付けた。 今日、友達の古いフィットビットをもらいました。 今チャージ中です。 部屋を素地しました時リップ５本を見つけた。 うちの猫ジェニーには友達のためジェニーって呼ぶ 今週末は忙しかったですけど仕事のやつできました。 よくできました！  English versions of the sentences above, just in case they are needed.
 This is the first time I have written an SOML in Japanese.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>State of My Life Address</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/03/state-of-my-life-address/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2017 10:02:44 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/03/state-of-my-life-address/</guid>
      <description>10:02 Sunday 03 December 2017 JST  I am training to work at Ty&amp;rsquo;s (headed there now) I have been transferring the CB backend to SB, where it will be streamlined / focused on artists and their events instead of artists and their products. It has been over a year since I first considered giving up this laptop for one on which I can run Ubuntu. The only thing I don&amp;rsquo;t like about this laptop now is the lack of battery.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>recently</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/11/28/recently/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2017 13:43:23 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/11/28/recently/</guid>
      <description>13:43 Tuesday 28 November 2017 JST Recently,
 An elderly man fell as he was getting off the bus with an elderly woman. Everyone on the bus exclaimed, but the bus driver took off before anyone moved. I nearly completed the M Splitter on Marble Track 3. I tried getting Netlify CMS working, but still have a few bits missing, starting with authentication. I failed an test at TY. There will be other chances, but I felt sad because I had thought I would do better.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>State of My Life Address</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/09/04/state-of-my-life-address/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2017 05:37:18 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/09/04/state-of-my-life-address/</guid>
      <description>05:37 Monday 04 September 2017 JST  As of last night, Lin and I plan to go to Peru, likely to The Way Inn, in 2018. I am up early to head to work (teach) at IL. I will soon have another lesson starting on Mondays, kinda within walking distance (1.5 hour walk) I have to leave for work in 5 minutes, and am debating taking my computer to work on SoML.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>recently (soml)</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/08/18/recently-soml/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2017 08:36:05 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/08/18/recently-soml/</guid>
      <description>08:36 Friday 18 August 2017 JST  Ma is in town! We are going to Nagano today Still don&amp;rsquo;t feel completely resolved regarding Renee and Gunma  20:43 Saturday 19 August 2017 JST  Lin, Ma, and I just got home from Nagano it&amp;rsquo;s raining harder than it does during the misnamed/mistimed &amp;ldquo;rainy season&amp;rdquo; of the past couple of years. I recently created https://tokyo.mypowercircle.org/ to be the MKP website for Tokyo / Japan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>State of My Life Address</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/07/31/state-of-my-life-address/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2017 20:50:14 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/07/31/state-of-my-life-address/</guid>
      <description>20:50 Monday 31 July 2017 JST  Today was the first day to teach at a restaurant in Hiroo. 10 students, most of whom are beginners, but all were able to get through some language, including, but not punctuated as, &amp;ldquo;how many in your party please follow me here you are here is the menu what would you like to drink please let me know when you are ready to order&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;this is sirloin sukiyaki may I help you prepare it we recommend rare but how would you like it cooked this is our original sauce dip the sirloin in egg wrap it around rice and enjoy&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>State of My Life Address</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/06/18/state-of-my-life-address/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2017 09:32:05 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/06/18/state-of-my-life-address/</guid>
      <description>09:32 Sunday 18 June 2017 JST  I completed 40 frames of animation yesterday with new camera and trial version of DragonFrame. I think I will buy a license for it. One big question at this point is how to handle N*10^6 images in the final project. I am currently headed to SOGO (Suns Out Guns Out) an exercise group I joined late last year, like in September I guess.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>State of My Life Address</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/06/05/state-of-my-life-address/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2017 18:03:55 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/06/05/state-of-my-life-address/</guid>
      <description>18:03 Monday 05 June 2017 JST  I met Caroline, who seems to be a soul I&amp;rsquo;ve met in previous lifetime(s) Two men might join Tokyo men&amp;rsquo;s circle, which would put us up to 5 (cause it seems 2&amp;frasl;3 men have stopped coming) A woman is interested in joining Tokyo co-gender circle. That will put us up to 7 if all 6 people come next time. Tokyo Men&amp;rsquo;s Circle meetings are on 1st and 3rd Tuesdays each month.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>State of My Life Address</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/04/29/state-of-my-life-address/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2017 22:39:35 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/04/29/state-of-my-life-address/</guid>
      <description>22:39 Saturday 29 April 2017 JST  I wonder why I&amp;rsquo;m writing an SOML now before the end of the month. Usually they are on the first, or recently, late, or very late. Lin and I are watching Alien Domicile, and I cannot say I am really expecting much. For time considerations, I abandoned upgrading to Ubuntu 16. Updating all my projects to use PHP 7 and figure out Ansible was too much.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>State of My Life Address</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/04/01/state-of-my-life-address/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2017 09:17:23 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/04/01/state-of-my-life-address/</guid>
      <description>09:17 Saturday 01 April 2017 JST  Lin and I are on our way to meet Tariq who will tell us what questions to ask of the business owner who offered to sell Lin her business for １０００万円 I got a surprise phone call the other day: &amp;ldquo;Hey Rob can I talk to Lin?&amp;rdquo; and offered the idea of selling to Lin. My first reaction is no way because I have no biz skizzles, no interest, and am too busy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mornin&#39;</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/03/16/mornin/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2017 07:35:33 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/03/16/mornin/</guid>
      <description>07:35 Thursday 16 March 2017 JST  The US shifted their clocks forward, so my online I-group now meets at 9:30am Tokyo time. That means I do not have enough time to head home before the meeting, and that means I need to find Wifi. I&amp;rsquo;ve been using Wired Cafe in Lazona, and I will probably resume. It also means I have my computer with me for this morning lesson to which students are often late.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>State of My Life Address</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/02/02/state-of-my-life-address/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2017 09:28:49 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/02/02/state-of-my-life-address/</guid>
      <description>09:28 Thursday 02 February 2017 JST  I&amp;rsquo;ve staffed 3 NWTAs for Mankind Project. Most recent two were in Perth, in October 2016 and October 2015. on 31 January, I presented Tokyo&amp;rsquo;s first Head Heart and Soul presentation, as suggested by John Gaughan in Perth last year. 14 people in attendance and great supportive response There are 6 men in the Toyo I-group, including 3 men who have not yet attended NWTA.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>recently</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/09/20/recently/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2016 22:01:30 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/09/20/recently/</guid>
      <description>22:01 Tuesday 20 September 2016 JST Great fun at Suns Out Guns Out on Sunday. It was a bit rainy, but I&amp;rsquo;m waterpoof so it was just fine. We worked out for 90 minutes then had lunch then played ultimate for a while. Great great great! I brought my new purple disc and it got its first scuffs on Sunday.
The next day boom I felt sick. I thought I was just sore from workout but I had a bit of a fever.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>State of My Life Address</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/08/19/state-of-my-life-address/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2016 19:00:12 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/08/19/state-of-my-life-address/</guid>
      <description>19:00 Friday 19 August 2016 JST  been a while since I&amp;rsquo;ve done a state of my life address Lin and I have been married for 5 years We live in Higashi Yurigaoka, and regularly use Shin Yurigaoka station We just had a party the other day for our house warming. We&amp;rsquo;ve lived in the house since June 2nd of this year. For Obon we went to Umi-no-koen on Seaside Line.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>stuffs</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/05/25/stuffs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2016 14:10:57 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/05/25/stuffs/</guid>
      <description>14:10 Wednesday 25 May 2016 JST We are moving soon! Buying a new house!
itshappening.gif</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mayが始めた / State of My Life Address</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/05/01/may%E3%81%8C%E5%A7%8B%E3%82%81%E3%81%9F-/-state-of-my-life-address/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2016 08:45:01 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/05/01/may%E3%81%8C%E5%A7%8B%E3%82%81%E3%81%9F-/-state-of-my-life-address/</guid>
      <description>08:45 Sunday 01 May 2016 JST  I&amp;rsquo;ve not been journaling regulary. I&amp;rsquo;ve been studying Japanese I&amp;rsquo;ve been studying TESOL I&amp;rsquo;ve been studying presentation skills I&amp;rsquo;ve got a long way to go in all three I had been studying AWS as in Amazon Web Services, but I&amp;rsquo;ve let that slide recently as no hard deadline I&amp;rsquo;m teach lessons to SS and fairly enjoying it, though it takes a lot of prep time to do it well I&amp;rsquo;m curious about chatbots, robots, arduino, drones, &amp;hellip; any of which could suck up all time and resources Lin and I are moving soon!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>State of My Life Address</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/02/07/state-of-my-life-address/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Feb 2016 21:14:50 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/02/07/state-of-my-life-address/</guid>
      <description>21:14 Sunday 07 February 2016 JST  I gave Lin her first 1 hour massage from me. She&amp;rsquo;s due for 15 this year, according to the massage coupon I gave her. She thinks I should start doing massages for real, and I enjoyed it enough to consider the same thing. We applied to buy our new house in 新百合ケ丘! I&amp;rsquo;m enjoying doing lessons on https://acloud.guru/ I still have my black iPhone 4S, though I will &amp;ldquo;soon&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;upgrade&amp;rdquo; to Lin&amp;rsquo;s 5S.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>State of my Life Address</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/11/06/state-of-my-life-address/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2015 18:59:43 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/11/06/state-of-my-life-address/</guid>
      <description>18:59 Friday 06 November 2015 JST  As I write this, I&amp;rsquo;m going the long way home around the Yamanote Line; I just sat down at Shinjuku station, and I plan to switch to the Keihin Tohoku Line in Ueno or somewhere convenient.
 Have had a few tickets stacking up for AB and CB websites, but on 1 November, I released version 2.0.0 of both the frontend and backend of the AB website.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>state of my life address</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/09/08/state-of-my-life-address/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2015 19:01:43 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/09/08/state-of-my-life-address/</guid>
      <description>19:01 Tuesday 08 September 2015 JST  Maybe the biggest overall thing, which I hope will become a big thing in the future: In October, I&amp;rsquo;m going to staff a NWTA in Perth, with other men from https://mkp.org I have my plane tickets and all other costs are covered cause I&amp;rsquo;m coming from overseas. I just bought a soft plastic stackable brick toy set for Lin&amp;rsquo;s clients&amp;rsquo; son&amp;rsquo;s enjoyment. PolyM, Art.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>soml of sorts</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/06/03/soml-of-sorts/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2015 12:26:03 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/06/03/soml-of-sorts/</guid>
      <description>12:26 Wednesday 03 June 2015 JST State of my life address  I recently received two Dell laptops. One had Windows 7 on it, so I&amp;rsquo;ve left that. The other had no hard drive, so I bought a new 700GB drive and put Debian on it. It didn&amp;rsquo;t have wifi, so I bought a USB nano wifi dongle. Still couldn&amp;rsquo;t wifi, so I installed Debian again to see if it would pick up the wifi automatically.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>state of my life address</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/05/03/state-of-my-life-address/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 May 2015 13:40:49 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/05/03/state-of-my-life-address/</guid>
      <description>13:40 Sunday 03 May 2015 JST  Golden week is this week. That means lots of time off. Lin was involved in an accident a couple weeks ago. She&amp;rsquo;s shrugged it off with flying colors save for the bruise on her leg. She&amp;rsquo;s been workin&amp;rsquo; lots recently. I&amp;rsquo;ve just agreed to work each Tuesday with Sho on projects he&amp;rsquo;s got going on Might do some work for R at A in E, but not sure yet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>State of My Life Address</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/04/08/state-of-my-life-address/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2015 15:34:20 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/04/08/state-of-my-life-address/</guid>
      <description>15:34 Wednesday 08 April 2015 JST Oops we&amp;rsquo;re arriving in Yokohama soon so not much time to write.
 Ted ran away; he has been gone 2 days. I&amp;rsquo;ve been working on body and soul website with Sho I&amp;rsquo;ve been doing AB website for past couple years but not a lot of work now. I&amp;rsquo;ve been taking Japanese lessons at 80s Cafe in Akihabara, up to 3 times per week (for about 2 weeks now).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>State of my life address</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/02/04/state-of-my-life-address/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2015 16:07:37 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/02/04/state-of-my-life-address/</guid>
      <description>16:32 Wednesday 04 February 2015 JST  TL;DR: I&amp;rsquo;m really happy with my situation right now.
 I&amp;rsquo;m working for a few different people/companies, going to different places each day. Mostly I&amp;rsquo;m teaching English, but also doing website work for AB and probably do some more website work for a different project, &amp;ldquo;coming soon&amp;rdquo;
 On new moon weekends, I&amp;rsquo;ve been attending Tokyo ET Contact meetups, organized by Mark, and on some other weekends, I&amp;rsquo;ve been attending Tokyo Reiki Circle meetups.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>State of my life address</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/12/10/state-of-my-life-address/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/12/10/state-of-my-life-address/</guid>
      <description>##16:00 Wednesday 10 December 2014 JST##
 TLDR: I&amp;rsquo;ve been a lazy bum recently. And I love it.
 Maybe the coolest thing recently: Mutsumi introduced me to Funatsu-san, who liked my art and asked if she can put some in a show in January!
 I&amp;rsquo;ve been teaching a few lessons per week with a language school, but other than that, doing a lot of Minecraft, and drawing a few mazes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>State of My Life Address</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/10/28/state-of-my-life-address/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/10/28/state-of-my-life-address/</guid>
      <description>##22:22 Tuesday 28 October 2014##
The very best thing about not using Wordpress or Hoken: I can repeat filenames and not have the URLs get mangled.
#State of My Life Address#
 I ain&amp;rsquo;t journaled consistently for a long time.
 I hope to become more consistent for years to come.
 THis SOML might get cut short, though; Lin is about to arrive in 8 minutes.
 Lin and I are married, living in Kawasaki, Japan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>State of My Life Address</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2011/04/19/state-of-my-life-address/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2011 10:18:46 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2011/04/19/state-of-my-life-address/</guid>
      <description>Monday 2 May 2011 (copied from email 23:53 Wednesday 28 June 2017 JST)
Tazura is a beautiful weimereiner, but I think weimereiners are beautiful by definition.
I don&amp;rsquo;t yet know how to organize our android app.
I finished my first Roy G Biv hex maze today. Just need to scan it.
Tomorrow I&amp;rsquo;ll attend Kevin&amp;rsquo;s advanced shamanism course, day 1 of 4 of advanced practice. I guess I should practice on my own as well as attend his classes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>status</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2001/09/30/status/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Sep 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2001/09/30/status/</guid>
      <description>30 September 2001
 Wende and I are separating. We are both sad, and continuing to communicate and stuff as we split up. You may know that I have never lived alone (and not been seriously dating someone) since I got out of high school. I&#39;m choosing to live alone and be flat single and not available for relationship for a while. (like a year at very minimum) We intend to not sell the house right now; one of us will live in it and the other will be in an apartment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>stateOfMyLife</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2001/02/11/stateofmylife/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2001/02/11/stateofmylife/</guid>
      <description>9:56pm Sunday 11 February 2001
State of My Life Address  Wende and I are leaving for Australia tomorrow! I&#39;ve had my passport since Costa Rica in November 1998. Wende just got her passport last Thursday. I got our ETA (Electronic Ticket Authorities (visas)) on Friday night.
 We&#39;ve started beeper duty at work. I just had it for a week and will give it to Dave tomorrow morning. It was my first duty at this work and it was quite easy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>soml</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/08/02/soml/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/08/02/soml/</guid>
      <description>17:22 Wednesday 2 August 2000
State of My Life Address  Erick Morrow has been killed. He was apparently drunk and playing chicken with a car (a friend (also drunk) was driving) one friend got out of the way of the car; Erick did not. He was a recently graduated YRUU youth. A lot of peeps in the YRUU community are emotionally upset about it. I&#39;m working on El Project - the coding is done; today we worked on getting the datasets all cleaned up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SOML</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/06/02/soml/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/06/02/soml/</guid>
      <description>12:noon Tuesday 30 May 2000
State of my life address

Wende and I are almost unpacked into our new house. I unpacked a couple of boxes yesterday. Maybe we are not as far along as I think, but the end seems to be in sight!
We are DSL connected at our house! My work is paying for it, which is way cool. I was able to get Wende&amp;rsquo;s computer connected, but have not yet gotten my linux box set up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>State of My Life Address</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/03/16/state-of-my-life-address/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/03/16/state-of-my-life-address/</guid>
      <description>16 March 2000
State of My Life
 Wende and I are engaged to be married! Planned date is Friday 21 June 2002. Ceremony will be Friday evening by a lake, then stay in cabins overnight, then play all day Saturday! Everyone we know will be invited! On more immediate time scale, we&#39;re in the process of purchasing a house! Our offer/contract has been accepted, and our loan broker is searching for a loan for us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>state-of-my-life</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1999/10/28/state-of-my-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 1999 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1999/10/28/state-of-my-life/</guid>
      <description>28 oct 1999
STATE OF MY LIFE

I have reviewed 48 CDs for KTRU, many of them this semester! I like being able to listen and shout in my mind, &amp;ldquo;I reviewed that!!&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Review&amp;rdquo; in this context means listen to the CD to see if it&amp;rsquo;s broadcastable by KTRU standards. We rate the songs on a 5 point scale basically and DJs know what&amp;rsquo;s good on the CD before they&amp;rsquo;ve ever heard it or even heard of it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>state-of-my-lif</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1999/09/14/state-of-my-lif/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 1999 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1999/09/14/state-of-my-lif/</guid>
      <description>17:39 Tuesday 14 September 1999
STATE OF MY LIFE

I love my new job! I&amp;rsquo;m network administrator for a small company called FSD Data Services. We have about 15 computers networked, about ten Windows NT 4.0, two Windows 95, and one unix (Free BSD). Unix box is the email server, one of the windows NT is our web server. I&amp;rsquo;m slowly crawling up the learning curve hill and loving getting paid to learn this stuff!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>state-of-my-life</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1999/07/07/state-of-my-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jul 1999 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1999/07/07/state-of-my-life/</guid>
      <description>7 July 1999
STATE OF MY LIFE &amp;ldquo;Feast or Famine&amp;rdquo;
This entry is ramblesome; read it only if you&amp;rsquo;re entirely interested.

I&amp;rsquo;ve heard many times that insanity is doing the same thing over and over and expecting a different result. Some parts of my life are insane in this manner; others are not.
I was working for a little at a company that shall remain nameless (have I already told this story?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>state-of-my-life</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1999/06/22/state-of-my-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 1999 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1999/06/22/state-of-my-life/</guid>
      <description>1:01pm Tuesday 22 June 1999
STATE OF MY LIFE

Right at this moment I am missing KTRU. I&amp;rsquo;m scheduled to be there, but I&amp;rsquo;m at work. Super duper special thanks to Aline for covering for me. Unfortunately, I won&amp;rsquo;t be able to KTRU (KTRU is a verb) next week either; I&amp;rsquo;ll be in Salt Lake City!
I got a job. I&amp;rsquo;m making $13/hour doing Y2K compliance type stuff. That amount looks pitiful, but I was making nothing otherwise, or not much.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>19-may-1999</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1999/05/19/19-may-1999/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 May 1999 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1999/05/19/19-may-1999/</guid>
      <description>Wednesday 19 May 1999
STATE OF MY LIFE

Jason and I are going to Australia in November. That&amp;rsquo;s why we&amp;rsquo;re working to save some dollars now. We&amp;rsquo;ll also take scuba lessons so we can dive while there.
This morning I was pondering the phases of my life since high school in terms of Big Focii Of My Life. Graduated high school in 1988. Spent 2 years at North Harris County College.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>state-of-my-life</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1999/01/07/state-of-my-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 1999 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1999/01/07/state-of-my-life/</guid>
      <description>07 January 1999
STATE OF MY LIFE

I recently came to the realization that my life feels too busy/complicated lately. With help from Wende, I pondered this in my diary and found that back in my college days, I was busy, but not quite as busy as now. Also, back then some of my busi-ness included good exercise (Ultimate and disc golf), good friends (hanging at the dorms) and good food (dorm food is more balanced than my current eating habits) Hmmmm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>soml 06-nov-1998</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/11/06/soml-06-nov-1998/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/11/06/soml-06-nov-1998/</guid>
      <description>State of My Life
6 November 1998
STATE OF MY LIFE  After some meditation, I have determined something. My want is not &#34;to be successful in my own business.&#34; I already knew I don&#39;t want a full time job. My want is to make some dollars and then have time to travel and play. So I decided to become a gigilo. Wait! no. no. just kiddin&#39;. So I&#39;m looking for some kind of part time consulting work - programming or HTML or whatever, and to that end I have called a couple of people and have put my want out to the universe, and now on my website.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>soml 30-oct-1998</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/10/30/soml-30-oct-1998/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Oct 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/10/30/soml-30-oct-1998/</guid>
      <description>State of My Life
30 October 1998
STATE OF MY LIFE  Today begins San Antonio Rally. From previous experience, I know if I don&#39;t write before the rally about stuff that happened before the rally, it probably won&#39;t be written This past week, Manda and I saw the movie ORGAZMO, the new Trey Parker film. There were 5 people in the theater, including us, and we had free passes to get in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>soml 22-sep-1998</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/09/22/soml-22-sep-1998/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/09/22/soml-22-sep-1998/</guid>
      <description>State of My Life
Tuesday 22 September 1998
 STATE OF MY LIFE   I have mostly recovered from losing my hard drive, and I am more careful to archive the documents I update regularly. However(!) my disply adapter is only running at 640x480 pixels and 16 colors! I&#39;ve tried everything I can think of and I can&#39;t get it to do more. Kinda hard to scan pics this way!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>soml 18-sep-1998</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/09/18/soml-18-sep-1998/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Sep 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/09/18/soml-18-sep-1998/</guid>
      <description>State of My Life
18 September 1998
STATE OF MY LIFE   It&#39;s currently 3:06am. Why am I up so late? I just uploaded two pages to my new domain www.MRLaboratories.com! This site is for my webpage design business! Spot, my cat, is curled up so very cutely in a small box beside me.. If I just had a camera! Speakin&#39; of cameras, I got a lotta pictures from when Houston flooded this past weekend!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>soml 17-aug-1998</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/08/17/soml-17-aug-1998/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/08/17/soml-17-aug-1998/</guid>
      <description>State of My Life
8:30am 17 August 1998
STATE OF MY LIFE  I am pissed right now at Windows 98 because my web browsers keep locking up and stuff.
I&#39;ve been feeling overall crappy in my life; I feel unproductive even though I&#39;m doing stuff all the time. I&#39;m doing youth work, organizing projects, encouraging participation, pulling staples, attending conferences and dinners... but my apartment is a wreck and sometimes I think &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>soml 25-jul-1998</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/07/25/soml-25-jul-1998/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jul 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/07/25/soml-25-jul-1998/</guid>
      <description>State of My Life Address
25 July 1998
State of My Life  I&#39;ll be leaving in a few hours for Oklahoma to be an advisor for a week at youth camp! Wheeee! I&#39;m still hacked about not being able to retrieve my email from flashnet. Windows 98 screwed up my mailstuff and it looking for a &#39;postoffice&#39; on my machine. I created one with the control panel but that didn&#39;t do the trick.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>soml 07-jul-1998</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/07/07/soml-07-jul-1998/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/07/07/soml-07-jul-1998/</guid>
      <description>State of My Life Address
7 July 1998
State of My Life 
Wow! so so so so so MUCH has happened! I quit my job. I mentioned that already. I&#39;m busier now that I quit my job than I was before! I got a flat tire on the way to the dentist. That was an interesting story which just completed today. I went to Rochester, New York for one week for a huge conference called General Assembly!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>soml 24-may-1998</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/05/24/soml-24-may-1998/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 May 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/05/24/soml-24-may-1998/</guid>
      <description>State of My Life Address
24 May 1998
State of My Life Address  I am for sure going to quit work at my JOB on 19 June.
I&#39;m super excited about activities planned for the youth group this summer and beyond!  First Sunday youth worship Third Wednesday youth dinner Last Sunday youth planning meeting  and we have scheduled a Social Action Lock-in for 13 June!  I have completed &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>soml 06-may-1998</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/05/06/soml-06-may-1998/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/05/06/soml-06-may-1998/</guid>
      <description>State of my life
6 May 1998
State of my Life   Wow- I haven&amp;rsquo;t written in a while. Lots of stuff has happened but I don&amp;rsquo;t think I&amp;rsquo;ll get caught up. I got a new computer: Pentium II 233 Mhz, two 2.5 gig hard drives, 64 Megs memory, 24X CD Rom, 17&amp;rdquo; monitor with 4 Megs on the card, sound card, etc. I&amp;rsquo;ve been messing with it a bit each day and will hopefully have a 56k modem working soon, and then I&amp;rsquo;ll get the Feel Good Net going again, which hasn&amp;rsquo;t gone out in 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>soml 15-apr-1998</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/04/15/soml-15-apr-1998/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/04/15/soml-15-apr-1998/</guid>
      <description>State of My Life
11:17 Wednesday 15 April 1998
 STATE OF MY LIFE    My brother Fred and I have been working a bit on some genealogical pages here on my website. They are not yet available for general consumption, but stay tuned.   Wende is going to move into another apartment on May 9. We have been hanging out lately and still are friends and all that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>soml 19-mar-1998</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/03/19/soml-19-mar-1998/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/03/19/soml-19-mar-1998/</guid>
      <description>State of My Life
19:44 Thursday 19 March 1998
 STATE OF MY LIFE    I normally don&#39;t do State of My Life Addresses so chronologically close together, but I am now.   At work I&#39;ve been working much longer hours than normal and I&#39;m still not getting my project done as fast as I want. I&#39;m working in C++ and I&#39;m stuck on a problem I&#39;m having with some objects written by another group.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>soml 13-mar-1998</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/03/13/soml-13-mar-1998/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/03/13/soml-13-mar-1998/</guid>
      <description>State of My Life
12:30am Friday 13 March 1998
 Some years ago I heard the President&#39;s State of the Union address and I thought it would be cool if I wrote State of My Life addresses in my diary.  They go something like this:  Friday 13 March 1998
STATE OF MY LIFE    I am flat tired of living with Wende but I&#39;m too fucking scared to tell her because I don&#39;t want to break her heart.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>State of my life address</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1993/12/05/state-of-my-life-address/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Dec 1993 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1993/12/05/state-of-my-life-address/</guid>
      <description>(transcribed from Book Six 4:42pm JST Sunday 28 June 2009 (day 14340))
4:20PM Sunday 5 December 1993 [Page 44]
State of my life address  Though my sign on my wall says &amp;quot;Stop Looking (for a girlfriend)&amp;quot; I still kinda am but not entirely.
Cathy has said no because I won&#39;t have sex. Diana is too religiously inclined for me. She said she&#39;s thought about becoming a nun so she could simply serve God.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>