<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>schedule on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/schedule/</link>
    <description>Recent content in schedule on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 17:46:31 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/schedule/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>got schedule mixed up</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/27/got-schedule-mixed-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 17:46:31 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/27/got-schedule-mixed-up/</guid>
      <description>17:46 Friday 27 April 2018 JST I forgot the monthly Integration Group Coordinator call is at 9am Japan time now that the time has sprung forward an hour. I was a few minutes late to the call, but all was good. Oh that reminds me, I gotta correct the time in my reminder messages for next month.
We talked about suicide prevention, and ways to raise awareness of this issue and how people can get support.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>dream scheduling conflict</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/23/dream-scheduling-conflict/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2017 04:49:53 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/23/dream-scheduling-conflict/</guid>
      <description>04:49 Saturday 23 December 2017 -03 I had a schedule conflict that I detected a few days out, but didn&#39;t try to rectify until the day of the conflict. Nate wanted to have me join a late night adventure sneaking into a dark house that only I knew the layout to find some prize close to midnight. I was more interested in joining Lin to meet Travis and Yumi for a roadtrip that started at 11pm, but planned to meet in nearly the same location, an empty field next to the building that Nate and I were going to explore in the dark.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>oops schedule</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/07/oops-schedule/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2017 18:15:23 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/07/oops-schedule/</guid>
      <description>14:30 Thursday 07 December 2017 JST (written 18:15 Thursday 07 December 2017 JST)
While on the phone with BoA credit card to close my account, I got a call from JB: &amp;ldquo;hey yeah why aren&amp;rsquo;t you at work?&amp;rdquo;
Stomach sank link oh damn are you kidding me?
Turns out they hadn&amp;rsquo;t sent me the schedule for December, but I certainly could have been more proactive to check. I have set a reminder for the 28th of each month to make sure I have the dates in my calendar for the subsequent month.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>almost</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1991/12/30/almost/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 1991 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1991/12/30/almost/</guid>
      <description>2:45AM Monday December 30th, 1991
(transcribed from Book Two of my diary)
I&#39;m working on my new sleep schedule. I have to be at work at 9AM. Tammy and I had great sex at about 11PM last night. I slept until 1:30AM, when I woke up &amp; took a shower. I&#39;m kinda groggy right now, but we&#39;ll see how it goes. I intend to sleep at 4AM until 6:30AM when Tammy wakes up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>schedule</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1991/12/29/schedule/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 1991 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1991/12/29/schedule/</guid>
      <description>Sunday, Dec 29, 1991 5:40PM
(transcribed from Book Two of my diary)
I was beaten soundly by Mr Bandecca 4 or 5 games in a row. I kinda felt bad, since he had commented about how he wanted a workout, not to just piss around.. He was very nice about it, and I believe sincere when he said he enjoyed playing. That&amp;rsquo;s cool.
Last night I got a call from Cheri, who said she was going out with some guy who&amp;rsquo;s 31, apparently a real charmer, he&amp;rsquo;s made comments about her nice blonde hair &amp;amp; &amp;ldquo;good proportions&amp;rdquo; and commented that he&amp;rsquo;d like to take pictures of her.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>