<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>mkp on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/mkp/</link>
    <description>Recent content in mkp on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 22:40:44 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/mkp/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Train home with Lukas</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/09/11/train-home-with-lukas/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 22:40:44 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/09/11/train-home-with-lukas/</guid>
      <description>Lukas recognized me on the way home!
Nambu line platform in Kawasaki and I kinda recognized his face but not his name until he Liked our MKP Tokyo page on FB.
Feeling blessed by the connection and really looking forward to catching up more!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tokyo men&#39;s group met in Shinjuku last night</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/09/10/tokyo-mens-group-met-in-shinjuku-last-night/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2019 18:53:52 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/09/10/tokyo-mens-group-met-in-shinjuku-last-night/</guid>
      <description>(written 18:53 Wednesday 11 September 2019 JST)
Tuesday night Tokyo Mankind Project men&amp;rsquo;s circle met in Shinjuku for the first time in our hourly-rented space.
The space worked well, so I have booked it for the next three months&amp;rsquo; worth of Tuesdays. It&amp;rsquo;s clean, quiet, has cool chairs and beautiful hardwood floor. Plus it&amp;rsquo;s only about 2 minutes from Shinjuku station, so come on out!
We have not sorted out how the group will pay for it exactly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>State of My Life Address</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/09/04/state-of-my-life-address/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2019 11:11:44 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/09/04/state-of-my-life-address/</guid>
      <description>11:11 Wednesday 04 September 2019 JST  Yesterday I walked from Shinjuku to Hiroo, from the men&amp;rsquo;s group new meeting location to our old one. Last night we met for the last time at Takeshi&amp;rsquo;s office, and next week we will be in Shinjuku, at a place I have not yet seen. I have booked it for all of September and October, and trust we can get it for longer if we like it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Great fun in Yoyogi with MKP Japan group</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/08/05/great-fun-in-yoyogi-with-mkp-japan-group/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2019 15:38:58 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/08/05/great-fun-in-yoyogi-with-mkp-japan-group/</guid>
      <description>15:38 Monday 05 August 2019 JST I was soooo tired after last night that I did not write about the great day we had in Yoyogi Park.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>let loose in my online men&#39;s circle</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/07/18/let-loose-in-my-online-mens-circle/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2019 13:11:01 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/07/18/let-loose-in-my-online-mens-circle/</guid>
      <description>13:11 Thursday 18 July 2019 JST I have been doing MKP stuff for a while. Today I expressed in my online group that I did not want to be there and I do not always want to be there. I am so thankful that I could just let loose with a barrage|littany of the stuff rolling through my mind and the men could be there just to hear me. It was stuff like</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>great fear and great meeting</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/06/07/great-fear-and-great-meeting/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2019 09:17:27 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/06/07/great-fear-and-great-meeting/</guid>
      <description> 09:17 Friday 07 June 2019 JST Had a great meeting this morning where I was able to express my fear and feelings of inadequacy about being a leader.
Next steps, I will:
 Ask men &amp;ldquo;who do you want to sit in circle with you?&amp;rdquo; send English version to Zumi write my experience online send Doodle regarding next meeting time contact 3 men to invite  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>men&#39;s group today</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/05/06/mens-group-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2019 18:11:18 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/05/06/mens-group-today/</guid>
      <description>08:40 Monday 06 May 2019 JST Right now I&amp;rsquo;m headed to Hiroo for two (2) workshops. One, for men already in the group, a Mission workshop to find or refine our life missions. Why are we here in this world, on this planet? What value do we bring to the world? How?
The next workshop is for new men, an introduction to our work. I think a couple men will attend even though I am the only person who has responded on Meetup for our second Journey of the Heart workshop.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>guest magician Robert Golden</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/04/30/guest-magician-robert-golden/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 21:52:55 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/04/30/guest-magician-robert-golden/</guid>
      <description>21:52 Tuesday 30 April 2019 JST Tonight, on the last day of Heisei, Robert Golden attend our men&amp;rsquo;s circle as a guest magician. It was really great to see his facilitation, and to see how closely it meshes with what we have already been doing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>deep work</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/03/23/deep-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2019 20:35:05 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/03/23/deep-work/</guid>
      <description>20:35 Saturday 23 March 2019 CDT Tonight men supported me doing a deep emotional piece. little boy all alone,
 take care of your mother figure it out you are alone you&amp;rsquo;re a little man  Felt vibrations in my body which come up when I do deep work. Vibration and tingling in legs stomach arms face lips.
Trust fall was so spooky, hard not to self-facilitate. Josh took all the stuff I have been carrying on my shoulders.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>bright moon light</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/03/22/bright-moon-light/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2019 03:23:11 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/03/22/bright-moon-light/</guid>
      <description>03:23 Friday 22 March 2019 CDT Full moon tonight and clear sky so at 3am it&amp;rsquo;s bright enough outside to walk around via moonlight.
Great to meet everyone. Spent good time talking to Dad last night. So glad he came down to see me!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hanging out with Michael Monkey</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/03/20/hanging-out-with-michael-monkey/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2019 23:27:39 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/03/20/hanging-out-with-michael-monkey/</guid>
      <description>23:27 Wednesday 20 March 2019 PDT Been sick as a dog for most of it, but I have had a great time hanging out at Michael Monkey&amp;rsquo;s in Houston. Thanks to Great Granny Good Witch for driving me to the store today to buy clothes and toiletries which should last a good while.
She has a lot lot lotta masks from around the world!
I have made a good start on the puzzle in the dining room, first expanding the table, then adding more white backing, then rotating the inner white backing to reduce waste.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>cyberknights with me and monkey in same room</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/03/20/cyberknights-with-me-and-monkey-in-same-room/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2019 21:37:56 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/03/20/cyberknights-with-me-and-monkey-in-same-room/</guid>
      <description>21:37 Wednesday 20 March 2019 PDT Good times.
Afterward, tried to scan a hand drawn blueprint through a glass table scanner, but the lighting was too distant to make it work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>was sick during BC NWTA</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/03/18/was-sick-during-bc-nwta/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2019 01:10:32 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/03/18/was-sick-during-bc-nwta/</guid>
      <description>01:10 Monday 18 March 2019 PDT I felt sad to have to check out for a significant portion of the NWTA this past weekend. So annoying, and certainly not what I had in mind for my trip!
Was great to meet awesome men. I stayed with Steve R in Vancouver the night before the weekend, and am now staying with Dave M in Victoria the night after the weekend. Headed to Houston tomorrow via Calgary.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dark Horse</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/03/13/dark-horse/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2019 23:15:22 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/03/13/dark-horse/</guid>
      <description>23:15 Wednesday 13 March 2019 PDT I attended an I group in Vancouver. After the group, since if the men did a Facebook Live
https://www.facebook.com/darkhorseigroup/videos/2033026273665997/
I think this could be a cool way to promote in Tokyo</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Headed to Narita with Lin</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/03/13/headed-to-narita-with-lin/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2019 16:50:52 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/03/13/headed-to-narita-with-lin/</guid>
      <description>16:50 Wednesday 13 March 2019 JST In preparation for this trip, I started my packing list a few weeks ago.
I had planned to copy it here, but for now, just imagine it.
I pre-packed most of the list a couple days ago, getting down to computer, phone, and other stuff I could not pack because I use it daily.
This morning I woke up early, and repacked everything, doublechecking the list, and taking pictures of all of it, in some kind of just in case scenario that will not happen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BC NWTA 3 weeks out</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/02/27/bc-nwta-3-weeks-out/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2019 22:03:45 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/02/27/bc-nwta-3-weeks-out/</guid>
      <description>22:03 Wednesday 27 February 2019 JST Today was the 3-weeks-out meeting for we staff of the New Warrior Training Adventure (NWTA) in British Columbia, Canada. It was a good meeting; we each have a buddy and each man on the call checked in for his buddy, with the presumption that the buddies have been in touch with each other.
I was inspired after the call and reached out to my two teams via email.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>State of My Life Address</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/02/06/state-of-my-life-address/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2019 07:44:19 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/02/06/state-of-my-life-address/</guid>
      <description>07:44 Wednesday 06 February 2019 JST  Lin and I still have our cat Jennie, still keep her in at night, still live in Asao-ku near the bottom of a hill. I&amp;rsquo;m still working on Marble Track 3, trying to do at least 2 hours of livestream per week. I have been working on AB, getting tests added to cover the important parts of the codebase. I do not have a lot covered, but 10 tests is an order of magnitude more than 0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Busy prepping for MKP trip</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/01/30/busy-prepping-for-mkp-trip/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jan 2019 22:10:31 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/01/30/busy-prepping-for-mkp-trip/</guid>
      <description>22:10 Wednesday 30 January 2019 JST Just a couple days ago I got my tickets all sorted to staff two different NWTA weekends and also attend the MKP USA Face to Face weekend in Texas.
After pretty much settling on the plans, it was pointed out that attending an IGFT might give me more of the training I am looking for, but I trust this is the training / trip I need.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>gofundme campaign is up</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/01/17/gofundme-campaign-is-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jan 2019 20:41:44 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/01/17/gofundme-campaign-is-up/</guid>
      <description>20:41 Thursday 17 January 2019 JST TL;DR: https://www.gofundme.com/launching-mankind-project-operations-in-japan
Just to confirm it is really me, I am posting a first person version of the ManKind Project Japan GoFundme campaign &amp;ldquo;Launching ManKind Project Operations in Japan&amp;ldquo; text here on my journal:
ManKind Project challenges each man to find and develop his own life’s mission, and to live that mission fully with the support of a powerful network. ManKind Project has become a global phenomenon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>life changing work</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/01/17/life-changing-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jan 2019 18:02:33 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/01/17/life-changing-work/</guid>
      <description>18:02 Thursday 17 January 2019 JST It has taken me a long time to reach this point, but from being afraid of men in 1997, I am now facilitating deep emotional work in men&amp;rsquo;s circles every week, both online and face to face in Tokyo.
I want to deepen my skills as a facilitator and have decided to step more fully into this emotional awareness work. To improve my facilitation skills, I plan to staff two (2) New Warrior Training Adventure weekends, back to back in March and April.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rough final draft of video for GoFundme</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/01/16/rough-final-draft-of-video-for-gofundme/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2019 21:54:54 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/01/16/rough-final-draft-of-video-for-gofundme/</guid>
      <description>21:54 Wednesday 16 January 2019 JST The GoFundme text is not finished yet, but I plan to finish it up tonight or tomorrow.
It took a while to get this version complete, including breaking a pen and crying my eyes out with Mark at the Jonathan&amp;rsquo;s near 向ヶ 丘遊園駅むこうがおかゆうえんえき mukogaokayuen station.
Between working for TY and AB, I got this version complete in one take, after about 30 takes over a period of a week or so.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>work and prep work</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/01/10/work-and-prep-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2019 13:55:38 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/01/10/work-and-prep-work/</guid>
      <description>13:55 Thursday 10 January 2019 JST One of the AB cronjobs has been throwing errors, but the job is still running.
I am in the middle of refactoring the code to use Dependency Injection; I don&amp;rsquo;t know how I broke something, but I cannot really go back to a previous version. Rather, I don&amp;rsquo;t know what version to go back to, and my local dev environment cannot recreate the error.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MKP open circles and New Warrior Training Adventure</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/01/10/mkp-open-circles-and-new-warrior-training-adventure/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2019 08:48:06 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/01/10/mkp-open-circles-and-new-warrior-training-adventure/</guid>
      <description>08:48 Thursday 10 January 2019 JST Men,
Back when I joined Mankind Project in 1997, the New Warrior Training Adventure was the only way to get started in Mankind Project.
Attending the weekend was a life changing experience for me. It was on that weekend that I realized I was a man. It was during that weekend that I began to get over my fear of men.
Over the years, as an organization, Mankind Project has begun encouraging new men to sit in Open Circles (like the one we have in Tokyo) before attending the New Warrior Training Adventure (NWTA).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>great session with D</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/11/18/great-session-with-d/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 16:42:50 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/11/18/great-session-with-d/</guid>
      <description>16:42 Sunday 18 November 2018 JST I was the only other man to show up for D&amp;rsquo;s men&amp;rsquo;s circle tonight. We walked to a park near his house which has a wooded area.
Away from the busy-ness of the park, we settled in for a meditation and then got into my work. Wondering how to balance my projects, where to focus my energy, how to do the right thing?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>headed to integration group</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/10/30/headed-to-integration-group/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 17:47:47 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/10/30/headed-to-integration-group/</guid>
      <description>17:47 Tuesday 30 October 2018 JST Headed to Tuesday night men&amp;rsquo;s circle. Train is nice and warm and I want to fall asleep.
21:44 Great meeting with 8 men in attendance!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>no mixed gender meeting</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/10/29/no-mixed-gender-meeting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2018 17:37:04 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/10/29/no-mixed-gender-meeting/</guid>
      <description>(written 17:37 Tuesday 30 October 2018 JST)
No mixed gender meeting last night nor the week before.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>book myself solid</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/10/13/book-myself-solid/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Oct 2018 10:14:37 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/10/13/book-myself-solid/</guid>
      <description>10:14 Saturday 13 October 2018 JST Matt suggested I go through Book Yourself Solid so I bought it today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>met with Paul about The Men&#39;s Work</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/10/05/met-with-paul-about-the-mens-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 19:53:05 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/10/05/met-with-paul-about-the-mens-work/</guid>
      <description>19:53 Friday 05 October 2018 JST Exciting MKP Tokyo news!
I sent this to my online Integration Group.
I just got confirmation: I will be co-facilitating a 3-week online MKP introduction called The Men&#39;s Work https://mkpusa.org/themenswork/ with Paul Newell, who is currently co-facilitating it in the US. On Fridays, 7pm - 8:30pm (Japan time), November 3rd, 10th, and 17th, we will do this online training for men in Tokyo. Once we run this 3 week series of meetings a couple of times, I will create a new men&#39;s circle in Gotanda (Tokyo) on Fridays for men who are interested.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>progress on multiple fronts</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/09/22/progress-on-multiple-fronts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Sep 2018 21:12:36 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/09/22/progress-on-multiple-fronts/</guid>
      <description>21:12 Saturday 22 September 2018 JST BH set up a Slack space for MKP Japan where we can discuss creating the organization and setting up some trainings.
I got a multi-month fix done for AB; now users can use the same filter on their custom list page as they can on the main list. I don&amp;rsquo;t recall why it was set up this weird way before, but it is better now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>work life balance livestream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/09/17/work-life-balance-livestream/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2018 12:10:14 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/09/17/work-life-balance-livestream/</guid>
      <description> 12:10 Monday 17 September 2018 JST Wondering why I feel obligated to work work work.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>went to Gotanda</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/09/10/went-to-gotanda/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018 21:04:06 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/09/10/went-to-gotanda/</guid>
      <description>We are planning to create a new men&amp;rsquo;s circle in Gotanda starting sometime soonishly. Hopefully this year or definitely by early next year omg.
五反田で新しい男のグループを始める予定です。今年か絶対来年の頭までに始 めると思います。
新しい日本語も作ります。来年の頭は一月から３月のことです。</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Excited (and scared)</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/09/06/excited-and-scared/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Sep 2018 20:31:29 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/09/06/excited-and-scared/</guid>
      <description>20:31 Thursday 06 September 2018 JST I&amp;rsquo;m excited when I think about my vision, and I&amp;rsquo;m scared what I think about implementing it.
I have been leading Tokyo men&amp;rsquo;s Circle for three years, And my vision is to create more circles that are empowered to continue doing their own emotional growth work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vision</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/09/06/vision/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Sep 2018 06:35:43 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/09/06/vision/</guid>
      <description>06:35 Thursday 06 September 2018 JST A man has two lives. The second one begins when he realized he only has one life.
My second life has begun. I am feeling the fire in my gut, mixed with the fear of rejection and failure. But as I have learned through experience, if I follow my fear I will be headed in the right direction in life.
For me these fears result in me dying alone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>great mission workshop last night in men&#39;s group</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/08/29/great-mission-workshop-last-night-in-mens-group/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Aug 2018 05:40:32 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/08/29/great-mission-workshop-last-night-in-mens-group/</guid>
      <description>05:40 Wednesday 29 August 2018 JST The Mission Workshop was a great success last night, with 8 men in attendance. We tapped in to our Little Boys Deepest needs, then visualized an ideal world with the needs met. Where everyone has had this deepest need met. What kind of world is it? _________, ___________, ____________.
Then we went back to this ideal world and found ourselves living within it. Not only living, but interacting and behaving in new ways in this ideal world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>great mens circle tonight</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/08/14/great-mens-circle-tonight/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Aug 2018 22:50:52 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/08/14/great-mens-circle-tonight/</guid>
      <description>22:50 Tuesday 14 August 2018 JST Four men in the circle tonight, including two relatively newcomers. I experienced beautiful facilitation to help me get the courage to implement my new idea.
I have just sent this message to my friend H.
I am thinking about doing a 6 month set of weekly circles on Friday nights. Could I do them at your place? Would you be able to attend, assuming you&#39;d be interested in the content?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>great meeting this morning</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/07/21/great-meeting-this-morning/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jul 2018 09:28:26 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/07/21/great-meeting-this-morning/</guid>
      <description>09:28 Saturday 21 July 2018 JST We are planning to do a one-day workshop to introduce the type of work we do in the men&amp;rsquo;s circle. November 10th or 17th, so mark your calendars!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mens circle process</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/07/19/mens-circle-process/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jul 2018 10:59:03 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/07/19/mens-circle-process/</guid>
      <description>10:59 Thursday 19 July 2018 JST Tonight I chose to work on my anger related to things not going my way.
Anger: why is this person standing blocking the escalator keeping people from going up?
Anger: why would R-san not trust a professional wine taster that he knows how to taste wine without getting drunk?
Anger: why would A-san suggest popcorn style for people to speak up instead of just asking each person?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>15 men in Tokyo Integration group</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/06/06/15-men-in-tokyo-integration-group/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2018 06:51:49 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/06/06/15-men-in-tokyo-integration-group/</guid>
      <description>06:51 Wednesday 06 June 2018 JST I did not keep careful track, but I believe we had 15 men in Tokyo men&amp;rsquo;s circle (Integration group) last night. According to A Circle of Men we should think about splitting the group if the group is larger than about 12 men.
I wonder about splitting the circle into two groups on the same evenings, or possible begin a circle on another evening of the week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>great co-gender circle tonight</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/05/07/great-co-gender-circle-tonight/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 May 2018 22:31:25 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/05/07/great-co-gender-circle-tonight/</guid>
      <description>22:31 Monday 07 May 2018 JST So thankful for my group tonight who were able to help me look at my income problem, pick me up out of the proverbial quicksand, and open me up to no limits for my business plan.
Not that I actually knew I was in proverbial quicksand, nor that I had unconsciously put limits on my possible business. Great to have great feedback from them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>full integration group meeting</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/05/03/full-integration-group-meeting/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 May 2018 09:39:04 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/05/03/full-integration-group-meeting/</guid>
      <description>09:39 Thursday 03 May 2018 JST Today is the first day I will be able to attend the entire integration group since seven weeks ago when I started the Court of Support meetings after LT1 in Portland.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>got schedule mixed up</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/27/got-schedule-mixed-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 17:46:31 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/27/got-schedule-mixed-up/</guid>
      <description>17:46 Friday 27 April 2018 JST I forgot the monthly Integration Group Coordinator call is at 9am Japan time now that the time has sprung forward an hour. I was a few minutes late to the call, but all was good. Oh that reminds me, I gotta correct the time in my reminder messages for next month.
We talked about suicide prevention, and ways to raise awareness of this issue and how people can get support.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>new man in mens circle last night</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/04/new-man-in-mens-circle-last-night/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Apr 2018 07:03:25 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/04/new-man-in-mens-circle-last-night/</guid>
      <description>07:03 Wednesday 04 April 2018 JST Nice synchronicity brought two old friends together on the train just in time for one to invite the other two men&amp;rsquo;s group last night, the first Tuesday of the month, when new men are welcome to join.
Six men in the circle last night. Good strong container in which we did a lot of good work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>State of My Life Address</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/01/state-of-my-life-address/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Apr 2018 15:25:24 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/01/state-of-my-life-address/</guid>
      <description>15:25 Sunday 01 April 2018 JST  I started a Meetup group ManKind Project Tokyo which will soon be linked to the Mankind Project Pro Meetup account. Men&amp;rsquo;s group meetings are now every Tuesday (since March). We had been meeting twice a month since about August 2015. The group has slowly grown and now twice a month is not enough for every man to do his work. SOGO is still going, although the leadership is changing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Created a meetup group for ManKind Project Tokyo</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/29/created-a-meetup-group-for-mankind-project-tokyo/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Mar 2018 15:50:35 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/29/created-a-meetup-group-for-mankind-project-tokyo/</guid>
      <description>15:50 Thursday 29 March 2018 JST https://www.meetup.com/ManKind-Project-Tokyo/
Thanks to Richard for giving me constructive feedback on the first version which was basically The Agreements, which include a lot of what we can&amp;rsquo;t do. He suggested putting some of the benefits on the site first.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>court of support</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/22/court-of-support/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2018 13:23:51 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/22/court-of-support/</guid>
      <description>13:23 Thursday 22 March 2018 JST The court of support meetings are being held for seven weeks after the LT1 I attended in Portland on March 9th weekend. Each man will take the role of a different archetype, King, Warrior, Magician, Lover, as described in many places, including King, Warrior, Magician, Lover: Rediscovering the Archetypes of the Mature Masculine, and bite sized Four Archetypes of the Mature Masculine on Art of Manliness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>men&#39;s circle meets every Tuesday</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/17/mens-circle-meets-every-tuesday/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Mar 2018 15:49:01 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/17/mens-circle-meets-every-tuesday/</guid>
      <description>15:49 Saturday 17 March 2018 JST The men&amp;rsquo;s circle now meets every Tuesday. New men are welcome on the first Tuesday each month. Email info@ this domain to get information about the meeting location.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>back in Tokyo</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/13/back-in-tokyo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Mar 2018 16:02:27 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/13/back-in-tokyo/</guid>
      <description>16:02 Tuesday 13 March 2018 JST Back in Japan now, on a bus headed to Tokyo from Narita airport. This bus is cheap and does not include electrical outlets like some airport trains do, but I have a bit of charge available on my computer (74% (was 79% when I started))
Ah; I can write Japanese for my lesson on Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Great LT1 weekend</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/11/great-lt1-weekend/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Mar 2018 16:05:39 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/11/great-lt1-weekend/</guid>
      <description>16:05 Sunday 11 March 2018 JST 23:05 Saturday 10 March 2018 JST Bunch of great guys here in Oregon for the LT1 and ST1 dual training. I attended ST1 (Staff Training 1) in Perth last year and am attending LT1 (Leadership Training 1) in Oregon this weekend. Got to meet Alan who I know from my online men&amp;rsquo;s circle, and met Mike P with dredlocks who I had met online as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Headed to Portland</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/09/headed-to-portland/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2018 12:16:24 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/09/headed-to-portland/</guid>
      <description>12:16 Friday 09 March 2018 JST I&amp;rsquo;m leaving in about an hour for a weekend in Portland. It&amp;rsquo;s for a training called The Container of Leadership. I will be challenged to look deeply at myself, really digging down into my -isms and other thoughts which unconsiously underly my perception of the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>great integration group tonight</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/02/06/great-integration-group-tonight/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2018 21:17:44 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/02/06/great-integration-group-tonight/</guid>
      <description>21:17 Tuesday 06 February 2018 JST Five men in attendance tonight despite three regulars being absent. Great to see men look inside to find their inner truth.
https://tokyo.mypowercircle.org/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Co-gender circle meets on Mondays</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/26/co-gender-circle-meets-on-mondays/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2018 13:21:11 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/26/co-gender-circle-meets-on-mondays/</guid>
      <description>13:21 Friday 26 January 2018 JST The co-gender circle has decided to move the meetings to Mondays so we can meet every week!
Soon the men&amp;rsquo;s circle will meet every week as well, I am fairly certain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>integration group council meeting</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/26/integration-group-council-meeting/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2018 11:38:53 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/26/integration-group-council-meeting/</guid>
      <description>11:38 Friday 26 January 2018 JST Great integration group council meeting today. I got some great ideas for how to help invite new men into the work. I mean the same type of work in The Work.
Blessings to all the men who make this work possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>lovely day</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/25/lovely-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2018 14:03:42 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/25/lovely-day/</guid>
      <description>14:03 Thursday 25 January 2018 JST Great online Integration Group today. Just six men in the call (we recently have had as many as 11 or 12). I was asked to facilitate twice (joy for me) and both men said it was very helpful. yay!
Headed to work now, slightly later than my arrive-early target, but still early enough to be on time. The weather is clear blue chilly with snow melting in the sun and frozen solid in the shade.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More Meetings</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/17/more-meetings/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2018 12:22:49 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/17/more-meetings/</guid>
      <description>12:22 Wednesday 17 January 2018 JST We had a great meeting last night with seven men in the circle.
This month has 5 Tuesdays, so normally we would skip the 5th Tuesday.
This month we will have a meeting on the 5th Tuesday.
Soon I imagine we will meet every Tuesday and have the co-gender group meet on a different day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>co-gender group</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/11/28/co-gender-group/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2017 22:34:08 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/11/28/co-gender-group/</guid>
      <description>22:34 Tuesday 28 November 2017 JST 4 people attended the co-gender group tonight. Great depth of work and great to have a chance to hear what people want to get from the group in the future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>today</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/11/16/today/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2017 13:18:54 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/11/16/today/</guid>
      <description>13:18 Thursday 16 November 2017 JST Funny talking to Scotty on Marco Polo; he kept not being able to hear me until I was like &amp;ldquo;okay bye&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;okay I hope you could hear it that time!&amp;rdquo;
I am headed to Kawasaki to support the guides in the English versions of their work. Then GG lesson in Akihabara.
Quick online I-group today; everyone checked out so it was just me and my coach near North Zulch, Texas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mens group</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/11/05/mens-group/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2017 21:50:40 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/11/05/mens-group/</guid>
      <description>21:50 Sunday 05 November 2017 JST We are building a peer support group of committed men who help each other meet their full potential. We meet twice a month
We build conflict resolution skills, create a personal mission statement, and create great friendships.
Would you be interested in hearing more about it? Come to one of our open sessions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>integration group tonight</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/10/17/integration-group-tonight/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 22:49:03 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/10/17/integration-group-tonight/</guid>
      <description>22:49 Tuesday 17 October 2017 JST Good I-group tonight.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>good v-group</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/10/13/good-v-group/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2017 18:19:03 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/10/13/good-v-group/</guid>
      <description>18:19 Friday 13 October 2017 Virtual Group was good today. I got some feedback on how to better handle a man joining in the middle of the call. Essentially, he knew he was late, and he knew why he was late; I did not have to ask him why he was late, but just if he knew why he was late.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>good i-group</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/10/12/good-i-group/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2017 14:09:20 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/10/12/good-i-group/</guid>
      <description>14:09 Thursday 12 October 2017 JST Great I-group today; I had chills from within when I got to yell at my dad from when I was 7 years old.
He said &amp;ldquo;if there were 100 people from your class all in a line, you would be the smartest.&amp;rdquo;
He meant it well, but it&amp;rsquo;s like hey fuck you don&amp;rsquo;t put that on a 7 year old! what is he going to do with that info?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>great weekend</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/10/08/great-weekend/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2017 23:29:20 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/10/08/great-weekend/</guid>
      <description>23:29 Sunday 08 October 2017 JST Yeah what can I say besides great except it wasn&amp;rsquo;t completely what I had hoped since I was looking for a bit more facilitation training. It will come though. This training was about the NWTA; next training is more focused on facilitation.
I told the group I might not be back next year; I will more carefully look at options for where would make the most sense for men from Japan to do a training.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>last virtual I-group</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/08/25/last-virtual-i-group/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2017 11:35:22 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/08/25/last-virtual-i-group/</guid>
      <description>11:35 Friday 25 August 2017 JST Today was the fifth of five virtual I-groups designed to give leadership practice to men in the group. Just five men in the group, one night each gives a sense of what it&amp;rsquo;s like and lets men see other men leading the calls.
So I will be the leader leader of the next set of calls, planned for 6 calls starting in October.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>co-gender group tonight</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/07/11/co-gender-group-tonight/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2017 16:36:56 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/07/11/co-gender-group-tonight/</guid>
      <description>16:36 Tuesday 11 July 2017 JST egad I need to finish the website.
08:07 Friday 14 July 2017 JST Group was great. 6 attendees and one who tried to come but could not find the place. oops!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Will continue online circle facilitation practice</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/07/07/will-continue-online-circle-facilitation-practice/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 09:26:37 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/07/07/will-continue-online-circle-facilitation-practice/</guid>
      <description>09:26 Friday 07 July 2017 JST I was invited to continue for another 6 weeks of online circle (not really a circle, but) facilitation practice starting 20 July. I feel fear about leading my own groups, but I will head that direction anyway.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>theory about emotions</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/06/26/theory-about-emotions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2017 06:51:41 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/06/26/theory-about-emotions/</guid>
      <description>06:51 Monday 26 June 2017 JST Back in high school I determed that emotions must be important.
Why do they stay available long after the cause is finished? Not like memories or scars which fade with time, but remain somehow somewhere, available until we experience them. I experienced this long after my granddad died and smelled something that reminded me of him. boom crying crying tears even though I only vaguely remembered the thing he gave me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tokyo Men&#39;s Circle</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/06/20/tokyo-mens-circle/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2017 21:15:20 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/06/20/tokyo-mens-circle/</guid>
      <description>last night (written 09:15 Wednesday 21 June 2017 JST)
Tokyo Men&amp;rsquo;s Circle had 6 participants including a new man last night. He said he plans to attend the co-gender group next week. We talked about ways to serve the community even more, possibly offering team-building workshops to businesses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>great Authenticity Circle last night</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/05/24/great-authenticity-circle-last-night/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2017 04:55:59 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/05/24/great-authenticity-circle-last-night/</guid>
      <description>04:55 Wednesday 24 May 2017 JST Still working on a name for the circle which I had been calling the co-gender group. Anyway, our second meeting was great last night. Five members in attendance, and we practiced exercises from Week 2 of A Circle of Men. After the circle, some members expressed interest in exploring this further, so I guided them through clearing charges, with the remaining member holding space.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>guardian angel</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/05/04/guardian-angel/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2017 11:08:32 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/05/04/guardian-angel/</guid>
      <description>11:08 Thursday 04 May 2017 JST In my integration group, B asked if &amp;ldquo;anyone would like to volunteer for&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo; and my hand immediately shot up, not knowing what I was volunteering for.
&amp;ldquo;Okay, Rob&amp;rdquo; continued B, &amp;ldquo;you get to be our Guardian Angel&amp;rdquo; and, based on your experience, offer answers to life questions that we pose.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Integration group</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/05/03/integration-group/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2017 01:13:58 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/05/03/integration-group/</guid>
      <description>01:13 Wednesday 03 May 2017 JST 3 men in Integration group tonight, fewer than I hoped, but very powerful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>integration group</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/04/27/integration-group/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2017 13:28:17 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/04/27/integration-group/</guid>
      <description>13:28 Thursday 27 April 2017 JST Good meeting today, including comfortable silence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>great head heard and soul last night</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/03/28/great-head-heard-and-soul-last-night/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2017 11:18:49 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/03/28/great-head-heard-and-soul-last-night/</guid>
      <description>11:18 Wednesday 29 March 2017 JST 11 people in attendance, 8 of whom had not seen the presentation before. This was the second time for me to present Head Heart and Soul in Tokyo (or anywhere). I did not look at my notes, and did it all from memory, except the parts I forgot. Gotta practice more before next time.
Great conversation at Zest afterward.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>i-group</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/03/21/i-group/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2017 23:16:58 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/03/21/i-group/</guid>
      <description>23:16 Tuesday 21 March 2017 JST Great I-group tonight. Great internal discovery of self empowering energy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>my First GST call</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/03/10/my-first-gst-call/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2017 03:52:09 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/03/10/my-first-gst-call/</guid>
      <description>03:52 Friday 10 March 2017 JST Good morning!(?) Wow sleepy.
Today is my first time to join the international suppport group Global Support Team call.
I plan to ask how to find the best match for a sponsoring community.
We might not use it, but will have people to contact, in case of need choose community I feel will support me. dont worry about upside down directions. its about who I can get support from energetically.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mkp gst</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/02/28/mkp-gst/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2017 15:36:59 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/02/28/mkp-gst/</guid>
      <description>15:36 Tuesday 28 February 2017 JST Nice. Just by proverbially raising my hand to ask for help, I have found many people to help. There exists a Mankind Project Global Support Team, specifically to help MKP communities in new areas. It&amp;rsquo;s all grassroots, like UU churches. Not some big entity which says &amp;ldquo;now let&amp;rsquo;s expand here.&amp;rdquo; Organic growth, just as nature intended.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>xoxoxo</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/02/25/xoxoxo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2017 09:04:29 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/02/25/xoxoxo/</guid>
      <description>09:04 Saturday 25 February 2017 JST I just sent C from P xoxoxo text in Skype after he said &amp;ldquo;Thanks man&amp;rdquo; for supporting him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Great great Head Heart and Soul presentation</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/01/31/great-great-head-heart-and-soul-presentation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2017 22:55:24 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/01/31/great-great-head-heart-and-soul-presentation/</guid>
      <description>22:55 Wednesday 01 February 2017 JST Aight so last night Head Heart and Soul presentation was at least as good as I thought it might possibly be. Super great questions from Rohini and Mitsue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>blob</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/01/19/blob/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 11:55:01 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/01/19/blob/</guid>
      <description>11:55 Thursday 19 January 2017 JST I&amp;rsquo;m in my online men&amp;rsquo;s group now and just did a process whereby I clarified some emotions coming up around a work situation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>online I-group</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/09/15/online-i-group/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2016 11:14:41 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/09/15/online-i-group/</guid>
      <description>11:14 Thursday 15 September 2016 JST Just had online I-group; I&amp;rsquo;ve been on the weekly call for about a year now. Awesome connection.
Well, these days my e-physical connection isn&amp;rsquo;t so great; I call in from Wired Cafe because the call starts 30 minutes after my English class ends and I&amp;rsquo;m too far away (at currently available technology) from my house to do the call from there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>online integration group</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/06/30/online-integration-group/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2016 13:30:05 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/06/30/online-integration-group/</guid>
      <description>13:30 Thursday 30 June 2016 JST Integration group was good today; I was asked to lead the second round, which was a bit tricky since I was on mobile and couldn&amp;rsquo;t see everyone at the same time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>considering staffing in NZ</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/06/23/considering-staffing-in-nz/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2016 13:21:34 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/06/23/considering-staffing-in-nz/</guid>
      <description>13:21 Thursday 23 June 2016 JST The September 2016 NWTA event north of Houston has a staff application deadline in 3 days. The one for New Zealand (a week later) has a staff deadline in August. Given that travel to NZ is way less expensive, plus I have more time to waffle, I think I&amp;rsquo;ll forego staffing in Houston and apply for New Zealand. Plus I&amp;rsquo;ve never been there so it would be nice to visit!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chuck</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/02/16/chuck/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2016 08:51:49 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/02/16/chuck/</guid>
      <description>08:51 Tuesday 16 February 2016 JST I chatted with Chuck (from men&amp;rsquo;s group, not ASL instructor) on Skype yesterday. We may make it a weekly thing. I&amp;rsquo;d benefit from having someone to bitch to and hold me accountable for shit I need to do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AJ</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/01/25/aj/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2016 16:39:18 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/01/25/aj/</guid>
      <description>16:39 Monday 25 January 2016 PST We met AJ selling T-shirts at the beach. Listening to him, I was inspired to tell him about MKP. He was like, &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m already there!&amp;rdquo;
Wow; nice!
His business partner Paul Lloyd Warner has a Patreon account where his compositions are available https://www.patreon.com/plw (Piano and Symphonic)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>great I-group</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/11/30/great-i-group/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2015 22:12:05 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/11/30/great-i-group/</guid>
      <description>22:12 Monday 30 November 2015 JST Tonight was the second open I-group in Tokyo, and it went quite well. I posed the question &amp;ldquo;what would you change in your personal life if you could change anything?&amp;rdquo; and looked in detail at some of the answers. I now have a nice plan for how to be a better husband/partner with Lin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MM lessons and Thai dinner</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/11/10/mm-lessons-and-thai-dinner/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2015 22:27:14 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/11/10/mm-lessons-and-thai-dinner/</guid>
      <description>22:27 Tuesday 10 November 2015 JST During the first half of his lesson, Sarupapa asked me about MKP and I told him as much as I was able with my broken Japanese and English hybrid sentences. He said it seemed interesting; I wonder if he&amp;rsquo;d eventually be interested in attending I-group with us.
Sarumama came after that and we went over her homework. She&amp;rsquo;s really improving and would be a great inspiration if I wasn&amp;rsquo;t so frickin&amp;rsquo; lazy to study Japanese!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>lessons</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/10/27/lessons/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2015 21:50:05 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/10/27/lessons/</guid>
      <description>21:50 Tuesday 27 October 2015 JST Near the end of each lesson today I talked about MKP; I&amp;rsquo;m beginning to develop a more concise and understandable way of explaining what the work is about.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Met Chris</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/09/26/met-chris/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Sep 2015 19:29:39 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/09/26/met-chris/</guid>
      <description>19:29 Saturday 26 September 2015 JST Today on the way to Paola and Jon&amp;rsquo;s I saw an apparently English speaking man on the train. We made eye contact and smiled, and I thought, &amp;ldquo;hmm maybe he&amp;rsquo;d be interested in MKP.&amp;rdquo;
I sat for a few stations before deciding fuckit, and I went back to speak to him. He seemed interested enough to swap email addresses, and I emailed him this afternoon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>first integration group meeting in a while</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/09/25/first-integration-group-meeting-in-a-while/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Sep 2015 20:51:52 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/09/25/first-integration-group-meeting-in-a-while/</guid>
      <description>20:51 Friday 25 September 2015 JST We met at Takeshi&amp;rsquo;s tonight, our first meeting in over a year, I imagine. The last meeting I called in an emergency being all confuzzled about junk, though the issues mostly resolved by the time the meeting happened.
This meeting was called from a much more sane and golden space: I&amp;rsquo;m going to staff NWTA in October, and I&amp;rsquo;d like to help our I-group grow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>95 percent sure I&#39;m going to Perth in late October</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/08/26/95-percent-sure-im-going-to-perth-in-late-october/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2015 01:02:33 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/08/26/95-percent-sure-im-going-to-perth-in-late-october/</guid>
      <description>01:02 Wednesday 26 August 2015 JST I changed my life in 1997 by attending a weekend men&amp;rsquo;s retreat organized by https://mkp.org/ My ability to understand myself and my emotions / motivations grew exponentially from there. I&amp;rsquo;m by no means an expert, but I&amp;rsquo;m much better able to listen to others, and express myself&amp;hellip;. though not in this post, apparently!!
Anyway, I have missed the energy of this organization since moving to Japan, and recently decided to get involved again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Warrior Training</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1997/11/15/new-warrior-training/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 1997 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1997/11/15/new-warrior-training/</guid>
      <description>Saturday 15 November 1997
 This weekend changed my life.  When I first heard about New Warrior Training I was quite not interested. Some kind of initiation into manhood&amp;hellip; and I wanted nothing to do with it. That was two years ago.  The reason I wanted nothing to do with it: I was afraid of men.
I certainly didn&amp;rsquo;t want to become a man. And I doubly certaintly didn&amp;rsquo;t want to be associated with men and known as a man.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>