<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>toastmasters on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/toastmasters/</link>
    <description>Recent content in toastmasters on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Sep 2018 13:27:12 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/toastmasters/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>best table topics speech</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/09/06/best-table-topics-speech/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Sep 2018 13:27:12 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/09/06/best-table-topics-speech/</guid>
      <description>13:27 Thursday 06 September 2018 JST Today I won best Table Topics speech for making backronyms for JEBI, the name of the typhoon that just blew through.
I am super bummed that I missed the obvious link to the word of the day, which was improvised to be &amp;ldquo;improvise&amp;rdquo;
I started my speech &amp;ldquo;Given that I have just started a business that has this acronym, I will be happy to tell you about Jumping Entertainment Business Incorporated.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Attending Toastmasters today</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/09/06/attending-toastmasters-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Sep 2018 09:57:03 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/09/06/attending-toastmasters-today/</guid>
      <description>09:57 Thursday 06 September 2018 JST Had a quick livestream today during which Reversible Guy (apparently) glued a single toothpick and G Choppy cut two others which I had hoped to glue but could not quite before I had to head out to Roppongi where I am currently on Zoom with MKP men&amp;rsquo;s circle before the Cisco Toastmasters meeting from noon to 1pm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>toastmaster&#39;s best English table topic</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/06/15/toastmasters-best-english-table-topic/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 23:45:58 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/06/15/toastmasters-best-english-table-topic/</guid>
      <description>23:45 Friday 15 June 2018 JST Tonight I won the best (of three) English table topics. Zero ums counted by the um-counter, and 1 apparent use of the word &amp;ldquo;marvelous&amp;rdquo; which I actually used as &amp;ldquo;marvel us&amp;rdquo;
The speech topic was anything, based on an item taken from a bag. I took out a piece of chocolate so did a sales pitch on it, basically saying how its dimensions and mass could be used a measurment units.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Toastmasters Yamanote event</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/05/18/first-toastmasters-yamanote-event/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2018 23:14:27 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/05/18/first-toastmasters-yamanote-event/</guid>
      <description>23:14 Friday 18 May 2018 JST Toastmasters Yamanote Club had its 360th event this evening, which was my first. The meeting was not in their normal location, but it included lots of mini-presentations and presentations about presentations and an overview presentation of the evening of presentations.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>