<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>walk on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/walk/</link>
    <description>Recent content in walk on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2019 14:37:38 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/walk/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>walked around with Lin</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/07/14/walked-around-with-lin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2019 14:37:38 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/07/14/walked-around-with-lin/</guid>
      <description>14:37 Sunday 14 July 2019 JST Lin and I walked around our neighborhood, which couulllddd possibly count as a Walk that I started doing last year and dropped after getting to 14 or so.
During this walk, I practiced a process I heard on an Esther Hicks video recently. &amp;ldquo;You&amp;rsquo;re my favorite rock. You&amp;rsquo;re my favorite leaf. You&amp;rsquo;re my favorite tree.&amp;rdquo; etc
I found the transcription at the bottom of this PDF from a church newsletter(?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>walked with Mai and Richard</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/11/17/walked-with-mai-and-richard/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Nov 2018 22:05:59 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/11/17/walked-with-mai-and-richard/</guid>
      <description>22:05 Saturday 17 November 2018 JST I walked with Mai and Richard as they walked with Fitz. They let Fitz off his leash so he could run around in a fenced area, but he just trotted around instead of doing the /r/zoomies that I expected.
He did a good job sliding down the slide, though he was not able to go up the slide.
I should have taken pictures of them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>walked from Nishi-Azabu to Yotsuya by way of Yoyogi Park oops</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/10/22/walked-from-nishi-azabu-to-yotsuya-by-way-of-yoyogi-park-oops/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Oct 2018 16:27:28 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/10/22/walked-from-nishi-azabu-to-yotsuya-by-way-of-yoyogi-park-oops/</guid>
      <description> 16:27 Monday 22 October 2018 JST １３時３０分に西麻布の授業後、４時１５分に飯田橋駅行く予定でした。 二時間４５分暇時間があったから歩く方がいいと思った。 マップを見たとほと んど分かりましたからマップ見えずに代々木公園の反対側まで歩きました。 あっ。表参道で右曲がりよかった。 戻りながら、ミミズただ見ました。ミミズが乾いた道頑張れましたから、彼を 強く太陽の光ないの植物の下で持ってきました。 彼が行きテラレったら、よかったです。 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>walking while talking to Dora</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/10/22/walking-while-talking-to-dora/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Oct 2018 16:03:33 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/10/22/walking-while-talking-to-dora/</guid>
      <description>16:03 Monday 22 October 2018 JST I chatted with Dora for 1.75 hours on the phone. She had some amazing insights on my presentation for MKP stuff. Plus a course she has enjoyed taking, designed to help people start their business projects.
While talking, I walked from Nishi-Azabu to the other end of Yoyogi Park before realizing I had intended to turn right before Yoyogi Park, or actually maybe even turn at Omotesando.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>morning walk (16)</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/10/16/morning-walk-16/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 05:30:08 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/10/16/morning-walk-16/</guid>
      <description>05:30 Tuesday 16 October 2018 JST Though it was short, I walked this morning around the new construction near our house. Took a picture of a stump or two growing on a wall.
I fell out of the habit since Walk 15, during which we bought eggs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>bought eggs during fifteenth walk</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/09/17/bought-eggs-during-fifteenth-walk/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2018 08:29:34 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/09/17/bought-eggs-during-fifteenth-walk/</guid>
      <description>08:29 Monday 17 September 2018 JST Ain&amp;rsquo;t been walking every day recently, but today Lin and I went to fetch some eggs from a street-side vending boxen machine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>fourteenth walk</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/09/13/fourteenth-walk/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 07:37:35 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/09/13/fourteenth-walk/</guid>
      <description>07:37 Thursday 13 September 2018 JST I walked to a new area and found a long, abandoned sidewalk between a school and an apartment complex. Then I found an egg farm!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>thirteenth walk, a week late</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/09/07/thirteenth-walk-a-week-late/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Sep 2018 07:46:21 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/09/07/thirteenth-walk-a-week-late/</guid>
      <description>07:46 Friday 07 September 2018 JST Walked this morning for the first time in a week or so oops. Good times, including meeting the guy who I usually meet on Wednesdays while he is on his exercise route. Oh, and nodded to the kid who runs around the neighborhood as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>walked yesterday</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/09/05/walked-yesterday/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2018 07:13:15 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/09/05/walked-yesterday/</guid>
      <description>07:13 Wednesday 05 September 2018 JST Yesterday a typhoon grazed Tokyo. We got some wind, but hardly any rain. I left early for men&amp;rsquo;s group to make sure I would be there even if the trains stopped for the typhoon.
I had loads of time, so I walked from Yoyogi Uehara to Nishi Azabu, by way of the Snoopy Museum! The museum costs 2000 yen to enter, so I skipped it until I have more time and can go with Lin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>did not walk this morning</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/08/31/did-not-walk-this-morning/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Aug 2018 09:53:39 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/08/31/did-not-walk-this-morning/</guid>
      <description>昨日の夕方の日本語の授業のための疲れによって歩けませんでした。</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>walk twelve: brick fishtank</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/08/30/walk-twelve-brick-fishtank/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Aug 2018 06:32:01 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/08/30/walk-twelve-brick-fishtank/</guid>
      <description>06:32 Thursday 30 August 2018 JST I heard some water trickling and noticed a fountain flowing into a basin made of bricks. There were a couple fish inside, effectively making it a brick fishtank.

The sky was overcast so not too hot.
Oh, today was the day I walked across part of the dirt lot and up into the back corner area. I didn&amp;rsquo;t think to take pics while on the inside, but I might go again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>walk ten sunny again</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/08/25/walk-ten-sunny-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Aug 2018 07:30:41 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/08/25/walk-ten-sunny-again/</guid>
      <description>07:30 Saturday 25 August 2018 JST Lin joined me at first but then bailed. I did not walk far, but talked to Delayna and Richard while walking. Told them both about Shift Your Shit program. They both seemed interested, and Richard may be interested in actually joining now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>walk number nine during typhoon</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/08/24/walk-number-nine-during-typhoon/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Aug 2018 07:47:34 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/08/24/walk-number-nine-during-typhoon/</guid>
      <description>07:47 Friday 24 August 2018 JST This morning I walked during the typhoon that passed by Tokyo today. I saw some interesting effects of water rushing down the hill near よみうりランド前駅 I captured them on vertical video on Marco Polo to send to Lin, who stayed home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>eighth walk and losing count</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/08/23/eighth-walk-and-losing-count/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Aug 2018 13:07:30 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/08/23/eighth-walk-and-losing-count/</guid>
      <description>13:07 Thursday 23 August 2018 JST I nearly did not write this entry; I had a vision of writing an entry after every walk, but I got sidetracked with an AB request that took 6 hours unfuckingpaid. Now I know how Google Maps feels, now requesting monies for their javascript API.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>started today with my seventh walk</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/08/21/started-today-with-my-seventh-walk/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Aug 2018 08:59:12 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/08/21/started-today-with-my-seventh-walk/</guid>
      <description>08:59 Tuesday 21 August 2018 JST 今朝超眠かったけど５時に起きて1時間ぐらい歩きました。
新しい場所を見たかったから初めての道を使いました。
おじいさん一人とちょっと挨拶しました(。|だ)けどちょっとドキドキでした。彼が優しい人だから、大丈夫だった。</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yesterday included sixth walk</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/08/20/yesterday-included-sixth-walk/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Aug 2018 05:20:01 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/08/20/yesterday-included-sixth-walk/</guid>
      <description>05:20 Monday 20 August 2018 JST Lin and I walked together yesterday on a completely new route.
I chose not to go to SOGO after flipping a coin after Lin asked if I wanted to stay at home and install the vertical labyrinth game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lin joined me on my fifth walk</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/08/18/lin-joined-me-on-my-fifth-walk/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Aug 2018 09:19:54 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/08/18/lin-joined-me-on-my-fifth-walk/</guid>
      <description>09:19 Saturday 18 August 2018 JST Lin and I got off to a later start than I had originally planned, but we walked an hour around our neighborhood, finding some new streets we had never used before and arriving via different routes in places we had been before. &amp;ldquo;Oh! we&amp;rsquo;re here!&amp;rdquo; kinda thing.
Wow! 3.9km in 58 minutes, according to Google maps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>fun fourth walk</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/08/17/fun-fourth-walk/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Aug 2018 07:21:12 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/08/17/fun-fourth-walk/</guid>
      <description>07:21 Friday 17 August 2018 JST I have been writing in Japanese about the walk.
Behind our house there are some houses under construction. There are no gates blocking entry so I went inside to have a look.
(English translations from my Japanese:)
Outside the houses there was scaffolding wrapped in blue fabric. On the first floor the fabric kept anyone outside from seeing me inside, but on the second floor, the fabric had gaps so I was nervous at times.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>break up cat fight before walk (3)</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/08/16/break-up-cat-fight-before-walk-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2018 06:25:47 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/08/16/break-up-cat-fight-before-walk-3/</guid>
      <description>06:25 Thursday 16 August 2018 JST Just before 5am, Lin let Jennie outside for her morning adventures. Soon thereafter we could hear her catching up with another cat. I woke up for my walk and headed toward the altercation. Unfortunately my approach was a catalyst for amplification of the catastrophe. They catapulted away from each other and Jennie ran under a car before I could catch her.
I continued walking and went 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>great walk this morning (2)</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/08/15/great-walk-this-morning-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Aug 2018 07:19:40 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/08/15/great-walk-this-morning-2/</guid>
      <description>07:19 Wednesday 15 August 2018 JST I woke up several times last night like 3am, 4am, and then ended up waking up at 5:30am instead of 5am for my walk. Got out of the house bleary eyed by 5:45 am and headed toward かさはら&amp;rsquo;s place. He wasn&amp;rsquo;t outside (and I was 45 minutes later than the previous day) so I strolled on past and walked up stairs to the right and met a man who I ended up exercising with in a park (Takaishi Dai 3 Park, according to Google Maps).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>fantastic first walk (1)</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/08/14/fantastic-first-walk-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Aug 2018 11:05:38 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/08/14/fantastic-first-walk-1/</guid>
      <description>11:05 Tuesday 14 August 2018 JST I have decided to wake up at 5am each day, and on the five days I do not have to immediately go to work (for which I have already been waking up at 5am), I will go for a brisk walk around the neighborhood.
Today I went up the hill and along the ridge and up left on a street I had never walked before, then up a hill into a park and then omg down a spooky mossy staircase with spiderweb strands hitting my face and cicadas buzzing my ears and mosquitoes chomping my legs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>walked 2 hours to Yoyogi Park</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/08/30/walked-2-hours-to-yoyogi-park/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2017 01:41:52 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/08/30/walked-2-hours-to-yoyogi-park/</guid>
      <description>01:41 Wednesday 30 August 2017 JST I walked for 2 hours from NB lesson to Yoyogi Park. I had 2 hours total and Google said it would take 1 hour and 45 minutes. I stopped once to get a snack and a drink (and to change from pants to shorts) and then stopped again to buy a 2 liter bottle of tea. Made it to Yoyogi Park with 2 minutes to spare.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>walked from there to here</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/06/27/walked-from-there-to-here/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2016 11:03:25 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/06/27/walked-from-there-to-here/</guid>
      <description>11:03 Monday 27 June 2016 JST I walked for 1.5 hours today, 25 minutes to the station, and then a lot of walking to look for the TUMI shop and then walked to work&amp;hellip; almost walked to work; Lin called me back and offered to meet me at our station to hand off a folder I forgot to bring with me today (not critical, but for men&amp;rsquo;s group meeting tonight, so I&amp;rsquo;d prefer to have it).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Walked to Torihama station</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/06/22/walked-to-torihama-station/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2016 16:08:46 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/06/22/walked-to-torihama-station/</guid>
      <description>16:08 Wednesday 22 June 2016 JST Right after I got on the bus to head back to 新杉田駅, I noted that I could walk there in just 2km. Or, better yet, I could walk to 鳥浜駅, which is even closer to where I need to go. So I got off the bus after a couple stops and walked toward 鳥浜駅.
Didn&amp;rsquo;t get too far when I saw a park!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>