<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ufo on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/ufo/</link>
    <description>Recent content in ufo on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2018 16:41:01 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/ufo/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>dream flew on UFO</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/16/dream-flew-on-ufo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2018 16:41:01 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/16/dream-flew-on-ufo/</guid>
      <description>16:41 Monday 16 April 2018 JST Had a very interesting dream last night. Most of the following was transcribed in a text message to Christine while walking to the station.
I was out on a field and we saw a spaceship flying above the clouds; it was moving to and fro, and had large glowing green and red lights illuminating large portions of the clouds around it. As it was coming down I was like &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Going to our first UFO contact event</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/22/going-to-our-first-ufo-contact-event/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/22/going-to-our-first-ufo-contact-event/</guid>
      <description>##09:33 Saturday 22 November 2014 JST##
Lin and I are packed and about to leave for 西武秩父駅 and then take a bus to something something and then see Rohini!
##13:12pm
In about 15 minutes we&amp;rsquo;ll arrive at 西武秩父駅. Right now it&amp;rsquo;s pretty warm, though we have lots of jackets and coats! I&amp;rsquo;m even wearing my hiking boots!!
Lin has been a bit moe joe on the trains; she doesn&amp;rsquo;t like having to change trains so much and slog through crowds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ET come home</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2008/03/02/et-come-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2008 13:29:44 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2008/03/02/et-come-home/</guid>
      <description>##13:29 Sunday 02 March 2008
Exopolitics: The Study of the Politics of Extraterrestrial Contact: Local ET Contact Activity
 A recent increase of ET activity worldwide seems to back up this assertion as well as what seems to be a corresponding increase in world government disclosure.
 About a year ago I asked my friends at work, &amp;ldquo;have you guys been seeing more reports of UFO sightings recently?&amp;rdquo;
They were like &amp;ldquo;no,&amp;rdquo; and I didn&amp;rsquo;t bring it up again, but the thought remained in the back of my mind.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>not 2013... 2017!</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2008/02/22/not-2013...-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2008 03:45:30 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2008/02/22/not-2013...-2017/</guid>
      <description>##03:45 Friday 22 February 2008
Confirmation &amp;amp; Update on Secret UFO Meeting at UN
 They pointed out that the “unambiguous showing up” of extraterrestrial life – sitting over major cities - would occur in 2017, rather than 2013 as described in the earlier article.
 D&amp;rsquo;oh! This is getting out of hand! 4 years back in just one day! ;-)
I&amp;rsquo;m still pretty excited.
Powered by ScribeFire.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>woohoo!!  UFOs in 2013</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2008/02/21/woohoo-ufos-in-2013/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Feb 2008 17:25:36 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2008/02/21/woohoo-ufos-in-2013/</guid>
      <description>##17:25 Thursday 21 February 2008
Source Reveals Secret UFO Meeting at U.N.
 A date of 2013 was given as the time for official disclosure and/or when extraterrestrials show up in an unambiguous way. In the interim there will be acclimation related releases of information. Importantly, the source revealed that the events leading up to official disclosure will involve more ethically oriented extraterrestrials, and they will not pose a military threat to the world.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>