<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>fossil on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/fossil/</link>
    <description>Recent content in fossil on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2018 00:15:53 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/fossil/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>git out</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/19/git-out/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2018 00:15:53 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/19/git-out/</guid>
      <description>00:15 Thursday 19 April 2018 JST  39c7bfa recent entries 17a339c removed : from titles 70ec6d3 TEMPoRARY commit, not including all years, and not cleaned up filenames 6086901 Added README 354c77e (bitbucket/master) p 1fbcd35 s c385ebb colon 492f2fc slash 3b91dec slash 40ba10c w ce5271f w 8be74d2 w afebd29 dot  The above shows a weird thing that happened to my git repo while I was messing with Fossil. The commit 6086901 is the first, and the commit 354c77e is the last, but it was shown right in a row.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>might try to set up Fossil on Dreamhost</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/15/might-try-to-set-up-fossil-on-dreamhost/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Apr 2018 11:30:53 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/15/might-try-to-set-up-fossil-on-dreamhost/</guid>
      <description>11:30 Sunday 15 April 2018 JST I found an article about setting up Fossil on Dreamhost, and may try to go through it today.
First, I will set up a new sub-domain and new user on Dreamhost.
12:07 Done. I recognize that I am using git on a server for Fossil, but am going to ignore that for now.
Though the previous article compiled from source, it appears Fossil provides Linux binaries now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>wow wow fossil is awesome</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/11/wow-wow-fossil-is-awesome/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 10:58:04 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/11/wow-wow-fossil-is-awesome/</guid>
      <description>10:58 Wednesday 11 April 2018 JST Fossil is awesome, but I am not ready to switch quite yet.
Can I get Fossil to host my journal like I have Hugo doing now? Should I? The point was to have it as a static site, so I guess not, but it seems weird to use something that can host sites just to track the site content and not host the site.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>