<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>spot on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/spot/</link>
    <description>Recent content in spot on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 May 2000 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/spot/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>spot</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/05/01/spot/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/05/01/spot/</guid>
      <description>Spot (not) 10:04pm CDT Monday 1 May 2000
Today at work I spent a lot of time talking to Savvis, our ISP, straightening out the three new DSL circuits we have ordered. One for each boss, and one for me. Somehow they have gotten the addresses mixed up for my bosses. Soon soon it will be all good.
Mine is still in the works; just got a dial-tone, so it may take a bit longer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>spot</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/04/27/spot/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/04/27/spot/</guid>
      <description>Spot 7:18pm CDT Thursday 27 April 2000
Spot is the coolest cat in the planet. Loyal readers will remember from back in the day that he used to leap four feet from a tree branch to enter my second story bedroom window. That was cool. Though we pulled him away from the outdoors and the tree, Spot has already found an equally cool trick inside the house. And this time, I have pictures.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>spot</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/04/25/spot/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/04/25/spot/</guid>
      <description>2:00pm Tuesday 25 April 2000
I have just learned that Data from Star Trek has a cat named Spot.
Let it be officially declared that without knowledge of Data&amp;rsquo;s cat, I named my cat Spot when I got him 3 or 4 years ago.
My friend Laura brought to my attention the situation of the unofficial cat named Spot when she saw the journal entry from April 9th.
She sent me a link which I will post here pending the site owner&amp;rsquo;s permission.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>