<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>puzzles on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/puzzles/</link>
    <description>Recent content in puzzles on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2017 18:17:21 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/puzzles/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>bought some puzzles</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/16/bought-some-puzzles/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2017 18:17:21 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/16/bought-some-puzzles/</guid>
      <description>18:17 Saturday 16 December 2017 I bought five puzzles today after seeing some that I had had as a kid. The woman at the shop suggested four as being difficult, and I selected a fifth one because I liked its design.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>toy store</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/12/08/toy-store/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2015 18:17:29 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/12/08/toy-store/</guid>
      <description>18:17 Tuesday 08 December 2015 JST Each week for the past few weeks I have solved the Rubick&amp;rsquo;s Pyramid (it&amp;rsquo;s very easy), and relinked the rings for any unlink ring-link puzzles. Today I also solved the pyramid-shaped wooden puzzle. The pieces don&amp;rsquo;t &amp;ldquo;link&amp;rdquo; at all, so its challenge is basically something like each piece looks like it could be a corner piece.
They&amp;rsquo;ve got a lot of Christmas themed items which are more decorative than interesting for me, but blah I guess it&amp;rsquo;s about to be Christmas in some places, so fine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Toy store has new puzzles</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/10/06/toy-store-has-new-puzzles/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2015 18:34:01 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/10/06/toy-store-has-new-puzzles/</guid>
      <description>18:34 Tuesday 06 October 2015 JST The best new puzzle was a wooden chain like a bicycle chain except some of its links were fixed, as if they were rusty and wouldn&amp;rsquo;t rotate, except they were actually uncut pieces of wood. Apparently, it&amp;rsquo;s possible to arrange the chain on a tree shaped board so that all the links exactly cover the tree, including one at the bottom for the trunk.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tweaked the Zebra puzzle</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/08/23/tweaked-the-zebra-puzzle/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2015 17:35:40 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/08/23/tweaked-the-zebra-puzzle/</guid>
      <description>17:35 Sunday 23 August 2015 JST The Zebra Puzzle features brand names of unhealthy products, so I changed them into less-unhealthy food items. I haven&amp;rsquo;t tried to solve it yet, but here&amp;rsquo;s my tweaked version:
 There are five houses, nationalities, pets, favorite foods, and favorite drinks: The Englishman lives in the red house. The Spaniard owns the dog. Coffee is drunk in the green house. The Ukrainian drinks tea.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>