<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ultimate on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/ultimate/</link>
    <description>Recent content in ultimate on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2019 14:14:37 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/ultimate/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Great SOGO and ultimate</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/06/16/great-sogo-and-ultimate/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2019 14:14:37 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/06/16/great-sogo-and-ultimate/</guid>
      <description>14:14 Sunday 16 June 2019 JST Fun in the sun today at SOGO Bootcamp. We had to adjust our normal workout area due to puddles, but all good and lots of fun. I remet Anuj, Valeria, Lisa, Alex, Ben. Got to see Haruo and Jim again as they led ultimate frisbee after bootcamp.
We played until about 1:18pm with about 6 on 6 down to 4 on 4 as people had to go.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>bought three discs</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/09/12/bought-three-discs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2016 13:38:16 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/09/12/bought-three-discs/</guid>
      <description>13:38 Monday 12 September 2016 JST Played ultimate with an Aerobee yesterday with Suns Out Guns Out. It was challenging to control, but fun even so. Even so, I bought three ultimate discs from Club Jr. I&amp;rsquo;ll bring them out one at a time until they&amp;rsquo;re too old to use.
Two weeks ago, my Y2K compliant disc cracked. Boo. It didn&amp;rsquo;t get used all its life, but it had a long life: 16+ years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ultimate</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/05/31/ultimate/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/05/31/ultimate/</guid>
      <description>Ultimate 10:33pm CDT Wednesday 31 May 2000
Ultimate was great fun tonight! I&amp;rsquo;m super pleased that for the second week in a row, Wende came out to watch me play! She even bought a collapsable chair so that she may enjoy watching for longer without sitting on the ground or standing the whole time.
My game was great - I had a few great catches, including a couple tall jumping catches that I would not have made in recent history.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ultimate</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/05/13/ultimate/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 May 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/05/13/ultimate/</guid>
      <description>Ultimate 2:02pm CDT Saturday 13 May 2000
Great ultimate game today. The field made play a bit tricky; the grass was wet, but the ground was all hard and full of cleat-ruts. Some suggested it was like broken concrete covered in ice.
When play began, each team only had 6 players. Then at the same moment, each team had 1 more player arrive. Seven players on the field is the norm, so we all played and neither team had subs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ultimate</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/05/10/ultimate/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/05/10/ultimate/</guid>
      <description>Ultimate (not) 9:16pm CDT Wednesday 10 May 2000
Frickken fracking fckfckfckfck grrrrrrrrr
I forgot about Ultimate tonight!!
I got off work all early and had plenty of time to do stuff and then Wende went to eat dinner with some of her homies and I got stuck on the computer and forgot about ultimate. DOHH!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!
SHe&amp;rsquo;s about to be back in a second and I tried to call her cell phone to get an ETA.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ultimate</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/05/03/ultimate/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/05/03/ultimate/</guid>
      <description>10pm Wednesday 3 May 2000
Ultimate was great fun tonight! The field was all mushy from the rain, causing me to slip a few times and fall a couple times. One fall was a lovely slide and catch, slathering water/mud all up my leg and shorts and everything.
The stickers in the field were a bit worse tonight than previous nights. I told Kat that I wasn&amp;rsquo;t sure if my feet are getting wussy, or if the stickers are tougher or if the rain has any effect.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ultimate</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/04/30/ultimate/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/04/30/ultimate/</guid>
      <description>12:51am CDT Sunday 30 April 2000
Just finished my shower after ultimate tonight. Got about 14 pics from the game, but I don&amp;rsquo;t necessarily expect them to all develop well. Meek took most of the pics tonight.
We played another game of Over 25 -vs- Under 25 and again, the Over 25 team won. (25 = 25 years old) Then we played a normal game and my team lost. Still did quite well, but we lost 9-7.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PPultimate</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/04/22/ppultimate/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/04/22/ppultimate/</guid>
      <description>Ultimate! 12:40pm CDT Saturday 22 April 2000
(written pre-phone)
(we are still without a dail tone)
Ultimate was alright today but not great. I had 1 great defensive play, 1 great catch (for a point), 1 great miss-the-disc smackola right below my nose, 1 all-out run leaping for the disc miss and tumble, bumping my head on the ground.
But Dave was grouchier today than previous days. He&amp;rsquo;s usually hard on himself when he misses a catch or throw, but today he was yelling at lots of people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ultimate</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/04/08/ultimate/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/04/08/ultimate/</guid>
      <description>Ultimate!! 11:55am CDT Saturday 8 April 2000
I caught two points in our ultimate game today! This is pretty great because I don&amp;rsquo;t get much disc handling on this team. One point was &amp;lsquo;pushed&amp;rsquo; to me (that means there was essentially no spin on the disc (that means the disc was not spinning) which made it wobbly) and I actually caught it easily. The other point was zinged in toward me and I had to reach one hand out to grab it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ultimate</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/03/29/ultimate/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/03/29/ultimate/</guid>
      <description>Ultimate! 6:55am CST Thursday 30 March 2000
Last night ultimate was a little bit wacky. We played at 6:30 to 8:30; someone else had reserved the field during our preferred timeslot of 8:30 to 10:30.
When we arrived on the field, about 30 people were enagaged in softball practice as the season is apparently gearing up. We told them we had reserved the field, so they shrunk their practice to the infield only.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ultimate</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/03/25/ultimate/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/03/25/ultimate/</guid>
      <description>1:04pm CST Saturday 25 March 2000
Ultimate was great fun today; our team won! Barely barely we won.. We had an 8 to 4 lead at one point, and won 10 to 9. The game had to be cut a bit short because it was taking so long for us to get points. Normal game is to 13.
During the game, I skinned my knee, made a couple of good throws, and a couple of not good misses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>centex</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/03/17/centex/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/03/17/centex/</guid>
      <description>Ultimate!! 6:22am CST Friday 17 March 2000
I don&amp;rsquo;t have a ride to Austin yet tonight, but in a way this is a relief; I don&amp;rsquo;t really feel that I have the time to go. I am still slowly working on cleaning up my apartment! It&amp;rsquo;s a meditative process, cleaning- after 10.5 years here, there&amp;rsquo;s lots of memories and stuff.
In some ways, I&amp;rsquo;m ready to let stuff go and begin anew.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ultimate Unicycle</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/02/17/ultimate-unicycle/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/02/17/ultimate-unicycle/</guid>
      <description>Ultimate and Unicycling 1:57am CST Thursday 17 February 2000
Ultimate was great fun tonight! Now I know how some of the guys (John) who play Saturday night have gotten so much better! On Wednesdays the field is huge and everyone runs! The structure of play is different, too: instead of playing a game to a certain number of points, we just play one point at a time. We maintain 7 or 8 people on each team, and as people get tired of play, they swap with people on the sidelines.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ultimate</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/02/12/ultimate/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/02/12/ultimate/</guid>
      <description>Ultimate 2:04am CST Sunday 13 February 2000
Just finished taking a shower after playing Ultimate. I play barefoot, so they call me Wonderboy on the field. This also means that when I shower, large muddy streams flow from my feet to the drain. Kinda fun for the 5 year old in me. I&amp;rsquo;m all clean now, though.
I got a surprising email recently from a woman named Dreama. She was doing genealogical research, looking for the middle name of her GGGrandfather.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ultimate</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1999/12/19/ultimate/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Dec 1999 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1999/12/19/ultimate/</guid>
      <description>2:34am Sunday 19 December 1999
Today at work, with significant help from David and Brian, we got all our DSL related problems solved, except we still can&amp;rsquo;t send email. Brian believes it&amp;rsquo;s cause our ISP didn&amp;rsquo;t set up our reverse-DNS-lookup tables. We can ask for the IP address of a machine name, but not for the machine name of one of our IP addresses.
Then I helped Liz at Blankets To You get set up on a new ISP.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ultimate population</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1999/10/10/ultimate-population/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Oct 1999 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1999/10/10/ultimate-population/</guid>
      <description>1:55am Sunday 10 october 1999
Tonight Ultimate was great fun. I played three games (lost two) and made some good catch attempts.
One was a wacked out tall throw that put me near the fence and a bench (with Kristen on it) and I went sky for the disc, and had both hands on it, but they weren&amp;rsquo;t together so it flipped out of my grasp. doh! I landed and scraped my arm on concrete (where the old benches were), but didn&amp;rsquo;t stop at all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ultimate catch</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1999/10/04/ultimate-catch/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Oct 1999 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1999/10/04/ultimate-catch/</guid>
      <description>4 October 1999
On Saturday night I played Ultimate with the guys at UH.
This is the third week in a row I&amp;rsquo;ve been back playing with them and I&amp;rsquo;m loving it! I used to play all the time back in 1993 and 1994 and into 1995 and maybe even a tad beyond that. I&amp;rsquo;d like to be a more regular player for some time to come.
For more info on this group, see McLeod&amp;rsquo;s Ultimate Frisbee Page, or Rod Meek&amp;rsquo;s SNS Ultimate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ktru ultimate</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1999/04/08/ktru-ultimate/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Apr 1999 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1999/04/08/ktru-ultimate/</guid>
      <description>7:12pm Thursday 8 April 1999
Aw man, first, super duper special thanks to Wende for reminding me last night that today is Thursday and I was supposed to work at KTRU!!!! I had totally forgotten it, and she mentioned it offhandedly (whatever that is supposed to mean) and I was like, &amp;ldquo;!!!!!!!!!&amp;rdquo;
Wende and I had just eaten at Dude and Veronica&amp;rsquo;s house and it was gettin&amp;rsquo; late. We still had to go to Sterling McCall to get Scott after he had his timing belt and water pump replaced.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>centex pics</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/03/22/centex-pics/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Mar 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/03/22/centex-pics/</guid>
      <description>These are stillshots taken from Tim&#39;s video of our ultimate tournament in Austin.  (update 2003 July: I can&#39;t find the pics)
   An unecessary close-up of our Mascott, Jo Boo!     Tim wrote:
 a picture of Cog strutting for the camera during warm-up. Notice how he warms up vs. how Sean warms up [in the background skying for a catch] and look at the results [also notice how i warm up behind the camera!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>centex rod</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/03/22/centex-rod/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Mar 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/03/22/centex-rod/</guid>
      <description>Centex according to Rod
Sunday 22 March 1998
 Written by Rod Meek  And so our team has returned from the Centex Ultimate Tournament in Austin, flushed with...uh...defeat. The Saturday Night Specials have now been renamed the Saturday Night Special Olympics, and our entry fee was picked up by our &#34;opponents&#34; (though that word implies a reasonably even contest) who were glad to earn cheap victories at our expense. We lost three on Saturday and then another in single-elimination in the consolation (read: &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ultimate!</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1997/10/18/ultimate/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 1997 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1997/10/18/ultimate/</guid>
      <description>3AM Sunday 19 October 1997
 Ultimate was super fun tonight. Cold dew on long grass froze my toes unless I kept running, dancing around all night (or stayed out of the grass). I played fairly well all night, scoring a few points and making a couple great catches, sliding, tumbling, and/or jump-thudding* to catch the disc. My teams lost the first two games we played, then I think won the second two.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ultimate!</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1997/10/05/ultimate/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 1997 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1997/10/05/ultimate/</guid>
      <description>5 October 1997
 Last night I played Ultimate at University of Houston as we do each Saturday night. Ultimate is the best frisbee game in the world, for those who don&amp;rsquo;t know.  The coolest thing lately is that a lot of new players (incoming freshman who live in the residence halls) have joined us this year. And they&amp;rsquo;re all good; some of them play super excellently!  HellKat, Mike, Jenny (sp), Rick, John, and Terry arrived (in that order) to play.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>