<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>work on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/work/</link>
    <description>Recent content in work on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2019 21:16:44 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/work/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Fun last lesson before vacation</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/10/02/fun-last-lesson-before-vacation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2019 21:16:44 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/10/02/fun-last-lesson-before-vacation/</guid>
      <description>Hide and Akiko from 7pm class each needed to make up some lessons, so stayed for the 8pm class featuring Misato and Tatsuya.
I think it worked pretty well; they had not met each other, and they are all pretty much similar personalities so I figured they would get along fine.
After self intros, most of the time they talked about Akiko&amp;rsquo;s challenging business trip to Hydrabad, India. Most of the rest of the time we talked about Hide&amp;rsquo;s work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>got AB webserver upgraded</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/09/24/got-ab-webserver-upgraded/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2019 17:37:10 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/09/24/got-ab-webserver-upgraded/</guid>
      <description>I got AB&amp;rsquo;s server upgraded from unsupported Ubuntu 12 to Ubuntu 18. Now running PHP 7 instead of unsupported 5.6 Now running RDS instead of MySQL on EC2.
Not yet running ALB, but AWS tech team is looking into why the application was sometimes throwing 502 errors when I routed requests through ALB.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working today</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/09/18/working-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2019 21:32:49 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/09/18/working-today/</guid>
      <description>(written 21:32 Wednesday 18 September 2019 JST)
Headed toward home on Nambu Line now after waking up at 4:30 (after one sleep cycle) and doing my morning routine (write dreams, write gratitude, meditate, brush teeth, etc) then headed to work in Kawasaki for JB in Solid Square. Sayuri came about 15 minutes late and was the only student in attendance.
Headed to JR Kawasaki afterward to meet やなさん but he ended up having to cancel for some reason.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>class no-show at JB School</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/09/11/class-no-show-at-jb-school/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 18:39:40 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/09/11/class-no-show-at-jb-school/</guid>
      <description>No students in my 6pm class here. And my most-common student in next lesson has called in that he will not attend. I&amp;rsquo;m gonna use this time to write a bit.
I had been planning to talk to them about WTC 7 and stuff on the anniversary of Airplane Day.
19:39 No students in my 7pm class&amp;hellip;
20:00 One student in 8pm class.
We started the lesson talking about the typhoon and her plans to practice piano next Sunday for a rehearsal on September 22nd.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Got email working on AB test server</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/09/09/got-email-working-on-ab-test-server/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2019 19:52:33 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/09/09/got-email-working-on-ab-test-server/</guid>
      <description>(written 19:52 Wednesday 11 September 2019 JST)
On Monday I got email working with AWS SES. It was pretty much plug-n-play level of easy since I already had a site set up that had been using PHPMailer.
But eff me I could not figure out what was different from the setup on our old server which was sending emails from itself using Exim no problem.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Early morning snooze before work</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/09/04/early-morning-snooze-before-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2019 07:50:24 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/09/04/early-morning-snooze-before-work/</guid>
      <description>I slept on 南武 line from 登戸 to 川崎 station today. Nice to get a 57 minute sleep on a 30 minute trip. (The train sits in Noborito for 27 minutes before departing.)
Early morning lessons on Wednesday are back after the summer break. I&amp;rsquo;ve been teaching here for some years, &amp;ldquo;wouldn&amp;rsquo;t mind&amp;rdquo; if the lessons were taken over by someone else.
&amp;ldquo;Wouldn&amp;rsquo;t mind&amp;rdquo; in quotes because that was the phrase Eriko doublechecked with me to be true regarding the lesson.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>today</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/08/30/today/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 16:45:26 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/08/30/today/</guid>
      <description>16:45 Friday 30 August 2019 JST Several different things on my day off today. Mostly related to work, where I realized the value of having a staging server with non-live data. &amp;ldquo;Ohhh that is right; I tested saving data as well..&amp;rdquo; when AB was like, &amp;ldquo;Um, where is the Azabujuban record?&amp;rdquo; which had been renamed to &amp;ldquo;Doraemon 5e5433a38e2b035689a75c9ed11ffb0e&amp;rdquo;
Once I fixed all of those (about 8 different records) based on the old live DB which is still available at cli with mysql as root, I watched episode 3 of The Naked Director.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AB RDS AZ</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/08/29/ab-rds-az/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 13:17:38 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/08/29/ab-rds-az/</guid>
      <description>13:17 Thursday 29 August 2019 JST I got AB&amp;rsquo;s DB on RDS, but had it in a different AZ than the server (oops) which caused some slowness that AB noticed. I turned on Multi-AZ and rebooted the RDS instance with &amp;ldquo;failover&amp;rdquo; selected and now AB&amp;rsquo;s RDS in AB&amp;rsquo;s EC2&amp;rsquo;s AZ makes it noticably faster. Yay!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>worked at SCC</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/07/18/worked-at-scc/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2019 16:58:39 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/07/18/worked-at-scc/</guid>
      <description>16:58 Thursday 18 July 2019 JST Today Naoko worked on introducing the history zone, including teacup carrying dolls, perpetual clock, and the early days of electricity in Japan.
What was it like back in the day when a simple thing like a few candle power light bulb could be so impressive?
Yasu talked about the Meissner effect and flux pinning. I would like to do an experiment.. will the Meissner effect keep a thing suspended above the magnetic table or is that only do to flux pinning?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>lesson in Akihabara</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/07/11/lesson-in-akihabara/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2019 19:51:55 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/07/11/lesson-in-akihabara/</guid>
      <description>19:51 Thursday 11 July 2019 JST Today there were only 1.5 students in my Akihabara class. This number is down from our high of like 8 last year when I had to stop checking homework during the lesson because there ended up being no time for class. I guess there would be time with just 2 students&amp;rsquo; worth of homework.
Anyway, the lesson kinda devolved into a China vs Japan debate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>lessons at SCC</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/07/11/lessons-at-scc/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2019 16:58:41 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/07/11/lessons-at-scc/</guid>
      <description>16:58 Thursday 11 July 2019 JST Interesting to talk about the Meisner effect and flux pinning at SCC today. I have always assumed I understand the meaning based on the English presentation, but I felt a bit unsure when I was breaking it down in detail for Yasu as he was practicing his explanation of the same.
My understanding: when a superconductor is below its critical temperature it pushes (almost) all magnetic flux out of itself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>longer than ya think</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/07/03/longer-than-ya-think/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2019 18:35:39 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/07/03/longer-than-ya-think/</guid>
      <description>18:35 Wednesday 03 July 2019 JST Today I wanted to write an email to AB as a status update on the upgrade I am doing for them. The update has been taking longer than expected, both in terms of the amount of work required and the amount of time I have not been able to spend on it.
To write the email, I wanted to make sure my plan will work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>super tired</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/07/02/super-tired/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2019 00:03:26 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/07/02/super-tired/</guid>
      <description>00:03 Tuesday 02 July 2019 JST Well, I missed the first day of the month by 3 minutes. I have been zoned out in front of my computer longer than 3 minutes so oh well.
Logged 6 hours of work and noticed how much longer it will take. At 10 minutes per line, and 400 more lines to change that&amp;rsquo;s 4000 minutes (hopefully max!), but that is just to get rid of a single singleton.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fun 3rd of 4th lesson at BP</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/06/21/fun-3rd-of-4th-lesson-at-bp/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2019 00:03:56 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/06/21/fun-3rd-of-4th-lesson-at-bp/</guid>
      <description>00:03 Friday 21 June 2019 JST JB got me 8 hours of lessons at BP over the 4 Thursdays in June. This was the 3rd lesson, during which we practiced taking taxis, ordering in a restaurant, and something else.
Yoko M wasn&amp;rsquo;t there, but she will be back next week. Yoko N volunteered a couple of times to go first!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I got a seat on the train</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/06/17/i-got-a-seat-on-the-train/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2019 06:17:53 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/06/17/i-got-a-seat-on-the-train/</guid>
      <description>06:17 Monday 17 June 2019 JST I got a seat on my preferred train. I arrived in just enough time, though it&amp;rsquo;s reasonable to say I could have ridden more slowly to be safer (down the big-ass whooo-hooo hill).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Headed to see my Babychan</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/05/09/headed-to-see-my-babychan/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2019 20:20:30 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/05/09/headed-to-see-my-babychan/</guid>
      <description>20:20 Thursday 09 May 2019 JST Lin said she had an &amp;ldquo;unbelievably hard day at work today&amp;rdquo; so I look forward to listening and hopefully helping her sort out her feelings on the whole thing. New job, new system, steep learning curve; I can relate!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>lesson in Akihabara</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/05/09/lesson-in-akihabara/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2019 20:18:11 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/05/09/lesson-in-akihabara/</guid>
      <description>20:18 Thursday 09 May 2019 JST Today I showed students in Akihabara the website and snippets for Marble Track 3. They were like &amp;ldquo;waow&amp;rdquo; etc. I love the project and felt a bit guilty for taking up a significant amount of class time with it. We have had lessons for years though, so I don&amp;rsquo;t think they will mind.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>great lessons at SCC</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/05/09/great-lessons-at-scc/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2019 17:19:56 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/05/09/great-lessons-at-scc/</guid>
      <description>17:19 Thursday 09 May 2019 JST Four lessons at SCC today. One was shorter than expected due to a (hopefully small) medical emergency. Third lesson on the third floor featured discussions of the other three lessons and hearing they students really enjoy my passion for the topics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Work at SCC</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/04/18/work-at-scc/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2019 20:34:39 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/04/18/work-at-scc/</guid>
      <description>20:34 Thursday 18 April 2019 JST Back at SCC today with four student for 30 minutes each. Hitomi came in for Lily, who could not come.
I bought Cast Arrows, a new Hanayama puzzle because I could not solve it in 20 minutes. (not that I can solve most of them in 20 minutes, but this one looked like I could solve it and then I was like &amp;ldquo;woah that&amp;rsquo;s not going to work?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>last lesson with Sweets Party Attendants</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/03/06/last-lesson-with-sweets-party-attendants/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2019 21:33:17 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/03/06/last-lesson-with-sweets-party-attendants/</guid>
      <description>21:33 Wednesday 06 March 2019 JST Today was the last lesson with Sweets Attendants. (Their office is being shut down at the end of this month, but I am leaving next week for three weeks overseas.)
I met Tomoko at CPK at 11am and helped her carry pizza to their office where we had a party, including candy I bought from the conveni ond 3F.
The party was fun, but afterward I unfortunately let myself get sidetracked into dealing with some work related Excel spreadsheet crap, but got it sorted out by moving the spreadsheet into Google Sheets, where I can use the =FILTER() function.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>lessons in Akiba</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/02/21/lessons-in-akiba/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Feb 2019 17:33:37 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/02/21/lessons-in-akiba/</guid>
      <description>17:33 Thursday 21 February 2019 JST Now I am headed to Akihabara for lesson with Mayumi and them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>lessons at SCC</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/02/21/lessons-at-scc/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Feb 2019 17:29:51 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/02/21/lessons-at-scc/</guid>
      <description>17:29 Thursday 21 February 2019 JST Today (and most Thursdays) I taught at SCC in Kawasaki. Naoko reviewed for her test next week. Yasu reviewed the same material for his test sometime in the future. Azusa did much better with her fluency and intonation for her presentation. Liliko asked about the brochure that has to change soon to accomodate new opening times.
After the lessons I went to say HI to Tomoko and Midori, but Midori had the day off.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>work is going faster with tests</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/02/18/work-is-going-faster-with-tests/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2019 10:23:20 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/02/18/work-is-going-faster-with-tests/</guid>
      <description>10:23 Monday 18 February 2019 JST Although I have not gotten all the way to the part of MLAPHP that we are supposed to be adding tests, I am close enough that I can add some tests. They have helped a lot, like OMG how did I live without tests? It hasn&amp;rsquo;t been so long that I don&amp;rsquo;t remember what it was like, and I sure like this better.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>lessons today</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/02/13/lessons-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2019 21:30:48 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/02/13/lessons-today/</guid>
      <description>21:30 Wednesday 13 February 2019 JST In the first adult lesson at JB, we flexed some reported speech muscles with Side By Side book 1, where the target language is &amp;ldquo;This is a photograph of my son Bart. He is riding a skateboard outside our house.&amp;rdquo;
We changed it to be &amp;ldquo;This is a photograph of me riding a skateboard in from of my house&amp;rdquo; and then &amp;ldquo;That is a photograph of him riding a skateboard in from of his house.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Second to last lesson with Sweets Party Attendants</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/02/13/second-to-last-lesson-with-sweets-party-attendants/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2019 21:26:23 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/02/13/second-to-last-lesson-with-sweets-party-attendants/</guid>
      <description>21:26 Wednesday 13 February 2019 JST Sweets Party Attendants had their second to last lesson with me today. The mood was both somber and joyful; it has been great working with them over the years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>State of My Life Address</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/02/06/state-of-my-life-address/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2019 07:44:19 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/02/06/state-of-my-life-address/</guid>
      <description>07:44 Wednesday 06 February 2019 JST  Lin and I still have our cat Jennie, still keep her in at night, still live in Asao-ku near the bottom of a hill. I&amp;rsquo;m still working on Marble Track 3, trying to do at least 2 hours of livestream per week. I have been working on AB, getting tests added to cover the important parts of the codebase. I do not have a lot covered, but 10 tests is an order of magnitude more than 0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>crontab -e as root vs sudo crontab -e [solved]</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/01/21/crontab-e-as-root-vs-sudo-crontab-e-solved/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jan 2019 21:10:29 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/01/21/crontab-e-as-root-vs-sudo-crontab-e-solved/</guid>
      <description>21:10 Monday 21 January 2019 JST I had a weird issue with crontab today.
If I editted the crontab while logged in as root, it did not work.
$# whoami root $# crontab -e ((( make edits ))) crontab: installing new crontab  But the changes did not work.
$# exit $ whoami ubuntu sudo crontab -e ((( make edits ))) crontab: installing new crontab  And the changes work just fine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>life changing work</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/01/17/life-changing-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jan 2019 18:02:33 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/01/17/life-changing-work/</guid>
      <description>18:02 Thursday 17 January 2019 JST It has taken me a long time to reach this point, but from being afraid of men in 1997, I am now facilitating deep emotional work in men&amp;rsquo;s circles every week, both online and face to face in Tokyo.
I want to deepen my skills as a facilitator and have decided to step more fully into this emotional awareness work. To improve my facilitation skills, I plan to staff two (2) New Warrior Training Adventure weekends, back to back in March and April.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>work today</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/01/16/work-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2019 22:00:54 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/01/16/work-today/</guid>
      <description>22:00 Wednesday 16 January 2019 JST tired
8am - 9am Shukoh, then 4 hours of AB in internet cafe, TY called in the middle, then JB lessons from 3:30 to 9pm</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>work and prep work</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/01/10/work-and-prep-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2019 13:55:38 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/01/10/work-and-prep-work/</guid>
      <description>13:55 Thursday 10 January 2019 JST One of the AB cronjobs has been throwing errors, but the job is still running.
I am in the middle of refactoring the code to use Dependency Injection; I don&amp;rsquo;t know how I broke something, but I cannot really go back to a previous version. Rather, I don&amp;rsquo;t know what version to go back to, and my local dev environment cannot recreate the error.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>today workin</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/01/09/today-workin/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2019 20:42:35 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/01/09/today-workin/</guid>
      <description>20:42 Wednesday 09 January 2019 JST Today was a long day, starting with recording a first draft of a video for my first GoFundMe campaign, then two TY lessons, two MKP meetings, lunch with Tomoko, then an hour chillin with &amp;ldquo;a flower in each hand&amp;rdquo; behind the desk of the Sweets Party Attendants, having a non-lesson with them because they have nothing going on.
During this non-lesson, Tomoko showed me her &amp;ldquo;personal こたつ&amp;rdquo; which consisted of a heater under her desk and a blanket strategically arranged to drape down over her legs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>last Akihabara lesson this year</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/12/20/last-akihabara-lesson-this-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Dec 2018 20:22:58 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/12/20/last-akihabara-lesson-this-year/</guid>
      <description>20:22 Thursday 20 December 2018 JST We had our last lesson of the year in Akihabara today. This is also Toshie&amp;rsquo;s last lesson so we had a party in her honor with all her favorite snack foods.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Closing out 2018</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/12/19/closing-out-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Dec 2018 21:30:39 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/12/19/closing-out-2018/</guid>
      <description>21:30 Wednesday 19 December 2018 JST I am on the way home after my last 2018 lesson at JB. I thought we had lessons next week, but apparently not! I kinda sorta wish we did have to work next week; the monies would be nice, but I guess I can work on AB during that time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>today</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/12/05/today/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 21:58:04 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/12/05/today/</guid>
      <description>21:58 Wednesday 05 December 2018 JST Yikes I derped and did not do my task for TY. First time, but I will definitely not miss again.
JB classes were fun; we used fake money notes as money in the 4:30pm kids class (Suzu, Kanta, Toshiro), and then I used them again in 8pm adult class (Misato, Kaori).
Working on ConSwi now, refactoring to make pieces move themselves down, and get a ton of code out of the main Game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>today</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/11/29/today/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 17:24:13 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/11/29/today/</guid>
      <description>17:24 Thursday 29 November 2018 JST Just finished four lessons at SCC: Naoko, Liliko, Hitomi, and Yasu each had 30 minute lessons, practicing various parts of their presentations.
During the first two lessons, my nose was running like yuck. I used a bunch of toilet paper and tissues blowing all the snot out.
This morning I worked on MT3 for 1.5 hours or so, getting maybe 8 frames taken. At this point, I am working on version 2 of the website, which focuses on the characters making the track instead of me making the characters make the track.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Too busy</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/11/14/too-busy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 21:10:01 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/11/14/too-busy/</guid>
      <description>21:10 Wednesday 14 November 2018 JST I can basically tell how busy I am by how much time I (don&amp;rsquo;t) spend writing in my journal. Inverse relationship between entries and busy. It&amp;rsquo;s not surprising, but just a thing to note.
Recently, my &amp;ldquo;journaling&amp;rdquo; has included Marble Track 3 website, and that has included revamping the website a bit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AB site progress</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/11/07/ab-site-progress/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2018 22:03:48 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/11/07/ab-site-progress/</guid>
      <description>22:03 Wednesday 07 November 2018 JST I have been upgrading AB&amp;rsquo;s PHP to the standards described in Paul Jones&amp;rsquo; Modernizing Legacy Applications in PHP. So far I am still in the Autoloading section, but have done nearly half of the classes. Almost all of the &amp;ldquo;data&amp;rdquo; classes are done, but none of the search or factory classes are done.
(I put data in quotes above because I think that is just a name we came up with .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hanayama Marble at Wednesday morning lesson</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/10/31/hanayama-marble-at-wednesday-morning-lesson/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 09:16:11 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/10/31/hanayama-marble-at-wednesday-morning-lesson/</guid>
      <description>09:16 Wednesday 31 October 2018 JST The lessons I teach on Wednesday morning used to be on Thursday mornings. They were one of the first lessons I taught for JB. Pretty convenient when Lin and I lived near Kawasaki station, but now it takes over an hour to go each way for an hour lesson.
Once I win the lottery, this will be one of the first lessons I release because I have to leave the house by 5:45 to get a seat on the train on the way there (or leave by 6:15 and stand for 40 minutes total on (two) trains).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>worked on AB</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/10/30/worked-on-ab/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 17:37:58 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/10/30/worked-on-ab/</guid>
      <description>17:37 Tuesday 30 October 2018 JST Still going through MLAPHP for the AB project. I guess I am about halfway through the step of naming all the class definition files so they can be loaded via the autoloader.
During this process I found Mabl which features a short domain name and some tools for automated testing. Pretty easy onboarding, and they are giving the site a good onceover every day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>training ty</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/10/30/training-ty/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 17:35:40 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/10/30/training-ty/</guid>
      <description>17:35 Tuesday 30 October 2018 JST Helped with training at TY&amp;rsquo;s today. Onboarding new instructors is a learning process in itself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Confirmed no meeting</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/10/15/confirmed-no-meeting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2018 15:36:27 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/10/15/confirmed-no-meeting/</guid>
      <description>15:36 Monday 15 October 2018 JST I will work on MLAPHP AB instead.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mondays are early days</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/10/15/mondays-are-early-days/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2018 14:25:13 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/10/15/mondays-are-early-days/</guid>
      <description>14:25 Monday 15 October 2018 JST On Mondays for the past year or more, I have been waking up at 5am on Mondays to work at IL for an hour from 8am to 9am. Today we talked about the new fish market in Toyosu, and how at 40 hectares, it is 1.7 times larger than the fish market that was in Tsukiji (which I never visited during the fish auctions).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>too busy for me</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/10/11/too-busy-for-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2018 13:38:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/10/11/too-busy-for-me/</guid>
      <description>13:38 Thursday 11 October 2018 JST I did MT3 livestream today, but have not made time to add an episode.
I attended online men&amp;rsquo;s circle this morning, but was distracted with emails.
Kevin&amp;rsquo;s website is throwing memory errors, probably because old version of site needs upgrading. I contacted his provider about getting it upgraded.
I am on the train headed to SCC, but forgot to bring my tea cup so I probably have to use a paper cup (or go without tea).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>working at work</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/10/10/working-at-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2018 18:29:26 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/10/10/working-at-work/</guid>
      <description>18:29 Wednesday 10 October 2018 JST No students in my lesson today so I am glad I brought my computer so I can do some work for AB. I am continuing with the Modernization of my Legacy PHP application based on the book described at https://mlaphp.com
Modernize Your Legacy PHP Application Get your code under control in a series of small, specific steps. by Paul M. Jones  In addition to simplifying the code, it has given me a refresher on what I wrote!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>productent</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/10/09/productent/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2018 23:25:22 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/10/09/productent/</guid>
      <description>23:25 Tuesday 09 October 2018 JST Today wasn&amp;rsquo;t as productive as I had planned, but I got some good stuff done.
4:30am meeting with Boysen, and should have a landing page for The Men&amp;rsquo;s Work soon.
8:00am IL lesson in which we talked about Tsukiji and 2020 Olympics https://the-japan-news.com/news/article/0004879769
came home to work on MT3, but ended up just sleeping
7:00pm Tokyo Men&amp;rsquo;s Circle https://tokyo.mypowercircle.org/
8:06pm someone killed themselves in Seijogakuenmae (a station along my train line)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>learning PHP</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/10/07/learning-php/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Oct 2018 07:10:40 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/10/07/learning-php/</guid>
      <description>07:10 Sunday 07 October 2018 JST I have started going through Modernizing Legacy Applications in PHP for AB website, and now the database is loaded via an autoloader.
&amp;lt;?php /** * This file is part of &amp;quot;Modernizing Legacy Applications in PHP&amp;quot;. * * @copyright 2014-2016 Paul M. Jones &amp;lt;pmjones88@gmail.com&amp;gt; * @license https://opensource.org/licenses/bsd-license.php BSD */ /** * Autoloads classes. * */ namespace Mlaphp; class Autoloader { public function load($class) { // strip off any leading namespace separator from PHP 5.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>met with Paul about The Men&#39;s Work</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/10/05/met-with-paul-about-the-mens-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 19:53:05 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/10/05/met-with-paul-about-the-mens-work/</guid>
      <description>19:53 Friday 05 October 2018 JST Exciting MKP Tokyo news!
I sent this to my online Integration Group.
I just got confirmation: I will be co-facilitating a 3-week online MKP introduction called The Men&#39;s Work https://mkpusa.org/themenswork/ with Paul Newell, who is currently co-facilitating it in the US. On Fridays, 7pm - 8:30pm (Japan time), November 3rd, 10th, and 17th, we will do this online training for men in Tokyo. Once we run this 3 week series of meetings a couple of times, I will create a new men&#39;s circle in Gotanda (Tokyo) on Fridays for men who are interested.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>refactor</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/10/05/refactor/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 08:27:57 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/10/05/refactor/</guid>
      <description>08:27 Friday 05 October 2018 JST I found a solution to all my work woes.
I just had an interesting thought about my computer job, which I brought up in the meeting on Monday. My website client is AB. It is likely that I can find a company that can do the work I am doing for less money, but it&#39;s not possible to secretly act as a middle man and keep the money due to how payments are done now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>progress on multiple fronts</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/09/22/progress-on-multiple-fronts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Sep 2018 21:12:36 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/09/22/progress-on-multiple-fronts/</guid>
      <description>21:12 Saturday 22 September 2018 JST BH set up a Slack space for MKP Japan where we can discuss creating the organization and setting up some trainings.
I got a multi-month fix done for AB; now users can use the same filter on their custom list page as they can on the main list. I don&amp;rsquo;t recall why it was set up this weird way before, but it is better now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>wednesday</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/09/19/wednesday/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2018 23:05:30 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/09/19/wednesday/</guid>
      <description>23:05 Wednesday 19 September 2018 JST (written 14:06 Thursday 20 September 2018 JST)
Wednesdays are usually long for me. Wake up at 5am (after getting home no earlier than 10:30pm after men&amp;rsquo;s group, but Tuesday night I went to The Pink Cow (great to see Traci after I have been away so long!) for an event for hemp oil that Rohini invited me to attend.
Anyway, got home Tuesday night at like 1:15am to find Lin sleeping on the couch and then showered so had 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>morning lessons</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/09/18/morning-lessons/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 12:19:03 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/09/18/morning-lessons/</guid>
      <description>12:19 Tuesday 18 September 2018 JST Good lesson this morning with just two students. We talked about rental おっさん in Japan. Interesting concept of renting old men because they are older and presumably wiser. They? We?
Walked with Tariq from Akabanebashi to Shibashi while we talked about future plans for our swipe game. He found a designer who can create excellent graphics.
Did not end up needing my computer, but I have my rolly bag so no worries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>egad working all day on AB</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/08/25/egad-working-all-day-on-ab/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Aug 2018 23:02:46 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/08/25/egad-working-all-day-on-ab/</guid>
      <description>23:02 Saturday 25 August 2018 JST I hope I can get paid for this scope creep.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>lesson via phone</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/08/12/lesson-via-phone/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Aug 2018 20:16:12 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/08/12/lesson-via-phone/</guid>
      <description>20:16 Sunday 12 August 2018 JST Today Lin and I are at her sister&amp;rsquo;s house, but they do not have strong wifi so I cannot use Skype. At least not in this quiet room. Maybe that is why it&amp;rsquo;s quiet haha.
I do not have unlimited data on my phone, but I do have unlimited calling, so I am doing a lesson via phone instead of Skype.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>headed to work</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/08/08/headed-to-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Aug 2018 13:00:33 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/08/08/headed-to-work/</guid>
      <description>13:00 Wednesday 08 August 2018 JST Headed to JB now soon; hopefully no big concern from the typhoon. I will bring my rain coat, but I ain&amp;rsquo;t too worried.
21:35 Wednesday 08 August 2018 JST The typhoon has been like a typhoon for ants.
But my train is nearly empty because apparently nobody came to work. Or at least everyone left work early.
I&amp;rsquo;m just finishing work and heading home now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>moe joe work</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/07/16/moe-joe-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2018 22:39:03 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/07/16/moe-joe-work/</guid>
      <description>22:39 Monday 16 July 2018 JST Bah. I&amp;rsquo;ve been working for like 12 or 16 hours trying to figure out how to keep a button visible, but I cannot figure out this spaghetti of code, domains, css, and browsers to figure out what is hiding it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>tired after long day</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/06/18/tired-after-long-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jun 2018 22:44:31 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/06/18/tired-after-long-day/</guid>
      <description>22:44 Monday 18 June 2018 JST 5am woke up. Home just a bit ago.
Tired long day.
IL Lesson
Wendy&amp;rsquo;s Wild Rock and Happy Dad&amp;rsquo;s day with Dad and Fred and Saundra on the line.
UG Lesson
Saizeria for lunch
ooops no cash. wrote my name and number; went to the bank; came back and paid.
Hung out with cats until time for co-gender circle.
Co-gender circle. 3 people in attendance, including me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>work and work</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/06/13/work-and-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jun 2018 21:34:20 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/06/13/work-and-work/</guid>
      <description>21:34 Wednesday 13 June 2018 JST Been working too much recently, but not enough to trigger carpal tunnel issues again, fortunately.
Today for AB I nearly finished a report that AB wants to have available. I thought I could finish in 2 hours, but it has taken 6.5 so far. fack. I will tell them it has taken longer.
Today for JB I did my normal Wednesday schedule (Solid Square with Ayano and them, then two kid lessons and two adult lessons in JB office from 15:30 - 21:00).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>work</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/06/06/work/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2018 21:33:07 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/06/06/work/</guid>
      <description>21:33 Wednesday 06 June 2018 JST I worked for JB at three different locations around Kawasaki Station today, as I do every Wednesday, at Solid Square, SSC, and JB main office. Solid Square lesson went pretty well; we drew mind maps of our favorite places and then said a few sentences about them. Then I had a break during which I Marco Poloed with Richard from ae911truth a bit and then worked on AB, nearly finishing this ticket since it received a bit higher priority at our last meeting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>(teaching) today</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/05/30/teaching-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 May 2018 23:03:40 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/05/30/teaching-today/</guid>
      <description>23:03 Wednesday 30 May 2018 JST On Wednesdays, I wake up at 5am and leave the house at 5:45am so I can get on a train that arrives in Noborito at 6:29am but leaves Noborito at 6:57am. That gives 58 minutes of sleeping time on the train including both waiting and riding to Kawasaki.
Then lesson in Solid Square with Ayano, Takato, Yohei, Ai, and I talking about reasons we (dis)like certain months or seasons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>All day in park</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/05/20/all-day-in-park/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 May 2018 21:57:19 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/05/20/all-day-in-park/</guid>
      <description>21:57 Sunday 20 May 2018 JST Great day at a park, but there were briars in the grass. Got to talk to Aaron for quite a bit and catch up with Francine who invited him. My student Misato attended and joined our little outing to find a nearby geocache which she was actually the one to find.
I napped for 30 minutes in the tent that went largely unused.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>worked on AB</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/28/worked-on-ab/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Apr 2018 20:35:11 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/28/worked-on-ab/</guid>
      <description>20:35 Saturday 28 April 2018 JST Good some good shiz done for AB today. Ran a DB update last night, and this evening added some calculated fields to a page. That was easy enough, but adding them to the output reports will take a bit more time to figure out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>worked with Mitsue on getting my sheet done</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/28/worked-with-mitsue-on-getting-my-sheet-done/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Apr 2018 20:33:08 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/28/worked-with-mitsue-on-getting-my-sheet-done/</guid>
      <description>20:33 Saturday 28 April 2018 JST Got some good sheet done on my speaker bio sheet from Soness&amp;rsquo;s course Build Your Speaker Bio and Media Sheet. Thank you Mitsue for your help!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Got some AB done today</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/26/got-some-ab-done-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 22:38:42 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/26/got-some-ab-done-today/</guid>
      <description>18:18 Thursday 26 April 2018 JST 22:39 Thursday 26 April 2018 JST haha I forgot to write anything.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>working on mobile app</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/26/working-on-mobile-app/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 10:44:13 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/26/working-on-mobile-app/</guid>
      <description>10:44 Thursday 26 April 2018 JST Woke up early to come out to Kawasaki so I could meet with Oriane, Cyber Knights, and Court of Support before meeting Tariq at 11:30.
We&amp;rsquo;ll have a good chunk of time (per my schedule) though I do not know how much time he will have.
I plan to get some app stuff or AB done today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>got 3.5 hours of work done today</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/25/got-3.5-hours-of-work-done-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 18:41:15 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/25/got-3.5-hours-of-work-done-today/</guid>
      <description>18:41 Wednesday 25 April 2018 JST World record for me recently. Not counting 6 hours of lessons, of course.
06:31 Thursday 26 April 2018 JST And then an hour last night, even after getting home and Talking with Lin for a bit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>good lesson before holidays</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/23/good-lesson-before-holidays/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Apr 2018 09:57:28 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/23/good-lesson-before-holidays/</guid>
      <description>09:57 Monday 23 April 2018 JST Good lesson at IL this morning, though only two students attended. I praised the student who came 35 minutes late to thank her for attending even though it was apparently a challenge to join.
Next week&amp;rsquo;s lesson is canceled due to a week of holidays, so on May 7th, I will invite them to talk about their holidays in English.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>easy lessons</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/18/easy-lessons/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2018 17:37:46 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/18/easy-lessons/</guid>
      <description>17:37 Wednesday 18 April 2018 JST Easy lessons today because Patrick was out. After combining the 4:30 classes, we played a game with target language &amp;ldquo;May I have a card, please?,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m ＿＿＿＿-ing,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;We&amp;rsquo;re ＿＿＿＿-ing,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Hey ＿＿＿＿, let&amp;rsquo;s go ＿＿＿-ing,&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Sorry I can&amp;rsquo;t. I&amp;rsquo;m busy.&amp;rdquo;
Matt is also out today, so I&amp;rsquo;ll teach his 6pm lesson.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>today</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/18/today/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2018 10:22:13 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/18/today/</guid>
      <description>10:22 Wednesday 18 April 2018 JST New regular students in SS lesson this morning; Kaede stopped coming relatively soon after joining last year, and Chika apparently took my bitcoin advice (whereas I did not haha) so she moved overseas. Satoshi has not come recently, and Sayuri said she was busy today, plus said Ayano something something so could not come. Nonoka and Ai came today. Ai helped Nonoka with some phrases and months of the year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>technical debt</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/13/technical-debt/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Apr 2018 16:37:48 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/13/technical-debt/</guid>
      <description>16:37 Friday 13 April 2018 JST I gotta figure out how to make the AB project go more smoothly.
 one: The system was designed to work with Customers logging in to the frontend, and Admin logging into the backend. two: A couple years ago, Admin asked if there is a way for SuperCustomers to log into the front end. three: I had to adjust the way people log into the site to allow them to be either Customers or SuperCustomers four: On the backend, I adjusted the way Inquiries were created because Customers and SuperCustomers will both need Inquiries five: Now I need to adjust the way Sets are created (Redmine ticket 3167) and I thought it would take 2 hours six: Oh crap it is taking way more than 2 hours to do correctly, because it affects how Customers are created, which is new, due to step 3  Fortunately, Nate understands, but it will take a while to do much about it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>last lesson this session</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/09/last-lesson-this-session/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2018 14:21:38 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/09/last-lesson-this-session/</guid>
      <description>14:21 Monday 09 April 2018 JST Today was the last lesson for Ushigoro. We had finished up everything last week, having done their exams, so today we just did lots of Q and A sessions, first with the class split into two groups, and then with all students asking questions of one student.
I offered my LINE QR code in case they want to ask questions or continue practicing their English.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>super sidetracked</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/30/super-sidetracked/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2018 12:54:56 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/30/super-sidetracked/</guid>
      <description>12:54 Friday 30 March 2018 JST Actually have gotten three (3) meetings done online: Prentiss and Ari helped with Mankind Project Tokyo; Ari said he will write some stuff for either Mankind Project Tokyo Meetup or My Power Circle. Oriane and I checked in with each other on our respective projects.
Planning to ask which inkan I can use for my personal seal today; maybe I will go do that now on my way to work at TY.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>work</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/22/work/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2018 13:31:04 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/22/work/</guid>
      <description>13:31 Thursday 22 March 2018 JST Right now I am in a coffee shop in Lazona, and about to go to SCC lessons for 3 hours, and then GG lesson for 1 hour.
18:02 Thursday 22 March 2018 JST Tears were apparently shed by one of the students at SCC; she is scheduled to present tomorrow and found out today that her presentation is going to be different than what she expected/practiced for.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting https working on AB</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/19/getting-https-working-on-ab/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Mar 2018 15:43:36 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/19/getting-https-working-on-ab/</guid>
      <description>15:43 Monday 19 March 2018 JST Nice to see setting up SSL certificates for Apache 2 on Ubuntu is pretty easy. They even automagically set up a cron job to renew the certificate after two months. See /etc/cron.d/certbot
I had a problem for a minute because one .conf file had a domain and an alias in it. I ran certbot for the aliased domain and told it to go ahead and force https, but then that broke the main domain (which was the main domain) by forcing SSL and using the certificates for the test domain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>today</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/08/today/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Mar 2018 18:16:25 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/08/today/</guid>
      <description>18:16 Thursday 08 March 2018 JST Today I spent the morning setting up a test image upload page to see why I can&amp;rsquo;t get the main page to work via https.
Frustrating: the test page is working fine.
Working, I was distracted from online integration group, and then zoned to SCC and found out the manager is leaving soon.
Now in Akihabara about to go to GG lesson.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>trying to get SSL working on cloudfront (not solved)</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/02/trying-to-get-ssl-working-on-cloudfront-not-solved/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2018 15:24:27 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/02/trying-to-get-ssl-working-on-cloudfront-not-solved/</guid>
      <description>15:24 Friday 02 March 2018 JST We have an image server behind cloudfront. Cloudfront can serve everything via https when using its subdomain. But using our own domain with https isn&amp;rsquo;t as easy as I would like.
Running Lets Encrypt on the server, I get an error like the https request was not allowed.
So I created a certificate with AWS Certificate Manager and told Cloudfront to use it, but I do not see how to tell the server to use it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>on track to finish entire list</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/01/on-track-to-finish-entire-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Mar 2018 14:18:34 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/01/on-track-to-finish-entire-list/</guid>
      <description>14:18 Thursday 01 March 2018 JST I am on track to finish my todo list today on Complice. I got my AB work complete, though there is the possibility they will want one more change on it. I am prepared for work tomorrow and now just gotta write this journal entry, studying Japanese, work tonight, Japanese lesson tonight with Mel, ..
I watched episode 6(?) of Kakegurui. They did not have the subtitles added yet, but I could understand the overall meaning because the acting is so over-the-top, plus explained visually (given that it&amp;rsquo;s a tv show)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>work work work</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/02/28/work-work-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2018 18:36:47 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/02/28/work-work-work/</guid>
      <description>18:36 Wednesday 28 February 2018 JST I&amp;rsquo;m on break now at JB, listening to the other class, where the teacher&amp;rsquo;s Japanesey English always kinda bugs me. But the students seem happy and have been in the class for a long time.
This morning thinking about C who apparently took my investment advice before bitcoin blew up. She quit her job and is overseas now. hahahah nice!
Then working on AB, getting three alleged issues sorted.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workin late</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/02/24/workin-late/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2018 23:52:27 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/02/24/workin-late/</guid>
      <description>23:52 Saturday 24 February 2018 JST This is taking longer than I guessed, but I got some tangential stuff cleared up, including a hardcoded value whose welcome has expired.
&amp;quot;unit_id&amp;quot;, meet record-&amp;gt;id_field_name
In other news, I randomly saw and later chatted with Hana today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>work work work all day</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/02/23/work-work-work-all-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 22:47:27 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/02/23/work-work-work-all-day/</guid>
      <description>22:47 Friday 23 February 2018 JST Sigh. Worked on AB all morning and then they were essentially like &amp;ldquo;yeah we don&amp;rsquo;t like it. Go back to the version that didn&amp;rsquo;t function, but looked pretty.&amp;rdquo;
I don&amp;rsquo;t understand their priorities, but I switched it back.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>work day</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/02/13/work-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2018 16:21:31 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/02/13/work-day/</guid>
      <description>16:21 Tuesday 13 February 2018 JST Worked at IL for ist today, and then with CE for MR, and then talked to Chika at B for JB.
Now going to AB to talk to T and S-san.
Tired, I would rather go home.
Oh, but I got past the tween issue I had with Godot 3
Yay!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>headed to BRIDGE</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/02/06/headed-to-bridge/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2018 13:49:03 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/02/06/headed-to-bridge/</guid>
      <description>13:49 Tuesday 06 February 2018 JST This is the fourth to last lesson at BRIDGE. They started off strong, but then started to get busy quite quickly last summer. Two hours of lessons went down to 1 hour which sucked considering it took 3 hours round trip travel. But I kept at it. During December they cancelled January saying they will be too busy. So I had a nice break during January, during which they said the will end at the end of February.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>work</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/02/02/work/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 19:51:52 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/02/02/work/</guid>
      <description>19:51 Friday 02 February 2018 JST Yikes my previously-used JQuery CDN isn&amp;rsquo;t responding so I replaced it and now the main page of the site breaks. When did that start happening? What do I do? How do I find someone to take over this site? (that is my real question / I do not want to maintain it forever)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AB work</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/29/ab-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2018 17:23:51 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/29/ab-work/</guid>
      <description>17:23 Monday 29 January 2018 JST Had a good meeting with T at AB today. Nate got me the information I needed before the meeting and everything went well. Got them a new account set up and on Wednesday night I will transfer their server from our account to theirs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>headed to work at SCC</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/26/headed-to-work-at-scc/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2018 12:55:17 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/26/headed-to-work-at-scc/</guid>
      <description>12:55 Friday 26 January 2018 JST Three hours of lessons in SCC today; looking forward to it!
On the way there, I hope to figure out why my local version of mypowercircle.org will not compile with Hugo. bah. it was supposed to be easy!!
Ah. I had gotten stuck trying to add Japanese language version of the site, but never got it working. It&amp;rsquo;s better to just have an actual Japanese speaker make the Japanese site, so I cut out the Japanese content from the site and now it&amp;rsquo;s working again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>work</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/17/work/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2018 18:34:31 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/17/work/</guid>
      <description>18:34 Wednesday 17 January 2018 JST First three classes were fine today, though I have been asked to blow through a book super fast to let one class catch up with another class. I don&amp;rsquo;t think that&amp;rsquo;s how it works.
In other news, JB has a new owner, who seems nice enough that I can keep working here. Really curious as to how much they paid!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>work yesterday</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/16/work-yesterday/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2018 08:39:06 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/16/work-yesterday/</guid>
      <description>08:39 Tuesday 16 January 2018 JST I worked for four companies yesterday. First was my lesson in Akabanebashi for Tariq. Then walked to Nishi Azabu for MR Laboratories client (company DNE yet). Then walked across the Nishi Azabu intersection to a lesson for TESS. Then bus and train to Kawasaki for 2 hours of lessons at my favorite, SCC. Came home and had one more lesson for MR Laboratories.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>five hours of work at SCC</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/13/five-hours-of-work-at-scc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2018 02:33:31 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/13/five-hours-of-work-at-scc/</guid>
      <description>02:33 Saturday 13 January 2018 JST Today was the first time I worked five hours at SCC. Due to a schedule snafu, 1.5 hours with Liliko chatting about her trip to Sydney and my trip to OZ, then Rick and Morty and Lucifer. I didn&amp;rsquo;t think of Dirk Gently, but she considered getting Netflix to see the others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Akihabara for GG lesson</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/11/akihabara-for-gg-lesson/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2018 18:02:54 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/11/akihabara-for-gg-lesson/</guid>
      <description>18:02 Thursday 11 January 2018 JST Now I am in Akihabara, across the street from GG lesson which starts at 18:30.
I bought a trackball mouse to replace the one I had before which seems to just mysteriously and annoyingly not work anymore. This time I will keep the receipt because I think the old one konked out before its warranty was up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>two hour lesson with Tomoko</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/11/two-hour-lesson-with-tomoko/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2018 17:59:27 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/11/two-hour-lesson-with-tomoko/</guid>
      <description>17:59 Thursday 11 January 2018 JST Today was the first of five 2-hour lessons this month at SCC. Today I helped Tomoko by making corrections to her written English. She plans to present the features of some of her company&amp;rsquo;s products. Pretty cool stuff like elevators and batteries, and elevators that run on batteries. We studied up in their cafeteria on the 4th floor, and then I went down the escalator to the third floor and went out the exit I had never gone out before (but had seen many times).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>getting back to work in 2018</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/10/getting-back-to-work-in-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2018 08:44:46 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/10/getting-back-to-work-in-2018/</guid>
      <description>08:44 Wednesday 10 January 2018 JST I worked yesterday for the first time in 2018. Monday was a holiday, and my
13:41 Wednesday 10 January 2018 JST I am on the train and the above is as far as I got before sidetracking myself with something before having a meeting with TY at 9am then lunch with Lin.
Today:
 I got my AWS account switched to JPY instead of USD so I can pay more efficiently.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>changed icon</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/14/changed-icon/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2017 22:15:57 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/14/changed-icon/</guid>
      <description>22:15 Thursday 14 December 2017 JST Nate asked if I can change the icon on the new site, and gave me a whole stack of icons for different Apple devices. I was like, &amp;ldquo;false&amp;rdquo; and just changed the existing ico file.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>in Akihabara for last lesson of 2017</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/14/in-akihabara-for-last-lesson-of-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2017 17:54:40 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/14/in-akihabara-for-last-lesson-of-2017/</guid>
      <description>17:54 Thursday 14 December 2017 JST After working 3 hours (5 lessons) near Lazona, I&amp;rsquo;m eating cold lunch in Akihabara across the street from GG lesson. I have Lin&amp;rsquo;s sister&amp;rsquo;s heavy-as-hell suitcase. (Now I know why gorillas cannot break them)
19:41 Lesson was great; everyone was there! Yoko, Maki, and Atusko all brought sweets! Mayumi and Toshie both did homework!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>testing exim</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/13/testing-exim/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2017 21:51:14 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/13/testing-exim/</guid>
      <description>21:51 Wednesday 13 December 2017 JST exim -v thunderrabbit@example.com From: yoexim@example.com To: yoeximumad@example.com Subject: Testing Exim This is a test message.  &amp;lsquo;twas delivered to spam, but it worked.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>headed to last Sunday work this year</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/10/headed-to-last-sunday-work-this-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2017 07:51:48 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/10/headed-to-last-sunday-work-this-year/</guid>
      <description>07:51 Sunday 10 December 2017 JST Headed to Ty&amp;rsquo;s for the last Sunday working this year; he is closing up for the holidays, and may actually have some sort of family thing back in the states. Probably going to hang out with them afterward for dinner.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>oops schedule</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/07/oops-schedule/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2017 18:15:23 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/07/oops-schedule/</guid>
      <description>14:30 Thursday 07 December 2017 JST (written 18:15 Thursday 07 December 2017 JST)
While on the phone with BoA credit card to close my account, I got a call from JB: &amp;ldquo;hey yeah why aren&amp;rsquo;t you at work?&amp;rdquo;
Stomach sank link oh damn are you kidding me?
Turns out they hadn&amp;rsquo;t sent me the schedule for December, but I certainly could have been more proactive to check. I have set a reminder for the 28th of each month to make sure I have the dates in my calendar for the subsequent month.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>students leveled up real quick</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/06/students-leveled-up-real-quick/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2017 17:47:10 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/06/students-leveled-up-real-quick/</guid>
      <description>17:47 Wednesday 06 December 2017 JST At my third of three kids classes here at JB, we had a new student, 4 or 5 years older than the others. The two previously-oldest girls in the class suddenly stopped messing around and tried significantly harder than usual. Such a nice change of pace! I used a technique I learned from Tariq: keep having them switch conversation partners and repeat the same conversation with a new partner.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>just finished the work I wanted to do this weekend</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/03/just-finished-the-work-i-wanted-to-do-this-weekend/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2017 19:44:02 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/03/just-finished-the-work-i-wanted-to-do-this-weekend/</guid>
      <description>19:44 Sunday 03 December 2017 JST Nate hasn&amp;rsquo;t set the Name servers for this domain the way he said he would, but I guess he understands the consequences.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>sb work before work with Ty</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/03/sb-work-before-work-with-ty/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2017 09:01:35 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/03/sb-work-before-work-with-ty/</guid>
      <description>09:01 Sunday 03 December 2017 JST Been working all morning on sb new admin site. I got it deployed and essentially working last night. Now need to deploy the API, which should be way less work. Nate still has not set the Nameservers though so even when I get it finished, he won&amp;rsquo;t be able to see it (unless he sets up local /etc/hosts file)
Going to meet Ty soon to figure out this protocol we are developing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>work</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/02/work/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2017 16:22:32 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/02/work/</guid>
      <description>16:22 Saturday 02 December 2017 JST Been working on SB pretty much all day.
20:23 Saturday 02 December 2017 JST All day, though I meditated for 20 minutes and watched Season 2 episode 1 of Lucifer and Season 3 episode 1 of Rick and Morty (for the nth time).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>work</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/02/work/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2017 16:22:32 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/02/work/</guid>
      <description>16:22 Saturday 02 December 2017 JST Been working on SB pretty much all day.
20:23 Saturday 02 December 2017 JST All day, though I meditated for 20 minutes and watched Season 2 episode 1 of Lucifer and Season 3 episode 1 of Rick and Morty (for the nth time).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>work</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/02/work/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2017 16:22:32 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/02/work/</guid>
      <description>16:22 Saturday 02 December 2017 JST Been working on SB pretty much all day.
20:23 Saturday 02 December 2017 JST All day, though I meditated for 20 minutes and watched Season 2 episode 1 of Lucifer and Season 3 episode 1 of Rick and Morty (for the nth time).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>woke up early with no alarm</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/11/30/woke-up-early-with-no-alarm/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2017 07:00:08 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/11/30/woke-up-early-with-no-alarm/</guid>
      <description>07:00 Thursday 30 November 2017 JST I woke up at 4am with no alarm, and then actually got up at 4:26. Chatted with Jason and Jimmy for a second before getting to work.
Work included getting Ansible to create directories for a SB website on AWS. Basically I am tweaking the playbooks and roles from AB website to work on SB website. I need to make them a bit more generalized, but to a degreee, I think they are pretty good.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SB DNS</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/11/29/sb-dns/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2017 22:54:45 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/11/29/sb-dns/</guid>
      <description>22:54 Wednesday 29 November 2017 JST 22:51 sb: What do u think is best? 22:51 me: It is best if you decide 22:51 me: The items I mentioned above I think are perfect 22:52 me: They make sense to me, and I think they will make sense to anyone who uses them. 22:52 me: I am worried that there may be some confusion about what you think is best. 22:53 me: I thought we had agreed at the cafe about which domain would be used for what purpose.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chillin in Tullys</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/11/20/chillin-in-tullys/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2017 15:55:34 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/11/20/chillin-in-tullys/</guid>
      <description>15:55 Monday 20 November 2017 JST I&amp;rsquo;m getting back into Ansible groove on AWS. Thanks to Ansible for making it relatively easy to set up AWS boxes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>new style TS lessons</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/11/16/new-style-ts-lessons/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2017 17:56:10 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/11/16/new-style-ts-lessons/</guid>
      <description>17:56 Thursday 16 November 2017 JST Mutsumi introduced a new style lesson format where the guides sit down together with me instead of just having individual lessons. Hopefully this will help them improve listening skills by listening to other people have conversations in English.
I showed mt3s.robnugen.com to Miyako and Ayaka. Miyako showed me pics from her trip to the US with Haruka.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>today</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/11/16/today/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2017 13:18:54 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/11/16/today/</guid>
      <description>13:18 Thursday 16 November 2017 JST Funny talking to Scotty on Marco Polo; he kept not being able to hear me until I was like &amp;ldquo;okay bye&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;okay I hope you could hear it that time!&amp;rdquo;
I am headed to Kawasaki to support the guides in the English versions of their work. Then GG lesson in Akihabara.
Quick online I-group today; everyone checked out so it was just me and my coach near North Zulch, Texas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>playing with AWS for sbs.net</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/11/15/playing-with-aws-for-sbs.net/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2017 12:27:25 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/11/15/playing-with-aws-for-sbs.net/</guid>
      <description>12:27 Wednesday 15 November 2017 JST Not actually sbs.net, but yes actually AWS. Using Ansible again, thanks to Travis having suggested it to me.
Right now as I write this entry, AWS my wifi in this cafe is being slow to realize that my VPC is already created. Not sure why, as it was fast a moment ago.
Yep it just timed out.
The error was: ssl.SSLError: The read operation timed out  Previously, I was getting</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>late for class near C&#39;s place</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/11/13/late-for-class-near-cs-place/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2017 16:51:07 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/11/13/late-for-class-near-cs-place/</guid>
      <description>16:51 Monday 13 November 2017 JST TL;DR: Would you like donuts delivered to your place on Monday morning Nov 20th? details: Story time! Today I was inexplicably late for class which happens to be near your place. I told them I would get donuts before class next week. I found a donut place, checked Google Maps to see how to get to the class... and the track goes right by your house!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>great meetings</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/10/30/great-meetings/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2017 21:06:48 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/10/30/great-meetings/</guid>
      <description>21:06 Monday 30 October 2017 JST Meeting was fine and then the next meeting was great! Actually first meeting was great and the second was awesome I was really worried about the first meeting and I didn&amp;rsquo;t even expect the second one to happen, so overall fantastic</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>meeting prepped I hope</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/10/30/meeting-prepped-i-hope/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2017 05:58:55 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/10/30/meeting-prepped-i-hope/</guid>
      <description>05:58 Monday 30 October 2017 JST CB wants a presentation about the API. I started to explain how an API works and they seemed to know that, but they wanted to know how it&amp;rsquo;s set up. I have answered in terms of what I know and I hope that is enough for them to be satisfied.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>morning lesson</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/10/25/morning-lesson/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2017 09:13:23 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/10/25/morning-lesson/</guid>
      <description>09:13 Wednesday 25 October 2017 JST Good lesson today, full of the word &amp;ldquo;full of&amp;rdquo; and after filling the paper with examples, &amp;ldquo;this page is full&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Liz English School</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/10/24/liz-english-school/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2017 13:05:14 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/10/24/liz-english-school/</guid>
      <description>13:05 Tuesday 24 October 2017 JST Met Yaw for the first time at Liz English School. He and I got on quite well, and even shared a prayer for world peace and supporting our community and family. I look forward to working closely with him in the future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>meeting standby</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/10/11/meeting-standby/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2017 17:42:11 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/10/11/meeting-standby/</guid>
      <description>17:42 Wednesday 11 October 2017 JST 5:30pm meeting is underway, but I am only being asked questions via text while here at JB since they are doing it in Japanese (at CB).
17:47 I&amp;rsquo;m dialed in now.
17:51 They are asking how the API works. I explained it is like a web server which gives just data instead of data and HTML. They said they understand that, but how does it work?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>lesson at TB</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/10/11/lesson-at-tb/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2017 17:34:45 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/10/11/lesson-at-tb/</guid>
      <description>13:54 Wednesday 11 October 2017 JST Good lesson today at TB; they had just redone the place so I got a grand tour of the show room. Midori talked to some clients while Tomoko gave me the tour. They didn&amp;rsquo;t have anything to check yet, but I saw lots of word-for-word translations which we will have to clean up later.
They actually had to leave 10 minutes earlier than normal, so I headed out at 1:50pm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1 hour lesson at NB</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/10/03/1-hour-lesson-at-nb/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2017 12:50:29 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/10/03/1-hour-lesson-at-nb/</guid>
      <description>(written 12:50 Friday 06 October 2017 JST)
Worked at NB on Tuesday, my first lesson there that only lasted 1 hour. Boo. It was okay going all the way there for 2 hours, but just for 1 hour kinda sucks. I hope we can work out something else, like maybe they buy lunch as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>first official NA lesson</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/09/25/first-official-na-lesson/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2017 10:14:06 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/09/25/first-official-na-lesson/</guid>
      <description>10:14 Monday 25 September 2017 JST NA is the two letter designation for a new lesson I will be teaching on Mondays. It is within walking distance of the Monday morning lesson, but there is a bit of a gap in between so I am chilling at a restaurant in Tokyo Tower.
15:35 Monday 25 September 2017 JST Lesson was tough at first when I tried terribly to explain my intention to the group of quietly patient students.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>working on (shinkansen)</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/09/15/working-on-shinkansen/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2017 06:51:37 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/09/15/working-on-shinkansen/</guid>
      <description>06:51 Friday 15 September 2017 JST On the shinkansen from Shin Yokohama to Shin Osaka. First stop is Nagoya (I think), 72(?) minutes away.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ab work</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/09/14/ab-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2017 13:52:29 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/09/14/ab-work/</guid>
      <description>13:52 Thursday 14 September 2017 JST AB said something changed suddenly. git blame says in changed in April 2014. AB conceded but asked that I change it back to the way it was.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>today</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/09/12/today/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2017 23:57:26 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/09/12/today/</guid>
      <description>23:57 Tuesday 12 September 2017 JST Just got home via taxi with Lin after eating ice cream with her near our station. I got Ben and Jerry&amp;rsquo;s cotton candy (which was similar to Baskin Robbin&amp;rsquo;s Popping Shower), and she got cherry by some other premium brand, the name of which escapes me now.
Lin and I took the same train from Noborito to our station. She had gotten on near Shinjuku, and we did not specifically plan to take the same train, but it worked out that way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>extra lesson</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/09/05/extra-lesson/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2017 07:02:54 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/09/05/extra-lesson/</guid>
      <description>07:02 Tuesday 05 September 2017 JST I plan to start (continuing) working on Marble Track 3 now, slightly earlier than normal because I have an extra class to teach today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>guaranteed seat to Shinjuku</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/09/04/guaranteed-seat-to-shinjuku/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2017 05:26:33 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/09/04/guaranteed-seat-to-shinjuku/</guid>
      <description>05:26 Monday 04 September 2017 JST I have taken to takin&amp;rsquo; the super express train to work on Monday mornings. I get a guaranteed seat for a 20 minute snooze instead of guaranteed standing room only for 30 minutes. Only problem is the schedule: I end up arriving 45 minutes early.
However, I have never been late to this class, given that I attempt to arrive at least 20 minutes early.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>plan for tomorrow</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/09/03/plan-for-tomorrow/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2017 21:28:33 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/09/03/plan-for-tomorrow/</guid>
      <description>21:28 Sunday 03 September 2017 JST 15-20 minutes: new student intro self, students ask questions, new student ask questions. (I write Time, Name, Job, Etc outline on left side and then old topics on board while questions are in progress)
15-20 minutes: students prepare to do a quick presentation (one line summary at least) on any topic
15-20 minutes: students give their presentation, starting with new student&amp;rsquo;s helper
15-20 minutes: move on to next topic</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>project management</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/09/01/project-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2017 16:41:09 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/09/01/project-management/</guid>
      <description>16:41 Friday 01 September 2017 JST One of my work projects has been in maintenance mode for years.
https://www.beargroup.com/ideas/agile-web-development-our-approach-project-management mentions &amp;ldquo;wing it&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;agile&amp;rdquo; as two methodologies. We are definitely in the &amp;ldquo;wing it&amp;rdquo; column.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>yikes stripes limited sleep coming right up</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/08/30/yikes-stripes-limited-sleep-coming-right-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2017 01:48:11 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/08/30/yikes-stripes-limited-sleep-coming-right-up/</guid>
      <description>01:48 Wednesday 30 August 2017 JST The past few entries are dated some hours after they happened, but this one is being written in real time. I gotta wake up in 3 hours. shit shit shit.
Fortunately, I can sleep for a bit on the train. Unfortunately, I can only sleep for 50 minutes on the train and it usually leaves me groggy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>free lunch after lesson at NB</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/08/30/free-lunch-after-lesson-at-nb/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2017 01:40:41 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/08/30/free-lunch-after-lesson-at-nb/</guid>
      <description>01:40 Wednesday 30 August 2017 JST Today after teaching for 2 hours at NB, they offered me lunch! Yay!
Today was Yusuke&amp;rsquo;s last day! Booo!!
All the students seemed to enjoy the lesson! Yay!!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>need to figure out email issue</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/08/28/need-to-figure-out-email-issue/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2017 17:14:05 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/08/28/need-to-figure-out-email-issue/</guid>
      <description>17:14 Monday 28 August 2017 JST aight I am going to dig in to why AB is not getting their email.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Terms and Conditions</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/08/28/new-terms-and-conditions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2017 17:09:33 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/08/28/new-terms-and-conditions/</guid>
      <description>17:09 Monday 28 August 2017 JST I called Apple Worldwide Support to ask why their docs say I need LaunchImages with sizes X, Y, Z, while an error message says I need a LaunchImage of size A. Their answer: accept the new Terms and Conditions and try my upload again.
What?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ordered an AC</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/08/11/ordered-an-ac/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2017 18:44:50 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/08/11/ordered-an-ac/</guid>
      <description>18:44 Friday 11 August 2017 JST Welp, I gave in. But I like to think my computer gave in. There have been a couple of times this summer that I could not get work done because my computer overheated and refuxed to turn on or do things like accept keyboard / mouse input.
My room gets a bit hot, even with windows open,.. and I realized recently, I have taken more naps because of my computer (and I) overheating, so it has actually affected my income.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>lesson</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/08/03/lesson/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2017 21:25:43 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/08/03/lesson/</guid>
      <description>21:42 Thursday 03 August 2017 JST Hopefully I have learned all the lessons I need to learn from this situation. I considered documenting everything in my journal, or a gist,.. but a bunch of deleted lines in git will have to do.
Let&amp;rsquo;s just say &amp;ldquo;Buffer 03s-effect.md has shrunk a lot; auto save disabled in that buffer until next real save&amp;rdquo;
I am going to go meditate now to regain some sanity and hopefully shine some good light on all this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>internetty lesson</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/07/26/internetty-lesson/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2017 09:07:29 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/07/26/internetty-lesson/</guid>
      <description>09:07 Wednesday 26 July 2017 JST Lesson at Zavas featured a high level discussion of two different peering arrangements (p2p vs centralized) and the concept of protocols. I was planning to talk about Bitcoin, but the word &amp;ldquo;peer&amp;rdquo; in the whitepaper started the discussion we ended up having.
I had a distinct sense of inadequacy when describing layers of protocols that make up the internet, but that may be because when I hear the phrase &amp;ldquo;the internet&amp;rdquo; in my mind, my mind replies with &amp;ldquo;the internet is made of cats, the internet is made of cats, cats!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Covered for Patrick 1 of 5</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/07/24/covered-for-patrick-1-of-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2017 20:06:48 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/07/24/covered-for-patrick-1-of-5/</guid>
      <description>20:06 Monday 24 July 2017 JST Worked at AK today for a 2 hour lesson. Pretty great because the students are all talkative and asked questions and such. Chatted a bit and then showed them an article I used with other class. This class had much higher comprehension of the article&amp;hellip; which is good, but shows me just how too-high the article was for my other class.
After the lesson, Eiko walked me back nearly to the security gate, asking about PB a bit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>weird work</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/07/24/weird-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2017 16:08:21 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/07/24/weird-work/</guid>
      <description>16:08 Monday 24 July 2017 JST For some reason, I cannot connect to an EC2 instance, but I can connect to its sibling which was created with same OS, security group,and ssh key. hmmm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>tweaked Kai&#39;s presentation</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/07/24/tweaked-kais-presentation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2017 14:15:33 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/07/24/tweaked-kais-presentation/</guid>
      <description>14:15 Monday 24 July 2017 JST Met Kai today at 1pm to edit her presentation which she translated from Japanese. It was pretty decent actually, with just a few wonky sentence structures and some punctuation typos. It was so easy that it did not take the 2 hours we had allocated, but boom done in an hour sitting at (&amp;ldquo;Fresh like a box of _______ ______&amp;ldquo;) down near Azalea.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>plan for tomorrow</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/07/23/plan-for-tomorrow/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2017 23:20:26 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/07/23/plan-for-tomorrow/</guid>
      <description>23:20 Sunday 23 July 2017 JST Plan for tomorrow:
 Have students sit at one table write words on board and have them make sentences walk around to offer support write their sentences on the board introduce the idea of who what where when why hand out document with wwwww examples have them practice making new sentences  urban suburban rural potential roof gust struck residential complaint populated depopulated westernmost vacant abandoned municipalities elementary ceremony fiscal</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>work for sb</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/07/21/work-for-sb/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2017 22:33:33 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/07/21/work-for-sb/</guid>
      <description>22:33 Friday 21 July 2017 JST Just got a call from Nate to set up O to use the old CB CMS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>work for JL</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/07/21/work-for-jl/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2017 20:37:22 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/07/21/work-for-jl/</guid>
      <description>20:37 Friday 21 July 2017 JST I spoke to J at JL; it seems like it will be tough, but good.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>today</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/07/19/today/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2017 23:38:08 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/07/19/today/</guid>
      <description>23:38 Wednesday 19 July 2017 JST Today while running to catch my preferred train, I stubbed my toe. It didn&amp;rsquo;t hurt all that much, but is just annoying that now I will have to wear shoes for a bit while it heals. I forgot to take a picture right after it happened, but I posted one on twitter tonight.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>new lesson</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/07/18/new-lesson/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 17:52:31 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/07/18/new-lesson/</guid>
      <description>17:52 Tuesday 18 July 2017 JST Met new students for a first lesson in Nihonbashi. Five beginner students who all seem pretty genki. Some are more beginner than others.
JB was there to do the introduction and everything went smoothly. See you guys again next week! &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m glad to hear that!&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>morning lesson</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/07/18/morning-lesson/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 09:04:57 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/07/18/morning-lesson/</guid>
      <description>9am Tuesday 18 July 2017 JST (written 17:54 Tuesday 18 July 2017 JST)
Lesson at Il was okay but not great. I had what I thought was a good plan, but it resulted in silence during the latter half. Hmmm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>work waves</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/07/13/work-waves/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2017 09:06:45 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/07/13/work-waves/</guid>
      <description>09:06 Thursday 13 July 2017 JST ALTER TABLE frontend_appt_requests CHANGE modified modified TIMESTAMP NOT NULL DEFAULT &amp;lsquo;0000-00-00 00:00:00&amp;rsquo;;
ALTER TABLE frontend_appt_requests CHANGE created created TIMESTAMP NOT NULL DEFAULT CURRENT_TIMESTAMP ;
ALTER TABLE frontend_question_sets CHANGE modified modified TIMESTAMP NOT NULL DEFAULT &amp;lsquo;0000-00-00 00:00:00&amp;rsquo;;
ALTER TABLE frontend_question_sets CHANGE created created TIMESTAMP NOT NULL DEFAULT CURRENT_TIMESTAMP ;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>up early</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/07/09/up-early/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2017 03:03:27 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/07/09/up-early/</guid>
      <description>03:03 Sunday 09 July 2017 JST I set my alarm to wake up early this morning so I can get some work done while it&amp;rsquo;s not too hot in my room. When my computer gets hot, it gets slow. (Basically because it is old and the kernel task starts to go crazy and take all the CPU.)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>work</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/07/08/work/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2017 21:37:16 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/07/08/work/</guid>
      <description>21:37 Saturday 08 July 2017 JST Having trouble getting work done for AB. I finished the one thing they wanted done, but cannot seem to figure out the thing I really want to do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ab site fixes</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/07/07/ab-site-fixes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 09:29:37 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/07/07/ab-site-fixes/</guid>
      <description>09:29 Friday 07 July 2017 JST Need to hopefully finish ticket 3135 today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GG lesson</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/06/29/gg-lesson/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2017 21:42:39 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/06/29/gg-lesson/</guid>
      <description>21:42 Thursday 29 June 2017 JST Tonight I talked about Marble Track 3 during the lesson with GG. The next streaming video I do will be for them because 6 minutes before the lesson started, I realized I had purchased the wrong type of extension cable (the clerk tried to tell me but I did not understand what she said. 180 yen wasted and a new wire to get stuck in some fish&amp;rsquo;s gill because the shop does not accept returns.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>cadence</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/06/28/cadence/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2017 18:49:44 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/06/28/cadence/</guid>
      <description>18:49 Wednesday 28 June 2017 JST Third lesson today was good; some of the students seemed to really enjoy the cadence practice we did, focusing on matching the natural native-speed rhythm of my speech. Finally I have found something that kinda gets their attention. Mental note duly noted.
Maybe I will try it with my next class, but I kinda doubt it will have the same effect.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>technical debt</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/06/28/technical-debt/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2017 10:40:52 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/06/28/technical-debt/</guid>
      <description>10:40 Wednesday 28 June 2017 JST The old code was this:
$search_id = uniqid(UserAuthentication::getUserId());  Now it is this.
switch ($report_id) { case &#39;2&#39;: // I have no idea how to fix this one case &#39;5&#39;: // contact edit page knows nothing of V2-style indices case &#39;9&#39;: // contact edit page knows nothing of V2-style indices case &#39;10&#39;: // uses `u` in query. See SELECT * FROM `defined_reports` WHERE `dr_id` = 10 case &#39;11&#39;: // uses `t` in query case &#39;13&#39;: // can probably fix if remove `u` from `query` SELECT * FROM `defined_reports` WHERE `dr_id` = 13 case &#39;16&#39;: // can probably fix if remove `u` from `query` case &#39;17&#39;: // can probably fix if remove `u` from `query` case &#39;18&#39;: // can probably fix if remove `u` from `query case &#39;19&#39;: // can probably fix if remove `u` from `query $search_id_version = 1; $search_id = uniqid(UserAuthentication::currentUserId()); break; default: $search_id_version = 2; $search_id = &amp;quot;v2-&amp;quot; .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>weird last day at CB</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/06/26/weird-last-day-at-cb/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2017 11:40:02 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/06/26/weird-last-day-at-cb/</guid>
      <description>11:40 Monday 26 June 2017 JST It is weird because I have only heard from Nate that today is my last day with CB. I got a message saying &amp;ldquo;let&amp;rsquo;s hold off on the server upgrade until July&amp;rdquo; &amp;hellip; but I am done today, as far as I know. It is so weird to not be able to speak directly about stuff.
13:07 Monday 26 June 2017 JST My contact had forgotten, but they know.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>morning lesson</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/06/21/morning-lesson/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2017 09:05:59 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/06/21/morning-lesson/</guid>
      <description>09:05 Wednesday 21 June 2017 JST Just finished teaching and am now seated on a balcony walkway thing overlooking the empty water fountain in middle of Solid Square.
The lesson featured drills on two different patterns. One student was like &amp;ldquo;I went to shopping&amp;rdquo; so we practiced variants of that pattern. Another student arrived and started talking about TV so we practiced a pattern like
______ is a _______ about _______ _____-ing ______ ____ __ _ _ _ _</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>worknt</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/06/19/worknt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2017 12:10:24 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/06/19/worknt/</guid>
      <description>12:10 Monday 19 June 2017 JST Aint shit to do for CB now.
Unless they have something I don&amp;rsquo;t know about.
15:06 Monday 19 June 2017 JST I am on the train now in Shinjuku. How is it they have more super-express trains that express trains? I guess they know what they are doing and it works out for me, so there&amp;rsquo;s my answer.
Anyway, I texted CB 44 minutes after our normal meeting time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CB is moving away</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/06/14/cb-is-moving-away/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2017 12:17:59 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/06/14/cb-is-moving-away/</guid>
      <description>12:17 Wednesday 14 June 2017 JST Today is the big day to move CB to new servers. I reset the master password after it became apparent that the normal user cannot dump the DB. CB was still not able to run mysqldump, so they ended up just getting a snapshot from their AWS RDS instance.
I hope hope hope hope the transition goes smoothly. Today I have been giving some advice but not actually doing anything (except reset the master password) because I have not been made privy as to what exactly they want to do with the data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hopefully finished CB testing</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/06/12/hopefully-finished-cb-testing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2017 12:41:44 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/06/12/hopefully-finished-cb-testing/</guid>
      <description>12:41 Monday 12 June 2017 JST Just finished going through the CB admin site and the CB staging site to look for any differences. I see some cases where functionality does not work, but both sites produce the same results, even in those non-working cases.
Right now they are in a meeting and I feel fear because I cannot anticipate if they are going to be pissed because they think I did not follow their unwritten expectations or if they will say yeah nothing to do see you next week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>set up Twilio to call me in case of ...</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/06/05/set-up-twilio-to-call-me-in-case-of-.../</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2017 14:04:14 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/06/05/set-up-twilio-to-call-me-in-case-of-.../</guid>
      <description>14:04 Monday 05 June 2017 JST We are in a kinda weird place with CB. They are moving to a new server / dev team. Fair enough. I knew it would not last fo-eva but as of now, I am updating their servers to new Ubuntu at the same time they are planning to shut down these servers in favor of different servers run by a different dev team.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>lesson</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/06/05/lesson/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2017 09:50:39 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/06/05/lesson/</guid>
      <description>09:50 Monday 05 June 2017 JST I survived the lesson pretty genkily; we had a discussion about what it means to be Japanese, and of the original list from which we later culled about 2/3rds of the items, we had
Japanese people
 believe they are Japanese grow up in Japanese school system like to wait in long lines watch NHK on New Year&amp;rsquo;s day are proud of Mt Fuji  That last one intrigued me; I had not predicted it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>sorta kinda back on track</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/05/22/sorta-kinda-back-on-track/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2017 14:43:37 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/05/22/sorta-kinda-back-on-track/</guid>
      <description>14:43 Monday 22 May 2017 JST After having gotten the servers upgraded ahem (1&amp;frasl;2 of) the servers, I no longer feel like I did for most of April and the first half of May, all panickly (*) like ohmygodicannottakeasinglebreak!
(*) nice misspelling; I think I will leave it</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>still can&#39;t get shit done</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/05/18/still-cant-get-shit-done/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2017 15:57:41 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/05/18/still-cant-get-shit-done/</guid>
      <description>15:57 Thursday 18 May 2017 JST Today I discovered the image server had run out of space; I hadn&amp;rsquo;t created a separate volume for its cache. Got that sorted, but now need to add a cronjob to prune the space. I hope wiping files older than N days should do it, because that what I plan to do.
But why tf are some images still showing up all FFFFFF white?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>cannot login</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/05/18/cannot-login/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2017 07:47:52 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/05/18/cannot-login/</guid>
      <description>07:47 Thursday 18 May 2017 JST CB: Onece we logout,we can&#39;t login. CB: it&#39;s a app things. me: hmm. I have not changed the iPhone app.. the only thing I changed recently was the image server. me: I wonder what could cause it.  Steps to check:
 Look up my username and password thunderrabbit / *********************************** see if I can log in if not, log in to server watch the logs see if there is an error if not, (shrug smiley) if so, hope the error tells me something  08:01 Thursday 18 May 2017 JST I was able to log in no problem.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>blargh</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/05/17/blargh/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2017 21:11:24 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/05/17/blargh/</guid>
      <description>21:11 Wednesday 17 May 2017 JST What&amp;rsquo;s the polite way to say show me the money when my language school is like oh can you make these tweaks to our website?
Lessons tonight were ssooo challenging for me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>can&#39;t get shit done</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/05/17/cant-get-shit-done/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2017 12:25:52 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/05/17/cant-get-shit-done/</guid>
      <description>12:25 Wednesday 17 May 2017 JST Man my productivity has been dismal for a while. Basically it&amp;rsquo;s cause I have too much shit going on and can&amp;rsquo;t keep the status of all my projects in mind.
Specifically, I wasted an hour wondering why one particular image would not show up, and turns out I had not yet updated my dev environment to use the new image server.
Then a tiny bit of maintenance success getting my dev environment fully working, but now it&amp;rsquo;s time to go to my next lesson.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mt Fuji&#39;s &#39;recent&#39; eruption</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/05/17/mt-fujis-recent-eruption/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2017 09:19:43 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/05/17/mt-fujis-recent-eruption/</guid>
      <description>09:19 Wednesday 17 May 2017 JST Today I learned from C-san that the southern face of Mt Fuji erupted in 1707, leaving a still clearly visible crater on the side of the mountain. So interesting!!
A-san showed us a satellite map which shows the hole and a river-looking thing on another face of the mountain.
I&amp;rsquo;m glad C-san remembered her homework!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>snoozy commute</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/05/17/snoozy-commute/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2017 06:25:43 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/05/17/snoozy-commute/</guid>
      <description>06:25 Wednesday 17 May 2017 JST Arriving on time for my 7:50am - 8:50am lesson requires I leave our house by 6:25am. However, if I leave home by 5:45am, I can sit down on a train at 6:25am, and sleeeeep until it arrives at 7:30am.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>work</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/05/15/work/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2017 16:28:57 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/05/15/work/</guid>
      <description>16:28 Monday 15 May 2017 JST Moe Joe.
CB was like &amp;lsquo;um where are the images in our app?&amp;rsquo;
Turns out the app source hardcodes the image server domain name instead of reading it from the API the app uses.
Spent 1.5 hours on phone with AWS support trying to get our domain pointed to CBs new image server. Ended up doing it at DNS level because I could not get redirects to work from the server.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>good ness</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/05/08/good-ness/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2017 18:33:43 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/05/08/good-ness/</guid>
      <description>18:33 Monday 08 May 2017 JST TL;DR: wasted a lot of time today.
Wall of crap:
I somehow confused myself and my vagrant VMs. The big change I made was to recreate my ~/.ssh/id_rsa keys in my management box. That meant I could not connect to the other VMs until I put the public key in their .ssh/authorized_hosts file, which I did, but then I could not deploy the sites without giving the new key to bitbucket, and then I ended up destroying and recreating a VM because for some reason the &amp;ldquo;exact same&amp;rdquo; (*) deploys that worked before were not working because they were being run as ubuntu instead of vagrant.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FS for AB and CB</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/05/06/fs-for-ab-and-cb/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2017 09:32:54 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/05/06/fs-for-ab-and-cb/</guid>
      <description>09:32 Saturday 06 May 2017 JST After upgrading it to Ubuntu 14, I split the FS box into two, and put one on CB&amp;rsquo;s AWS account so they have control over it. (cough) and pay for it. The AB version we still pay for, but the load is much lighter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Got AB their own FS</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/05/05/got-ab-their-own-fs/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2017 14:32:51 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/05/05/got-ab-their-own-fs/</guid>
      <description>14:32 Friday 05 May 2017 JST Since recovering from my little DB restore delimma, I have instantiated an instance of FS just for AB. I will move the existing FS instance to CB&amp;rsquo;s account so they can pay their own way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>no,no,no,no,no,yes</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/05/05/nononononoyes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2017 11:27:18 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/05/05/nononononoyes/</guid>
      <description>11:27 Friday 05 May 2017 JST While trying to fix the backup process, I destroyed the database by overwriting with data from April 20th.
Had a good cry, and now am restoring the data from a 1GB backup file.
(It&amp;rsquo;s this file that I guessed would be troublesome in a restore process, so I wanted to break it up into bits. Now we get to do the restore starting with this file.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Productive X2</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/04/29/productive-x2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2017 20:54:24 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/04/29/productive-x2/</guid>
      <description>20:54 Saturday 29 April 2017 JST Pretty much got everything sorted. I never got the old AB VM to have connectivity again, but my new AB VM is in better shape than the old VM ever was:
The new VM
 can send emails can easily have deploys target specific branches uses domain names that differ from production by a single character (.cojp vs .co.jp) uses Ubuntu 14 is fully deployed via Ansible  and that last item means if I lose my physical computer, I can pretty quickly recreate my development environment, at least as far as that VM is concerned.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>back on track</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/04/29/back-on-track/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2017 14:34:18 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/04/29/back-on-track/</guid>
      <description>14:34 Saturday 29 April 2017 JST Well, I have recovered nearly to the point that I was 24+ hours ago before killing connectivity to my VM.
I tried restoring the old VM, but didn&amp;rsquo;t get it working. It&amp;rsquo;s a non-issue at the moment. I have a new VM to which I can connect from my host (allowing SublimeText2 (Registered) to save files to it), and from a sibling guest VM which provisioned the new VM using Ansible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TY, T!</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/04/29/ty-t/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2017 09:26:58 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/04/29/ty-t/</guid>
      <description>09:26 Saturday 29 April 2017 JST TL;DR: https://www.packer.io/
Travis gave a fantastic reply to my tale of disconnectivity. I am going to dive in to Packer for a few units of time, and then try to restore connectivity to my old VM, and then try to finish installing site on my new VM, and then try to do the update I wanted to do yesterday morning!
09:43 Saturday 29 April 2017 JST Okay, let&amp;rsquo;s install Packer!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>productivent</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/04/28/productivent/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2017 16:23:15 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/04/28/productivent/</guid>
      <description>16:23 Friday 28 April 2017 JST Last night AB was like &amp;ldquo;hey we cannot send emails.&amp;rdquo;
They got a 500 error because I forgot to enable mcrypt to create passwords for new users.
Enabled mcrypt and manually fixed some shit that didn&amp;rsquo;t work due to the 500 error. Got everything sorted today and then ready to work but denied because
the local VM in virtualbox does not have access to the internet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>working from home</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/04/27/working-from-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2017 13:33:13 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/04/27/working-from-home/</guid>
      <description>13:33 Thursday 27 April 2017 JST Now I am working from home, hoping to get test AB talking to test FS behind a load balancer and cdn.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>lessons</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/04/26/lessons/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2017 22:59:35 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/04/26/lessons/</guid>
      <description>22:59 Wednesday 26 April 2017 JST Today&amp;rsquo;s first three lessons went really well by simply having a four part target per lesson: questions, text, test, game. Thanks, Yuji!
I did a gamification of the questions portion of the lessons. For question correctly answered within about five seconds, the student received a &amp;ldquo;prize&amp;rdquo; (single card from Stacker Crackers). The cards give them something to fiddle with while other students are answering questions, and hopefully inspires them to answer correctly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Got fake FS working on new server</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/04/26/got-fake-fs-working-on-new-server/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2017 12:03:02 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/04/26/got-fake-fs-working-on-new-server/</guid>
      <description>12:03 Wednesday 26 April 2017 JST Nice. Now that I&amp;rsquo;ve got a few Ansible playbooks set up (thanks, Travis!), it&amp;rsquo;s sorta kinda easy to spin up a new server with all its personalized packages, bells, and whistles.
Today I got FS set up on a temporary server, including pulling a copy of the DB and static files from the live server.
Basically, I need to split the live server into two: one that we can give to CB and one that we continue to use for AB.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>oops and whew</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/04/25/oops-and-whew/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2017 12:53:24 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/04/25/oops-and-whew/</guid>
      <description>12:53 Tuesday 25 April 2017 JST I left the AB DB backup process in testing mode (backup every hour, do not clean up the files) and it killed the disk this morning and locked up the server.
Thankfully, I was able to request support from AWS. They called me immediately and helped me dismount the flooded disk, remount it at /mnt on a different server where I was able to clean up the disk, then remount it on AB server and get the server running again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>work</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/04/24/work/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2017 10:05:49 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/04/24/work/</guid>
      <description>10:05 Monday 24 April 2017 JST Today I hope to get AB server upgrade officially complete. Need to clarify a time with client and then do it, hopin&amp;rsquo; all goes smoothly (i.e. I have not missed anything).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>slowly</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/04/15/slowly/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Apr 2017 12:42:02 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/04/15/slowly/</guid>
      <description>12:42 Saturday 15 April 2017 JST Man this is going slowly. Part of it is pain in my neck, wrists, head, fingers..</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>plan</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/04/14/plan/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2017 10:02:07 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/04/14/plan/</guid>
      <description>10:02 Friday 14 April 2017 JST Because it takes 5 hours to import the data in my reliable way, I will not recreate the machine from scratch in Tokyo region.
I&amp;rsquo;ll finish it up in California and then move it over to Tokyo.
steps
 add cron jobs Make sure site works change the domains to correct domains make an AMI of the box copy it to Tokyo spin it up copy latest data changes over point DNS to new box activate SSL  Step One requires</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1 of 5 servers almost updated</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/04/13/1-of-5-servers-almost-updated/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Apr 2017 18:00:53 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/04/13/1-of-5-servers-almost-updated/</guid>
      <description>18:00 Thursday 13 April 2017 JST It looks like I&amp;rsquo;ve nearly got AB&amp;rsquo;s server rebuilt with new Ubuntu OS. I just need to put the crontab entries on it, and run it through all the tests. yay.
CB&amp;rsquo;s two servers are close to being almost updated, but I just have not taken the time to do them. Glad they do not have to have mysql data on them. Just gotta deal with a big disk.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CB site</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/04/10/cb-site/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2017 23:58:48 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/04/10/cb-site/</guid>
      <description>23:58 Monday 10 April 2017 JST Wow the CB site is sooo much easier to deploy given that it does not have mysql data served from the same server.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>weekend</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/04/10/weekend/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2017 10:11:35 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/04/10/weekend/</guid>
      <description>10:11 Monday 10 April 2017 JST This past weekend it rained, so SOGO was cancelled. I was kinda glad because I feel behind schedule on getting servers running with Ansible. I&amp;rsquo;ve abandoned jumping from Ubuntu 12 to Ubutnu 16 this time. I&amp;rsquo;m focusing on Ubuntu 14 with the hopes that having this groundwork laid (on the groundwork laid by Ansible), the next upgrade will be ready ahead of schedule.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mornin</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/03/30/mornin/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2017 07:54:25 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/03/30/mornin/</guid>
      <description>07:54 Thursday 30 March 2017 JST I kinda wanna put an apostrophe on both sides of Mornin, to replace Good and g, but it seems weird no matter where I put them so bah.
I woke up just before 5am this morning without my alarm oh man my student is here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My desk will not attend my funeral</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/03/29/my-desk-will-not-attend-my-funeral/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2017 10:54:32 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/03/29/my-desk-will-not-attend-my-funeral/</guid>
      <description>10:54 Wednesday 29 March 2017 JST Too busy working to read this, but I bet it says I am too busy working https://medium.com/personal-growth/your-desk-will-not-attend-your-funeral-779515a81dd3</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>presentation lesson</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/03/27/presentation-lesson/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2017 11:11:45 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/03/27/presentation-lesson/</guid>
      <description>11:11 Monday 27 March 2017 JST This morning we reviewed last week&amp;rsquo;s article about Nissan having been selected to provide New York City taxi minivans until 2024. Talked about the benefits of the taxis from the points of view of different people: passengers, drivers, owners. Then we did mock sales presentations, tailored to our imaginary audiences.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>thanks Dr Fred!</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/03/26/thanks-dr-fred/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2017 22:23:16 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/03/26/thanks-dr-fred/</guid>
      <description>22:23 Sunday 26 March 2017 JST Talked with Fred today for 6+ hours working on a backup script. When I tried to run it on all the tables, the resulting .tar.gz file was like 8GB and was hanging the machine when I tried to work with it.
So I split the archive by years and got Fred to help me write a bash script to loop through the years of the data and bundle the tables up into more useably sized archives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>thank you, mobile office</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/03/22/thank-you-mobile-office/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2017 14:51:25 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/03/22/thank-you-mobile-office/</guid>
      <description>14:51 Wednesday 22 March 2017 JST At home, I set up a URL that I could reload repeatedly to process N records at a time. I logged in to the site on my phone and repeatedly loaded it while walking to the train station, and now while on the train, I just now used my phone&amp;rsquo;s wifi tethering option to rerun a CSV create script after all the records had been updated.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>too late</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/03/21/too-late/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2017 12:17:52 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/03/21/too-late/</guid>
      <description> 12:17 Tuesday 21 March 2017 JST Yesterday was a holiday, and happily enough, I basically took the day off. The previous two days I had been up working until an average of 4am.
Today I just read HN and now about to work on Ansible playbooks again.
But first, a silly thing I just made up:
A: 鍵はどこかな? B: 車内じゃない？  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>workin</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/03/18/workin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2017 13:36:34 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/03/18/workin/</guid>
      <description>13:36 Saturday 18 March 2017 JST Work work work gah</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>workin</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/02/25/workin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2017 09:06:18 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/02/25/workin/</guid>
      <description>09:06 Saturday 25 February 2017 JST Now about to work on worky work work to fix the issue that I triaged last night by setting up old code on staging server. It&amp;rsquo;s interesting that these different issues are coming up now when I&amp;rsquo;ve got other projects already going for same client.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>work</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/02/24/work/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2017 23:04:56 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/02/24/work/</guid>
      <description>23:04 Friday 24 February 2017 JST I just found out that the Big Change I made to clients website last month broke some important functionality that I didn&amp;rsquo;t have an automated test set up to catch the mistake. Now am putting an old version of the code on test website so they can use the old version for the old functionality .. basically supporting two websites for them (well 3, counting the frontend) while I fix the code to work with new data structure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>workin</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/02/20/workin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2017 05:54:06 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/02/20/workin/</guid>
      <description>05:54 Monday 20 February 2017 JST Though I went to SOGO yesterday (and had a great time), I have been working too much. My pinky still hurts, but less now that I use it less. My shoulders are tense.. perhaps I should switch my mouse to left hand again.
But, I have now gotten Redmine installed via Ansible, and another website installed on same server.
Still need to install one more site on this server, and hopefully this time I can figure out why it went sideways before.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>moe joe up all night working</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/02/16/moe-joe-up-all-night-working/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2017 05:33:18 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/02/16/moe-joe-up-all-night-working/</guid>
      <description>05:33 Thursday 16 February 2017 JST And have to wake up in 10 minutes to go to work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>yay I think I got Redmine securely installed</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/02/12/yay-i-think-i-got-redmine-securely-installed/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2017 23:14:49 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/02/12/yay-i-think-i-got-redmine-securely-installed/</guid>
      <description>23:14 Sunday 12 February 2017 JST Only reason I am not sure rests in the fact that I had to switch to LetsEncrypt &amp;ndash;staging certs, so now my browser does not trust the site. As far as I can tell, though the SSL is installed properly. Yay!
I may switch to my domain for testing again tomorrow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>fun request</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/02/03/fun-request/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2017 18:55:54 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/02/03/fun-request/</guid>
      <description>18:55 Friday 03 February 2017 JST [2/2/17, 11:25:56 AM] caught-in-middle: Hi, I updated ticket #2978. Please check when you can.  ticket 2978:
The code we gave you before doesn&#39;t display the page views correctly. Could you switch the code to this?  
Uh, yeah that&amp;rsquo;s not going to work. {{$article-&amp;gt;title}} is obviously a placeholder.
[2/2/17, 12:20:07 PM] Rob Nugen: thank you. I got it, but I need a little bit of time to test.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>might install redmine</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/01/29/might-install-redmine/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2017 11:10:08 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/01/29/might-install-redmine/</guid>
      <description>11:10 Sunday 29 January 2017 JST Wow; I hope this script works! https://www.hiroom2.com/2017/01/22/ubuntu-16-04-install-redmine/
12:02 Sunday 29 January 2017 JST I couldn&amp;rsquo;t get it to work.
Travis replied to my plea and gave some more resources, which I hadn&amp;rsquo;t looked at before.
Here is a current guide that covers your target OS: https://www.digitalocean.com/community/tutorials/how-to-install-linux-apache-mysql-php-lamp-stack-on-ubuntu-16-04 As for Redmine, I noticed that Docker has an official Remine repository: https://hub.docker.com/_/redmine/ I see that it is based on Debian, but that is not too different from Ubuntu.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AB testing</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/01/24/ab-testing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2017 08:12:29 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/01/24/ab-testing/</guid>
      <description>08:12 Tuesday 24 January 2017 JST Okay I&amp;rsquo;m going to figure out why Ghost Inspector test failed on changes I made to AB site.
08:33 Tuesday 24 January 2017 JST Aha! Uninitialized value. PHP ftw!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>good luck at work</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/01/23/good-luck-at-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2017 10:39:26 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/01/23/good-luck-at-work/</guid>
      <description>10:39 Monday 23 January 2017 JST I need some luck today; I hope I can figure out Facebook&amp;rsquo;s Instant Articles. Specifically, figure out why they won&amp;rsquo;t reload articles that have been updated in the RSS feed (with an expiry date in the past), after I changed the GUID of the article, after I changed its canonical URL.
12:57 Monday 23 January 2017 JST Okay, the main thing I determined:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>simon</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/01/20/simon/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2017 00:36:27 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/01/20/simon/</guid>
      <description>00:36 Friday 20 January 2017 JST Via my repo to set up new Dreamhost shell account
[server]$ ./password_fix.sh This script will set your password to 432 random characters if you enter your current password now: Enter your password only if you are CERTAIN you can log in without password: Okay interactively changing password. Do NOT enter anything at the next password prompt: Changing password for user. (current) UNIX password: Enter new UNIX password: Retype new UNIX password: passwd: password updated successfully if password is reported as changed, then it&#39;s now 432 random characters but I didn&#39;t keep a copy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>work deadlines</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/01/18/work-deadlines/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2017 12:26:31 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/01/18/work-deadlines/</guid>
      <description>12:26 Wednesday 18 January 2017 JST I know I didn&amp;rsquo;t say I could definitely finish. At the start of this year, they were like, &amp;ldquo;oh god the competition has ABC! We need ABC too!&amp;rdquo; yeah well ABC has been available for 6 months. Asking me to spend 8 hours to catch up to what they&amp;rsquo;ve done in as long as 6 months is not something I would have said I could do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Started a repo which will eventually deploy Redmine to AWS</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/01/17/started-a-repo-which-will-eventually-deploy-redmine-to-aws/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2017 01:29:03 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/01/17/started-a-repo-which-will-eventually-deploy-redmine-to-aws/</guid>
      <description>01:29 Tuesday 17 January 2017 JST I&amp;rsquo;m creating a git repo of Ansible playbooks that I can post online to see if someone can figure it out.
And this little repo gets it all started: https://github.com/thunderrabbit/bootstrap-redmine-deploy</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>(solved) Ansible incorrect values in usr share redmine config database.yml</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/01/15/solved-ansible-incorrect-values-in-usr-share-redmine-config-database.yml/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2017 03:29:28 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/01/15/solved-ansible-incorrect-values-in-usr-share-redmine-config-database.yml/</guid>
      <description>03:29 Sunday 15 January 2017 JST now it&amp;rsquo;s 3:29. fuck this I&amp;rsquo;m going to bed.
for some reason I can&amp;rsquo;t figure out what command added the database config file that I want on my new server
I have some old copies of the new server and on one of them the database is configured properly. But when I ran through (what I thought were) the same steps again, the database is not configured.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>work</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/01/10/work/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2017 10:49:25 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/01/10/work/</guid>
      <description>10:49 Tuesday 10 January 2017 JST Right now I&amp;rsquo;m in a conveni across from GG class in Akihabara (formerly Akibahara). I&amp;rsquo;ve just walked here (in about 25 minutes) from the imperial gardens, during which time I talked to Chuck from online I-group.
Soon I&amp;rsquo;ll teach GG&amp;rsquo;s lunch lesson for whoever usually teaches it. It&amp;rsquo;s great because they are largely self-directed; we just talk about the latest news or whatever they want to discuss.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>worked</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/01/08/worked/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2017 09:32:24 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/01/08/worked/</guid>
      <description>09:32 Sunday 08 January 2017 JST Yesterday I worked on SB, trying to get Ansible to install Redmine on a server. radamanth.redmine-ansible installed a self-signed SSL key, but I couldn&amp;rsquo;t get that to work, so I manually converted the HTTPS version of the site to HTTP version. I got something to load, but it mentions a 500 error, and I can&amp;rsquo;t see anything in the log.
Oh wait, after that I told the config to treat all requests as local, so it spit out the error message, something like &amp;ldquo;can&amp;rsquo;t find this function&amp;rdquo; when referencing something like use default language for anon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>back to work</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/01/04/back-to-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 11:01:02 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/01/04/back-to-work/</guid>
      <description>11:01 Wednesday 04 January 2017 JST Headed back to work today, by way of shopping for wallets in Kawasaki Lazona.
(am almost finished with a new waterslide in minecraft world I made for Fred)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>workin</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/12/27/workin/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2016 10:35:13 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/12/27/workin/</guid>
      <description>10:35 Tuesday 27 December 2016 JST Okay back to work! I gotta wanna finish work for AB before end of the year. yahooo
12:01 Tuesday 27 December 2016 JST I&amp;rsquo;ve added two (debug) lines, removed one superfluous line, and now I&amp;rsquo;m ready to write some lines that will hopefully stay for a while.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>early lessons</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/12/21/early-lessons/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2016 11:45:51 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/12/21/early-lessons/</guid>
      <description>11:45 Wednesday 21 December 2016 JST I covered for Matt at his two lessons in Ginza. Of the seven students, I remembered Aya&amp;rsquo;s name and remember Hiroshi&amp;rsquo;s name as Hiroki. It&amp;rsquo;s been about 6 months since I taught them for the 3rd time. (Today was the fourth time.)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>having Ansible install redmine</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/12/16/having-ansible-install-redmine/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2016 20:01:29 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/12/16/having-ansible-install-redmine/</guid>
      <description>20:01 Friday 16 December 2016 JST Here&amp;rsquo;s the error:
TASK [redmine-ansible : Change admin default account] ************************** fatal: [54.175.38.243]: FAILED! =&amp;gt; {&amp;quot;changed&amp;quot;: true, &amp;quot;cmd&amp;quot;: &amp;quot;ruby script/rails runner -e production &#39;user = User.find(:first, :conditions =&amp;gt; {:admin =&amp;gt; true}) ; user.mail=\&amp;quot;youradmin@robnugen.com\&amp;quot;; user.salt_password(\&amp;quot;redmine\&amp;quot;); user.save!&#39;&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;delta&amp;quot;: &amp;quot;0:00:00.033956&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;end&amp;quot;: &amp;quot;2016-12-16 10:58:40.837395&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;failed&amp;quot;: true, &amp;quot;rc&amp;quot;: 1, &amp;quot;start&amp;quot;: &amp;quot;2016-12-16 10:58:40.803439&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;stderr&amp;quot;: &amp;quot;ruby: No such file or directory -- script/rails (LoadError)&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;stdout&amp;quot;: &amp;quot;&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;stdout_lines&amp;quot;: [], &amp;quot;warnings&amp;quot;: []} to retry, use: --limit @/home/vagrant/create-server-on-aws/US_EAST_030_website_redmine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>work</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/12/15/work/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2016 17:24:25 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/12/15/work/</guid>
      <description>17:24 Thursday 15 December 2016 JST Worked on iPhone app a bit, wiping out the paddle and balls from breakout style, and just allowed touching the bricks to destroy them. I added little explosion impulse (reverse gravity) when each brick is destroyed so it&amp;rsquo;s like they explode and blow the other bricks around the screen.
func breakBlock(_ node: SKNode) { // boom simulates an explosion which affects blocks around the block let boom = SKFieldNode.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wednesday late Thursday early</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/12/15/wednesday-late-thursday-early/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2016 07:48:34 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/12/15/wednesday-late-thursday-early/</guid>
      <description>07:48 Thursday 15 December 2016 JST My transition from Wednesday to Thursday each week includes just about 4 hours of sleep. I work until 9pm at JB (get home at 10:40pm) and then teach at 7:50 the next morning (for which I wake up at 5:49am). So I guess if I go zoom straight to sleep, I could sleep 7 hours. I&amp;rsquo;ll try that next year when the schedule resumes after the holidays.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>play</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/12/11/play/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2016 10:26:47 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/12/11/play/</guid>
      <description>10:26 Sunday 11 December 2016 JST Party at JB school today at 1pm; gotta leave soon!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>work</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/12/11/work/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2016 10:20:11 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/12/11/work/</guid>
      <description>10:20 Sunday 11 December 2016 JST This weekend I&amp;rsquo;ve continued working on ansible playbooks to spin up EC2 instance, update the packages, install a couple websites (these sites are why I haven&amp;rsquo;t released the playbooks), and now I&amp;rsquo;m trying to get redmine installed.
I found radamanth/redmine-ansible and tried to use it.
It depends on radamanth/mysql-ansible but it doesn&amp;rsquo;t work on Ubuntu 16 server.
So I&amp;rsquo;m going to see if I can get sbstrm/redmine-ansible working on top of geerlingguy/ansible-role-mysql, which does work on Ubuntu 16 server.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>busy work</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/12/09/busy-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2016 09:48:34 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/12/09/busy-work/</guid>
      <description>09:48 Friday 09 December 2016 JST Now I&amp;rsquo;m on 小田急 line to 登戸駅 where I&amp;rsquo;ll hop on the 南武線 to head to 川崎駅 where I&amp;rsquo;ll work at Wired cafe or something for a bit before meeting with Tariq at 12pm or so. Then head toward JB to buy some bananas from はしもと on the way to 3:30pm - 5:30pm class(es).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>more work</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/12/06/more-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2016 17:29:35 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/12/06/more-work/</guid>
      <description>17:29 Tuesday 06 December 2016 JST In addition to fixing the functionality of a survey thing, I watched an hour of David Blaine freak people out, and nearly got my ansible thing to install a website, but it&amp;rsquo;s not working 100% due to an AJAX call returning 404 on the test system. Is it due to the fact that I&amp;rsquo;ve got the domain set to the test IP locally? Hmmm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>work</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/12/05/work/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2016 19:11:08 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/12/05/work/</guid>
      <description>19:11 Monday 05 December 2016 JST Nice at work today I was able to do some actual work! None of this &amp;ldquo;oh can you change the design that we asked you to change before?&amp;rdquo; bah.
Today it was, &amp;ldquo;can you add a new page to the site based on this old page that allows users to submit content? We&amp;rsquo;ll do the design after you upload it.&amp;rdquo;
Yay! No problem.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>morning</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/12/01/morning/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2016 07:39:17 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/12/01/morning/</guid>
      <description>07:39 Thursday 01 December 2016 JST Lin offered to drive me to the station because it was raining. I declined her offer because it&amp;rsquo;s a waste of gas, and the rain wasn&amp;rsquo;t torrential. But even now, the fact that I declined her offer is stuck in my head.
I arrived 10 minutes early for my morning lesson.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>lesson</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/11/28/lesson/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2016 17:27:02 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/11/28/lesson/</guid>
      <description>17:27 Monday 28 November 2016 JST This morning&amp;rsquo;s lesson featured an article about something about something. Man what was it?
Oh yes: Tokyo University has decided to give $300 per month to newly enrolled women in an attempt to increase enrollment.
Ummmm yeah if they&amp;rsquo;re already enrolled, paying them won&amp;rsquo;t help enrollment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>work</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/11/28/work/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2016 17:24:26 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/11/28/work/</guid>
      <description>17:24 Monday 28 November 2016 JST Worked today with S at s and finally figured out Google Doubleclick For Providers or whatever it&amp;rsquo;s called. Basically there&amp;rsquo;s inventory and orders. Inventory has ad units and ad placements (multiple ad units). Orders have line items which have creatives. Orders can have multiple line items. Creatives are many-to-many with Line items. Creatives are basically banners or videos the end users will see as ads.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>five lessons</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/11/23/five-lessons/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2016 21:58:24 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/11/23/five-lessons/</guid>
      <description>21:58 Wednesday 23 November 2016 JST There&amp;rsquo;s scaffolding all around the building where I taught five lessons this evening. After they were finished, I climbed on the scaffolding a little bit. I could have climbed up quite high, but chose not to for reasons of propriety. It was my first time to climb on scaffolding like this in Japan. Usually they close it off quite carefully.. but not in this case.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>lesson</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/11/17/lesson/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2016 09:46:58 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/11/17/lesson/</guid>
      <description>09:46 Thursday 17 November 2016 JST Lesson with C and A went well; A was late (as usual), but C was on time! Amazing!
I told them a bit about Pecha Kucha and how I&amp;rsquo;m nervous, ill-prepared, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Work</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/11/16/work/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2016 21:44:27 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/11/16/work/</guid>
      <description>21:44 Wednesday 16 November 2016 JST I worked three jobs today.. not full time shifts, but I worked for 3 distinct companies. First in Akabanebashi I taught the early lesson I usually teach on Mondays, but they moved it to today for some reason.
Then I went to my programming job in Ebisu where I did a tiny bit of (unpaid) work while mostly preparing for PechaKucha.
Then headed to JB where I taught for five hours.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New schedules</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/11/10/new-schedules/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2016 09:33:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/11/10/new-schedules/</guid>
      <description>09:33 Thursday 10 November 2016 JST Because Lin and I moved to Shin Yurigaoka, my commute to Fukuura cost more than I was paid for travel, so I mentioned that to them and then boom new Wednesday schedule starting yesterday. Two classes were new students for me; kids classes, so it will be a good chance to get some experience with kids classes. Next week there will be 3 other classes as well; with adults, I guess.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>rubber ducking in the bath</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/11/05/rubber-ducking-in-the-bath/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 00:42:24 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/11/05/rubber-ducking-in-the-bath/</guid>
      <description>00:42 Saturday 05 November 2016 JST While taking a bath, I just talked to Fred for 45+ minutes on the phone, rubber ducking a problem with him.
Before I started working on this a couple days ago, I did the following:
 Save a list of indices each time the user tweaks a search on index Once a record is selected, use the indices to allow prev/next Rerun the search if they go back to the index  This worked fine at first, but item #1 above now takes too much time now that the DB has grown.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>one to one lesson before holiday</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/11/02/one-to-one-lesson-before-holiday/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2016 21:05:11 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/11/02/one-to-one-lesson-before-holiday/</guid>
      <description>21:05 Wednesday 02 November 2016 JST My group lesson had only one student; I suggested https://newsinlevels.com and https://breakingnewsenglish.com as ways she can practice extensive reading. There are probably some free sites that are actually geared toward ER, but I don&amp;rsquo;t have their domains memorized.
11:42 Saturday 05 November 2016 JST Surprise! That turned out to be my last lesson there. I had mentioned to them that it&amp;rsquo;s a bit far for me to travel and then boom they got a new teacher.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>workin</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/11/02/workin/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2016 16:11:22 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/11/02/workin/</guid>
      <description>16:11 Wednesday 02 November 2016 JST Sweet; I&amp;rsquo;ve got my refactored code nearly complete. I just need to snag a copy of the number of records. I know the data already exists in DataTables; I just need to pick it up from there or maybe I already have it server-side somewhere.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>lessons</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/10/27/lessons/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2016 20:22:30 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/10/27/lessons/</guid>
      <description>20:22 Thursday 27 October 2016 JST Lesson with A this morning was good; one-to-one because C is out of town. Not sure about K.
Lessons with guides today were fine. Six back-to-back lessons in 3 hours about fun sciency topics.
Lesson with GG was great; we played an &amp;ldquo;a / the&amp;rdquo; game using coins. Y got a bit confused and I was suprised about that. I think it might have been because M seems to have fibbed, but I let it go.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>work</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/10/24/work/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2016 12:22:20 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/10/24/work/</guid>
      <description>12:22 Monday 24 October 2016 JST Oops I haven&amp;rsquo;t written in a bit. Working right now in Ebisu, from where I need to depart at 15:30 to head down past Shin Yurigaoka for a substitute lesson.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>work</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/10/03/work/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2016 10:53:29 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/10/03/work/</guid>
      <description>10:53 Monday 03 October 2016 JST At work today I hope to fix this installation of CKEditor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>worked at home</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/09/30/worked-at-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2016 20:22:20 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/09/30/worked-at-home/</guid>
      <description>20:22 Friday 30 September 2016 JST Worked at home all day today, basically on Ansible. I found Ubuntu 16.04 is available on AWS as an AMI, so I switched my Ansible playbooks to use it, and then installed git, apache2, php, and apache-php-fpm (I think) because it seems to be needed to get Apache to let PHP tell it what to serve.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>substitute lessons</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/09/28/substitute-lessons/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2016 12:41:18 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/09/28/substitute-lessons/</guid>
      <description>12:41 Wednesday 28 September 2016 JST I subbed for Matt again this week. Each class had one more student than last week, so I guess that was a good sign. I talked about neti with one of the students who was suffering from allergies.
We imagined luxurious vacations in both classes. &amp;ldquo;They will fly to Italy to eat pizza&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;they would fly in a hot air balloon&amp;rdquo; are examples of the grammar structures used in each class.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>work bluh</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/09/27/work-bluh/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2016 20:08:23 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/09/27/work-bluh/</guid>
      <description>20:08 Tuesday 27 September 2016 JST Bluh computer work kinda sucked today; I spent 5 hours on one thing and 3.5 hours on a different thing and made almost 0 progress on them. The second thing was futzing around with .htaccess file, and for 2.5 of the 3.5 hours it actually wasn&amp;rsquo;t being read. facepalm I needed to AllowOverride All in the Apache2 directives&amp;hellip; but do I want to do that on live server?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>early work</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/09/27/early-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2016 05:18:48 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/09/27/early-work/</guid>
      <description>05:18 Tuesday 27 September 2016 JST I woke up without an alarm this morning because I took a big nap yesterday, knowing that I have to wake up earlier than normal to teach a lesson for Matt who is at home in UK at the moment. Train is at 6:29, so I plan to leave the house at 6am.
Better get my butt off my computer and go! Lemme just check hacker news and reddit real quick&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>productive yesterday</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/09/27/productive-yesterday/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2016 04:57:58 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/09/27/productive-yesterday/</guid>
      <description>04:57 Tuesday 27 September 2016 JST After teaching in the morning, I pretty much spent all day playing with Ansible. I now have a vagrant installation that sets up ansible, git, and emacs on a vagrant box on my local machine which creates an ssh keypair (half of which I manually copy to bitbucket). I run setup and it pulls in a git repo and runs setup on that, which asks for an ansible-vault passphrase to unlock my AWS keys and gives me ansible playbooks which I can run to set up VPC + subnet + internet gateway on AWS, launch an ubuntu instance in the subnet, and install git on it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>work</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/09/23/work/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2016 10:47:48 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/09/23/work/</guid>
      <description>10:47 Friday 23 September 2016 JST I&amp;rsquo;m working with Ansible again today. I&amp;rsquo;m creating a set of three repos. One sets up a vagrant box on my local machine and then clones the second repo inside the machine.
The second repo will set up VPC and subnet and internet gateway on AWS then spin up a box in a public subnet. It will clone the third repo on that box.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>work</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/08/30/work/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2016 12:07:12 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/08/30/work/</guid>
      <description>12:07 Tuesday 30 August 2016 JST I added a little ajax action to my DataTables instance. The problem with using table.row.add was my use of Datables 1.9.4 instead of the newer 1.10.x. A-ha!
Thank you, Alan!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>lessons at T near Lazona</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/08/04/lessons-at-t-near-lazona/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2016 17:21:50 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/08/04/lessons-at-t-near-lazona/</guid>
      <description>17:21 Thursday 04 August 2016 JST Had three lessons over a two hour period at T today. Miyako , Mizuho , and Ayaka .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>train work</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/08/02/train-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2016 10:14:45 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/08/02/train-work/</guid>
      <description>10:14 Tuesday 02 August 2016 JST I&amp;rsquo;m headed to work on the local train; we left 新百合ケ丘 at 10:12am. I&amp;rsquo;m not sure what time we&amp;rsquo;ll arrive in 新宿, but I have a seat, my computer, art supplies, and a snack, so I should be able to keep myself entertained until we arrive.
Haha just kidding; my main concern is arriving on time, but yeah I have my computer because I had been reading at home, wondering just how long I could keep going before rushing off to my meeting on time&amp;hellip; hey wait a minute; if I take a local train I can read while going to work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>work</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/07/11/work/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2016 12:53:28 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/07/11/work/</guid>
      <description>12:53 Monday 11 July 2016 JST After a bit of a break (5 days), I&amp;rsquo;m working on Ansible again today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>created security group on AWS with Ansible</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/07/05/created-security-group-on-aws-with-ansible/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2016 09:35:16 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/07/05/created-security-group-on-aws-with-ansible/</guid>
      <description>09:35 Tuesday 05 July 2016 JST Thanks, Travis!
For a long time I got an error: ERROR! &#39;ec2_group&#39; is not a valid attribute for a Play
ERROR! &amp;lsquo;ec2_group&amp;rsquo; is not a valid attribute for a Play My playbook.yml looked fine to me:
- name: Create security group ec2_group: name: &amp;quot;test_security_group&amp;quot; description: &amp;quot;Test security group&amp;quot; region: &amp;quot;ap-northeast-1&amp;quot; rules: - proto: tcp from_port: 22 to_port: 22 cidr_ip: 0.0.0.0/0 - proto: tcp from_port: 80 to_port: 80 cidr_ip: 0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>lesson</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/06/30/lesson/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2016 13:28:38 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/06/30/lesson/</guid>
      <description>13:28 Thursday 30 June 2016 JST Lesson with K and A today featured only K at first; I told her a bit about urbit until A arrived and we talked about her semi-precious gem necklace and other stuff, including urbit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>work</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/06/28/work/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2016 14:37:22 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/06/28/work/</guid>
      <description>14:37 Tuesday 28 June 2016 JST Bah. My computer keeps overheating; kernel_task is hogging 700% of the CPU and I can&amp;rsquo;t get shit done.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Great GG lesson</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/06/23/great-gg-lesson/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2016 20:28:44 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/06/23/great-gg-lesson/</guid>
      <description>20:28 Thursday 23 June 2016 JST Great lesson today with GG class: we finished taking apart the 1TB hard drive, which cost just over $200 in 2009.
(I thoughtlessly destroyed it with magnets; oops!)
I think I net 3000 yen per GG lesson, so I got half the hard drive price back by taking it apart across three lessons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>lessons at T</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/06/23/lessons-at-t/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2016 17:16:19 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/06/23/lessons-at-t/</guid>
      <description>17:16 Thursday 23 June 2016 JST Lessons at T today were good; my five students all had ample questions, and I&amp;rsquo;m beginning to remember their names. It&amp;rsquo;s a bit hard because the lessons are only once every 2 weeks, and they take turns taking lessons, so I might see each of the students once a month for 45 minutes.
I explained how (at current earthly understanding of physics,) a wind turbine must spin (same as aircraft wings): thick leading edge and thin trailing edge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workin</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/06/13/workin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2016 16:40:58 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/06/13/workin/</guid>
      <description>16:40 Monday 13 June 2016 JST Today I had a good lesson this morning; the students really seemed keen, even taking pictures of the notes and recording my voice to use for shadowing later.
Now I&amp;rsquo;m at my computer job (have been here for a bit) and just finishing up some instructions for how to set up a web server on AWS with DB on private subnet of VPC. Fun stuff even if I only understand half of it!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>early fs work</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/04/18/early-fs-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2016 05:22:01 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/04/18/early-fs-work/</guid>
      <description>05:22 Monday 18 April 2016 JST 5am create new image of FS box
cloudfront seems to be serving all CB images find, but not AB
5:15am AB images seem to be back (though server image is not complete)
5:40am started having problems getting new box to work (added it to ELB but it&amp;rsquo;s not serving images)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>fake fs</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/04/16/fake-fs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Apr 2016 13:52:56 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/04/16/fake-fs/</guid>
      <description>13:52 Saturday 16 April 2016 JST Today I&amp;rsquo;m making a fake FS for AB and CB (eventually) because I&amp;rsquo;m testing/practicing making a new one because AWS said they are going to boot the existing one during our prime usage time. eep!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Work</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/04/15/work/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2016 18:21:02 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/04/15/work/</guid>
      <description>18:21 Friday 15 April 2016 JST Been working lots and studying lots; 2 different teachers, 5 lessons per week this week. I will try a new face to face teacher on Sunday (via Jon and Paola), and see if it&amp;rsquo;s worthwhile to go somewhere instead of just doing lessons on Skype..
Been working on AB; I&amp;rsquo;ve added a quick little system that acts as a reminder for AB to contact their clients every once in a while and be like &amp;ldquo;wazaaaa&amp;rdquo; .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>funny at work</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/04/02/funny-at-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2016 11:32:27 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/04/02/funny-at-work/</guid>
      <description> 11:32 Saturday 02 April 2016 JST  ubuntu$ history | grep cron 1009 sudo crontab -e 1127 crontab -e 1128 history | grep crontab 1129 sudo crontab -e 1413 crontab -e 1414 history | grep crontab 1415 sudo crontab -e 1418 sudo crontab -e 1432 crontab -e 1433 history | grep cron 1444 sudo crontab -e 1787 history | grep cron 1788 sudo crontab -e 1790 sudo crontab -e 1793 sudo crontab -e 1805 sudo crontab -e 2001 history | grep cron ubuntu$  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>work work workin</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/03/29/work-work-workin/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2016 12:18:04 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/03/29/work-work-workin/</guid>
      <description>12:18 Tuesday 29 March 2016 JST I&amp;rsquo;ve just moved online some code for AB to hopefully easily and smoothly correct the data that was messed up and then not corrected perfectly last week.
Basically the correction assumed all values started at 0, so didn&amp;rsquo;t write 0 where it thought it didn&amp;rsquo;t need to. So this time I will set everything to 0 first before fixing the data.
But the main issue is that the data is being updated on day-to-day basis incorrectly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>work data</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/03/28/work-data/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2016 07:49:58 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/03/28/work-data/</guid>
      <description>07:49 Monday 28 March 2016 JST HI AB!
some good news: I found a mistake in the data
surprising news: correcting the mistake will make the dom value even a little lower.
I found a mistake in the data for unit 64935
The values are all correct all the way down through December 2015. The value of dom for January 2016 should be 0, but it listed as 43.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>workin</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/03/08/workin/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2016 21:48:10 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/03/08/workin/</guid>
      <description>21:48 Tuesday 08 March 2016 JST Today I worked on CB and AB websites, making some tweaks to CB while AB tests were running. Not A-B tests, but tests on the AB site.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Work</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/02/23/work/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2016 18:31:12 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/02/23/work/</guid>
      <description>18:31 Tuesday 23 February 2016 JST I got three tickets done at work today. For a moment, I had a sense that I should work more diligently. The feeling passed quickly enough, but it was interesting.
I got approval to have the camera guys film at the office, but then the director of the camera guys said he would just film me as a programmer at home. Oh well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>work</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/02/17/work/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Feb 2016 08:25:28 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/02/17/work/</guid>
      <description>08:25 Wednesday 17 February 2016 JST Worked yesterday with Satomi, finishing a ticket, starting a ticket, aborting a ticket. Working now on AB site; trying to get back into the groove.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>did some work</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/01/30/did-some-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2016 11:10:24 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/01/30/did-some-work/</guid>
      <description>11:10 Saturday 30 January 2016 CST Would love to have a project manager for this thing.
Three tickets for HA site, and haven&amp;rsquo;t been able to finish any of them.
They require more info or send to someone else or get corrected files or determine the request was incorrectly stated.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>workin</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/01/27/workin/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2016 10:34:32 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/01/27/workin/</guid>
      <description>10:34 Wednesday 27 January 2016 CST Just getting started doing some work for HN site for Nate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First lesson in a month</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/01/21/first-lesson-in-a-month/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2016 07:04:46 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/01/21/first-lesson-in-a-month/</guid>
      <description>07:04 Thursday 21 January 2016 JST I&amp;rsquo;ve even forgotten what short-code I previously used for this class.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Automated testing FTW</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/01/20/automated-testing-ftw/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2016 12:59:03 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/01/20/automated-testing-ftw/</guid>
      <description>12:59 Wednesday 20 January 2016 JST It&amp;rsquo;s actually not automated testing FTW yet; it&amp;rsquo;s my choice to carefully go through all the tests even though I am anxious to get the changes to live server before I go on vacation FTW.
I have a list of tests that I was performing manually, and am now in the process of performing them all manually just a couple more times as I teach Ghost Inspector how to do them for me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monday I think I was on my computer all day</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/01/18/monday-i-think-i-was-on-my-computer-all-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jan 2016 20:57:48 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/01/18/monday-i-think-i-was-on-my-computer-all-day/</guid>
      <description>(written 20:57 Thursday 21 January 2016 JST) I just noticed a gap in my recent journal entry dates.. I bet I was on my computer all day Monday&amp;hellip; oh but I remember I slept 12 hours (!!) from 8pm to 8am after having a headache after (carrying my heavy bag to and from) the ET Contact weekend at Pyramid Meditation Center near Yanagawa station.
Being on my computer all day doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean I worked all day, but probably included watching an episode of Family Guy, which I remember having done recently.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>fixed a bug that I missed due to lack of testing</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/01/13/fixed-a-bug-that-i-missed-due-to-lack-of-testing/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2016 18:50:53 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/01/13/fixed-a-bug-that-i-missed-due-to-lack-of-testing/</guid>
      <description>18:50 Wednesday 13 January 2016 JST Oops shit. I didn&amp;rsquo;t fully test the system before putting admin server live. That shit won&amp;rsquo;t happen again because I&amp;rsquo;ve got Ghost Inspector on my side, helping me inspect the site. I&amp;rsquo;ve taught it how to test logging in, fucking up the log in, viewing the units list, and the unit edit page, as well as the group-of-units list and the group-of-units edit page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>moe joe cookies</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/01/12/moe-joe-cookies/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2016 18:13:21 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/01/12/moe-joe-cookies/</guid>
      <description>18:13 Tuesday 12 January 2016 JST I haven&amp;rsquo;t been able to log in to my local machine using ngrok.com because of something I haven&amp;rsquo;t probably figured out yet. Earlier today, I realized the problem must be that I&amp;rsquo;m trying to setcookie on the wrong domain, or rather, on the domain my local box sees, and not on ngrok.com.
I can&amp;rsquo;t test it directly because I&amp;rsquo;m currently offline, but I tried to break the cookie here locally, but I can still log in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ghost Inspector 1000 tests per month yay</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/01/11/ghost-inspector-1000-tests-per-month-yay/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jan 2016 12:09:34 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/01/11/ghost-inspector-1000-tests-per-month-yay/</guid>
      <description>12:09 Monday 11 January 2016 JST A few days ago I signed up for Ghost Inspector and thought hmmm I&amp;rsquo;d love to have 1000 tests per month instead of just 100.
Boom they have that option!
We&#39;re glad you&#39;re enjoying the product! Unfortunately, we don&#39;t offer any paid plans that are less than 10,000 test runs/month. However, we do have a promotion with Runscope (our parent company) where your free account will be bumped up from the 100 test runs per month on the default free plan to 1,000 test runs per month if you sign up for both services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>testing local sites</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/01/09/testing-local-sites/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2016 10:27:01 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/01/09/testing-local-sites/</guid>
      <description>10:27 Saturday 09 January 2016 JST I just bought an account on https://ngrok.com so I can use ghost inspector to test my local machines running on virtualbox. Sweet!
I sent a couple emails back and forth with Alan who quickly solved the setup issue I was having. He showed me how I can easily use ngrok to test my site which only exists on my local virtualbox machine via a domain which only exists in my /etc/hosts file:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning a lot about AWS</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/01/05/learning-a-lot-about-aws/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2016 23:51:07 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/01/05/learning-a-lot-about-aws/</guid>
      <description>23:51 Tuesday 05 January 2016 JST I spoke on the phone for 1.5 hours to a guy at AWS support. He was patient, understanding, helpful, and many other things that I appreciated. He summarized the convo for me, pasted below with some parts redacted:
Hi, Thanks for contacting AWS Premium Support. It was a pleasure to speak with you today in relation to the errors your clients encountered when accessing your website CB.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Automated testing is fun!</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/01/05/automated-testing-is-fun/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2016 08:25:48 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/01/05/automated-testing-is-fun/</guid>
      <description>08:25 Tuesday 05 January 2016 JST I woke up early (compared to when I went to sleep) because I had some ideas for doing automated testing. I guess there&amp;rsquo;s no harm in adding some CSS classes to make finding things easier. I may even add a click all that are unselected option if I can&amp;rsquo;t figure out how to do it with CasperJS.
But first I gotta repair a script which runs every 5 minutes via cron.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fixing a bug and setting up automagic tests</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/01/05/fixing-a-bug-and-setting-up-automagic-tests/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2016 02:51:07 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/01/05/fixing-a-bug-and-setting-up-automagic-tests/</guid>
      <description>02:51 Tuesday 05 January 2016 JST By far the large part of my time today was spent in a bit of a panic trying to figure out why the AB site was acting horribly wrong. Not even the most basic thing was working: logged in users couldn&amp;rsquo;t sort nor even filter the properties. Yikes stripes!
I was really close to a major upgrade which was alllllmost working on my local system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Moe Joe mo problems</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/12/29/moe-joe-mo-problems/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Dec 2015 19:05:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/12/29/moe-joe-mo-problems/</guid>
      <description>19:05 Tuesday 29 December 2015 JST Bah the CB website is acting up. I happen to have been in Harajuku so I&amp;rsquo;m heading in to the office now.
21:25 Tuesday 29 December 2015 JST Well, I don&amp;rsquo;t know what caused the problem, but everything seems to be working again. It happened last night for a few hours and again tonight for a few hours, so I guessed it was simply being overloaded by traffic, but Google analytics says it&amp;rsquo;s not particularly swamped right now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>workin</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/12/22/workin/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Dec 2015 17:49:20 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/12/22/workin/</guid>
      <description>17:49 Tuesday 22 December 2015 JST Today:
was able to get my e-money back from Toho Cinemas after I accidentally bought Japanese dubbed Star Wars tickets last night.
got some end of year fixes done for CB site, including those which they want to have done by Friday. yay!
finished a ticket for AB site, though it&amp;rsquo;s not completely tested yet. (gotta test code note written in Hakyll, ya know)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Invoice template</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/12/15/invoice-template/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2015 18:42:46 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/12/15/invoice-template/</guid>
      <description>18:42 Tuesday 15 December 2015 JST Nate seems to have this need for things to be just the way they need to be. So for the nth time in n years, we agreed I&amp;rsquo;ll use the template he sends me to create invoices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Got v1 of AB sortable reports done</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/12/09/got-v1-of-ab-sortable-reports-done/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2015 11:31:54 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/12/09/got-v1-of-ab-sortable-reports-done/</guid>
      <description>11:31 Wednesday 09 December 2015 JST The output columns can be sorted, but not searched.
I plan to add &amp;ldquo;back to list&amp;rdquo; functionality by saving the page data on each page so it can be recreated when going back.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Finished two CB tickets</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/12/08/finished-two-cb-tickets/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2015 17:00:18 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/12/08/finished-two-cb-tickets/</guid>
      <description>17:00 Tuesday 08 December 2015 JST Meeting with Satomi was fine as usual. yay! We got her inbox filters fixed so she actually sees emails sent from redmine when I do updates; because those emails were skipping her inbox (and redmine folder/tag) she didn&amp;rsquo;t see when I finished things and so didn&amp;rsquo;t approve them until the next meeting.
Now they can preview things and I removed the unused sharing options (Mixi, Google+, Pinterest) from the (demo) site.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yay AB defined_report thing works for a few different reports</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/12/06/yay-ab-defined_report-thing-works-for-a-few-different-reports/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Dec 2015 16:11:09 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/12/06/yay-ab-defined_report-thing-works-for-a-few-different-reports/</guid>
      <description>16:11 Sunday 06 December 2015 JST I need to make (sure) it work(s) for reports with JOINs in the query, but at least it&amp;rsquo;s better than what it was earlier today!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>working today</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/11/24/working-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Nov 2015 21:50:54 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/11/24/working-today/</guid>
      <description>21:50 Tuesday 24 November 2015 JST This morning I worked a bit on Apple TV app, but couldn&amp;rsquo;t figure out how to set the preferredFocus to the correct view. I see what the docs say, and I tried to click and drag the thing in the interface, but it simply didn&amp;rsquo;t work. Bah.
I&amp;rsquo;ll skip it for now and move on to the next bit.
Then at CB I increased the images on two of the site indices to be 90 by 90 pixels instead of 70 by 70.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Selenium</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/10/28/selenium/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2015 19:16:05 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/10/28/selenium/</guid>
      <description>19:16 Wednesday 28 October 2015 JST Speaking of (not) wasting time, I may take the time to set up Selenium and learn how to use it to test the AB site. I&amp;rsquo;ve spent a couple days testing and re-testing before doing this major change which is due Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Preview_key</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/10/27/preview_key/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2015 18:55:37 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/10/27/preview_key/</guid>
      <description>18:55 Tuesday 27 October 2015 JST Today S at CB requested they be able to preview articles before they&amp;rsquo;re published. I was like, &amp;ldquo;um, it&amp;rsquo;s already finished,&amp;rdquo; because Alfonzo wrote that functionality ages ago.
&amp;ldquo;Wow! I didn&amp;rsquo;t know that.&amp;rdquo;
So now they want to preview other things, so I&amp;rsquo;ll be copying his code to those other not-yet-previewable things.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>today at work</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/09/01/today-at-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2015 18:38:32 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/09/01/today-at-work/</guid>
      <description>18:38 Tuesday 01 September 2015 JST Satomi came down at the perfect time; I had just finished and committed a set of changes for a new process for the AB site. They want new data added to the historical primary tables, gleaned from data in the secondary tables (basically log tables).
Basically things in the primary table can be active or inactive. We have a log of when they were activated and deactivated.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>breakage</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/08/24/breakage/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2015 16:27:41 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/08/24/breakage/</guid>
      <description>16:27 Monday 24 August 2015 JST So S-san at AB used the new function that I added, but it didn&amp;rsquo;t seem to fully work. I tested it locally so I&amp;rsquo;m not sure what&amp;rsquo;s wrong. Basically it&amp;rsquo;s supposed to edit historical data, but it didn&amp;rsquo;t seem to work for one set of tables.
While looking at the historical tables to see what had changed, I found a record missing from all the tables!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AB site version 3 work</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/07/17/ab-site-version-3-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jul 2015 12:23:32 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/07/17/ab-site-version-3-work/</guid>
      <description>12:23 Saturday 18 July 2015 JST Yesterday I spent a few hours working on AB site; they basically want a new login type for the frontend, so I need to restructure how the logins are processed. Basically I had put the email address in the R table because only Rs can log in to the frontend, and we need to email Rs from the backend. But now Os can also login to the frontend, and I don&amp;rsquo;t want to check two tables (because it will soon be three or four or 95) against login credentials.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AB site updates</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/06/29/ab-site-updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2015 21:20:32 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/06/29/ab-site-updates/</guid>
      <description>21:20 Monday 29 June 2015 JST Yesterday or maybe this morning I finished a relatively significant change to the AB site. Now they can edit some records which were never meant to be edited, just logged&amp;hellip; but the logs are of human-driven changes and sometimes they have errors which need to be fixed, so they need to be fixed in the log as well. Fair enough!
Then got another request to log one more thing in that log.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>good shite</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/06/16/good-shite/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jun 2015 18:08:26 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/06/16/good-shite/</guid>
      <description>18:08 Tuesday 16 June 2015 JST got some pretty good shite done at work today. S and I have set up weekly meetings and they&amp;rsquo;ve been pretty productive. Today we closed 3 tickets right off the bat (she hadn&amp;rsquo;t seen that I finished them during the week) and probably closed a couple others today. There are still some outliers I don&amp;rsquo;t know how to solve yet, but generally speaking we are making much faster progress than before (when I didn&amp;rsquo;t have meetings with her during which I can ask questions, usually some variant of &amp;ldquo;can you be more specific?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>to do at work today</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/05/26/to-do-at-work-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2015 10:42:29 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/05/26/to-do-at-work-today/</guid>
      <description>10:42 Tuesday 26 May 2015 JST  Figure out why proposed fix to 2613 ain&amp;rsquo;t working (and fix it) meet with S and Y get new subdomains into DNS  11:15 Finished #1 above. It turns out it was working, oops, nevermind.
15:39 actually #3 isn&amp;rsquo;t done yet, but I&amp;rsquo;ve done as much as possible for now. It&amp;rsquo;s weird. There&amp;rsquo;s a website which exists at t.example.com but it&amp;rsquo;s not shown in the list of DNS records at the example.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>workin</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/05/13/workin/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2015 13:35:08 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/05/13/workin/</guid>
      <description>13:35 Wednesday 13 May 2015 JST Today for CB I did 1&amp;frasl;3 of a ticket which I split into 3 tickets, primarily because they reference different websites, one of which isn&amp;rsquo;t even in the same repo.
I&amp;rsquo;ll do the second ticket soon, and may have to ask Andrew for help on the third.
18:35 On the train now after having finished my lesson in Fukuura. I have alternating classes in that timeslot and I expected (and prepared for) one class, but the other class came because they had no lesson during Golden Week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fun day at work</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/05/12/fun-day-at-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2015 17:35:08 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/05/12/fun-day-at-work/</guid>
      <description>17:35 Tuesday 12 May 2015 JST Today we had a meeting that we should have held some time ago! It was the first of what I hope will be weekly meetings. なちゃん translated and we got a lot done, including translating some things that I hadn&amp;rsquo;t had translated before so couldn&amp;rsquo;t do the work!
Hopefully we&amp;rsquo;ll be aable to chew through the backlog of tickets and they&amp;rsquo;ll be happy and I&amp;rsquo;ll feel helpful/productive/happy yay!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>worked a bit</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/04/14/worked-a-bit/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2015 16:59:49 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/04/14/worked-a-bit/</guid>
      <description>16:59 Tuesday 14 April 2015 JST Finally got approval for a thing I did like 3 weeks ago, so I moved it to the live server. Then they were like, yeah but what about this: it&amp;rsquo;s not working. and showed me the URL
www.example.com/report/xml  um, yeah, that&amp;rsquo;s because I told you it was
demo.example.com/news/xml  It&amp;rsquo;s on the demo server because you haven&amp;rsquo;t approved it and it&amp;rsquo;s the news URL because that what you originally requested to be updated.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>fun working day and met Scean</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/04/13/fun-working-day-and-met-scean/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Apr 2015 18:30:10 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/04/13/fun-working-day-and-met-scean/</guid>
      <description>18:30 Monday 13 April 2015 JST Just finished eating sakura ice cream with Scean, Kasagawa, and another guy whose name I didn&amp;rsquo;t get. We talked a lot (though I didn&amp;rsquo;t ask for permission to transcribe his interesting stories)!
This was all after about 6 hours of group lessons, all coordinated from the front of the room; basically the lesson content wasn&amp;rsquo;t difficult but all the coordination took a bit of focus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>workin</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/04/07/workin/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Apr 2015 11:47:10 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/04/07/workin/</guid>
      <description>11:47 Tuesday 07 April 2015 JST I&amp;rsquo;ve essentially finished a maze today for a person on Fiverr.
12:20 Finished changes to the bodyandsoul dev site.
14:50 I made some changes to the AB website which only I can see. They asked me to estimate how long it would take and I ended up just doing it to confirm my time estimate was accurate. I added code like, &amp;ldquo;if userID == 1&amp;rdquo; to block the execution unless I&amp;rsquo;m the one logged in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>bah doing it all over again</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/04/02/bah-doing-it-all-over-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2015 17:50:13 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/04/02/bah-doing-it-all-over-again/</guid>
      <description>17:50 Thursday 02 April 2015 JST The project was originally described as &amp;ldquo;keep the same structure and just change all the text.&amp;rdquo;
Cool sounds good, and it paid relatively well.
Once I accepted, it was, &amp;ldquo;oh and put up a full page banner with four clickable images below it while we change all the text and change all the images&amp;rdquo;
Fine fuckit so I put the banner up and I changed all the images; it was still fair pay for the total amount of work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>replacing images on Body and Soul website</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/03/24/replacing-images-on-body-and-soul-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2015 13:11:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/03/24/replacing-images-on-body-and-soul-website/</guid>
      <description>##13:11 Tuesday 24 March 2015 JST##
Headed in to sbstrm now to replace some images on the new Body and Soul website. Sho said there were more than he expected, but I expect I can finish them all in 4 hours before I have to leave for Mutsumi&amp;rsquo;s lesson.
##6pm
5:55 pm suddenly arrived and I was like oh fuck and ran out the door to go to the toy store on the way to Muchan&amp;rsquo;s lesson.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workin late</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/03/23/workin-late/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2015 22:43:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/03/23/workin-late/</guid>
      <description>##22:43 Monday 23 March 2015 JST##
Workin&amp;rsquo; late with Sho on a new site for Body and Soul; they put on an event each year in May so we&amp;rsquo;re prepping for the announcement.
I put their original site in a git repo and have their banner page on the master branch, but edits to the new site were started from a few commits back. Blarg. I agree with my decisison to start edits from a few commits back, but maybe I should have two &amp;ldquo;master&amp;rdquo; branches: one master-banner and one master-site, or something.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>tonight</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/03/07/tonight/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2015 21:54:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/03/07/tonight/</guid>
      <description>##21:54 Saturday 07 March 2015 JST##
Tonight I set up a repo for a site I&amp;rsquo;m supposed to temporarily replace with a full page banner ad on Monday. I think I&amp;rsquo;ll call the site BS or maybe BSJ.
It&amp;rsquo;s running in csh not bash, so my preferred git log replacement looks like ass.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Added genres to CB DB</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/02/21/added-genres-to-cb-db/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2015 14:30:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/02/21/added-genres-to-cb-db/</guid>
      <description>##14:30 Saturday 21 February 2015 JST##
I&amp;rsquo;ve been taking copious notes while doing updates for the CB website; Alfonzo will be moving to a new department soon so I won&amp;rsquo;t be able to bug him as much with questions.
Today I finished adding the genres to the staging server.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Done did today</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/02/20/done-did-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2015 18:05:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/02/20/done-did-today/</guid>
      <description>##18:05 Friday 20 February 2015 JST##
Recently I have been posting &amp;ldquo;Daily meditation threads&amp;rdquo; on /r/bitTippers, encouraging myself and others to take some time to sit quietly each day.
The posts get about an 80% approval rate, with some people saying &amp;ldquo;wow thank you!&amp;rdquo; and some saying variants of &amp;ldquo;no way jose&amp;rdquo;. Fun stuff!
Today was the fourth such thread, I think.
I worked on a maze for a guy on Fiverr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AB site testing</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/02/19/ab-site-testing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2015 17:44:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/02/19/ab-site-testing/</guid>
      <description>##16:44 Thursday 19 February 2015 JST##
Spent 6 hours working on AB site, planning for how to migrate them to their new server(s) (web + DB). That was while emailing S about some problem with server running out of memory. That ain&amp;rsquo;t good. I boosted the allowed memory in config file, but would love to figure out what the actual problem is (more precisely than there&amp;rsquo;s a lotta records!)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Great office space</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/02/17/great-office-space/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2015 12:30:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/02/17/great-office-space/</guid>
      <description>##12:30 Tuesday 17 February 2015 JST##
Sweet as. I came to Wired Cafe in Atre and asked if they have an electrical outlet. Not only do they, but to use it I get to sit in a glass-wall corner overlooking Azalea and the front of Kawasaki station.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Today worked on AB DB</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/02/16/today-worked-on-ab-db/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2015 22:32:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/02/16/today-worked-on-ab-db/</guid>
      <description>##22:32 Monday 16 February 2015 JST##
AB DB primarily consists of two big tables. Table U has 77k records, and 160 columns. Table B has maybe 40k records and maybe 70 columns. There&amp;rsquo;s a 1-to-many relationship from B to U. Doing joins on them takes about 3 or 4 seconds.
That ain&amp;rsquo;t good, considering the joins are done all the frickin time.
I guess that&amp;rsquo;s why when I got the original data, a lot of what&amp;rsquo;s now in the B table was in the U table.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Studio Soness</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/02/13/studio-soness/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2015 20:54:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/02/13/studio-soness/</guid>
      <description>##20:54 Friday 13 February 2015 JST##
Full day of shooting at Studio Soness! In 8 hours, we got about 1 hour of video recorded.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Turned in my key card</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/01/13/turned-in-my-key-card/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/01/13/turned-in-my-key-card/</guid>
      <description>##17:09 Tuesday 13 January 2015 JST##
I turned in my key card today in Harajuku. I guess I won&amp;rsquo;t be working there anymore, but they were like, &amp;ldquo;we&amp;rsquo;ll contact you.&amp;rdquo; I shan&amp;rsquo;t hold my breath.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>copy database</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/12/25/copy-database/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/12/25/copy-database/</guid>
      <description>##12:31 Thursday 25 December 2014 JST##
Copying a database over to clone the website; I&amp;rsquo;m toasting most of the data, but I think it will still work as a demo site.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>actual work</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/12/08/actual-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/12/08/actual-work/</guid>
      <description>##Monday 8 Dec 2014
(written 10:38 Tuesday 09 December 2014 JST)
I spoke with Nate and Alfonzo yesterday about work stuff; Alfonzo has been too busy to do it so I may get a chance to make a few extra dollars. The contract may be terminated though, not sure yet. This is for the CB project we started six years ago. They&amp;rsquo;ve been on a &amp;ldquo;maintenance&amp;rdquo; contract but asking for lots of changes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meeting with Nate</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/04/meeting-with-nate/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/04/meeting-with-nate/</guid>
      <description>##16:24 Tuesday 04 November 2014 JST##
Speaking with Nate before I go to teach M&amp;amp;M in Harajuku tonight. JB emailed and asked if I can work for them 3 days over the next week and a half.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Started Phase 3 of AB website</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/01/29/started-phase-3-of-ab-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/01/29/started-phase-3-of-ab-website/</guid>
      <description>##4pm Wednesday 29 Jan 2014 JST##
Just finished meeting with Tomomi and Sho about phase three of their website. I&amp;rsquo;m thankful that Tomomi took into consideration the existing technologies we&amp;rsquo;ve used on the site when planning how to do the next steps. My next steps are to create some rough mockups and estimate time required to make the changes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>lawnchair to solve a different thing at work</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2013/05/08/lawnchair-to-solve-a-different-thing-at-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2013 19:27:32 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2013/05/08/lawnchair-to-solve-a-different-thing-at-work/</guid>
      <description>##19:27 Wednesday 08 May 2013
7:10pm Wednesday 8 May 2013
I was thinking recently how I didn&amp;rsquo;t use lawnchair to keep track of which items were on a page when coming back to it.
But today I did use lawnchair for a different thing, mostly because I was already using lawnchair for a similar issue. There&amp;rsquo;s a page which uses Datatables to display lists of units in the system. When clicking to view a particular unit, there are previous and next buttons on the page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>yesterday at work</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2013/05/08/yesterday-at-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2013 06:43:31 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2013/05/08/yesterday-at-work/</guid>
      <description>##06:43 Wednesday 08 May 2013
6:38am Wednesday 8 May 2013
Yesterday at work I got the pagination to be ajax driven if javascript is enabled and GET driven if javascript is not enabled.
I&amp;rsquo;ve started to cut a couple corners as the project is a bit overdue. For example, instead of figure out how to redisplay the same units when clicking back to the map page (I&amp;rsquo;d probably use Lawnchair), I just open units in a new tab.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ajax at work</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2013/04/26/ajax-at-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2013 08:00:47 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2013/04/26/ajax-at-work/</guid>
      <description>##08:00 Friday 26 April 2013
7:04am Friday 26 April 2013
I found some code online in Perl that showed an awesome fast way to do clustering of pins on a map. I&amp;rsquo;ll probably post the code on SO where many people have been asking how to do it. That might make up for the points I lost yesterday by asking a question.
When a map marker is clicked, I load the units associated with it via ajax.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>good day at work</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2013/04/10/good-day-at-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2013 21:45:17 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2013/04/10/good-day-at-work/</guid>
      <description>##21:45 Wednesday 10 April 2013
8:57pm Wednesday 10 April 2013
Pretty good day; our new server on AWS had been barfing hourly errors like, &amp;ldquo;the MySQL server has gone away&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;could not connect to mySQL server&amp;rdquo; even though 99.n% of the connections were fine. We had been using MySQL 5.6, and certainly I may not have had it set up right. Once I instantiated a server with 5.5 (and reverted the DB to MyISAM tables for those with FULLTEXT indices), it has worked perfectly fine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>new server for AB</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2013/03/30/new-server-for-ab/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2013 10:57:32 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2013/03/30/new-server-for-ab/</guid>
      <description>##10:57 Saturday 30 March 2013
10:55am Saturday 30 March 2013
Came in to work today to move AB from server which we didn&amp;rsquo;t totally control to one which we control a lot more. We still don&amp;rsquo;t have to touch the hardware, but now we have sudo access as needed.
The move was smooth; the longest part was waiting for DNS to update.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>closed some redmine tickets</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2013/01/07/closed-some-redmine-tickets/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jan 2013 21:48:45 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2013/01/07/closed-some-redmine-tickets/</guid>
      <description>##21:48 Monday 07 January 2013
I found an slow, but easy way to close redmine tickets. Today I asked about some that have been lingering from the beginning of the project, and Shirata-san said those features are no longer needed. Nice(?)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>notes to self on the final day of the world</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2012/12/21/notes-to-self-on-the-final-day-of-the-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Dec 2012 18:43:04 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2012/12/21/notes-to-self-on-the-final-day-of-the-world/</guid>
      <description>##18:43 Friday 21 December 2012
because Monday is a holiday, I figure my brain will need some notes to reload its current state. Some notes on my desk point to a URL that will result in the notes here, spewed out by code in progress:
in code above line 64, we need to fill in the default email from site_text factory (into array shown below) Array ( [renter_id] =&amp;gt; 23 [to_name] =&amp;gt; doug e fresh [to_email] =&amp;gt; doug@e.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>working on front end&#39;s back end</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2012/12/10/working-on-front-ends-back-end/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Dec 2012 22:50:51 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2012/12/10/working-on-front-ends-back-end/</guid>
      <description>##22:50 Monday 10 December 2012
The AB project has classes I created a year ago, at which time were the next iteration of our in-house framework. Six months ago we created the next iteration, which handles multi-lingual sites a bit more elegantly.
So now the AB project&amp;rsquo;s front end will be using the new classes while the back end is still on the old classes. But the front end has some classes in the back end so they can make updates to the public facing site.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>news at work</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2012/12/06/news-at-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2012 21:27:39 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2012/12/06/news-at-work/</guid>
      <description>##21:27 Thursday 06 December 2012
We&amp;rsquo;ll be moving soon, though haven&amp;rsquo;t yet confirmed our new place. Hopefully it will be near The Pink Cow in Roppongi, so I&amp;rsquo;ll be able to hang out there a bit more easily.
In other news, I&amp;rsquo;m getting the reporting engine a bit more completed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>pushed 72 commits to github</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2012/12/05/pushed-72-commits-to-github/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2012 15:36:56 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2012/12/05/pushed-72-commits-to-github/</guid>
      <description>##15:36 Wednesday 05 December 2012
So sad that it&amp;rsquo;s all closed source, but I just pushed the first version of the reporting system to our client&amp;rsquo;s admin site. It uses backbone to do most of its goodness, including: add fields for filtering, add fields for output, run the report, and copy the report for more reporting fun!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I wanna know how to asynchronously save selections in a multiselect dropdown</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2012/11/28/i-wanna-know-how-to-asynchronously-save-selections-in-a-multiselect-dropdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2012 15:12:40 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2012/11/28/i-wanna-know-how-to-asynchronously-save-selections-in-a-multiselect-dropdown/</guid>
      <description>##15:12 Wednesday 28 November 2012
So I asked this question on SO:
https://stackoverflow.com/questions/13598834/detect-select-status-of-options-in-a-multiselect-with-backbone-picky
There may be a slick way to do it without Backbone.Picky; it&amp;rsquo;s curious that Derick hasn&amp;rsquo;t touched Backbone.Picky in 6 months (since May 2012).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>workin on my backbone</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2012/11/27/workin-on-my-backbone/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2012 21:45:25 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2012/11/27/workin-on-my-backbone/</guid>
      <description>##21:45 Tuesday 27 November 2012
Today at work I stopped trying to convert my code into a Marionette app; I just don&amp;rsquo;t seem to have enough smerts to do it yet. I&amp;rsquo;m gonna try again tomorrow, making a Marionette app from scratch. Well, from a semi blank js slate, so hopefully it will go a bit more easily.
The code I&amp;rsquo;ve got so far uses Backbone to do some pretty sweet ajax compared to writing all the ajax queries in jQuery.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Insanity at work</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/09/27/insanity-at-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/09/27/insanity-at-work/</guid>
      <description>10:05am JST Saturday 27 September 2003
Well, it may be coming to an end. Monster-good-stories may be coming soon.
 Greetings Robert, My name is M____. Through a very convoluted path of rumors and faxes I found your website by request of my Japanese wife. Journal entry 12:19 am JST Friday 26 September 2003 is making its rounds! Apparently there is a pissed off mother who ready your message and interpreted it as unprofessional.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>work</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/06/30/work/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/06/30/work/</guid>
      <description>8:20pm Friday 30 June 2000
I&amp;rsquo;ve essentially started over my generic survey project. My goal this time is to make it so generic that we can just drop information into about 20 variables and a few datasets and bang. New survey.
So far I&amp;rsquo;ve gotten the first page 1&amp;frasl;3 of the way finished. Great job, Rob!
Tonight hopefully Wende and I are going to watch a movie. We might also see Chicken Run tomorrow morning!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Work</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/06/23/work/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/06/23/work/</guid>
      <description>6:45am CDT Friday 23 June 2000
Yesterday at work seemed strange because literally I didn&amp;rsquo;t have a project that needed attention. Two projects are on hold as we wait for further information from our clients. Yay!
So I began working on some generic macro type things that will hopefully allow us to code more efficiently on future projects. Since I&amp;rsquo;m beginning to get a better grasp on SAS and how it can be used (and how we use it at work), this is pretty much the first time I&amp;rsquo;ve been able to do this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>work</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/06/21/work/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/06/21/work/</guid>
      <description>12:15am CDT Thursday 22 June 2000
Work &amp;ldquo;today&amp;rdquo; was unique in that I actually caught up with all the projects. By this I mean that there was no more SAS programming to be done until we hear more from our clients. Wow!
I transcribed some 1991 journal entries, recognizing that I&amp;rsquo;m more inspired to do so now that Molly has offered to help. :-)
Tomorrow at work we will celebrate Kevin&amp;rsquo;s birthday!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>work</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/06/15/work/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/06/15/work/</guid>
      <description>5:48pm Thursday 15 June 2000
So I&amp;rsquo;m working now on a project I&amp;rsquo;ll call the DTRU Project (If I refer to the KTRU Project, it&amp;rsquo;s probably a type-o). DTRU Project is a subset of the Big Monster Project that I had been working on for months.
I have been commenting out huge sections of code that I think we will eventually need as the DTRU project experiences Feature Creep, but for now, it does not need.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Work</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/05/09/work/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/05/09/work/</guid>
      <description>Work 6:31pm CDT Tuesday 9 May 2000
A couple of interesting things at work today:
 With some help from Kevin, I rewrote a screen on our big project. This screen is called rateWho; it displays a list of names for whom an individual may provide feedback. Originally, I designed the screen so that if a person had missed the time-frame to rate someone, that someone&amp;rsquo;s name would not show up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Work2</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/05/09/work2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/05/09/work2/</guid>
      <description>Work 11:33pm CDT Tuesday 9 May 2000
Ack. I just got a call from Kevin. He booted our webserver tonight and it&#39;s not coming back up. After it checks the memory, finds the disks, gets past the &#34;press spacebar to use last known good configuration&#34;, it flashes error codes and restarts. I&#39;m going in to work now. 3:45am CDT Wednesday 10 May 2000
Sure enough, when I arrive the server was still rebooting itself as described above.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workin</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/04/30/workin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/04/30/workin/</guid>
      <description>9:30am CDT Sunday 30 April 2000
Wende is at work all day today (9am to 7pm) and I intend to do a lot around the house. I&amp;rsquo;ve sent out The Feel Good Net, and wrote a letter to Karen.
Now for the house, I&amp;rsquo;m going to Home Depot to purchase some motor &amp;ldquo;dimmer&amp;rdquo; switches for our ceiling fans so we can control their speed from the wall outlet!
I also plan to flea-spray my old bed (which has been quarantined in the garage since I moved my junque two weeks ago) and move it to the guest bedroom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>work</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/03/28/work/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/03/28/work/</guid>
      <description>12:48pm Tuesday 28 March 2000
Both of my bosses are pausing for lunch today, which means the work load is manageable, and therefore I will likely get to meet with them about full timeliness and maybe DSL at me and Wen&amp;rsquo;s new house!
Honestly, I think the prospect of them paying for DSL is pretty good; it&amp;rsquo;s relatively inexpensive and will allow me to work from home on projects and problems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>work</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/03/27/work/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/03/27/work/</guid>
      <description>9:33pm CST Monday 27 March 2000
Probably the coolest most imminent unknown in my life is around work: I&amp;rsquo;m going to be meeting with my bosses tomorrow to discuss me shifting to a full time position, with paid medical benefits! The unknown part is my salary. How much do I want? How much do I think I&amp;rsquo;m worth?
I can start by calculating my hourly wage out to 40 hours per week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>work</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/03/22/work/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/03/22/work/</guid>
      <description>7:28am CST Wednesday 22 March 2000
I&amp;rsquo;ll call it lovely synchronicity, and not manic work work work to make money for the new house. Yesterday I worked 14.5 hours to complete my portion of the SAS project, then handed it over at 9pm to my boss to do the rest. This version of the project goes into production today as a pilot for a small group of people before we set the masses of users loose on it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>coding</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/03/21/coding/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/03/21/coding/</guid>
      <description>12:07pm Tuesday 21 March 2000
I&amp;rsquo;ve been working diligently for the past 4.5 days on this SAS stuff, and my SAS brain is getting pretty smart (I think). Yesterday I wrote my most complex SAS program ever - it merges datasets, creates datasets dynamically, updates the datasets on disk according to user preferences.. Good nerdy computer stuff.
There are a couple of things I still haven&amp;rsquo;t been able to figure out - some aspects of writing a new row to dataset, and keeping track of iterations&amp;hellip; simple in concept, but I just don&amp;rsquo;t know the syntax.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>work1</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/03/17/work1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/03/17/work1/</guid>
      <description>Work 3:30pm CST Friday 17 March 2000
(transcribed from my diary)
Today I&#39;m working on a big ol&#39; SAS project and I&#39;ve drwan out flow charts on my big sheets of paper. (big = 25.5&#34; X 11&#34; (from Scholars&#39; Community at UH)). Work flow is good; project is due mid next week. I&#39;m working on it tomorrow too and maybe Sunday. Missing Centex (Ultimate tourney in Austin) to work. 6:20pm CST Friday 17 March 2000</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>trauma</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/03/08/trauma/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/03/08/trauma/</guid>
      <description>6:41p wednesday 8 march 2000
ACK
All day I&amp;rsquo;ve been doing great coding here at work (all day after KTRU) and then I was asked to reboot a machine. I rebooted it properly I thought, but turns out I mis-chose one of the startup options.
Ack ack ack ack
30 minutes in mental agony standing behind my boss as he tried to figure out how to fix it. I had no idea how to help, AND I&amp;rsquo;m supposed to be somewhere at 6:30.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>workin</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/03/07/workin/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/03/07/workin/</guid>
      <description>5:49pm Tuesday 7 March 2000
Welp, Wende and I looked at the little house across the street. I thought it was cool, but she found the bedrooms to be too small, and it had an extra garage thingy converted to a dog/cat grooming salon. She felt it would be wasted space, and realistically, she&amp;rsquo;s right.
We requested from Diane our credit ratings, to see what kind of loan we could get and stuff like that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>work</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/03/05/work/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/03/05/work/</guid>
      <description>12:43pm Sunday 5 March 2000
Heh. That&amp;rsquo;s funny. I just realized I wrote February for the previous entry instead of March.
I&amp;rsquo;m at work now, designing a desk addition thing that will allow me to clear of the cluttery crap from my desk. Papers, books, pictures, hard drive, fork, plate, water bottles, grocery bag, CDs, glue stick, floppy disks, telephone, binder, tools, paper paper paper all clutter my desk now. I believe that if I had more place to put it all, I could keep the desk surface less covered in crap so I could actually use my desk for things like writing or coloring or something.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>work</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/03/02/work/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/03/02/work/</guid>
      <description>Work work work 9:01pm CST Thursday 2 March 2000
Today I basically worked all day. Woke up crazy early and decided therefore to do laundry!! Two great things about that:
 My laundry is now complete! I found Wende&amp;rsquo;s Sacagawea dollar! 
I had left her new dollar coin in my shorts pocket. Now we know what they will look like after a nice laundering. Not brilliant shiny, but still golden in color.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>work</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1999/12/30/work/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Dec 1999 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1999/12/30/work/</guid>
      <description>Today I read Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s installation manual for Win NT 4.0 Server. Not particularly informative, but it gave some good information. Then I got the wonderful phone call from Wade at the computer place. &amp;ldquo;Your computers are ready.&amp;rdquo;
Wow!
I&amp;rsquo;m thankful that he asked, &amp;ldquo;would you like us to put the wheels on your server?&amp;rdquo; because otherwise I woulda just driven out there in Scott, my little Camry and said, &amp;ldquo;load &amp;lsquo;em up!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>work-etc</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1999/12/22/work-etc/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 1999 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1999/12/22/work-etc/</guid>
      <description>22 December 1999
Wow. 3 days till Christmas; 10 days till 2000!!
Today at work I finalized purchase orders for three machines!! This is a first for me on this scale, and with this level of precision piece by piece construction.
The data server will be a dual PIII 500 mhz machine with 256meg ram, four 9.1gig hard drives (scsi ultra 2, 10,000 rpm) arranged into a RAID 5 array with a hot spare, single channel raid controller that can handle 15 physical drives, 8 gig tape backup, two NIC 10&amp;frasl;100 cards, dual power supply in a big tower case with 12 drive bays, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>work late</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1999/12/17/work-late/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 1999 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1999/12/17/work-late/</guid>
      <description>1:35am
I logged 11 hours today, 9 of which go to DSL switchover.
Was not able to get the mail server happy. We can receive email, but not send it; the mail server thinks our new IP addresses are hackers trying to use our server as a mail relay. (This is a technique used to spam people; our server won&amp;rsquo;t allow it.) I don&amp;rsquo;t know where to add our IP addresses and say, &amp;ldquo;hey!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>work</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1999/12/05/work/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Dec 1999 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1999/12/05/work/</guid>
      <description>Yay!
Great fun at work today; got to learn some new SAS stuff. I pretty much don&amp;rsquo;t like the language - it&amp;rsquo;s not strictly structured like C, sloppy variable typing and sloppy function calls. but I can handle it!
Oh, and the best thing of all- I asked if I could be paid today for the past week of work instead of waiting until next official payday, and Karla was like, &amp;ldquo;no problem!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>work praise</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1999/12/02/work-praise/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 1999 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1999/12/02/work-praise/</guid>
      <description>I really love my job. I just got this message from my boss.
&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;Original Message&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash; From: Karla (Rob&amp;rsquo;s boss) Sent: Thursday, December 02, 1999 4:23 PM To: Rob Nugen Subject: Good job!
It gives me great reassurance to overhear you talking with the tech people at Savvis as well as other places. You sound confident and you know what you are talking about.
Thanks for working with us.
K.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>laundry work</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1999/10/07/laundry-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Oct 1999 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1999/10/07/laundry-work/</guid>
      <description>7 october 1999
Today it was decidedly cold when I woke up! I&amp;rsquo;ve been sleepin&amp;rsquo; with only a sheet for the past some weeks, and my bedroom window is open so Spot can get in and out via his tree. But this morning I woke up and brrrr! It was like 60 degrees! I couldn&amp;rsquo;t find my comforter in my sleepy state, so I grabbed my sleeping bag and recuddled myself up for a bit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>work</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1991/12/26/work/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 1991 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1991/12/26/work/</guid>
      <description>2:53PM Thursday Dec 26, 1991
(transcribed from Book Two of my diary)
I&#39;m at home for lunch right now. I parked at a parking meter under Pierce Elevated. I put enough money in for 9 hours. When I went to lunch, so that no one could use my time, I put a brown bag that said, &#34;Out Of Order&#34; over the meter. Pretty sneaky... I got a picture of Joy today.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>