<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>colleen on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/colleen/</link>
    <description>Recent content in colleen on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2019 09:01:03 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/colleen/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>On time for flight to IAH</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/10/04/on-time-for-flight-to-iah/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2019 09:01:03 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/10/04/on-time-for-flight-to-iah/</guid>
      <description>Yay Colleen for adulting me safely to the airport! As we gave huge hugs at the drop off area, we joked about adulting and I asked her to let me know if she figures it out!
Great to see a snippet of her life in Seattle.
I wrote bye to Colleen as I was on the jetway, but it did not go through because apparently no wifi there.
Flight departure prep now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Good morning in Seattle</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/10/04/good-morning-in-seattle/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2019 06:53:10 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/10/04/good-morning-in-seattle/</guid>
      <description>(written 09:53 Friday 04 October 2019 PDT)
This morning Colleen woke me up at 6:40 as I hoped to leave by 7am for the airport. I was shocked to know Ryan had already left; I didn&amp;rsquo;t notice him at all while I was sleeping.
I am grateful that Colleen woke me up after I had not set an alarm or anything; I was just able to conk out asleep last night and she handled all the details.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Super great day with Colleen</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/10/04/super-great-day-with-colleen/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2019 00:07:01 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/10/04/super-great-day-with-colleen/</guid>
      <description>(written 00:07 Friday 04 October 2019 PDT)
Colleen had to wait an extra hour for me to go through immigration and customs in Seattle. Once we hung out, though, it was like no time had passed!
                          
Lively laughy fun dinner with Colleen and Ryan at their house while eating pizza.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Awesome connection &#43; synchronicity</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/10/03/awesome-connection-synchronicity/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2019 18:19:11 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/10/03/awesome-connection-synchronicity/</guid>
      <description>Wandering a bit aimlessly, I discovered there&amp;rsquo;s a lounge where certain customers can chill and maybe get food and drinks.. I am apparently not one of those customers, so I don&amp;rsquo;t know!
Rejected, but not too dejected, I noticed an information booth so went to talk to them. I found out exactly what kind of customer is allowed (over 50,000 miles), but she wasn&amp;rsquo;t able to look up the mileage I have since I am flying on a different airline.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>lazy Sunday mornin</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2013/04/14/lazy-sunday-mornin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2013 11:24:10 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2013/04/14/lazy-sunday-mornin/</guid>
      <description>##11:24 Sunday 14 April 2013
10:25am Sunday 14 April 2013
While chatting with Colleen we had a little earthquake. Colleen wasn&amp;rsquo;t impressed that I was unimpressed with earthquakes in general, but meh, most of them are no big deal.
Then, just moments after I saw the details of the earthquake posted online, a bowl broke in the kitchen! It seems like an unrelated event, but one can never be too sure!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>