<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>dream on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/dream/</link>
    <description>Recent content in dream on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 16:53:14 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/dream/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream: Unstoppable Trains</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/08/30/dream-unstoppable-trains/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 16:53:14 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/08/30/dream-unstoppable-trains/</guid>
      <description>16:53 Friday 30 August 2019 JST One train came and slammed through the car on the tracks. Another train came on the adjacent tracks and slammed through the car on those tracks. A third train came through and I knew it must be a dream so I threw the garbage of the KKK uniforms under the train and watched it be carried away relentlessly by the wheels unstopping and then noticed the train was not that long so they could see it was me and I thought good thing it&#39;s a dream and then an old black man came by laughing and we laughed our asses off as they train curved its way slowly around the whole valley as I started to make up straight lies &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream: Unstoppable Trains</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/08/30/dream-unstoppable-trains/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 16:53:14 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/08/30/dream-unstoppable-trains/</guid>
      <description>16:53 Friday 30 August 2019 JST One train came and slammed through the car on the tracks. Another train came on the adjacent tracks and slammed through the car on those tracks. A third train came through and I knew it must be a dream so I threw the garbage of the KKK uniforms under the train and watched it be carried away relentlessly by the wheels unstopping and then noticed the train was not that long so they could see it was me and I thought good thing it&#39;s a dream and then an old black man came by laughing and we laughed our asses off as they train curved its way slowly around the whole valley as I started to make up straight lies &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream twenty-one meter landing</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/07/28/dream-twenty-one-meter-landing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jul 2018 08:35:36 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/07/28/dream-twenty-one-meter-landing/</guid>
      <description>08:35 Saturday 28 July 2018 JST There&#39;s an approach to Dallas airport over a mountain, where we fly through a mountain pass, over a ridge, right around an outcropping of rock, and then into a cave which serves as the runway. This was my forth time to arrive on this runway, and the big screen window in front gives everyone a great view of the approach in real-time. As usual, everyone shares the same awestruck feelings, ranging from &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>dream flying b52</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/07/22/dream-flying-b52/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jul 2018 17:38:13 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/07/22/dream-flying-b52/</guid>
      <description> 17:38 Sunday 22 July 2018 JST We were in a B52 that for some reason had to crash so they were going to simply move all the refrigerators from one side to the other so it would go off balance and plummet down at an angle, ensuring its destruction so the enemy would not be able to use anything from it. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>dream used wrong toilet</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/07/09/dream-used-wrong-toilet/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jul 2018 04:41:43 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/07/09/dream-used-wrong-toilet/</guid>
      <description>04:41 Monday 09 July 2018 JST While on campus at a university I needed to use the restroom to go number 2, but all the restrooms had lines. From experience, I knew that the restrooms on higher floors had shorter lines, but I had to go up to a floor I had never previously seen.
I got to some kind of room with a lectern and chairs and wanted to see what was on the next floor, but it was locked.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>YRUU dream oh my darlin clementine</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/07/02/yruu-dream-oh-my-darlin-clementine/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2018 05:03:46 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/07/02/yruu-dream-oh-my-darlin-clementine/</guid>
      <description>05:03 Monday 02 July 2018 JST It&amp;rsquo;s been a while since I woke up with a YRUU dream in my mind.
We were somewhere and someone sang some made up lyrics There was a new attendee from Colorado, and we jokingly said we had not heard of their football team, the California Nuggets. As an apology, someone sang Oh my darling, oh my darling
Oh my darling, Clementine
We don&#39;t know the football team name</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>dream snippets</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/06/30/dream-snippets/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jun 2018 07:21:53 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/06/30/dream-snippets/</guid>
      <description>07:21 Saturday 30 June 2018 JST I used my deodorant stone incorrectly and it just started melting before my eyes. I thought, well, at least I got more than the advertised year of use out of it. Riding in an apparently-self-driving car, I sure who was driving it. There were no people in the front seats. It was being controlled by someone who could see from above, like playing a 2D video game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>dream wearing shoes in public</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/05/28/dream-wearing-shoes-in-public/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2018 05:06:16 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/05/28/dream-wearing-shoes-in-public/</guid>
      <description>05:06 Monday 28 May 2018 JST Walking outside, I realized I was wearing hiking boots and was shocked that I was wearing them while walking around on vacation. I asked store owner if I could have a bag to put them in, but he said he could not give me one, but I could not understand the reason why. I walked further and found a place to put my boots in a locker so I did that and saw Yumi there who taking things out of her locker and she said I could put my shoes with her stuff with kinda the implication that her son would be able to wear them when he got older.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>dream flew on UFO</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/16/dream-flew-on-ufo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2018 16:41:01 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/16/dream-flew-on-ufo/</guid>
      <description>16:41 Monday 16 April 2018 JST Had a very interesting dream last night. Most of the following was transcribed in a text message to Christine while walking to the station.
I was out on a field and we saw a spaceship flying above the clouds; it was moving to and fro, and had large glowing green and red lights illuminating large portions of the clouds around it. As it was coming down I was like &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>dream flying back</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/30/dream-flying-back/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2017 20:47:50 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/30/dream-flying-back/</guid>
      <description>20:47 Saturday 30 December 2017 -02 I got an email from my friend saying her sister had died. She decided to tart a new estaurnt like The Pink Cow which was really friendly and had great food so we went there to check it out and it was super busy so I asked them about making a reseration but it was a bit confusing about what time we would be able to get ther because our driver would be avaialble at 10am or 10pm and neither time was exactly convenient</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>dream scheduling conflict</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/23/dream-scheduling-conflict/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2017 04:49:53 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/23/dream-scheduling-conflict/</guid>
      <description>04:49 Saturday 23 December 2017 -03 I had a schedule conflict that I detected a few days out, but didn&#39;t try to rectify until the day of the conflict. Nate wanted to have me join a late night adventure sneaking into a dark house that only I knew the layout to find some prize close to midnight. I was more interested in joining Lin to meet Travis and Yumi for a roadtrip that started at 11pm, but planned to meet in nearly the same location, an empty field next to the building that Nate and I were going to explore in the dark.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream three years ago</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/10/05/dream-three-years-ago/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2017 07:00:50 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/10/05/dream-three-years-ago/</guid>
      <description>07:00 Thursday 05 October 2017 JST We watched as two security guards dove into the river to help the tourists who had fallen out of the rafts. The river water came right up to the window, which surprised me, but was normal to the locals. We started climbing down the tower and walking towards the rocket to launch to the mon. I was like oh snap I forgot to pack!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>dream paid for sandwich with itself</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/10/01/dream-paid-for-sandwich-with-itself/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2017 04:40:29 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/10/01/dream-paid-for-sandwich-with-itself/</guid>
      <description>04:40 Sunday 01 October 2017 JST I was a little bit confused on the train as it went through a tunnel, I realized the train was different than other trains. It was longer, like one continuous car as it snaked along the route. The seat next to me was available, so I patted on it to invite the guy sitting on the other side of the empty seat to sit closer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>dream time stops</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/09/06/dream-time-stops/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2017 05:22:52 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/09/06/dream-time-stops/</guid>
      <description>05:22 Wednesday 06 September 2017 JST In my dream, I answered &amp;ldquo;time stops&amp;rdquo; to a question, just as my alarm rang. Something similar happened in my dream when my alarm rant yesterday as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream sixty foot physics</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/08/11/dream-sixty-foot-physics/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2017 03:58:23 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/08/11/dream-sixty-foot-physics/</guid>
      <description>03:58 Friday 11 August 2017 JST Walking with some women, asking about their work, one said she was into 60 foot physics. What do you mean by sixty foot physics? Like from this spot right here, exactly sixty feet in all directions, what happens?
and my alarm went off
04:01 Friday 11 August 2017 JST MKP GST meeting has been cancelled this month; that&amp;rsquo;s why I didn&amp;rsquo;t see any messages leading up to it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>dream rage at a guy</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/08/09/dream-rage-at-a-guy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2017 07:46:17 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/08/09/dream-rage-at-a-guy/</guid>
      <description>07:46 Wednesday 09 August 2017 JST Driving Mr Van with some friends, including Natalie from PB, I learned that one of my friends was able to start Mr Van with a lockpick key that worked very easily. He wanted to drive, but because he wasn&#39;t on our insurance, I said it was illegal and asked him not to.
He distracted me with a puzzle and then when I looked up, I disocvered he was driving the van!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>dream： brush teeth proudly</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/12/24/dream-brush-teeth-proudly/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2016 06:15:29 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/12/24/dream-brush-teeth-proudly/</guid>
      <description>06:15 Saturday 24 December 2016 JST Was at someone&#39;s house like family reunion and wanted to get away from it all
Girl was beautiful but couldn&#39;t skateboard, and we took the time to teach her to skateboard. She went from zero ability to basically being able to skate. I gave her a congratulations hug and kiss at the end and she thanked me for taking time to help her learn.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream bought dragon playground for my room</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/11/05/dream-bought-dragon-playground-for-my-room/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 09:51:39 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/11/05/dream-bought-dragon-playground-for-my-room/</guid>
      <description>09:51 Saturday 05 November 2016 JST My dragon arrived, and it was much larger than expcected! I helped the UPS driver deliver it. There were a few light things but then some pieces we had to carry together. First was a large mirror, though it was covered in fabric. The tires were like truck tires which I suggested a game to roll up the driveway together. She agreed after realizing I would help carry things, and wasn&#39;t just fooling around.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/10/14/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2016 05:57:34 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/10/14/dream/</guid>
      <description> 05:57 Friday 14 October 2016 AWST Dreamt I was sparring with Sae in karate; I got one point on her after a while, which was a surprise because she knows what she&#39;s doing and I know nothing of karate. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Colleen team basketball</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/02/26/colleen-team-basketball/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2016 07:59:16 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/02/26/colleen-team-basketball/</guid>
      <description>07:59 Friday 26 February 2016 JST Colleen and another tall girl were playing basketball against two young kids, easily beating them so I joined the little kids&#39; team to help even the game. Colleen jumped onto my back to slow me down, but I still while lying down on the sidelines, trying to throw the ball to the smaller kids. Eventually I was able to get up and do slam dunks with Colleen piggybacking me; I was pretty impressed, but I figured my body had just gotten used to having my heavy backpack all the time and Colleen was no heavier.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream soccer</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/02/18/dream-soccer/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2016 06:46:40 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/02/18/dream-soccer/</guid>
      <description>06:46 Thursday 18 February 2016 JST Arrived at a hedge where I needed to climb up to meet my peps, but two people were waiting to come down, so I invited them to come down first before I climbed. I wasn&#39;t sure how they had been standing on the top of the bushy trees, but after I climbed up using a horizontal branch fork to press up and climb up from there, I found the top of the bushes had been covered in a raft of logs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/01/07/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2016 08:29:38 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/01/07/dream/</guid>
      <description>08:29 Thursday 07 January 2016 JST In my men&#39;s group, we were asked to organize some images based on how important they were to us, and it was supposed to give some insights on our character. When it was my turn to do it, only a few of the cards have images. I kept looking at them and trying to figure out what was wrong. The people asked me and I said &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream Kevin&#39;s phone</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/01/04/dream-kevins-phone/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2016 07:29:35 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/01/04/dream-kevins-phone/</guid>
      <description>07:29 Monday 04 January 2016 JST I knew i was able to fly, and determined that I would beat the effects of gravity, I tried various things to lift off the ground. Then I found that looking up allowed me to fly up; this was great! I was able to control my flight, even able to fly around in a small space. I was able to break through some walls repeatedly, and finally the roof opened up for me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream of Thrones</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/12/25/dream-of-thrones/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Dec 2015 07:21:15 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/12/25/dream-of-thrones/</guid>
      <description>07:21 Friday 25 December 2015 JST There was some graffitti painted on the gate near the spies camp inside the castle, something ke &#34;The downfalll of W will be from the camp of R on the inside&#34;, where W and R were the initials of the family names involved. I can&#39;t recall if R or W was the good guys, but I was in favor of the good guys and we noticed that one man had gone missing, and realized that he must have been converted to the bad side, so I went off to find him and protect his girlfriend who loved him but didn&#39;t know he would kill her.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream grouchy</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/12/19/dream-grouchy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Dec 2015 08:34:33 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/12/19/dream-grouchy/</guid>
      <description>08:34 Saturday 19 December 2015 JST I bought a neat game and asked Lin if she&#39;d like to play. She was like, &#34;I don&#39;t like games&#34; or something and I got pissed off like &#34;you haven&#39;t even seen what game I&#39;m talking about!&#34; and I got it out to start playing with it, but couldn&#39;t find it in my backpack due to all the other crap that was in there, including a cooler full of watermelon and spinach which had apparently gone bad because I didn&#39;t remember having put it in there, and some bread type sweets, so I started throwing all of them out of my bag, and noticed I couldn&#39;t really stop though I knew it was infantile, and lots of people were nearby so I wasn&#39;t making a very good example of emotional awareness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/12/18/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Dec 2015 06:08:35 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/12/18/dream/</guid>
      <description>06:08 Friday 18 December 2015 JST Fred came to Japan and I helped him unload his car while teling him about the things I had been thinking about which included how to make some computer programs, or wondering how to make some computer programs to do some type of calculations. Like how to write news article titles based on news articles; we&#39;d have a function `title.txt()` for the article thatwould calculate the article We went into the house and Fred realized that he had left his car unlocked and I was like, &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream Tariq died</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/12/01/dream-tariq-died/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2015 06:18:08 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/12/01/dream-tariq-died/</guid>
      <description>around 4 or 5am Tuesday 01 December 2015 JST Making a copy of Tariq&#39;s data, I noted a pattern of full backups and partial backups, so I was able to go back a week to get the most recent full backup. The current backup was going to be a full backup, but it was aborted before it finished. Later, he and I were walking to the train station, and after I crossed the street, I was like, &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream teach massage offer</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/10/24/dream-teach-massage-offer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2015 05:07:17 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/10/24/dream-teach-massage-offer/</guid>
      <description>05:07 Saturday 24 October 2015 JST On a bus with lots of people including two people who were co-workers. One was a reporter who had been standing all day. She said to the other as she got off the bus that her feet hurt and she really wanted a foot massages. After she got off the bus, I asked him if I could have her phone number to give her a massage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream in vampire bat movie</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/09/21/dream-in-vampire-bat-movie/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2015 07:01:12 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/09/21/dream-in-vampire-bat-movie/</guid>
      <description>07:01 Monday 21 September 2015 JST Living inside a QT movie, therewas a spooky scene and then a couple guys were walking along the beach with the task of digging up a dead body. One of them goes, &#34;okay start digging, and the other was like where? and then the first one fell down a bit of a cliff and revealed her corpse, and he goes, &#34;right there&#34; so they dug her out and she was actually still alive, though animated with spooky spirit ghost or something and the card overlay said &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream： The Magician</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/07/24/dream-the-magician/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jul 2015 09:13:02 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/07/24/dream-the-magician/</guid>
      <description>09:13 Friday 24 July 2015 JST Was on the train next to a cute girl with braces, and I started talking to her by saying, &amp;ldquo;I like your braces.&amp;rdquo; She smiled and we talked a bit and determined we were both going the same directions on the Tokaido Line, though she was going farther than me. We arrived at a station where we needed to change trains, and I went down the left side of the train to get seats for us, but the train doors were closed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream SBK</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/07/17/dream-sbk/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jul 2015 05:04:13 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/07/17/dream-sbk/</guid>
      <description>05:04 Friday 17 July 2015 JST With SBK and her twin sister, we had a big bed together and I got to sleep with both at the same time, with the door open, and we heard some noise during fellatio with SBK twin, so I got up and bumped the door closed without leaving the bed and came back and SBK began fellatio and I joked like &#34;hey you&#39;re cutting in line; let&#39;s kiss,&#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/07/03/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jul 2015 05:02:36 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/07/03/dream/</guid>
      <description>05:02 Friday 03 July 2015 JST Next to some train tracks with Lin, I wanted to hop on the next train to see where it would go, but we needed to go somewhere. The next train tat came through stoped so I could watch and actually split some cars off and sent them toward a deep rock quarry with limestone boulders precariously falling from the other side and occasionally bouncing onto tis side.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/06/21/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jun 2015 20:18:12 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/06/21/dream/</guid>
      <description>20:18 Sunday 21 June 2015 JST Two types of monsters existed in the city which had existed for thousands of years and recently we realized they had found a weakness in our defenses. We had secured some way that disallowed them from climbing up this set of buildings but they had found a way to beat that with a new building which had been built recently, so they could climb up the new buildng above the defenses and the swing across to our set of buildings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>dream youth group</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/06/16/dream-youth-group/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jun 2015 07:12:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/06/16/dream-youth-group/</guid>
      <description>##07:12 Monday 16 June 2015 JST##
Playing silent football, with Nick and Laura D, they kept footballing to each other and then Nick sent it to me and expected me to send it to her, so I made a big show of finding a way to measure the distance to her: I searched in my pockets for a measuring device and found a short length of string and began to measure the distance to her, but it was more than 5 string lengths to get just to the next person so I dramatically tossed it over my shoulder and pulled out a pantomime string and measure one unit for each person away, and determined that Laura was in fact 4 people away from me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/06/16/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jun 2015 04:40:32 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/06/16/dream/</guid>
      <description>04:40 Tuesday 16 June 2015 JST I climbed the tree by using my legs/feet as hands, and baically climbed with hands and feet gripping the tree below me. I had to climb back down a bit once I reached the level of the tree house because there was no door on the tree side of the house, so I climbed down ~~to the roof are~~ to the floor level and carefully stepped onto the floor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream lising in a sand world</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/05/04/dream-lising-in-a-sand-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 May 2015 08:58:21 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/05/04/dream-lising-in-a-sand-world/</guid>
      <description>08:58 Monday 04 May 2015 JST Climbed up a light pole and found some eggs whihch were soft, but viable bird eggs and I placed some which were above a line down below the line just to do it, and while I was there, one of them started to hatch. A little video game bird came out and was attracted to the video screen. I realized it was a simlation of sort, the bird was attracted to the sceand the scene itself was changing through a different rndomzider.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/04/27/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2015 08:24:18 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/04/27/dream/</guid>
      <description>08:24 Monday 27 April 2015 JST At a shop selling food: healthy brown rice and stuff cooked, I bought something and was counting things I had bought: a lot of empty bottles and received 20,000 yen change but hadn&#39;t paid that much. The employee said it was okay so I kept it, but didn&#39;t understand the logic. But I couldn&#39;t remember the overall transaction so assumed it was correct. She asked if I want to have some brown rice and I was like, &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream detachable penis</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/04/20/dream-detachable-penis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Apr 2015 08:36:36 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/04/20/dream-detachable-penis/</guid>
      <description>08:36 Monday 20 April 2015 JST This dream was from a few hours ago
I was outside near a street and a woman asked me something like if she could take a picture with me, and I was like sure, so I sat down and patted on lap and was like, have a seat and was a bit surprised because she was an older woman like a short round cigar smokin cuban grandma, but she was open to new adventures, so she sat down on my lap.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/04/19/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Apr 2015 03:20:32 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/04/19/dream/</guid>
      <description>03:20 Sunday 19 April 2015 JST Sleeping time now.
08:05 Each time I tried to enter my Japanese vocabulary words, they were not being auto-fefined by the dictionary. I had ot write &#34;ager-teen&#34; instead of &#34;teeenager&#34; before the translation would come up. When discussing the event with students in my Japanese class, I realized we hadn&#39;t tried to disprove the dust theory by throwing dust into the air. It makes sense that dancing would kick up dust and cause more orbs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/04/18/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Apr 2015 06:23:41 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/04/18/dream/</guid>
      <description>06:23 Saturday 18 April 2015 JST In an open area wher people wer playing sports, a guy was hitting baseballs toward a wal and sometimes the balls would go astray so I went to pick one up and throw it to him. As I approached it he said, &#34;free sex if you touch my ball&#34; so I jokingly stopped and didn&#39;t touch it. He recoverd the baseball and threw it hard at me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dreams</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/04/17/dreams/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2015 07:27:53 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/04/17/dreams/</guid>
      <description>07:27 Friday 17 April 2015 JST GG long lesson I looked up at the clock and stopped mid-sentence. &#34;What? Is it 1:30am? Oh my god I must have fallen asleep! I can only remember maybe 45 minutes extra, but it&#39;s been three hours!!&#34; I asked each one if they fell asleep but they wer lie (shrug) &#34;no not really&#34; but I was sure they were just not sure because we were all groggy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream walking onstage with shoes on</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/04/13/dream-walking-onstage-with-shoes-on/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Apr 2015 07:59:11 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/04/13/dream-walking-onstage-with-shoes-on/</guid>
      <description>07:59 Monday 13 April 2015 JST Soness and them went over to the right and I got caught up in a crowd, so I turned the other way and went straight to the stage where we were about to perform. The director was like, &#34;hey Rob!&#34; and &#34;ya know, I see you each day right in the center of the gap in the crowd way up on the top seating area.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream baseball with Travis</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/04/11/dream-baseball-with-travis/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Apr 2015 07:59:35 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/04/11/dream-baseball-with-travis/</guid>
      <description>07:59 Saturday 11 April 2015 JST In a slightly enclosed area, Travis and I were playing a version of baseball. We would each take one turn at bat, and keep track of where our ghost players had made it around the bases. We were pretty well tied, though we kept getting hits. It was my turn at bat, and someone gave me a broken bat as a joke, so I used it as a joke and got a pretty good hit, making it to third base, though Travis tagged home base before my ghost runner would have made it there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream virtual room with Travis</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/03/23/dream-virtual-room-with-travis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2015 06:39:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/03/23/dream-virtual-room-with-travis/</guid>
      <description>##06:39 Monday 23 March 2015 JST##
Travis and I were in a virtual reality on my computer. He showed me a room that was similar to what I had seen before, so I almost didn&#39;t go inside to explore. Then I was like, &#34;wait if Travis showed me this, it must be cool&#34; so I went inside to check the place out. It was *amazing* with 3D virtual games inside the groom, a hologram which could be manipulated by touching the screen and project into the room; and some hidden rooms behind the walls with hinged doors on mirrors that caused the hologram to reflect &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>dream driving in mud</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/03/04/dream-driving-in-mud/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2015 06:01:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/03/04/dream-driving-in-mud/</guid>
      <description>##06:01 Wednesday 04 March 2015 JST##
In a large city the train was late or otherwise displaced but we arrived on time on the right hand side of a large building where we had been. Everyone was lined up in three lines, waiting for the van to be ready. I jokingly ran up to be in front of one of the lines in front of a youth to tease her, but she wasn&#39;t phased by my cutting in line.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/02/22/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2015 02:52:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/02/22/dream/</guid>
      <description>##02:52 Sunday 22 February 2015 JST##
Sleeping now in meditation room below pyramid. Completely dark and quiet.
##08:05 Sunday 22 February 2015 JST##
Dreamt Japan was at war and Tokyo had been attacked. We were all on a wall outside a highway and scrambled up the wall when we heard the news. I tried to put on my armor and as I watched from bird&#39;s eye perspective, an enemy truck invaded the town.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream flew quickly</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/02/20/dream-flew-quickly/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2015 08:43:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/02/20/dream-flew-quickly/</guid>
      <description>##08:43 Friday 20 February 2015 JST##
(dream) In a large house with many rooms, a woman was kinda stalking me, telling me she wanted me to give her a baby; I was like no way and trying to escape her, through different interconnected rooms and department store displays. I ran down a long hallway and downstairs to where my sane friends were outside and I realized I could fly, so I flew upwards and wondered if I could fly quickly this time, and found that I could.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream with Lin boat to Japan</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/02/15/dream-with-lin-boat-to-japan/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2015 08:58:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/02/15/dream-with-lin-boat-to-japan/</guid>
      <description>##08:58 Sunday 15 February 2015 JST##
In a school, Lin and I walked up some steps to a counter where we were to pick up our tickets for travel. The guy was like, do you have your stripe card? which I had been given but couldn&#39;t find at that moment. I found it latler in a different pocket of my wallet (change compartnemtn) and moved it to the first plae I had looked for it, while thinking of the LPT I had seen regarding this, though Iit was already a practice I practice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/01/28/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/01/28/dream/</guid>
      <description>##23:52 Wednesday 28 January 2015 JST##</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/01/27/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/01/27/dream/</guid>
      <description>##09:03 Tuesday 27 January 2015 JST##
Walking next to the train while he spoke in English and it was translated to Spanish for the local population riding on the train. The train slowed down as I realized I was gonna get squished between it and a fence, so I leapt across the tracks (with fence behind me and train paused, approaching on my left) and then climbed aboard the train as it continued its journey.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/01/22/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/01/22/dream/</guid>
      <description>##04:30 Thursday 22 January 2015 JST##
A guy from MKP arrived with four gallons of ice cream. I was like, &#34;nice!&#34; Dad showed me a plastic cup with ice in the freezer, saying it was his, but one of my girlfriends had drunk out of it.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/01/19/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/01/19/dream/</guid>
      <description>##09:25 Monday 19 January 2015 JST##
Fred and I were going opposite directions on the train between Shibuya and Ebisu; I got on the train as he got off. We waved to each other, doing huge waves so we could see each other even as the train was fully outside the station; I was running back and forth along the seats as my wave so he could see the motion, and I could see he was doing something equally wavy and we could see each other all the way until I arrived at Shibuya station where I realized I was walking in my underwear, but holding a briefcase through the area and then walking toward the train station, some guys were like, &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/01/18/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/01/18/dream/</guid>
      <description>##03:21 Sunday 18 January 2015 JST##
Special thanks to past-self who was resting in bed and decided to set up this buffer for writing my dream when future-self wakes up.
##09:11
During some kind of war, recieved a flying motorcycle which had been gear to my DNA and was a gift from the past. Our friend had driven a car to kill two bad guys by crushing them into a wall, and we ran over to take care of him because he was injured in the accident.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream featuring Andrew Basiago</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/01/07/dream-featuring-andrew-basiago/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/01/07/dream-featuring-andrew-basiago/</guid>
      <description>##06:31 Wednesday 07 January 2015 JST##
Andrew Basiago was looking for an assistant and I applied for the job. He knew me already, so I just wrote Rob Nugen on the list because I figured he already had my contact information. For a while I thought I should have written it just to be sure, but it was okay. There were several other people in the line, and I glanced over and saw my name on the list he had written so I guesed it was fine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/12/15/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/12/15/dream/</guid>
      <description>##03:20 Monday 15 December 2014 JST##
Interesting set of movies were planned at local theater: Planet Terror, etc I was in back of theater and read the list of movies for the crowd, while Paola was the projectionist. First movie had a secret menu before it started, like a master menu for all six movies. The top of one menu said &#34;Planet Terror Real Menu&#34; and had items like, &#34;PLAY ALL MOVIES&#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/12/12/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/12/12/dream/</guid>
      <description>##10:45 Friday 12 December 2014 JST##
With food still onthe table som epeople started to pull the blanket from the bed to cver it, and I kept holding it back saying wait because it would get the balnketst dirty with peach sauce and water some chicken remains; I tried picking up the food; there wasn&#39;t much left and finally they stopped and I asked for a towel to wipe up the water and then some orange juice got spiled on the bedge of the bed mattress.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/29/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/29/dream/</guid>
      <description>##08:51 Saturday 29 November 2014 JST##
We were walking around the kitchen / stores and a woman offered a sample donut. It was sticky raw on the inside but crispy on the outside, just like the dough from which she pulled it. She would rip off part of the dough, including some crust and soft part inside and fold it so that the crust would be outside. I asked how she made them and she showed me and I wondered if they were safe to eat, not being cooked.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream new restaurant</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/27/dream-new-restaurant/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/27/dream-new-restaurant/</guid>
      <description>##4:17am
&#34;ohhhh, those are *our* boxes!&#34; we kept repeating it because the reality was setting in We had decided to start a restaurant. &#34;Oh, those are *our* boxes&#34; Oh my goodness, we started a restaurant, that&#39;s *rtight*! I wondered how we were even going to get the boxes upstairs where we had space to put tables for people to eat. I tried to wonder what it would be like with people inn our home, eating; who was going to cook?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/23/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/23/dream/</guid>
      <description>##08:25 Sunday 23 November 2014 JST##
Flying away from bad guys over a large hilly area, they were trying to get me and my cat. We were in a city street and I was able to fly to get away from them after a while. I didn&#39;t realize I was dreaming but I realized I could fly away so I did so. I realized I could control the situation a bit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream snippet</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/18/dream-snippet/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/18/dream-snippet/</guid>
      <description>##07:47 Tuesday 18 November 2014 JST##
(I&amp;rsquo;m writing this way after I woke up at 6:15)
Building things, like in Minecraft, but not a game, Fred there  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream- floating behind ship</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/17/dream-floating-behind-ship/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/17/dream-floating-behind-ship/</guid>
      <description>##09:34 Monday 17 November 2014 JST##
Floating on a rubber aft, lofted by the wind I was disconnected from thwe ship&#39;s mast for a while, but was able to swim through the air to get back to it a few times. After a bit, I seemed not able to get back, so my friend went to ask for help, but while he was gone, I made it back and shimmied down the mast along with the raft.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>dream karaoke drink</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2013/05/10/dream-karaoke-drink/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2013 07:42:13 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2013/05/10/dream-karaoke-drink/</guid>
      <description>##07:42 Friday 10 May 2013
7:37am Friday 10 May 2013
In karaoke, singing &amp;ldquo;The Last Blueberry&amp;rdquo; by Anikiko, I wanted to fast forward to the good part so quickly consumed the drink from the song carton. It seemed a bit strange, but the guy with me agreed it was the fastest way to fast-forward the song: fast-drink the drink!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>disclosure dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2013/05/09/disclosure-dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2013 06:53:58 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2013/05/09/disclosure-dream/</guid>
      <description>##06:53 Thursday 09 May 2013
6:42am Thursday 9 May 2013
I was in a small room, controlled by the government that was a bit like prison but not completely terrible conditions and it was time for alien disclosure but they were doing it in a very specific way. Some spider webs were in my room in the corner, and there was a pillow but nothing else. I was asked to lie face down with pillow ofer my head and to cover my ears as the aliens were revealed and each person could be shwon the aliens under supeision and not get freaked out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>dream fighting against bow and arrow wielding peeps</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2013/05/07/dream-fighting-against-bow-and-arrow-wielding-peeps/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2013 06:59:49 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2013/05/07/dream-fighting-against-bow-and-arrow-wielding-peeps/</guid>
      <description>##06:59 Tuesday 07 May 2013
6:54am Tuesday 7 May 2013
We had been retreating but I realized it was &amp;ldquo;that place where I can control things&amp;rdquo; so I went toward them firing arrows at me. I wasn&amp;rsquo;t hit/hurt by any arrows and I got close enough to shoot some of them, but didn&amp;rsquo;t because it wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be nice, so I found an old cave where we had had a school or something and went down into it and turned right behind an old saloon that was filled with chairs and stuff.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>dream back of the bus with ectoplasm</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2013/03/28/dream-back-of-the-bus-with-ectoplasm/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2013 06:31:10 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2013/03/28/dream-back-of-the-bus-with-ectoplasm/</guid>
      <description>##06:31 Thursday 28 March 2013
6:15am Thursday 28 March 2013
Riding in the back of a bus, after there had been a pretty devastating earthquake, but we were still trying to go somewhere, and the driver had to back up a try again to go this way or that way around the city to get to where we were going. I was sitting in the back, and Lin was sitting a few seats ahead of me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>dream didn&#39;t want to get older</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2013/03/25/dream-didnt-want-to-get-older/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2013 03:46:42 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2013/03/25/dream-didnt-want-to-get-older/</guid>
      <description>##03:46 Monday 25 March 2013
3:40am Monday 25 March 2013 Sho was discussing with Jonas about a new site, and I wanted to work on something but didn&amp;rsquo;t have enough information to get started on my site. I tried to get back to work and the scene shifted.
At our old house again, my mom went outside to sleep in the pullman trailer and I went to my old rom. I heard a noise with sounded like the neighbors pulling trailers around so I went outside to make sure they were only pulling their own trailers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>dream Sabina traveler</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2013/01/28/dream-sabina-traveler/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jan 2013 05:21:06 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2013/01/28/dream-sabina-traveler/</guid>
      <description>##05:21 Monday 28 January 2013
Dusk was approaching on a rainy night and we got a knock at the door. I opened it and a western looking guy wearing a backpack introduced himself. &amp;ldquo;HI; I&amp;rsquo;m Joe from Nagano,&amp;rdquo; and I interrupted him, &amp;ldquo;you came from Nagano??&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;yes&amp;rdquo;. &amp;ldquo;Okay sorry please continue..&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;and I&amp;rsquo;m was working in IT there but lost my job so I&amp;rsquo;m looking for IT work in Tokyo..&amp;rdquo; He was dripping a bit with rain, so I offered him to come in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>received lip piercings in my dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2013/01/24/received-lip-piercings-in-my-dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2013 08:20:25 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2013/01/24/received-lip-piercings-in-my-dream/</guid>
      <description>##08:20 Thursday 24 January 2013
Was in south pacific island and was admiring the piercings of some of the locals. An older guy held two needles in a downward non-threatening way and nodded his head toward me questioningly. I was like &amp;ldquo;sure!&amp;rdquo; and approached him. He quickly and painlessly inserted needles in either side of my upper lip, then out a bit lower, so they didn&amp;rsquo;t actually pierce into the mouth; just like subcutaneous, but not deeper than that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>dream driving with Colleen and my family</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2013/01/17/dream-driving-with-colleen-and-my-family/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jan 2013 07:39:07 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2013/01/17/dream-driving-with-colleen-and-my-family/</guid>
      <description>##07:39 Thursday 17 January 2013
Driving Mr Van with Colleen and my family, we arrived at a place where we had just been druing thew inter. In winter the stream had lights and snow and looked quite different from no lights and no snow version as it was now. Colleen commented on that and I was like, &amp;ldquo;yeah that was a once in a lifetime opportunity because I&amp;rsquo;ve heard they&amp;rsquo;re not going to do the lights next year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>dream chatting with trent reznor</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2013/01/17/dream-chatting-with-trent-reznor/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jan 2013 03:40:28 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2013/01/17/dream-chatting-with-trent-reznor/</guid>
      <description>##03:40 Thursday 17 January 2013
hanging out with Trent Reznor of nine inch nails (still?), I got to really ask him and hear some of his thoughts about stuff. I was like &amp;ldquo;oh I know what I can tell you that&amp;rsquo;s personal, different than just &amp;lsquo;omg I love your music&amp;rsquo; which is true, or I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be here now, but I feel sad that I didn&amp;rsquo;t try to engaage you personally earlier.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>dream around shopping mall</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2013/01/15/dream-around-shopping-mall/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2013 05:16:56 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2013/01/15/dream-around-shopping-mall/</guid>
      <description>##05:16 Tuesday 15 January 2013
Outside a large shopping mall, I was riding my bicycle searching for a specific store or searching for Fred to help him find the store or books that he wanted to find. I wanted to change some parts of the mall to make it easier for blind shoppers to navigate safely around; there were some unnecessary cubs and I considered ways to make them elsewhere so the traffic flow would be revitalized for the good of all the shoppers, bt then I noted that shopping is not for the good of the people but for the good of the economy which is for the good of the bankers and held back on doing any more shopping supportive activities</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>dream grampa died and meeting the family</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2013/01/14/dream-grampa-died-and-meeting-the-family/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2013 06:48:43 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2013/01/14/dream-grampa-died-and-meeting-the-family/</guid>
      <description>##06:48 Monday 14 January 2013
In a large store room with lots of old articles and stuff, I was talking to a young woman who had lived and played there for some years / her whole life. I found that I could hang from the ceiling slats that were spaced enough apart to get my hands between, so I was walking myself from beam to beam, suspended by my fingers. I was surprised at how well I could do it, and she joined me, and kinda chased me around on the ceiling as we walked our hands around hanging from the ceiling.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>dream about lava streaming down the steep shoreline</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2013/01/13/dream-about-lava-streaming-down-the-steep-shoreline/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jan 2013 07:12:39 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2013/01/13/dream-about-lava-streaming-down-the-steep-shoreline/</guid>
      <description>##07:12 Sunday 13 January 2013
With peeps from PB, walking along a seashore at the bottom of a relatively steep rocky face, not steep enough to be a cliff, but about 60 degree descent, but upon which were many people sitting enjoying the water, including families and dogs and kids, we were at the top , and I had been sweeping sweeping inside the house, debris had collected from the night before as the garage door was ajar (from the bottom) and pine needles had been blown in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>bad dream Lin upset text message</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2013/01/03/bad-dream-lin-upset-text-message/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2013 07:17:34 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2013/01/03/bad-dream-lin-upset-text-message/</guid>
      <description>##07:17 Thursday 03 January 2013
Lin, Ma, and I went to a university library where we were looking for books or something. I saw Christine and helped her find a book (which was unavailable ever since a KTRU dj had mentioned its greatness on the air). Christine needed the book for a report due in April, but the book cost $91 so she wanted to borrow it from the library.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>went through a teleporter without being told</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2012/12/23/went-through-a-teleporter-without-being-told/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Dec 2012 05:25:13 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2012/12/23/went-through-a-teleporter-without-being-told/</guid>
      <description>##05:25 Sunday 23 December 2012
In a military built facility, there was a door designed for entry only, but from previous experience, we knew it would be more efficient to just go out the in door than to go around to the designated out door. However, this time when we went out the in door, we were suddenly in a room 20 yards back from where we thought we&amp;rsquo;d be. I was like, &amp;ldquo;?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>dream Paola&#39;s name is Jane</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2012/12/22/dream-paolas-name-is-jane/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Dec 2012 07:56:22 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2012/12/22/dream-paolas-name-is-jane/</guid>
      <description>##07:56 Saturday 22 December 2012
Went to Paola&amp;rsquo;s home party with several other people there, baking cookies and yummy stuff. I was helping Paola slice bread and put butter on it. She was stabbing the loaf with the knife instead of slicing with the knife, and it seemed to get a bit dangerous so I stopped holding the loaf until she was done. I pulled some first pieces off the loaf to put butter on them, and went to get the butter then came back and couldn&amp;rsquo;t find the slices where I put them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>dreamt I discovered the new June project details</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2012/12/20/dreamt-i-discovered-the-new-june-project-details/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Dec 2012 05:55:04 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2012/12/20/dreamt-i-discovered-the-new-june-project-details/</guid>
      <description>##05:55 Thursday 20 December 2012
Looking at some notes, I found a cryptic word like Pinecal, and then Obreil. With those, I was able to look up online that they&amp;rsquo;re putting together a property in Hawaii! Awesome! Just as I was looking away from the notes, I heard her behind me, &amp;ldquo;is someone off the list?&amp;ldquo; I was caught looking where I shouldn&amp;rsquo;t have been looking. I didn&amp;rsquo;t lie; I just said &amp;ldquo;yes,&amp;rdquo; and then she lied for me so no one else would know.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>dream sent back to 1978</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2012/12/16/dream-sent-back-to-1978/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Dec 2012 07:45:33 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2012/12/16/dream-sent-back-to-1978/</guid>
      <description>##07:45 Sunday 16 December 2012
I was sent back in time from the present era to about 30 years ago, and saw my friend Kellie who I hoped could help me.
I was talking to Kellie, and was now about the same age as her. We were in a military installation or at least a government building, and I wanted to go outside, so I asked if she would show me the area.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>dream at airport and then flat tire</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2012/12/12/dream-at-airport-and-then-flat-tire/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Dec 2012 05:39:01 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2012/12/12/dream-at-airport-and-then-flat-tire/</guid>
      <description>##05:39 Wednesday 12 December 2012
At the airport waiting for Lin to arrive, I saw a pregnant woman walking by and thought she was Lin. &amp;ldquo;woah, she&amp;rsquo;s showing a lot more than I expected!&amp;rdquo; Then I realized Lin is not pregnant so that couldn&amp;rsquo;t have been her. We got in the van driving home in Texas, and I remembered the time that Sabina had been at the airport but couldn&amp;rsquo;t remember the way home so stayed there all day until we got back.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>dream if iHad iPad</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2012/12/11/dream-if-ihad-ipad/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2012 07:42:14 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2012/12/11/dream-if-ihad-ipad/</guid>
      <description>##07:42 Tuesday 11 December 2012
Riding in the back of a car, holding Lin&amp;rsquo;s iPad, I thought, &amp;ldquo;man if I had an iPad, I could easily write in my journal all the time.&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>dream helping at UU event</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2012/12/10/dream-helping-at-uu-event/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Dec 2012 06:45:55 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2012/12/10/dream-helping-at-uu-event/</guid>
      <description>##06:45 Monday 10 December 2012
Some of the younger kids had been playing in an off limits area, kicked a soccer ball, and knocked out the sound system for a large number of UU churches. I heard about the story after it was too late to help restore the sound, but was volunteering for something else or something.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>dream traveling with Lin and my dad</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2012/12/10/dream-traveling-with-lin-and-my-dad/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Dec 2012 06:39:05 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2012/12/10/dream-traveling-with-lin-and-my-dad/</guid>
      <description>##06:39 Monday 10 December 2012
Lin and I were traveling with my dad; we were in a hotel with nice view overlooking a neighborhood. I was looking out at the neighborhood overhearing the neighbors playing in the pool. Lin was facing the other direction which surprised me because my dad was in the same room, though he was sleeping. My dad&amp;rsquo;s brother/friend came in and said he was going camping with his friends and we were like, &amp;ldquo;cool&amp;rdquo; and then he left.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream about Andy at The Pink Cow</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2012/10/12/dream-about-andy-at-the-pink-cow/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2012 06:18:06 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2012/10/12/dream-about-andy-at-the-pink-cow/</guid>
      <description>##06:18 Friday 12 October 2012
Sitting with two of Andy&amp;rsquo;s long-time friends, I got to hear how he became associated with the Pink Cow. He had been working in a bar serving beer when a guy noticed how precisely Andy served the beers, taking great care that each one was optimally poured with a perfect foamy head that just crested the top of the mug. The guy asked Andy if he could mix drinks as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shoes dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2012/06/10/shoes-dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jun 2012 03:09:11 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2012/06/10/shoes-dream/</guid>
      <description>##03:09 Sunday 10 June 2012
listen to &amp;lsquo;Shoes dream &amp;rsquo; on Audioboo</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/12/27/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/12/27/dream/</guid>
      <description>9:29am JST Saturday 27 December 2003
I was a spy and was asked to sneak into a small room and use a power drill with a grinder bit to cut a power cable to the building. The room had a glass window and a bad guy was cleaning the window from the other side with a power sprayer. I wondered if, like in a movie, he would cover the window with suds, just allowing me to cut the calbe before he saw me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/12/26/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/12/26/dream/</guid>
      <description>11:12am JST Friday 26 December 2003
I was masturbating in my room and realized that people outside behind me could see me so I stopped and turned around. They were peeking out their windows, and looked like they hadn&#39;t seen me, but then one guy does a jackoff motion question mark and I (in a cheerful way) gave them the finger. &#34;haha fuck you for looking&#34; kinda thing.
One of the guys came outside and was talking to me and then dreamshift and I was watching this bird slash friend eat seeds, but he couldn&#39;t pick up a certain seed with his beak so he cocked his head over to pick it up with his eye using adhesion from his tears (*)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/12/19/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/12/19/dream/</guid>
      <description>7:24am JST Friday 19 December 2003
I was coloring a picture of three chefs in a coloring book. Just systematically slowing filling the shapes with color, being careful not to go outside the lines, gently slowly filling in all the nooks and crannies.
I was with a male friend of mine, working on this little project with him. In the background a rock band was playing covers of loud 80s rock bands, kinda one step down in loudness from glam rock.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/12/18/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/12/18/dream/</guid>
      <description>9:02am JST Thursday 18 December 2003
At KTRU but I wasn&#39;t supposed to be the one DJing and I turned off the station when I left, kinda thinking that the signal must be coming from somewhere else than this studio, as I was not the official DJ for that timeslot. I walked out of the studio, which was like a kiosk sized building in the middle of an entrance to a university and Ali came up some stairs (from underground) to be like, &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/12/16/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/12/16/dream/</guid>
      <description>7:20am JST Tuesday 16 December 2003
I was talking to a guy and we had to use two words that had the same hiragana and make like a crossword puzzle with them.
There was more, but I read janette&#39;s ultra-super-emails before writing. I don&#39;t remember.
Wow. C-c C-v works on emacs now!
7:58am
I remember more of my dream
I was living with some women roommates, including a Morag-energy and her roommate Lisa-energy woman.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/11/28/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/11/28/dream/</guid>
      <description>8:16am JST Friday 28 November 2003
I was in my apartment here in Japan (and Fred was over) and Elizabeth Anderson (YRUU, Austin) came over specifically to say goodbye; she was leaving. I invited her in, chatted with her a bit, Fred gave her a big hug, and then she left.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream Idea</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/10/31/dream-idea/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/10/31/dream-idea/</guid>
      <description>4:49am JST Friday 31 October 2003
&#34;My name is Takako.&#34;
:: &#34;Hi Takako.&#34; ::
&#34;I feel _______&#34; (happy, sad, angry, afraid)
:: &#34;You feel ______. Thank you.&#34; ::
&#34;My _____ is (most) important to me.&#34;
:: &#34;Your ______ is important to you. Thank you.&#34; ::
&#34;I love my _____ (because ....)&#34;
:: &#34;You love your _____. Thank you.&#34; ::
- - - -
I have heard that it&#39;s easier for Japanese to express their emotions in English than in Japanese.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/10/10/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/10/10/dream/</guid>
      <description>8:25am JST Friday 10 October 2003
Flying between two sections of island over water. Awe inspiring view as I made it over the craggly black silouhette of rocks and trees of the middle mountain ridge thing. My dad was there to support me getting across the water of the final section. I was flying slowly, not like superman or a jet, but like a cessna. This final section of water kept drawing me down and I couldn&#39;t stay aloft over it; ended up in the water before I got to the next bit of land.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/10/02/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/10/02/dream/</guid>
      <description>7:11am JST Thursday 2 October 2003
In the restroom, sitting on the john at work when Guy came in and sat on the throne across from me. I was surprised that no divider separated us, but we just talked like it was no big deal, though I was having a hard time excreting anything, and after just a ridiculously long time, I used my fingers and realized that my number 2 was lodged up in me sideways and would *never* have come out without assistance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/08/12/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/08/12/dream/</guid>
      <description>6:24am JST Tuesday 12 August 2003
Getting ready to go to gymnastics, I was back at my dad&#39;s house in my old room, but like back there again (now) not in the past and I had grabbed a soft t-shirt, but it was long sleeved, and I grabbed a short sleeve shirt that flaired at the bottom but it was all itchy, so I put on a t-shirt underneath it and then put on the flair-ey soccer shirt with holes in it and then put on a &#39;mask&#39; of plastic fishnet material over my face as a mokc way to hide my face.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/08/03/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/08/03/dream/</guid>
      <description>11:29pm JST Sunday 3 August 2003
With some friends near a UU congregational meeting, with a discussion about money. I said, &#34;the current system is that we ask members to give money to individual congregations, and the congregations are asked to give money to the UUA in order to be a member of the UUA. But the only fair way is to not require individual members to give money, though we still require the congregation as an entity to give money to the UUA.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/07/28/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/07/28/dream/</guid>
      <description>10:53am JST Monday 28 July 2003
I had a dream this morning about kissing a woman. I didn&#39;t know her; just some random hottie on the street and I realized it was a dream so I pulled her on top of me and we just started smooching. I was practically animal gross slobbery kissing her at first and then I realized that wasn&#39;t too sensual, so I slowed it down a bit and after that we stopped and just sat on the steps wondering what to do next.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/07/20/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/07/20/dream/</guid>
      <description>7:29am JST Sunday 20 July 2003
I saw a funny commercial on TV about doing whatever it takes to be successful. Professional American football game, one player was running down the field to score and the protagonist of the commercial saw him, but there were too many players in the way, so he ran off the field and around the world to plow the offensive guy off the field just before he made a touchdown.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/07/12/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/07/12/dream/</guid>
      <description>7:36am JST Saturday 12 July 2003
With all the kangaroos in Japan, of course I&#39;d have a dream about one.
A young girl was waalking down a bridge, like a freeway overpass and listening to a walkie talkie type thing to tell her where certain people were located. &#34;There&#39;s a young woman walking right; thereis a young man coming toward you,&#34; but it turns out these spoken words were warning her where not to go, or where to go she came running back up the bridge and then down beside it and jumped onto a hospital stretcher next to a kangaroo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream 04</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/06/21/dream-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/06/21/dream-04/</guid>
      <description>4:22am JST Saturday 21 June 2003
Went home early. I did something wrong at work and they were like that&#39;s it you&#39;re outta here and I was like whoohoo! but I wanted to surprise janette so I didn&#39;t tell her, but I had to get home from the airport some way, so I called Fred, or I was going to ride my bike to his house, but he had to get it from her house first without telling her he was getting it, nor why if she found out and I was in my old neighborhood and a dog was yapping so I took off its lower jaw and started to eat some of the meat (tasted like chicken) and it was cooked so it wasn&#39;t gross and the next dog wanted some so I fed him some to keep him quiet and the first dog wasn&#39;t upset, but was hungry so I fed him some meat, but not his own jaw cause he wouldn&#39;t be able to chew the bones and then I threw the jaw into the trash, but realized that they would find it and do DNA analysis on it and know it was me, so I had to run away and I was climbing over fences in my old neighborhood but I kept having to come back cause I forgot something and I finally made it down toward the creek and janette was planning to go to a skinhead type show out in the woods where they were going to burn a bunch of machines not like robots but mechanical stuff to show humans&#39; superiority and I wasn&#39;t really interested but I wanted to see her and maybe there was some benefit from seeing this performance that I didn&#39;t understand yet</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream 07</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/06/21/dream-07/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/06/21/dream-07/</guid>
      <description>7:47am JST Saturday 21 June 2003
Cory was all, &#34;I had a look at your website, and it&#39;s pretty interesting, your website.&#34;
He pointed at the window, which indicated he had read what I wrote during OJT. &#34;Don&#39;t kill me.&#34;
&#34;I won&#39;t. You&#39;re one of the people I respect a lot here.&#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/06/16/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/06/16/dream/</guid>
      <description>4:23am JST Monday 16 June 2003
During Thanksgiving Holiday, Mark Holt was cooking a tremendous meal,but he added some kind of rubber to the nodles, like he cooked in some fishing lure rubber to see what would happen. The result was less than optimal; he had to cook some new noodles because the rubber melted and mage a huge mess of the original noodles.
My dad drove Fred and I to New York to meet up one of Fred&#39;s friends that dad and I had never met, but we had heard of from Fred&#39;s stories.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/06/09/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/06/09/dream/</guid>
      <description>10:03am JST Monday 9 June 2003
Earlier (before 2am) dream
The entire world had been clearcut except for the land next to my dad&#39;s house. I hugged my dad, thanking him for his stability and for keeping that land. During the hug he began to hug someone else as well, and at first I felt jealous, and then I realized he was bringing other people in to hug _me_. I felt quite thankful and quite loved.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream decoded</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/06/09/dream-decoded/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/06/09/dream-decoded/</guid>
      <description>10:04am JST Monday 9 June 2003
Yay Janette for decoding the dream from a week ago!
I&#39;ve fixed the typos of what she sent me, as I do for all my dreams.
So I held onto Spot and we were moving along a trail and some other people were having a picnic on the side. They were also eco tourists and I was new to the group, but my group and their group knew one another, though they were in different parts of the group.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/06/03/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/06/03/dream/</guid>
      <description>8:02am JST Tuesday 3 June 2003
I was in the passenger seat of my van as a friend of mine was driving it. I had been all, yeah, you can have the van; I won&#39;t need it while I&#39;m gone, and then after I had told him that, but bfore I had actually given it to him, I remembered I had promised it to Josephine. I was all like, &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/05/17/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/05/17/dream/</guid>
      <description>7:06am JST Saturday 17 May 2003
Watching a large ship in the water moving from Japan to an island. I was floating out in the water at the time and the ship accelerated for a while and then decelerated the same amount for the second half of its journey. I swam over to its path and found the water was quite shallow, like only a couple of feet deep and I didn&#39;t understand how such a large boat could have been floating in such shallow water.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/05/15/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/05/15/dream/</guid>
      <description>8:21am JST Thursday 15 May 2003
I was living back in Tomball except the terrain included a huge gulley with large piles of dirt like 60+ feet tall to shape the flow of water. Some kids were racing motorcycles on it, destroying the contours and creating a general nuisance of themselves.
I asked how I could report them and there was to be a town meeting in a few days run via Robert&#39;s Rules and I immediately wondered if I could remember all the rules so that I could bring up the complaint.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/05/12/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/05/12/dream/</guid>
      <description>9:27am JST Monday 12 May 2003
My dreams this morning featured people I haven&#39;t seen or spoken with in a while, including Bryn and Marcel. Each time Bryn shows up in my dreams lately, I&#39;m quite excited to see her.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/05/10/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/05/10/dream/</guid>
      <description>7:19am JST Saturday 10 May 2003
Playing sports on a hill and as I slowly climbed up the hill to my hotel I was collecting cheap balls and frisbees and such. The frisbees were ultimate calibre and a guy bit me on the back as I tried to get away with his frisbee but I started tohit him with it and he let me go as one of his friends was all, &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/05/09/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/05/09/dream/</guid>
      <description>6:27am JST Friday 9 May 2003
I went to some tourist attraction and Bryn was there and I&#39;m all &#34;hi, Bryn!&#34; and she goes &#34;I don&#39;t want to explain&#34; so I ignored the gap in communication and asked how she&#39;s doing.
We were in some big hall with a huge golden flame in the middle of the room. Bryn was excited by something so huge and nearly yellow so she ran down the steps to check it out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/05/07/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/05/07/dream/</guid>
      <description>8:11am JST Wednesday 7 May 2003
Japanese words are more often showing up in my dreams. A few Japanese patterns of speech are beginning to feel natural.
A kid was on the street corner with a yoyo ball thing that he was throwing toward the street and then yanking it back well before it hit any traffic. Then he&#39;d throw it again and yank it back. He missed catching the ball a few times and was unaware that when he missed it, he almost hit a woman walking behind him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/05/05/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/05/05/dream/</guid>
      <description>7:52am JST Monday 5 May 2003
I had clocked out of a different work 10 minutes early where the boss tried to be in such control that he wanted me to pay him for the final 10 minutes, or at least not get paid for them.
He asked me until what time I worked and I&#39;m like &#34;around midnight&#34; and he&#39;s all, &#34;well this says you clocked out 10 minutes early.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/05/04/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/05/04/dream/</guid>
      <description>7:49am JST Sunday 4 May 2003
I was with friends in a house on the beachfront. The house had thick glass walls like an inch thick facing the water. Across the water I could see a train bridge and maybe a train station. We were talking in the living room and suddenly there was a large swell of waves and the waves were gushing into the house, though they were dampened by the walls they weren&#39;t completly stopped.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/05/03/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/05/03/dream/</guid>
      <description>6:57am JST Saturday 3 May 2003
Drew Barrymore was over somewhere like a hostel with me and she needed to do laundry and I lived at the hostel (had just moved in) and only residents were allowed to use the laundry facilities so I said that she could join me doing laundry and we could both say we were new since I was actually new they could verify the story. She agreed and we didn&#39;t go immediately, but I went off somewhere else to get my laundry and then realized oh I have a laundry date with Drew Barrymore and I ran back and she was still there which made me really happy, but then I woke up which made me really sad.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/05/01/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/05/01/dream/</guid>
      <description>8:46am JST Thursday 1 May 2003
I had come back to the US and was at Maggie&#39;s house. She lived in a set of condominiums and the pizza guy who was her friend came to deliver a pizza to some people at the pool, but the pool was closed and he had no way to know who had been there, nor where they were now. So he asked if Maggie would take the pizza, which she did, but she wrote a note with her umbrella in the cheese, like she drew a pictogram of the people at the pizza place telling him &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/04/26/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/04/26/dream/</guid>
      <description>6:29am JST Saturday 26 April 2003
I was with the guys from my old work at the Wolf Shop and there was a new cat there who said he appreciated how respectful I was of him after I asked him before leaning back against his boots while we were all piled into the back of a truck.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/04/25/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/04/25/dream/</guid>
      <description>6:53am JST Friday 25 April 2003
I had a dream in Japanese!
Homer Simpson knew Japanese; he was wearing glasses and asking Ned to fill out a form with the prompts written in Japanese. Between them, a woman who could read hiragana was trying to help Ned.
Homer knew English but didn&#39;t translate anything for Ned cause, being Homer, he didn&#39;t think about it and realize this would be helpful. He just let the woman stumble through reading the hiragana and wondered why Ned was clueless not understanding anything.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/04/20/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/04/20/dream/</guid>
      <description>7:23am JST Sunday 20 April 2003
I looked out the window and saw how close I am to Paris! This seemed surprising that I hadn&#39;t realied it before, but that I could just jum on a train and go to another part of the city and visit the Eiffel Tower which was visibl in the distance. Ryan had told me how he had climbed the Eiffel Tower and I was like, &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/04/19/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/04/19/dream/</guid>
      <description>6:18am JST Saturday 19 April 2003
My dad was at church leading the newcomers meeting, describing what it would mean for them to commit to the church. He was winging his speech and I could tell he was nervous. Afterward, he was talking to people and I was nearby, but didn&#39;t turn around when he exchanged nice-to-meet-yous with a couple of guys. I didn&#39;t want to meet them cause they were saying some bullshit about how great his speech was and it really wasn&#39;t.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/04/13/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/04/13/dream/</guid>
      <description>5:31am JST Sunday 13 April 2003
Dreamt that I was old friends with Eminem and that he was basically a nice guy who got really popular by emphasizing his pissed off side. We talked a bit about old times and how&#39;s the family and stuff like that. He asked how my mom was doing and she showed up in the dream and tickled him a bit like she always did with us (*).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/04/09/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/04/09/dream/</guid>
      <description>8:08am JST Wednesday 9 April 2003
Dreamt that I was invited to one more rally. Eeek! I felt honored and a bit weird to attend after I said I&#39;d already attended my last, and I wondered if I&#39;d be able to remember all the names of all the kittens I should know.
We arrived via bus at the Canadian side of Niagra falls and saw a model of the city in the water below us, floating like a future version of our society, one filled with glittering beauty all around.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/04/04/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/04/04/dream/</guid>
      <description>8:40am JST Friday 4 April 2003
&#34;It&#39;s a charley barley barely burger&#34;
My friends and I had through it would be fun to ride on the back of the truck as our boss was driving to Tennessee or someplace hopefully not so far away. The truck had started out as trains and we were testing our train boarding skills. I had been able to barely climb up the slick stainless steel outer casing of the train, but somehow I did it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/03/31/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/03/31/dream/</guid>
      <description>6:24am JST Monday 31 March 2003
Riding around with Ryan McCarthy in his little car, we were reminiscing about old times living and playing at the Bibby&#39;s house. About making toy paper B-52 bombers of various sizes, and sometimes making two in a row cause all we had was time to do anything we wanted. &#34;Oh and remember that one where we added all the extra plastic and gum and shit on it?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/03/18/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/03/18/dream/</guid>
      <description>7:54am CST Tuesday 18 March 2003
In a small section of town like an amusement park with Ma and Jon leading the way to a restaurant that they thought was closed but was just under cleaning aor it was being built and was really expensive but I peeked my head in the door and saw a room with green short carpet and a partition behind which people were cleaning the carpet and the hostess was at the other end of the room and motioned for me to follow her, so I walked past the partiition and to the other end of the room and outside after assuring Ma and Jon they should come with me and they did and I reached the outside area and the hostess had gone down some old steps of varying heights and not supersturdy and I daintily skipped down them and then warned my mom they were different heights so she should be careful and they got down the steps and the hostess showed us to an outdoor table like a picnic table big wooden kind and asked who would be paying for the bill and I didn&#39;t say anything cause I had no money and had assumed my mom or Jon could pay for me, and then the busboy had joined us and he said he would pay for Jon and my mom could pay for me and everyone agreed that was a good idea it seemed, and the hostess was describing something and then she left and Jon was all quiet and like, &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/02/27/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/02/27/dream/</guid>
      <description>7:10am CST Thursday 27 February 2003
Riding my bike with Janette riding hers on some back country roads somewhere, looking for places to go camping. We ended up doing a U-turn or something interestng like that.
Got back to the city ando Janette and I were walking our bikes up the median of I-10; we had reached I-10 and I-20 almost and she was asking me &#34;is that I-10?&#34; &#34;no that&#39;s the feeder for I-10&#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AAM Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/02/18/aam-dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/02/18/aam-dream/</guid>
      <description>5:13am HST Tuesday 18 February 2003
Mark Leonard was there when I got a job in sales for a software company and he immediately helped me with some advice that was wisdom in his mind that I simply didn&#39;t have (or actually do cause it was my dream) he was all, &#34;now what you could do is have some guys run around and get people to fill out questionaires to prequalify customers for the software.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AM Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/02/18/am-dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/02/18/am-dream/</guid>
      <description>6:27am HST Tuesday 18 February 2003
I was at a UU conference including adults and youth like GA or SWUUSI and sitting with the youth and my mom came in, looking to me like Julia Roberts. I asked Kate Robinson &#34;doesn&#39;t she look like Julia Roberts?&#34;
&#34;A little bit&#34;
But no she really did look like her and then she was looking around (my mom was looking around) and she found me and said HI then saw some of her friends were crying and my mom started crying and I knew immediately that meant we had started to bomb Iraq.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AM Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/02/15/am-dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/02/15/am-dream/</guid>
      <description>1:09am HST Saturday 15 February 2003
at dad and karen&#39;s house, and helping them put some glass doors back into place which were supposed to be laying on some metal rack thing but the rack was bent or something and the doors were not laying just the way they should so I was trying to line them up properly and a couple YRUUers showed up to help and they were all putting some roof pieces on the doors but were doing it from top to bottom which wasn&#39;t going to work so I got mad and left, or I told them it was the wrong way and I wasn&#39;t going to wait around cause I had already been working for a long time on it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/02/15/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/02/15/dream/</guid>
      <description>1:09am HST Saturday 15 February 2003
at dad and karen&#39;s house, andhelping them put some door some glass doors back into place which were supposed tobe laying on some metal rack thing but the rack was bent or something and the doorws were not laying just eh way they should so I was trying to line them up properly and a couple YRUUers show e up to help and theywere all putting some roof pieces on the doors but were doing i from top to bottom which wasn&#39;tg oing to work so I got mad and left, or I told them it was the wrong wa y and I wasn&#39;t going to wait around cause I had already working for a long time on it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AM Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/02/14/am-dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/02/14/am-dream/</guid>
      <description>3:15am HST Friday 14 February 2003
With two cute girl-friends of mine, one new and one kinda old, and I was trying to decipher the meaning of the screenname of the newer girlfriend. It was like ah-pl8-gr8 or something and I kept trying to attach English words to it like English, but she gaave me a hint that it was Spanish, and that changed the whole paradigm, of course. (thanks g).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Angelique dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/02/14/angelique-dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/02/14/angelique-dream/</guid>
      <description>9:10am HST Friday 14 February 2003
This dream was probably around 4 or 5 am, before the first rooster started hollerin&#39;.
I was chatting with Angelique from back in my UH days at the dorms. We were being all flirtatious and may have been about to hook up or go on our first date when she said something like, &#34;well we can date if you don&#39;t mind sometimes ending up in the restroom in Paris in a puddle of vomit&#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/02/13/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/02/13/dream/</guid>
      <description>5:05am HST Thursday 13 February 2003
I had to get up to go pee, and I figured I could just go back to the little bathroom and pee but when I got there it had no walls, so I used a sleeping bag to cover me while I was there. But there was no way to hang the sleeping bag from the ceiling anymore, and I was surprised that I hadn&#39;t thought this through a bit more completely; when I got up to pee it seemed like everything would go smoothly, that all conditions were accounted.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AM dreams</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/02/10/am-dreams/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/02/10/am-dreams/</guid>
      <description>4:48am HST Monday 10 February 2003
a rooster is crowing across the street.
Janette and I were walking and climbed up a sand hill. a bad guy came up behind us and a friend came up on the other side of this hill. I told the friend if the bad guy shoots at us, you run to the cops. There were cops sitting in police cars not too far away.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/02/02/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/02/02/dream/</guid>
      <description>8:58am CST Sunday 2 February 2003
Driving by a big field with a large flat rock and a bunch of guys sitting on the rock, all wearing construction outfits, i turned around and walked up all barefoot to say HI and figure out why a bunch of guys wer sitting on this large flat rock.
I got a bit good naturedly harassed for no soes and ignored it, &#34;Well it doesn&#39;t take shoes to sit on a big rock.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/01/31/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/01/31/dream/</guid>
      <description>7:25am CST Friday 31 January 2003
I was in school, like a college situation, and it was my last day to be there; I was leaving in the middle of the semester. Super happy and nostalgic and went down to the cafeteria, sitting between two girls I hadn&#39;t met before across from a friend of mine, randomly yammering about what it will be like in my new life, and what it will be like here when I&#39;m gone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/01/23/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/01/23/dream/</guid>
      <description>4:26am CST Thursday 23 January 2003
Woah. I&#39;m reminded that I had a dream last night. I&#39;m not sure if the dream happened before or after my mouthguard cracked.
(dream)
In my dad&#39;s living room, my grandpa/dentist was sitting on the couch to my back right, and his wife was on the recliner to my front left. He was looking through pictures and came across some that showed my teeth before he had worked on them to make the front teeth all straight and such.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/01/15/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/01/15/dream/</guid>
      <description>7:05am CST Wednesday 15 January 2003
Reading some literature about how Amway has the finest, most effective sales and marketing plan in the US. How they&#39;ve got distribution centers all over the place, in about 20 different states. How I can make a pile of money in commissions selling, for example, refrigerators to restaurants, like Jason&#39;s restaurant back when he had a restaurant.
Walking with my friend Tom from I-group, wearing slacks and button up shirt, I told him, &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream fred</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/01/08/dream-fred/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/01/08/dream-fred/</guid>
      <description>9:43am CST Wednesday 8 January 2003
(dream)
In a shopping mall in France with Fred. I had walked away from him and came back to find him haning money to a fat guy who grabbed it without trying to look conspicuous, except that he had to reach over to get it. I asked Fred what was the dealio and he was all, &#34;dammit $100 for nothing&#39;&#34; as he had apparently been looking at some new shoes and shit fat cat had told him that he could get Fred the soes for $100 instead of the price indicated.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream KTRU</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/01/08/dream-ktru/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/01/08/dream-ktru/</guid>
      <description>6:52am CST Wednesday 8 January 2003
(dream)
Had just arrived at KTRU and Meg as in the station. I was the next DJ and I put on some music randomly as per my usual custom, and then i realized I needed to read the MRA on, so I fumbled around to find the headphones and the voume dial to keep from getting feedback, and none of the controls are how I remember them, and I keep getting feedback until I turrned the headphone volume all the way down so I can&#39;t tell if anyone can hear me or not.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/01/03/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2003/01/03/dream/</guid>
      <description>7:11pm CST Friday 3 January 2003
(dream)
Someone speaking some dialog for a movie, maybe Sean, but she was a girl. We were filming a movie and basically didn&#39;t have enough script so were trying to go over old script again in a different way to make it seem longer.
I woke up and Joel was beside me. He had been sleeping in a weird position; weirder than Marty McFly in Back to the Future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream Godfather</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/12/25/dream-godfather/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/12/25/dream-godfather/</guid>
      <description>8:00am PST Wednesday 25 December 2002
(dream)
In a futuristic setting, needed to travel by getting inside a tube that would launch me like through a slide (like on Jetsons or Futurama) except we sometimes had two way traffic in the same tube and would have to like suck in a gut or try to squish over to one side to get past. I didn&#39;t always know which side and one time I went past a guy who had a candle that he was taking to a birthday party and the candle blew out as we passed each other.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream KTRU</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/12/25/dream-ktru/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/12/25/dream-ktru/</guid>
      <description>8:16am PST Wednesday 25 December 2002
(dream)
It had been a long time since I played anything at KTRU, but I was going through my CDs and noticed that I had a CD that KTRU used to have, but no longer had; the case was still there but the CD was missing. (This happens more often at KTRU than an honest DJ might like)
The particular CD I found was one that I bought a long time ago at Record Rack; I could tell because the price sticker was still on the face of the CD instead of the back of the CD, or even the case where it should be.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/12/24/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/12/24/dream/</guid>
      <description>6:35am PST Tuesday 24 December 2002
(dream)
With five other men from my men&#39;s group, or some men&#39;s group (though Wende may have been one of them) we were in a house that looked a lot like my dad&#39;s house, at least in the ceiling. We needed to paint the ceiling white. With six people, I suggested we either get into three teams of two or two teams of three, and I knew of a way for each setup to work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/12/22/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/12/22/dream/</guid>
      <description>10:32am PST Sunday 22 December 2002
(dreams)
Wende and I were at SWUUSI and I saw Bryn and her mom. Grabbed Wende by the hand and ran up to Bryn. &#34;HI!&#34; but she was rather non-responsive. So I told her I got her a guitar pin from Hard Rock Cafe, and she didn&#39;t seem to want it.
- - - -
Saw some cats doing tricks on skateboards, jumping over curbs and chain guardrails and such.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/12/18/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/12/18/dream/</guid>
      <description>9:44am PST Wednesday 18 December 2002
(dream)
Wende and one of her girl friends and I and two youth were at SWUUSI. We had our own cabin, away from all of the other youth at SWUUSI. I hadn&#39;t been to the past couple of events, so I was unsure of everyone&#39;s name and kinda embarassed about that. Unsure of myself to go meet everyone cause I didn&#39;t know who I was supposed to know and who I didn&#39;t.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/12/17/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/12/17/dream/</guid>
      <description>6:42am PST Tuesday 17 December 2002
I had a million dreams last night, some of which featured Jason Fricke, Maia Cudhea, Sean Murray, Erick Morrow, Bryan Beck. Fun to get back to old school YRUU.
I was in an auto parts store and Jason called me from the beach somewhere on the auto parts store phone. He tried to pretend he was someone else, &#34;hey my car is broken down because of parts you sold me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/12/10/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/12/10/dream/</guid>
      <description>7:43am PST Tuesday 10 December 2002
(dream)
On a road trip, I went back to Bloomington, staying in a garage apartment at the same address as Maggie and Molly&#39;s house. I felt all sad like, &#34;what am I doing here?&#34; and was crying when I came from the store where Barb was working, but when I opened the door, some other traveler was in the room as well.
&#34;When did you get here?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/12/07/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/12/07/dream/</guid>
      <description>9:55am PST Saturday 7 December 2002
(dream)
Back at Emerson Church, we were having a ceremony for some of the graduating seniors, including Zach Wood. Anyone who wanted to speak positively of him was able to do so.
I ended up first in line, even though I figured advisors shouldn&#39;t go first, but be somewhere near the end, cause of all people advisors probably know them best except for family (and in some cases, more than family)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dreams</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/12/06/dreams/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/12/06/dreams/</guid>
      <description>7:59am PST Friday 6 December 2002
(4am dream)
Driving on a road that had been just freshly poured, like fresh asphalt had just been layed down where previously there was only grass and a forest, I felt so bad for the animals who would be cut off from their buds on the other side of the road, but I was forced to use this road for some reason to get someplace I had been to before using other roads in the past.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/12/01/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/12/01/dream/</guid>
      <description>9:02am PST Sunday 1 December 2002
(dream)
Driving up a mountain, Sally and I were helping to hold the highway together, like reinforcing it with big metal plates, attaching them to rocks and such to make sure that nothing would fall apart, so that the freeway below would not collapse under its own weight and slide down or break off the mountain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/11/10/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Nov 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/11/10/dream/</guid>
      <description>3:13am CST Sunday 10 November 2002
(dream)
Headlines on TV that we had just engaged in military battle with Iraq, watching a plane fly in and launch a missle, and watching the missle as it rocketed across the landscape and finally detonated near a lot of people and then I was with all the guys from the Wolf Shop, up on a platform with the bad guys all around us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/11/06/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/11/06/dream/</guid>
      <description>7:03am CST Wednesday 6 November 2002
With an ethnically diverse group of people at a SWUUSI Young Adult type situation, talking in a cabin in the woods after having witnessed a guy who was in charge of food try to fund something by stealing the remainder of alcohol from a party next door and everyone got mad at him for being so silly and thoughtlesss about this community.
As i walked upstairs with my plate/bowl of food, someone said, &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream Aaron</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/11/04/dream-aaron/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/11/04/dream-aaron/</guid>
      <description>3:56am CST Monday 4 November 2002
(dream)
At a rally at Aaron Ryan&#39;s house, like a farm and he neeeded to cut down a large tree in his back yard and that fact had been advertised on the rally flyer. But when he cut it down, no one was watching except me and it fell into a the neighbor&#39;s yard and knocked down one of their trees. Actually Aaron&#39;s tree was so enormous that its branches basically dwarfed and bullied over the neighbor&#39;s tree, and it fell on their roof and destroyed their garage at first, and then smashed to bits their home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream diversion</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/11/04/dream-diversion/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/11/04/dream-diversion/</guid>
      <description>5:07am CST Monday 4 November 2002
(dream)
&#39;you create a diversion,&#34; I said to my friend.
We were in a mental hospital, so he starting spraying shaving cream on the walls and theatening to kill someone.
I became him and sprayed shaving cream thickly at the floors, with a spray can powerful enough to shoot like a waterhose worth of foam at once. I said threatening things like, &#34;I&#39;m going to kill so and so&#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream dolly</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/11/04/dream-dolly/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/11/04/dream-dolly/</guid>
      <description>7:51am CST Monday 4 November 2002
(dream)
Driving Karaoke, Janette, and Jack really fast down some clay hills streets of Dallas, except we were riding on a dolly. Very fun wizzing around on that.
We headed quickly down a hill on which we had to turn at the bottom, but they got off before we got to the bottom. I was a bit offended that they wouldn&#39;t trust that I could stop the dolly smoothly in time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AM dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/11/01/am-dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/11/01/am-dream/</guid>
      <description>6:33am CST Friday 1 November 2002
(dream)
At Northwoods last week Drew Barrymore had come to visit and that she might come this week as well! I wondered if it would be worth it to drive the hour to church to possibly see her (she&#39;s my girlfriend, but I just haven&#39;t told her yet), but it was predicted that she wouldn&#39;t likely be there.
I ended up not going.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/10/31/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/10/31/dream/</guid>
      <description>3:39am CST Thursday 31 October 2002
(dream)
In a hospital, working there, I am made aware by listening in on a conversation between a doctor and nurse that the hospital will make 800 dollars per year on a patient if we are able to perform surgery on her this coming month. We&#39;ll be guaranteed $800 per year after that.. The nurse is asked to try and get that surgery &#39;account.&#39;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/10/30/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/10/30/dream/</guid>
      <description>7:37am CST Wednesday 30 October 2002
Working in a supermarket restocking magazines kinda and also folding a wire to measure something and talking about languages and deciding to learn Iranian because they say toilet for toilet and if any language is based on that, then I dcan learn it.
I wasn&#39;t clear on whether I was restocking books or magazines or building shelves forthem or coosing good books to read; they had some by ray Bradbury and Bill Clinton and some magazines like Vogue and Cosmopolitan and Redbook and stuff.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/10/29/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/10/29/dream/</guid>
      <description>9:06am CST Tuesday 29 October 2002
Talking with the two members of NWA in my room. They were black in my dream with white skin. I listened to their music and it was really funny and creative and good. I told them in honesty that I now wish I had gotten into them a long time ago so I could have grown up listening to their shit.
&#34;But instead, I know all the songs by DJ Jazzy Jeff and Fresh Prince, plus um, Beastie Boys, and a lot by Sir Mix-A-Lot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/10/18/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/10/18/dream/</guid>
      <description>6:19am CDT Friday 18 October 2002
Okay, so I woke up to this most recent dream:
I found myself outside of this (Norma&#39;s) house, and walking past my old house. Did they add on that garage? Hmmm. What about that wall there? I tried to visualize myself at 8 years old, playing in these locations. These were added onto the right hand side of the house, as viewed from the street.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dreams</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/10/17/dreams/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/10/17/dreams/</guid>
      <description>1:39am CDT Thursday 17 October 2002
(dreams)
Up in a tree I was on the phone with a friend of my ex-DJ partner, Donna who changed her shift from 7 to 10pm to 10 to 1am, but still did the 7 to 10 shift at times. I was standing way up in the trunk of this tree talking KTRU gossip with these people on the phone, and trying not to fall down out of the tree as I kept slowly rocking back and forth looking at the schedule of DJs written on the trunk of the tree written really small, like printed right on the bark.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/10/16/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/10/16/dream/</guid>
      <description>8:15am CDT Wednesday 16 October 2002
(most extensive dream ever)
&amp;lt;! p class=dream I took a risk and told Sally how much I love her, while we&amp;gt; Sally and I were hanging out at some small city that I&amp;rsquo;ve never previously been. We were in her old neighbohood, inside a cafe type thing, with lots of other students, all friends. Sally was eating some toast from another&amp;rsquo;s plate and after a while I reached over to get some eggs off this plate that had apparently been abandoned, and she was all, &amp;ldquo;oh!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dreams</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/10/15/dreams/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/10/15/dreams/</guid>
      <description>8:49am CDT Tuesday 15 October 2002
My dreams featured Jennifer from Paint This!, in a big new store, and a customer that was trying to hit on me or something.
Fred showed up in a later dream; he was also on a road trip, and jokingly asked me if I wanna race. I was all &#34;sure,&#34; and held my hands side by side like two cars and then made them drive off quickly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/10/11/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/10/11/dream/</guid>
      <description>9:20am EDT Friday 11 October 2002
(dream)
Walking with Barbie maybe, and came across a house under construction. I needed some 2x4s to use as stakes in my house to help me sell it. Inside the garage of this house (not mine) I found some pieces of 2x4 about 4 feet long with pointy ends to use as a stake. Found four pieces. Also found 4 smaller pieces to be used for something else.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eminem dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/10/11/eminem-dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/10/11/eminem-dream/</guid>
      <description>9:43am EDT Friday 11 October 2002
I met Eminem in a previous dream. I don&#39;t remember details except that we had met that day and were becoming friends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/10/09/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/10/09/dream/</guid>
      <description>8:48am EDT Wednesday 9 October 2002
(dream)
With my Aunt Madeleine in a parking lot at her car, kinda inside a building with some water nearby, and she started to get ill or fall under water and I couldn&#39;t really keep her afloat, so I hollered at someone to call 911, but they ignored me, so I grabbed her phone and called 911 while trying to keep her from sinking and the operator was all, &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/09/26/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/09/26/dream/</guid>
      <description>9:35am CDT Thursday 26 September 2002
(dream)
At a Wal-mart, outside in the parking lot and sorta loitering there waiting for them to open because they were closed having an employee only meeting. I packed my stuff up and my backpack was too light; my computer wasn&#39;t in it. I freaked a bit and went into the front of the store in an attempt to walk through and get my coputer that I thought I had left on the other side of the building, but some employee was all, &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/09/25/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/09/25/dream/</guid>
      <description>9:14am CDT Wednesday 25 September 2002
(dream)
Driving a car around a block and needing to drop off Dude and Gene, but at first thinking that I couldn&#39;t go but to within a block of where they needed to be dropped off, but then I realized I could, so I turned left up this small driveway into a parking lot and dropped them off.
They had just helped me carry something in my car to somewhere or some shit like that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/09/24/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/09/24/dream/</guid>
      <description>8:55am CDT Tuesday 24 September 2002
(dream)
In a library writing html to represent entries in a checkbook register, I was just hardcoding all the entries themselves, and then realized that it would be much easier in the long run to write a template and let the entries be stored in a database and let the comptuer format them nicely.
I paced around the library a bit and my laptop power cord got stuck on the opposite side of a shelf than where I had been so I untangled it and woke up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dreams</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/09/07/dreams/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/09/07/dreams/</guid>
      <description>9:11am CDT Saturday 7 September 2002
(dream)
In a something above the ground like 40 feet up and one of my youth jumped out and his parachute didn&#39;t open so he kinda bonked on the ground, but he was okay. He pulled his parachute out like gosh darn stupid parachute! and then he tossedthe top part of a rop up to me and it took a few tries but I caught it and then pulled him up to our level again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/09/05/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/09/05/dream/</guid>
      <description>6:43am CDT Thursday 5 September 2002
(dream)
I was somewhere and Heather from back in my high school days called and came to visit! We hadn&#39;t been in touch for a long time, lke a few years, so it was good to catch up, but we didn&#39;t really talk about much. When she first saw me, she said, &#39;you look good; you look like Mr Reagh,&#39; which was a total compliment cause he was one of our best teachers in the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/08/29/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/08/29/dream/</guid>
      <description>5:23am CDT Thursday 29 August 2002
(dream)
In an area with a shallow pool and I was surprised to see some cats sitting patiently at the bottom of the pool. I surmised it must be an optical illusion of some sort, but I got into the pool and it was no trick; there really were cats in there. I tried to avoid them as they seemed not too keen on having visitors, but one of them clawed me in the back of my right hand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/08/28/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/08/28/dream/</guid>
      <description>8:00am CDT Wednesday 28 August 2002
(dream)
Went to a nice restaurant with Wende, and then to the restroom to wash my hands, and Robin and Chris from my I-group were there each taking a piss. I was at the sink and could hear their voices, and then when they came out I was like, &#34;HI&#34; and told them I&#39;d be out in a second.
Robin came back in and said he had to go somewhere real quick, and then I was out in the restaurant and one of the waitresses asked me if I worked there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/08/21/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/08/21/dream/</guid>
      <description>3:32am CDT Wednesday 21 August 2002
(dream)
Out by a curb meeting two kids on the street. One of them was all, &#34;Joe,&#34; or something and I asked the other for his name and he took a breath and said, &#34;Chapsanova.&#34;
&#34;Spell it,&#34; I said, then &#34;oh wait. I got it.&#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/08/08/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/08/08/dream/</guid>
      <description>9:06am CDT Thursday 8 August 2002
(dream)
Peering over the edge of some rough clay bluff (about 20 feet tall) I witnessed the process of life as ants were attacking a velvet ant. I climbed down for a closer look and saw more ants chewing on a butterfly or something. I really really wanted to help the butterfly by picking it up, but I just sent it positive thoughts with my mind and encouraged it to have the strength to fly free.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/07/30/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/07/30/dream/</guid>
      <description>8:00am CDT Tuesday 30 July 2002
(dream)
In a hotel type thing, and Will Robidee, the general manager of KTRU was in charge of taking care of stuff. I took an elevator up, and couldn&#39;t find the button to go up, so I flipped a little switch and it went up beyond the level of the roof. I was really scared that I might fall, but it didn&#39;t and I was able to get it back down to the level of the roof.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/07/22/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/07/22/dream/</guid>
      <description>6:29am CDT Monday 22 July 2002
(dream)
Someone was describing a utopian YRUU community.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/07/15/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/07/15/dream/</guid>
      <description>8:33am CDT Monday 15 July 2002
(dream)
I was meditatively removing was from a jar while talking to Jennifer at Paint This!, but I was not really getting any productive work done toward etting my butt out of Houston.
She was making plans for us to paint on Saturday, but I was all, &#34;I won&#39;t be here...&#34; It was disconcerting for a friend to forget that little detail.
I hadn&#39;t made any plans for where to stay in Dallas, nor did I have any money to stay anywhere.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/07/03/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/07/03/dream/</guid>
      <description>7:49am CDT Wednesday 3 July 2002
I was living back in our house that I lived in from 3rd to 7th gread. I had packed all my laundry and my mom took it somewhere and I couldn&#39;t find it. I scoured through the house multiple times, but it was not there. My mom thought maybe she had accidentally taken it out as garbage.
So I went outside and walked down the street a bit to a neighbor&#39;s house and saw bags of trash.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/06/27/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/06/27/dream/</guid>
      <description>5:45am CDT Thursday 27 June 2002
(dream)
In a classroom situation, a student was outside with the intention of knocking down the flag pole in such a way that it would crash into the classroom.
The professor didn&#39;t seem too worried, saying something like &#34;I wonder what it will be this time?&#34;
I was all he&#39;s going to crash into the school; look out
But when I saw the plan unfold outside, it was less than menacing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/06/18/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/06/18/dream/</guid>
      <description>7:27 am Tuesday 18 June 2002
Woke up early and considered getting up to fold my laundry (rally shirts on the bed), but rolled over onto them and fell back asleep.
(dream)
With YRUU peeps - Bryn, Mark V-S and others. I had something to give to Mark, but I couldn&#39;t remember where I had put it. I looked in a trash can next to where we were standing, but it had gross food wrappers in it so I didn&#39;t look too deeply.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/06/06/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/06/06/dream/</guid>
      <description>7:11 am Thursday 6 June 2002
(dream)
At work Kevin had received a letter thouhgt it had been sent to his wrong address and was forwarded to him. He was surpised that anyoe would have the old address considering how much mail he was getting on a dialy basis.
I set out to desig a way to allow us to verify that a human was writing him an email from the place online where the old address was published.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/05/10/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/05/10/dream/</guid>
      <description>7:42 am Friday 10 May 2002
(dream)
In my old apartment on West Gray, I was listening to one of the obnoxious night DJs on KRBE - Adam Smasher I think. Except his telephone helper girl was at my apartment chillin&#39;.
I wanted to tell a story or some such over the air, so she got me through to the DJ who was all, &#34;blah blah what&#39;s your name?&#34;
I told him and just started this tirade description of what I&#39;ve been up to lately as if people want to hear about that, and he was surprisingly quiet, no inerrupting me as I was expecting him to do, even when I got sidetracked by Christine and Daniel bounding into the room un-announced, except that it wasn&#39;t Daniel, but Will from YRUU.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/05/09/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/05/09/dream/</guid>
      <description>4:34 am Thursday 9 May 2002
(dream)
Had just driven my car (it was my old Oldsmobile Omega) and had a bit of trouble parking it because the steering wheel seemed to be missing, and the brakes didn&#39;t work.
I looked all around, and the place where the steering column should be had nothing but the gear shift of the automatic transmission and a little tiny bit of the steering column, which I could use to steer the car with some difficulty.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dreams</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/05/06/dreams/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/05/06/dreams/</guid>
      <description>8:11 am Monday 6 May 2002
dreams
Many many ceiling tiles were missing in my apartment, and I helped fix them by drilling holes in some wooden frames so they could be attached to the ceiling.
Someone pointed out that we could get some natural glue products that would work better than screws to hold the frame in place - carrots. I&#39;m not sure how that was supposed to work exactly, though.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/05/03/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/05/03/dream/</guid>
      <description>8:am 3-5-02 dream
with Tammy/Lee-eh and some one who might have been my gay friend Kenneth from gymnastics outside in a Target parking lot, and we were getting in to Tammy&#39;s car, but we were arbitrarily trying to make it more difficult in the following way. We all had to remain in physical contact with one another, 9touching the hand of someone else in the group, and had to get in on opposite sides of the car.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/03/26/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/03/26/dream/</guid>
      <description>4:30am Tuesday 26 march 2002
(Dream)
I went back to work at Kroger, back in Tomball it seemed. I had just arrived we they were all, &#34;okay, whoever does the best work helping to clean up he store will get a prize of some sort.&#34;
I had noticed that on top of the display cases was enough dust to keep me busy collecting dust for a while. So I searched briefly for a broom and a bucket to collect dust in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/03/26/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/03/26/dream/</guid>
      <description>4:30am Tuesday 26 march 2002
(Dream)
I went back to work at Kroger, back in Tomball it seemed. I had just arrived we they were all, &#34;okay, whoever does the best work helping to clean up he store will get a prize of some sort.&#34;
I had noticed that on top of the display cases was enough dust to keep me busy collecting dust for a while. So I searched briefly for a broom and a bucket to collect dust in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/01/05/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jan 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/01/05/dream/</guid>
      <description>12:58pm CST Saturday 5 January 2002
(dream)
Fred and I were our current age, but alone at our ex-ex house from elementary school. We were so mad and fighting with each other. I was just so pissed at him! I don&#39;t even really know why, but just pissed and calling him all sorts of names, refusing to help him with our chores, and we were both undermining each other&#39;s work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream.254</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/08/30/dream.254/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/08/30/dream.254/</guid>
      <description>KTRU with more Rob! 2:54am CDT Wednesday 30 August 2000
(dream)
I got a postcard from my friend Suzanne, something like, &amp;ldquo;Rob! I just heard that KTRU might let each DJ have his own radio show so you can actually talk on the air! You can say whatever you want! You can take callers on the air!! &amp;ldquo;
She wanted an internet connection that would allow her to listen online. &amp;ldquo;But frst&amp;rdquo; she said, &amp;ldquo;what works?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream.505</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/08/30/dream.505/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/08/30/dream.505/</guid>
      <description>5:05am CDT Wednesday 30 August 2000
(dream)
Driving back to my old neighborhood, this time driving all the way in through the front of the subdivision so I could have a glimpse of some trains being driven backwards at 10am. Somehow I had seen a note written that the train would drive backwards at 10am on the day.
I got to the model train museum, which was about a mile from my house on Methil and the guy inside was driving a model train.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/08/25/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/08/25/dream/</guid>
      <description>6:20am CDT Friday 25 August 2000
Lately, each time I type a dream, I stumble from our bedroom to the study and start typing my dream. Always with my eyes closed because my right-hand brain is watching images of the dream in my head. When I watch the words, the pictures tend to fade because my left brain takes over. (that&amp;rsquo;s my theory anyway)
The end result is that my typing is not perfect - missing letters, extra letters, misplaced letters, etc&amp;hellip; After it was complete, I would go back and tweak the whole thing and edit it into a reader friendly format.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/08/21/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/08/21/dream/</guid>
      <description>Spy vs Spy 5:05am CDT Monday 21 August 2000
(dream)
I was totally a spy. There had been a treasure buried on the hull of a crashed airplane and the treasure was marked with a rubber spy-vs-spy (from MAD Magazine) mask. To get to the treasure, one had to get the key from inside an elevator shaft, and to get the key, one had to have a flashlight, and the elevator shaft was in a fancy hotel somewhere far away from the airplane hull.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/08/20/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/08/20/dream/</guid>
      <description>flying 6:45am CDT Sunday 20 August 2000
(dream)
Youth Council YRUU peeps were all floating around in a pool, talking in small groups. The life guard asked a couple of youth who were walking around to either go back to the cabin or to join a group in the pool. Duncan&amp;rsquo;s group of about 15 people floated at one end of the pool as he described a game to his small crowd.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/08/19/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/08/19/dream/</guid>
      <description>Anti-racism 3:52am CDT Saturday 19 August 2000
(dream)
anti racist workshop inspired
YRUU, we were in a house, and about to get on a bus to go somewhere. We were in a meeting and (Bitter Bitter) Kate walked in, but she was like older and coming back from having been in YRUU a couple of years ago. I didn&amp;rsquo;t recognizer her.. had heard her name but not seen her. It was late at night for this group of youth; we were all talking.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/08/17/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/08/17/dream/</guid>
      <description>8:18am CDT Thursday 17 August 2000
(dream)
We were at SWUUSI (week long youth camp) inside a building at a workshop. a boring workshop and it was more like a lecture.. I was wanting to be outside playing. Youth were coming in disruptfully and the guy up front, who had been reading asked one of the youth o read instead. The youth (Ken, who was in our local LRY and graduated in 1998 or so) was reading all quietly so no one could hear.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/08/16/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/08/16/dream/</guid>
      <description>6:04am CDT Wednesday 16 August 2000
(dream)
I was sleeping and heard the weather report on 740 KTRH, the am 24 hour news radio in Houston. The weather guy said that a big storm was coming toward the city and he advised that everyone go buy some duct tape and tape up windows so they wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be broken by the storm. I woke up in my dream and the storm was already pounding rain against the windows.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/08/15/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/08/15/dream/</guid>
      <description>7:00am Tuesday 15 August 2000
Looking over the FSD financials with Kevin, he said I would get $6000 as a bonus at the end of the year. We had a project that would net us 110,000,000,000,000,000 dollars. I was all, &amp;ldquo;Kevin, that is more then the debt of the US Treasury; how can this be???&amp;rdquo;
(different dream)
I was in a shopping mall with continental YRUU youth and looking at some videos in a movie rental place.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>tornado-dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/08/09/tornado-dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/08/09/tornado-dream/</guid>
      <description>7:03am Wednesday 9 August 2000
(dream)
We were on a Hawaiian Island in a big field. We = a lot of YRUU people. Someone said, look at that tornado they&amp;rsquo;re having over there. We looked over and certainly there was some cloud disturbance, but it was not a tornado. A youth told him so.
Then from the same direction, something was coming toward us, and there were screams from that direction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/07/28/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/07/28/dream/</guid>
      <description>5:31am Friday 28 July 2000
(dream)
in this dream I lived on Methil drive at the inside a corner:
 * = my apartment * | - = Methil ------------| | = a different street  each week I would walk down to Matt&amp;rsquo;s house to spend the night. This time when I went down, it was like 1am by the time I got there; too late to knock on their door.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream4.04</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/07/26/dream4.04/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/07/26/dream4.04/</guid>
      <description>4:04am Wednesday 26 July 2000
(dream)
we were the poke&#39; mons. (ack). I was Shadowe. Other names were hollered like &#34;blodle&#34; and &#34;chilsed&#34; or &#34;aglonse&#34; shouted names as we moved from otside parking lot into 1 story strip center bulding room. big empty room and we all went in and it was my job to write the rules on the door on the inside of the glass door in dry erase marker.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream6.18</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/07/26/dream6.18/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/07/26/dream6.18/</guid>
      <description>4:19am Wednesday 26 July 2000
pee, get a drink, sleep 4:32am
stretch turn sleep after almost making it to sleep 6:18
(dream)
tossing and back and forth wake to almost alseep, seeing wende in my deams then waking up. then soon asleep and on an outdoor patio type thing with wooden slats and big oak trees around it,. then asking my friend if I could ride his unicylce. he was all, &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/07/25/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/07/25/dream/</guid>
      <description>6:45am CDT Tuesday 25 July 2000
(dream)
In a dark alley with goons around, trying to take my watch and wallet, I was all, &amp;ldquo;No&amp;rdquo; but they kept chasing me, until I ended up in a warehouse that was actually like a bunkhouse where my cousin peter was staying. He was playing cards on a card table with Fred, playing spades, and I ran past them and jumped on the bed, and the goons started playing cards as if distracted but also as if nothing had happened.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream3.57</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/07/24/dream3.57/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/07/24/dream3.57/</guid>
      <description>21:57 Saturday 23 July 2000
been reading java for 2.5 hours. cool stuff. 3:57 am Sunday 24 July 2000
(dream)
at a hotel, parking lot, after having driven up while tired, all my stuff was in the car as I waited for the other passengers to get their stuff out, but once they got it out, they didn&#39;t wait for me to get my stuff out. then some other youth were in the car (kT for one) and I think Mike L for the other (Danielle&#39;s ex-um friend) and I asked them to help me carry everything inside in one trip.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream6.05</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/07/24/dream6.05/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/07/24/dream6.05/</guid>
      <description>6:05am Monday 24 July 2000
(dream)
In a walgreen&#39;s type store, I saw a new nine inch nails CD that I hadn&#39;t seen before. I 1/2way recognized it was a dream, and began to carefully memorize the image on the CD. interesting thing that on the bottom of the picture on the back, which appeard to be simply a photograph of the stage being set up, I noticed that the people near the bottom were all images of John Goodman at various stages of his life all with the same expression of no emotion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/07/23/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/07/23/dream/</guid>
      <description>7:15am Sunday 23 July 2000
(dream)
explaining to my boss kevin why having playstation at a rally is better than trying to set up a playstation workshop&amp;hellip; just have it available and people will play it whenever they want instead of trying to force the fun to happen at a certain time.
I was watching movie set in the old west mexican american war and the bad guys rode into town and said, &amp;ldquo;here take care of my bosses head&amp;rdquo; and the head had beeen severed, some spanish curly locks conquistador with moustache and he threw it at the townsfok and they shouted &amp;lsquo;outlaw!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/07/20/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/07/20/dream/</guid>
      <description>6:16am CDT Thursday 20 July 2000
Racing Sean from ultimate across a field to the gymnasium door. He won, but just by a little bit.
Then changing clothes in the locker room like back in high school and college, but this time there were also two girls watching me. I ignored them essentially (or more like didn&amp;rsquo;t treat them any different that two guys) and changed in front of them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/07/17/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/07/17/dream/</guid>
      <description>4:54am Monday 17 July 2000
dream
I feel like I&amp;rsquo;ve been dreaming for hours that I&amp;rsquo;ve been late for work, as a result of watching TV and pissing around all day. A small amusement park thing that I owned or was renting on someone else&amp;rsquo;s land..
and I needed to get my dad&amp;rsquo;s advice on something, but he wasn&amp;rsquo;t available so I was relaxing outside, looking up at some apartments and a guy looked down and saw me and asked if I was going to watch the game and I was all no that I didn&amp;rsquo;t have internet access.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/07/16/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/07/16/dream/</guid>
      <description>9:18am CDT Sunday 16 July 2000
(dream)
I was at work, and Deborah was verifying that she had our correct SSNs so that we could start having our checks direct deposited into our accounts. While she had the work financial numbers near my desk, I noticed a line that said &amp;ldquo;35 million shares outstanding.&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;Kevin,&amp;rdquo; I asked, &amp;ldquo;what is the deal with all these shares?&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Are there shares out there that no one can purchase?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/07/15/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/07/15/dream/</guid>
      <description>am Saturday 15 July 2000
(dream)
playing ultimate and the game had just ended but I hadn&#39;t plalyed yet. people were leaving to go see movies. then my brother walked up unexpected, wearing a big smile, &#34;like I&#39;m here; let&#39;s play ultimate!&#34; People had just arrived and started to line up to play. I was in great anticipation of playing against Fred, I expected he would be better player than me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/07/12/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/07/12/dream/</guid>
      <description>12 July 2000
Outside in a parking lot, Wende and I were unravelling a long water hose, which needed to connect from the McDonald&amp;rsquo;s in the parking lot to wash her car.
The hose was in a cabin where we stayed while looking for our wedding spot, and we carried it across the parking lot then unrolled it. The middle of the hose was hooked way up high on a small balcony above the parking lot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/07/11/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/07/11/dream/</guid>
      <description>7:44am Tuesday 11 July 2000
(dream)
I was in gymnastics class, happy to be back and bouncy bouncing on the runway trampoline. There was some sort of competition, or just a time to show our skills. My name was called (along with Mark W from ultimate) and I climbed onto the runway trampoline.
I was able to do a branny (front flip with half twist), but not able to do bigger stuff because I kept bottoming-out the trampoline (hitting the floor below), effectively stopping my bounces.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/07/10/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/07/10/dream/</guid>
      <description>am 10 July 2000
(dream)
for a while I dreamt I was typing all this. trying to memorize my dream while thinking I was typing, but not typing. I was sleeping.
melted into sleep and then another dream.
Setting up our new house which was one story and I had Wende&amp;rsquo;s three witching balls which (no pun intended) are designed to capture evil spirits who get entranced by the spiderweb like strands of glass inside the ball.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream1.52</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/07/07/dream1.52/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/07/07/dream1.52/</guid>
      <description>1:52am Friday 7 July 2000
dream
We were at my cousin Bridgette&amp;rsquo;s house and several kids were over and her son Matt had to hurl. He didn&amp;rsquo;t make it to the bathroom the first time.
Bridgette cleaned it up and then the kids were all playing in the room again and the room was all messy with toys everywhere.. Me and Bridgette were in there and Matt was all, &amp;ldquo;um, mom, uh oh.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream4.46</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/07/07/dream4.46/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/07/07/dream4.46/</guid>
      <description>4:46 am Friday 7 July 2000
dream
I was at KTRU playing some vinyl and the microphone was.. well the dj console was up like on a taller table and the turntables up on that. I played some hip hop on vinyl and then was going to play something in stark contrast to that, but I realized I had already played it. Wende was there so I was all &amp;ldquo;Go grab a CD&amp;rdquo; and then on the air, &amp;ldquo;My helper is grabbing a CD for me&amp;rdquo; and she grabbed a fanfold Christmas card, which unfolded off the shelf as she grabbed it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/07/04/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/07/04/dream/</guid>
      <description>5:35am CDT Tuesday 4 July 2000
(dreams)
Wende and I were in the car listening to the radio at about 3am. Listening to 104KRBE and Sam Malone was just arriving into the station. We arrived at the station and I was going to go say HI to him and try to get free tickets and stuff.
We pulled into the parking lot, facing some tennis courts, and the station was behind us in the parking lot in a small one-or-two room building.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/07/03/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/07/03/dream/</guid>
      <description>4:48am CDT Monday 3 July 2000
dream
kT and I were in my new house hanging out and the house was my parents old house but it was somehow given to me to live in . The house had been moved to some new land.
We were waiting for Anna to come by and we were going to say goodbye to her before she goes off to the wild blue yonder in Canada.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream car</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/06/22/dream-car/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/06/22/dream-car/</guid>
      <description>6:54am CDT Thursday 22 June 2000
I had parked my car in a parking lot that was a guys yard where we had all parked every day for a long time. When I went back to get my car, the gas tank was open and a piece of plastic bag was stuck in the gas tank hole. I went back into the school (dorms) and started knocking on doors to see if anyone knew what had happened to my cars gas cap.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream Wende</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/06/22/dream-wende/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/06/22/dream-wende/</guid>
      <description>7:10am CDT Thursday 22 June 2000
Wende and I were living in an old old house that had been built back in the day when the island we were on was dominated by black plague, with thousands of people dying. All of that was over, and we were in Jamaica, going through our house, trying to turn off all the lights in the house because Wende had found an old flashlight that barely glowed when she turned it on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dreams</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/06/16/dreams/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/06/16/dreams/</guid>
      <description>8:23am CDT Friday 16 June 2000
(Dreams)
(1)
I was arrested for creating a nuisance, and disturbing the peace in a small town, but the arrest was somehow a joke (on whom, I don&amp;rsquo;t know, cause I was in on it), so they still let me go to Australia and even gave me $500 calling card so I could check in each day.
I don&amp;rsquo;t remember much more detail of this dream&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/06/15/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/06/15/dream/</guid>
      <description>6:10am CDT Thursday 15 June 2000
I was at work and there was a phone call for Kevin. I almost picked it up, thinking it was for me. It was Christine!! She was on speaker phone and was all, &amp;ldquo;Kevin, this is Christine and was just calling to tell you blah blah blah &amp;ldquo; and I was all freakin&amp;rsquo; because two reasons: 1) I really wanted to talk to her and 2) Her ex-boyfriend happened to be at my work too, and I didn&amp;rsquo;t want him to hear her on the phone cause he really hates her.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/06/14/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/06/14/dream/</guid>
      <description>accident dream 6:19am CDT Wednesday 14 June 2000
Walking along a road, making pretty good speed, Wende and I came up to an accident. The reporters were all on camera talking blah blah blah about the accident and then a reporter saw my name on my shirt and asked, &amp;ldquo;Rob, how do you feel about this?&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;ve lived in this area for a really long time and have never actually witnessed an accident so this is really emotional &amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/06/12/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/06/12/dream/</guid>
      <description>Dream 7:06am CDT Monday 12 June 2000
Have you ever had a dream that you were naked in public? I just dreamt that Wende was naked in public.
Maggie, Wende and I were all waiting for the school bus. We weren&amp;rsquo;t high school age, but we were attending high school. While we waited for the bus, Wende was wearing no shirt nor bra.
When the bus arrived, I was all, &amp;ldquo;here; wear my shirt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/06/01/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/06/01/dream/</guid>
      <description>5:27am CDT Thursday 1 June 2000
Dreamt Marcel and I were on the bus on the way home after work. We were talking to a man on the bus.. He was basically some stranger that we met.
Once we arrived at the bus station, we had to slide down a sharp incline to actually get to the terminal/waiting area.
Marcel and I were talking nerdy stuff as we visited the restroom to P.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/05/30/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/05/30/dream/</guid>
      <description>Dream 6:04am CDT Tuesday 30 May 2000
Wende and I were living in the house I lived in during high school. We had our 3 cats and no parents living there.
Two kids were trying to be mean to our cats - trying to &amp;ldquo;catch&amp;rdquo; the cats messing up stuff at the kids house. Their idea was to put orange powder on the cats, and then look out for orange powder at their house, thereby knowing the cas had been there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/05/26/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/05/26/dream/</guid>
      <description>Dream 6:51am CDT Friday 26 May 2000
I dreamt that I had corrupted a database at work, and spent the entire evening trying to fix it. Weird thing is that SAS never entered the dream - only database and the sense that I was having nerdy fun rebuilding it.
Lynda arrived and was hanging from a showerhead to help stretch out her back while Wende tackled the database problem for me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/05/08/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/05/08/dream/</guid>
      <description>Dream 5:02am CDT Monday 8 May 2000
Dreamt I was sitting with YRUU peeps, looking through the ultimate YRUU mugbook ever compiled. Hundreds and hundreds of YRUU youth pictures and all of them labeled by name.
Looking through them with me was Bryn, who knows tons of youths&amp;rsquo; names. We quizzed each other, and gleefully pointed out names of peeps that we&amp;rsquo;re close to. We didn&amp;rsquo;t get very far: Moonfrog, Alva and her brother Sam.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>dreams</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/05/05/dreams/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/05/05/dreams/</guid>
      <description>8:42am CDT Friday 5 May 2000
Last night I had an extended remix dream including 18 wheelers used as roller coaster trains, a huge amusement park with waterslides that spanned highways and neighborhoods.
I was talking/flirting with the woman in the ticket booth, asking her how I can purchase a season pass to the park. She had a little shells just inside the glass window behind which she sat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>dream back to apartment</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/05/03/dream-back-to-apartment/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/05/03/dream-back-to-apartment/</guid>
      <description>Dream 7:12am CDT Wednesday 3 May 2000
Last night in the wee hours my dream took me to my old apartment. I felt as if I were going home and then realized, whoah! this isn&amp;rsquo;t my home anymore. In my dream I tried to act cool as if I were just coming to check out the progress on the apartment.
Ex-landlord Mark was happy to show me around. Walked in and the first thing I noticed is that the yellow walls / blue ceiling look (which Wende painted in the bedroom) had been extended through the entire apartment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/03/30/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/03/30/dream/</guid>
      <description>Ultimate 7:37am CST Thursday 30 March 2000
Last night, as predicted, I had an elaborate dream about all of the guys from ultimate fighting some battle. Basically there was a seige of a castle, though I&amp;rsquo;m not clear on who &amp;lsquo;owned&amp;rsquo; it or who built it. Most interesting part for me: We magically built a spiral staircase up to the top of the tower. The &amp;lsquo;bad guys&amp;rsquo; didn&amp;rsquo;t know about the appearance of a hole in the roof of the castle, so when they were near it, I would toss them down to their demise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/03/28/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/03/28/dream/</guid>
      <description>Dream 7:10am CST Tuesday 28 March 2000
(transcribed from a dream)
This morning I woke up from a full and complete dream:
Jon Benet Ramsey was being questioned about her parents and their actions and about her actions and just various questions about the living situation in general.
I just happened to be there at the questioning; the meeting was at my church, with a few impartial members asking her things so they could get a better idea about what would be the best course of action.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/03/03/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/03/03/dream/</guid>
      <description>8:41am CST Friday 3 March 2000
I just woke up from a dream where I was living in a house with several people that I didn&#39;t really trust, and I found a gun left carelessly under a desk. I had to sneak away to call the police and explain to them the situation but I couldn&#39;t call 911 because the phone was triggered to alarm if 911 was called so I had to call the non emergency police number, but I couldn&#39;t look it up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>dream Project</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/02/25/dream-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/02/25/dream-project/</guid>
      <description>3:26am CST Friday 25 February 2000
I just woke up cleanly from a clear dream. Wende and I were trying to find the owner of a cat, and we went to the cat&amp;rsquo;s apartment, which was right down the street from me.. We had never met the people before, but I talked to the guy about this idea I had for using the Internet to connect people with special talents and skills.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream 09am</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1993/12/06/dream-09am/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 1993 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1993/12/06/dream-09am/</guid>
      <description>(transcribed from Book Six 5:51pm JST Sunday 28 June 2009 (day 14340))
9:10AM Monday 6 Dec 1993 (page 44]
I fell asleep instead of doing a Shamanic Journey.
This morning I dreamnt [sic] that I was with Madonna and that she was living with me in dad&#39;s house. She did my laundry for me and interacted with me as friend and lover.
I don&#39;t remember actually kissing her, but I bet that&#39;s how I met her in the dream.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream 11am</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1993/12/06/dream-11am/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 1993 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1993/12/06/dream-11am/</guid>
      <description>(transcribed from Book Six 5:54pm JST Sunday 28 June 2009 (day 14340))
11:15AM Monday 6 December 1993
I just had a long dream about Melanie Barr we were in her room and some dudes ran by outside naked &amp;amp; we turned off the lights to wa see who it was and Melanie &amp;amp; I didn&#39;t kiss or anything, but she acted as if she were a much closer friend to me than in &#39;real&#39; life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1993/12/01/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 1993 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1993/12/01/dream/</guid>
      <description>(transcribed from Book Six 1:46pm JST Sunday 28 June 2009 (day 14340))
9:45 AM Wednesday 1 December 1993 Day 68
Last night I had a dream. I was walking with 4 or 5 different girls. I had been working in a Target-like store and there was a beautiful female customer and I asked her if there was anything I could do for her. Anything. She told me that her new job was skydiving.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bobbi dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1992/09/16/bobbi-dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 1992 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1992/09/16/bobbi-dream/</guid>
      <description>(transcribed from Book Two of my diary) 8:47AM Wednesday 16 September 1992
Bobbi was in a class with me and she held my hand during class. Cool.
Oh - last night Molly said that I will kiss her this semester. Double Cool.
The dream was set in Mr Reagh&#39;s class at 12 or 1am (so I could say &#34;Good Morning,&#34;) The lights went out and I immediately held her hand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1992/05/25/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 May 1992 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1992/05/25/dream/</guid>
      <description>(transcribed from Book Two of my diary)
Memorial Day Monday May 25, 1992 8:41 AM.
Last night I had a dream that
I was at the airport, and a skycrane helicopter descended and picked up 4 people, each with a HUGE umbrella over them. These umbrellas must have been 10 or 12 feet in radius. 20-24 feet diameter, (Duh). Then there was a problem and 2 umbrellas crashed and came tumbling, so I ran over there and talked to the two girls that fell.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dreams</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1987/03/31/dreams/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 1987 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1987/03/31/dreams/</guid>
      <description>(transcribed 4:17pm CST Wednesday 22 January 2003)
March 30 - 6:00AM
I didn&#39;t have lucid dreams. I did dream that everyone from school was outside on some bleachers, and I leaned back on the top and it dumped over. 6:05
6:35 Oh yeah, I dreamed that the comics were changed up. Some were taken out, some were new or all mixed up. 6:37</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1987/03/30/dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Mar 1987 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1987/03/30/dream/</guid>
      <description>(transcribed 11:20am CST Wednesday 22 January 2003)
March 30
No lucid dreams. It&#39;s 5:50AM. I dreamt that I was at a store looking for Jams. Danny Dillard showed up and thought that was funny. Next thing I know, I&#39;m sitting with my back against a wall and a wall is on my left. There are some girls on my right against the wall. In front of me is an open area, maybe a store or a cafeteria.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>