<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>tired on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/tired/</link>
    <description>Recent content in tired on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2019 18:09:21 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/tired/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>evenin</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/10/05/evenin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2019 18:09:21 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/10/05/evenin/</guid>
      <description>I chose not to go out to dinner with them to Ninfa&amp;rsquo;s tonight. Pretty much super tired and need to sleep, but it may have been good to go so I would be forced more onto this timezone.
I plan to go buy candles at Kroger, but not sure when I will.
Today went by super slow at first with a bunch of theory, but then when it got to the practice, everyone was like &amp;ldquo;whoah&amp;rdquo; with questions and head proverbially spinning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working today</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/09/18/working-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2019 21:32:49 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/09/18/working-today/</guid>
      <description>(written 21:32 Wednesday 18 September 2019 JST)
Headed toward home on Nambu Line now after waking up at 4:30 (after one sleep cycle) and doing my morning routine (write dreams, write gratitude, meditate, brush teeth, etc) then headed to work in Kawasaki for JB in Solid Square. Sayuri came about 15 minutes late and was the only student in attendance.
Headed to JR Kawasaki afterward to meet やなさん but he ended up having to cancel for some reason.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>language exchange with Akiko</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/07/11/language-exchange-with-akiko/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2019 23:05:56 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/07/11/language-exchange-with-akiko/</guid>
      <description>23:05 Thursday 11 July 2019 JST Akiko and I went to her train line&amp;rsquo;s side of Akihabara, and ate at the Indian restaurant on the 9th floor of the BIC Camera building. Bottomless cheese nan seems like a good deal until I eat the second one!
We talked about her upcoming trip overseas and pets and other stuff I am too tired to remember, much less write. Oh, we also talked about commas and when to use them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>super tired</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/07/02/super-tired/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2019 00:03:26 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/07/02/super-tired/</guid>
      <description>00:03 Tuesday 02 July 2019 JST Well, I missed the first day of the month by 3 minutes. I have been zoned out in front of my computer longer than 3 minutes so oh well.
Logged 6 hours of work and noticed how much longer it will take. At 10 minutes per line, and 400 more lines to change that&amp;rsquo;s 4000 minutes (hopefully max!), but that is just to get rid of a single singleton.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>woke up late this morning</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/11/12/woke-up-late-this-morning/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 06:24:57 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/11/12/woke-up-late-this-morning/</guid>
      <description>06:24 Monday 12 November 2018 JST I usuually set my alarm for 5am on Mondays and Wednesdays so I can leave the house at 5:45am. This morning I turned off my 5am alarm and planned to snooze until my second alarm, but the phone was in silent mode so that alarm did not sound. Fortunately, Lin had set an alarm for 5:35. I had already packed my computer so I got out early enough to catch my preferred train, featuring enough seats that I can sit and write, or snooze, which I plan to do now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>productent</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/10/09/productent/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2018 23:25:22 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/10/09/productent/</guid>
      <description>23:25 Tuesday 09 October 2018 JST Today wasn&amp;rsquo;t as productive as I had planned, but I got some good stuff done.
4:30am meeting with Boysen, and should have a landing page for The Men&amp;rsquo;s Work soon.
8:00am IL lesson in which we talked about Tsukiji and 2020 Olympics https://the-japan-news.com/news/article/0004879769
came home to work on MT3, but ended up just sleeping
7:00pm Tokyo Men&amp;rsquo;s Circle https://tokyo.mypowercircle.org/
8:06pm someone killed themselves in Seijogakuenmae (a station along my train line)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>tired after long day</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/06/18/tired-after-long-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jun 2018 22:44:31 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/06/18/tired-after-long-day/</guid>
      <description>22:44 Monday 18 June 2018 JST 5am woke up. Home just a bit ago.
Tired long day.
IL Lesson
Wendy&amp;rsquo;s Wild Rock and Happy Dad&amp;rsquo;s day with Dad and Fred and Saundra on the line.
UG Lesson
Saizeria for lunch
ooops no cash. wrote my name and number; went to the bank; came back and paid.
Hung out with cats until time for co-gender circle.
Co-gender circle. 3 people in attendance, including me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>went to SOGO today</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/01/went-to-sogo-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Apr 2018 14:44:39 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/01/went-to-sogo-today/</guid>
      <description>14:44 Sunday 01 April 2018 JST &amp;ldquo;Happy Easter!&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s not Easter!&amp;rdquo;
&amp;rdquo;?????&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;April Fools!&amp;rdquo;
Finally got back to SOGO today and it was touch! Camelia (sp) saw me and was like, &amp;ldquo;remember me??&amp;rdquo; and I was like, &amp;ldquo;I remember your face&amp;ldquo; (could be an insult, but wasn&amp;rsquo;t in this case), and she reminded me she had volunteered for Peace Boat since I last saw her. So neat to hear that it&amp;rsquo;s growing but still has the same genki energy as before.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>today</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/14/today/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Mar 2018 21:12:11 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/14/today/</guid>
      <description>21:12 Wednesday 14 March 2018 JST After my morning lesson I had a big gap during which I had a big nap because dang I was tired. I seem to have gotten over the jet lag (new vocabulary word for some students today). I was roused by a security guard when I tried to nap on a grassy field on 3F of Lazona (next to Eggs N Things (or something)).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>today</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/07/19/today/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2017 23:38:08 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/07/19/today/</guid>
      <description>23:38 Wednesday 19 July 2017 JST Today while running to catch my preferred train, I stubbed my toe. It didn&amp;rsquo;t hurt all that much, but is just annoying that now I will have to wear shoes for a bit while it heals. I forgot to take a picture right after it happened, but I posted one on twitter tonight.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rainb</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/12/23/rainb/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2016 13:08:26 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/12/23/rainb/</guid>
      <description>13:08 Friday 23 December 2016 JST Okay I just took a photo of a rainbow eclipsed by steam/poop from some orange/white painted smoke stacks. &amp;ldquo;Nice.&amp;rdquo; (not nice)

Before that, I took a picture of a Spolt Golf store.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>tired</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/11/17/tired/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2016 07:48:10 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/11/17/tired/</guid>
      <description>07:48 Thursday 17 November 2016 JST I got 4 hours of sleep last night after watching the rest of Batman and the first episode of Mythbusters. Thanks Netflix for enabling me!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>tired</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/05/20/tired/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2015 19:38:33 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/05/20/tired/</guid>
      <description>19:38 Wednesday 20 May 2015 JST Usually after teaching in Fukuura, I go to Akihabara for Japanese lesson. Right now I&amp;rsquo;m headed home from Akihabara; the lesson started without me 8 minutes ago. tl;dr version is that I&amp;rsquo;m tired, but a few little angelic hints have suggested I go home instead:
 missed by seconds the connection in Yokohama and had to wait 10 minutes missed by seconds the connection in Tokyo and had to wait 2 minutes didn&amp;rsquo;t have enough money on my Suica to exit in Akihabara.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>