<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2019 on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/2019/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2019 on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2019 11:11:44 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/2019/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>State of My Life Address</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/09/04/state-of-my-life-address/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2019 11:11:44 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/09/04/state-of-my-life-address/</guid>
      <description>11:11 Wednesday 04 September 2019 JST  Yesterday I walked from Shinjuku to Hiroo, from the men&amp;rsquo;s group new meeting location to our old one. Last night we met for the last time at Takeshi&amp;rsquo;s office, and next week we will be in Shinjuku, at a place I have not yet seen. I have booked it for all of September and October, and trust we can get it for longer if we like it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>State of My Life Address</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/08/08/state-of-my-life-address/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2019 17:22:04 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/08/08/state-of-my-life-address/</guid>
      <description>17:22 Thursday 08 August 2019 JST  My old thunderrabbit router conked out so now we are using a new one with three antennas and mutiple channels and all that good stuff. The conking coincided with new printer disallowing login so I reset the networking and therefore lost the few scan-to-ssh profiles I had set up. I have half of them restored and a few new ones planned. This allows me to scan A4 pages and upload to my b.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eye Gazing Workshop - 17 August 2019</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/blog/2019/08/05/eye-gazing-workshop-17-august-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2019 09:33:44 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/blog/2019/08/05/eye-gazing-workshop-17-august-2019/</guid>
      <description>In two weeks I will be leading an Eye Gazing Workshop near Shibuya station.
To help plan my first workshop, Rin asked me to choose something that made me really excited.
I told her I would have to think about it, and a couple days later it suddenly came to me as the perfect workshop.
After determining what I wanted the final outcome to be, the workshop plan went through a few iterations, with support from Georgie, Mark Wild, Soness, Kevin Turner, and others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>State of My Life Address</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/06/01/state-of-my-life-address/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2019 20:29:45 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/06/01/state-of-my-life-address/</guid>
      <description>20:29 Saturday 01 June 2019 JST  I met Yuri Logo today to talk about making a logo for my brand. She was recommended by Rin so I was like yay! She asked lots of questions and said she had good ideas for it. I could see in her smile the excitement and I felt good about that. I will be working with Rin in a life coaching capacity. I look forward to an accountability partner and learning some new facilitation techniques.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>State of My Life Address</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/03/03/state-of-my-life-address/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2019 21:46:31 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/03/03/state-of-my-life-address/</guid>
      <description>21:46 Sunday 03 March 2019 JST  I will be traveling to the US for 22 days starting March 13th. Not packed yet, but have it planned for next week. I have just sent a list of workshops to Tokyo Men&amp;rsquo;s Circle
Men, my stretch was to find workshops that we can do in Tokyo.
I have led #1 and #3 below. As a group, we did #2 in August 2018 for ourselves, and then again in November 2018 for new men.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>State of my life address</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/01/05/state-of-my-life-address/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jan 2019 20:27:25 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/01/05/state-of-my-life-address/</guid>
      <description>20:27 Saturday 05 January 2019 JST  I have not been writing in my journal a lot recently.. But I have been writing a lot on https://www.marbletrack3.com/ Been working a lot for AB, JB, TY, IST For AB, I have been going through https://mlaphp.com. Middle of step 5 now, trying to untangle class dependencies. Been working on game app with Tariq and recently Dipendra Very likely to go to US in late March and April for men&amp;rsquo;s group weekends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy New Year 2019</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/01/01/happy-new-year-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 01:55:18 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/01/01/happy-new-year-2019/</guid>
      <description>01:55 Tuesday 01 January 2019 JST 2019 is pretty easy to type because the numbers are right next to each other on both sides of the keyboard.
Lin and I went to her sister&amp;rsquo;s house for new years celebrations. Went to karaoke and then a Chinese izakaya (fusion?) before going to the local shrine where some guys were burning bamboo in metal drums.
We arrived home about an hour before 2019 and took turns taking showers.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>