<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>car on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/car/</link>
    <description>Recent content in car on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Oct 2018 15:59:04 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/car/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>blue car</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/10/21/blue-car/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Oct 2018 15:59:04 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/10/21/blue-car/</guid>
      <description>15:59 Sunday 21 October 2018 JST On my way to SOGO there was a blue car amongst the stalls where people were selling bread and beads and stuff. Huh. Old car looks new. It was old, and I asked the guy how old it was. Older than me by 2 years.
After SOGO I talked to him (in English) for about 20 minutes, and met his daughter, who has an accupuncture place nearby.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PM</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/11/23/pm/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/11/23/pm/</guid>
      <description>12:27pm CST Saturday 23 November 2002
Now I&#39;ve gotten my finances up to date. Have paid off the balance on fixing Scott just before I left for SWUUSI way back in July. Have paid my credit card off (mostly gas purchases, but also for my website hosting for the next 13 months) and all is lovely.
Going to put new spark plugs on Scott now.
I got these new crazy spark plugs with four (4) electrode things to spark.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bought a different car!</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1997/12/24/bought-a-different-car/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 1997 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1997/12/24/bought-a-different-car/</guid>
      <description>Wednesday 24 December 1997
  This weekend I purchased a car. I bought a 1990 Toyota Camry, 5 speed manual transmission, 94242 miles, beautifully clean silver exterior and grey velure interior.  Wende and I had just looked again at the first Camry I looked at. I was all, &amp;ldquo;welll .. maybe I&amp;rsquo;ll get it.&amp;rdquo; Wende suggested that we go see what was available at the Toyota dealership we happened to be passing.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>