<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>renee on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/renee/</link>
    <description>Recent content in renee on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2017 10:27:01 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/renee/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>review for airbnb</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/08/05/review-for-airbnb/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2017 10:27:01 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/08/05/review-for-airbnb/</guid>
      <description>10:27 Saturday 05 August 2017 JST Huge Japanese home next to parks &amp;amp; hot springs (https://www.airbnb.com/rooms/17957650) is probably ideal for couples, but not big groups.
Maybe it&amp;rsquo;s because we tried to do too much, or because Dr Wada was overbooked, and did not keep to the originally planned schedule.
It&amp;rsquo;s all very confusing, actually, but in short, I do not recommend bringing big groups to this location.
(( About a week before the weekend, my co-coordinator tried to get a group discount for having invited / brought so many (14+) people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gunma weekend</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/07/30/gunma-weekend/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2017 18:47:31 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/07/30/gunma-weekend/</guid>
      <description>18:47 Sunday 30 July 2017 JST Thanks to Rohini for inviting all the beautiful people who joined the Gunma adventure staying at Renee&amp;rsquo;s place.
Yesteray morning Lisa led yoga and later in the day she played an instrument with four strings. We tried doing some chanting with it, but no one knew the chants.
We went to the caves apparently dug by hand with a bunch of different statues (33?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>it became zero</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/07/15/it-became-zero/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2017 18:31:26 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/07/15/it-became-zero/</guid>
      <description>18:31 Saturday 15 July 2017 JST Lin was all set to buy Shungite from Renee, but we ended up with not enough time to do so after going to Haruka lake and shrine. The lake was fine and the shrine was nice, but because we were late leaving because of this extra trip, neither Lin nor I really took the time to enjoy it. I did get a couple of pics, but nothing like wow holy shit this was worth being late.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Healing from Renee</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/07/14/healing-from-renee/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2017 18:58:39 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/07/14/healing-from-renee/</guid>
      <description>18:58 Friday 14 July 2017 JST I got a glimpse of some past life when Renee offered me diksha today under the canopy of trees overlooking the base of Biyakue Dai Kannon.
11:56 Saturday 16 September 2017 JST Here are some pics I took:
                  )](//b.robnugen.com/travel/japan/Gunma_2017_francois/thumbs/2017_07_14_rob_joins_francois.jpg)](//b.robnugen.com/travel/japan/Gunma_2017_francois/2017_07_14_rob_joins_francois.jpg))
Pics from the next day</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Going to Renee&#39;s in Gunma today</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/07/14/going-to-renees-in-gunma-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2017 07:53:44 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/07/14/going-to-renees-in-gunma-today/</guid>
      <description>07:53 Friday 14 July 2017 JST Leaving in 2 hours.
18:51 Friday 14 July 2017 JST Such a nice area! We went to a long cave thing that was apparently dug without modern equipment. It is 400 meters long, and was apparently supposed to go 400 meters more, but life and heavy rock got in the way. Really nice quiet energy there.
Visited a 41.8 meter tall statue which is 10 meters taller than Corcovado in Rio.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>met Renée</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/07/01/met-ren%C3%A9e/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2017 01:47:01 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/07/01/met-ren%C3%A9e/</guid>
      <description>01:47 Saturday 01 July 2017 JST Tonight on the Tokyo Bay cruise (1200 yen with Yukata) I met Renée who has recently started a business called MRS Gunma in Gunma with her husband. They have a romantic getaway house and an onsen nearby, plus they are distributors for Shungite a stone which arrived on earth via meteorite back in the day in Russia, I think.
23:03 Tuesday 15 August 2017 JST For the record, I gave Renee 20,000 yen cash on the day I met her because I was so inspired by her story.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>