<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>optimistic on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/optimistic/</link>
    <description>Recent content in optimistic on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 May 2019 22:00:16 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/optimistic/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>benefits of leaving an airport at 00:01</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/05/09/benefits-of-leaving-an-airport-at-0001/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2019 22:00:16 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/05/09/benefits-of-leaving-an-airport-at-0001/</guid>
      <description>22:00 Thursday 09 May 2019 JST My friend wanted to buy a ticket to leave on Saturday and accidentally bought a ticket that leaves at 00:01am (one minute after midnight) Saturday morning. (26 hours from now as I write this)
I challenged him to write 25 benefits of such a situation. Here are mine:
 have a funny story be awake with nothing to do but watch digital clock turn from 23:59:59 to 00:00:00 arrive at airport when it&amp;rsquo;s relatively quiet get a chance to see behind-the-scenes stuff they only do at night at airports not have to wake up early for a flight have already halfway solved the jetlag issue get to really ponder the human construct of tracking time have a chance to put a smile on face of staff working late save time shopping for souvenirs save money on buying souvenirs have moving walkway all to yourself get to wonder if other passengers made the same mistake get to joke about how early the flight is easy chance to sleep late on Saturday no worries about a large choice of food vendors in airport immediate night mode on plane so can sleep quickly &amp;ldquo;I leave tonight&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;I leave tomorrow&amp;rdquo; are both true passport stamps says you left the day before you actually leave opportunity for taking nighttime photos at airport can play in kids zone because no kids will be there can say &amp;ldquo;good evening&amp;rdquo; to one seatmate immediately before &amp;ldquo;good morning&amp;rdquo; to next seatmate.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>