<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>recently on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/recently/</link>
    <description>Recent content in recently on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Sep 2018 06:12:06 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/recently/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>state of my life address</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/09/03/state-of-my-life-address/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Sep 2018 06:12:06 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/09/03/state-of-my-life-address/</guid>
      <description>I have just removed the ## 06:12 Monday 03 September 2018 JST date from the top of this journal. Marking them in h2 tags makes them a bit too big for this theme. I hate to modify my source code to fit a theme, but that happened.
 I recently got the website for Mable Track 3 (nearly) up to date. It now has all the entries that had been in my journal at https://new.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>taxing work</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/08/08/taxing-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Aug 2018 12:58:04 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/08/08/taxing-work/</guid>
      <description>12:58 Wednesday 08 August 2018 JST Been working on my taxes for 2017. I filed them on time, but did not provide any list of expenses. Now they are like &amp;ldquo;yeah you owe $2000.&amp;rdquo;
I have compiled a list of expenses based on the train stations I had to use to get to the various lessons. Hopefully that will be enough.
I have been keeping better track of my expenses in 2018.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>recently</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/07/11/recently/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jul 2018 17:51:58 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/07/11/recently/</guid>
      <description>17:51 Wednesday 11 July 2018 JST Last night we discussed presenting a day-long workshop to men in Tokyo. My vision is to expand the work to new men around Tokyo and eventually Japan. I am looking for 2 or 3 men to help me present the workshop in October or November this year. I hope to meet with whoever steps up and create a plan by early August.
Today Tomoko seemed quite entertained with the magnitude of Marble Track 3&amp;rsquo;s Construction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>work and work</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/06/13/work-and-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jun 2018 21:34:20 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/06/13/work-and-work/</guid>
      <description>21:34 Wednesday 13 June 2018 JST Been working too much recently, but not enough to trigger carpal tunnel issues again, fortunately.
Today for AB I nearly finished a report that AB wants to have available. I thought I could finish in 2 hours, but it has taken 6.5 so far. fack. I will tell them it has taken longer.
Today for JB I did my normal Wednesday schedule (Solid Square with Ayano and them, then two kid lessons and two adult lessons in JB office from 15:30 - 21:00).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>最近の僕の世界</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/10/%E6%9C%80%E8%BF%91%E3%81%AE%E5%83%95%E3%81%AE%E4%B8%96%E7%95%8C/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2018 21:31:41 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/10/%E6%9C%80%E8%BF%91%E3%81%AE%E5%83%95%E3%81%AE%E4%B8%96%E7%95%8C/</guid>
      <description>21:31 Wednesday 10 January 2018 JST I can&amp;rsquo;t remember what Mel suggested about this title besides use the correct kanji for 僕
I just finished work and cannot quite bear to think in Japanese.
仕事がおわったばっかりだからまだ日本語であまり書きたくない。
電車乗りますので寝ちゃうかも知れない。
I am on the train so I will probably fall asleep.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>State of My Life Address</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/03/state-of-my-life-address/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2017 10:02:44 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/03/state-of-my-life-address/</guid>
      <description>10:02 Sunday 03 December 2017 JST  I am training to work at Ty&amp;rsquo;s (headed there now) I have been transferring the CB backend to SB, where it will be streamlined / focused on artists and their events instead of artists and their products. It has been over a year since I first considered giving up this laptop for one on which I can run Ubuntu. The only thing I don&amp;rsquo;t like about this laptop now is the lack of battery.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recently</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/08/18/recently/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2015 08:54:03 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/08/18/recently/</guid>
      <description>08:54 Tuesday 18 August 2015 JST This past Sunday, Lin and I went to the end of the Keikyu line, then took a bus to Jogashima, which had sedimentary rocks tilted at about an 80 degree angle in some places.
It was great fun, and worth its own entry!
This past Saturday, Mikako joined us to watch Jurassic World in IMAX 3D. It was okay, but I thought the third movie was better.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recently</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/03/03/recently/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2015 08:57:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/03/03/recently/</guid>
      <description>##08:57 Tuesday 03 March 2015 JST##
Wow first entry in March. I wonder why, but it seems I often miss the first day(s) of months.
Worked on stuff for Nate yesterday on new redmine installation, makin&amp;rsquo; it all customized and nearly getting emails working. The server can send them from command line, and Redmine says its email is set up, but maybe it doesn&amp;rsquo;t check past &amp;ldquo;is there a configuration file&amp;rdquo; (i.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>