<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>tariq on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/tariq/</link>
    <description>Recent content in tariq on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2018 17:26:01 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/tariq/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>conswi dipendra</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/11/02/conswi-dipendra/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2018 17:26:01 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/11/02/conswi-dipendra/</guid>
      <description>17:26 Friday 02 November 2018 JST Today I met with Tariq and Dipendra to talk about ConSwi. They are all excited about the graphics and I am in the camp of getting a minimum viable product out. I want to empower Dipendra to update the graphics in the app. He got a copy of Conswi from Github. Instead of giving him write access to the app, I had him create his own account and push to his own ConSwi.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>morning lessons</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/09/18/morning-lessons/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 12:19:03 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/09/18/morning-lessons/</guid>
      <description>12:19 Tuesday 18 September 2018 JST Good lesson this morning with just two students. We talked about rental おっさん in Japan. Interesting concept of renting old men because they are older and presumably wiser. They? We?
Walked with Tariq from Akabanebashi to Shibashi while we talked about future plans for our swipe game. He found a designer who can create excellent graphics.
Did not end up needing my computer, but I have my rolly bag so no worries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>working on mobile app</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/26/working-on-mobile-app/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 10:44:13 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/26/working-on-mobile-app/</guid>
      <description>10:44 Thursday 26 April 2018 JST Woke up early to come out to Kawasaki so I could meet with Oriane, Cyber Knights, and Court of Support before meeting Tariq at 11:30.
We&amp;rsquo;ll have a good chunk of time (per my schedule) though I do not know how much time he will have.
I plan to get some app stuff or AB done today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>met Tariq</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/08/met-tariq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2018 13:22:25 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/08/met-tariq/</guid>
      <description>13:22 Monday 08 January 2018 JST Met Tariq to talk about next steps on our game. My next step is to see about having a backend we can talk to. His next step is to design the progression of levels and think about audio within the game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>app plans for new game with Tariq</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/11/17/app-plans-for-new-game-with-tariq/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2017 20:36:47 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/11/17/app-plans-for-new-game-with-tariq/</guid>
      <description>20:36 Friday 17 November 2017 JST Tariq and I have what I hope is an interesting game idea. That&amp;rsquo;s why I have been messing with Godot Engine. Hopefully I can get up to speed on it soon enough.
We are trying to figure out how to allow users to sell items on the app.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream Tariq died</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/12/01/dream-tariq-died/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2015 06:18:08 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/12/01/dream-tariq-died/</guid>
      <description>around 4 or 5am Tuesday 01 December 2015 JST Making a copy of Tariq&#39;s data, I noted a pattern of full backups and partial backups, so I was able to go back a week to get the most recent full backup. The current backup was going to be a full backup, but it was aborted before it finished. Later, he and I were walking to the train station, and after I crossed the street, I was like, &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>