<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>eyes on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/eyes/</link>
    <description>Recent content in eyes on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2019 15:29:42 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/eyes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Brain pounding eyes vibrating too much computer</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/09/03/brain-pounding-eyes-vibrating-too-much-computer/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2019 15:29:42 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/09/03/brain-pounding-eyes-vibrating-too-much-computer/</guid>
      <description>Last night when I finally went to sleep around 11 pm my brain was pounding headachey and my eyes were vibrating in a strange way like, not in a good way.
I chalk it up to too much time spent on my computer.
it kept me awake for a while, but I was finally able to calm myself down into sleep.
I&amp;rsquo;m on my way to the dentist now, recording this with voice transcription.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>soon thereafter, at Majingos...</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/27/soon-thereafter-at-majingos.../</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/27/soon-thereafter-at-majingos.../</guid>
      <description>##00:54 Friday 28 November 2014 JST##
On my way out of Roppongi, I shook the hands of the various bar managers/owners who said hello, and I took a liking to Ken, who had white hairs in his beard.
He invited me to come up just to see the place so I could come back next time. Okay; that can&amp;rsquo;t hurt, I figured, and followed him up to 6th floor of some building.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>eyes</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/03/01/eyes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/03/01/eyes/</guid>
      <description>Eye Exam 3:58pm CST Wednesday 1 March 2000
KTRU was fun today, but not stellar or even spectacular music-wise. I did play two pretty cool songs - one jungle and one almost blues tune. My mom called during my radio show to congratulate me and Wende! She saw my marriage news in The Feel Good Net. I put on a long song and we talked for about 10 minutes while it played.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>