<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>kai on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/kai/</link>
    <description>Recent content in kai on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 May 2018 08:06:12 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/kai/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>with Kai and Mika met Mike at The Pink Cow</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/05/18/with-kai-and-mika-met-mike-at-the-pink-cow/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2018 08:06:12 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/05/18/with-kai-and-mika-met-mike-at-the-pink-cow/</guid>
      <description>08:06 Friday 18 May 2018 JST 昨日ピンクカウ美佳さんと佳依さんと会って楽しみました。　Had a good time chilling with Kai and Mika at The Pink Cow last night.
マイケルさんも会った。彼が世界の1番よくなバーテンダーでしたって。We also met Michael. He said he&amp;rsquo;s the worlds best bartender.
そうでもそうでもないわからないけど、彼と面白い話できた。I don&amp;rsquo;t know if that&amp;rsquo;s true, but we had a good time talking to him.
美佳さんと佳依さんと日本語でも英語でも喋りました。I spoke in Japanese and English with Kai and Mika.
戸からピンポン音はピッザヂリベリかたが来た。みんながびっくりした。笑 Everyone was surprised when we heard a knock at the door; it was a pizza delivery guy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>thank you Kai!</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/05/11/thank-you-kai/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 May 2018 00:14:24 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/05/11/thank-you-kai/</guid>
      <description>00:14 Friday 11 May 2018 JST Thank you Kai for helping me find a doctor who can help figure out what is up with my wrist. Ouch ouch ouch.
Mika thought dinner was tomorrow night so we are going to meet again next Thursday, so I have to bump my Japanese lesson again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Great day</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/04/great-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Mar 2018 20:56:47 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/04/great-day/</guid>
      <description>20:56 Sunday 04 March 2018 JST Went to SOGO for workout with about 50 people in attendance. Great weather and great workout. I met Shell, Koji, Tyler, and others, but cannot remember now.
Went to lunch with Lisa at Laska and chatted with her a bit, and got to see a video of the type of dancing she is doing.
Went down to Tsujido for karaoke after recording video at karaoke with Kai, Mitsue, and Soness as the stars.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kai and Mika tonight</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/11/25/kai-and-mika-tonight/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Nov 2017 00:42:59 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/11/25/kai-and-mika-tonight/</guid>
      <description>00:42 Saturday 25 November 2017 JST Hung out with Kai and Mika near Mika&amp;rsquo;s work tonight. They gave me a stack of flyers to hand out for a show that Mika and Kai will be staffing on Monday. Thanks to Mika for sending my medium rare burger back to be recooked to well done as I had ordered! Thanks to Mama for snacks she brought back today from her trip.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>tweaked Kai&#39;s presentation</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/07/24/tweaked-kais-presentation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2017 14:15:33 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/07/24/tweaked-kais-presentation/</guid>
      <description>14:15 Monday 24 July 2017 JST Met Kai today at 1pm to edit her presentation which she translated from Japanese. It was pretty decent actually, with just a few wonky sentence structures and some punctuation typos. It was so easy that it did not take the 2 hours we had allocated, but boom done in an hour sitting at (&amp;ldquo;Fresh like a box of _______ ______&amp;ldquo;) down near Azalea.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Good time at Suns Out Guns Out</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/07/23/good-time-at-suns-out-guns-out/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2017 17:08:41 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/07/23/good-time-at-suns-out-guns-out/</guid>
      <description>17:08 Sunday 23 July 2017 JST I missed SOGO 4 weeks in a row, and will miss it again next week, but I enjoyed being back today! Saw Kai while walking near Harajuku station so got to say HI to her for a bit. Super glad that she has been enjoying the workout as well. She met Tai while there, so they enjoyed having rhyming names.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kai&#39;s great presentation</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/06/21/kais-great-presentation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2017 23:03:55 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/06/21/kais-great-presentation/</guid>
      <description>23:03 Wednesday 21 June 2017 JST I have not yet seen Kai&amp;rsquo;s great presentation, but I have been assured it was great! Soness coached her, so I know she received compassionate knowledgable wisdom from a speaking pro!
I arrived just as the last speaker finished; I found the room because I heard the applause from outside the door.
Lukas invited me in for the final picture, so we stood together in the back.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>lunched with Kai</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/04/13/lunched-with-kai/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Apr 2017 17:57:12 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/04/13/lunched-with-kai/</guid>
      <description>17:57 Thursday 13 April 2017 JST Had lunch with Kai at CPK in Lazona today. She helped allay my fears about conducting the orchestra in July. Not that I have even applied yet, but I plan to. After I get these servers updated.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>lunch with Kai</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/02/23/lunch-with-kai/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2017 13:01:26 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/02/23/lunch-with-kai/</guid>
      <description>13:01 Thursday 23 February 2017 JST (written 09:02 Saturday 25 February 2017 JST)
Great to see Kai preparing for her presentation! She got it all planned out and we ate yummy pizza at CPK!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mika bye bye party</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/03/19/mika-bye-bye-party/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2015 23:14:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/03/19/mika-bye-bye-party/</guid>
      <description>##23:14 Thursday 19 March 2015 JST##
On the train now after hanging out with Mika and Kai for nearly 3 hours around Tokyo station. French restaurant Gabo and then Mary&amp;rsquo;s (chocolate) Cafe where customers can self-serve white chocolate shavings on drinks!
Mika is moving to a new company, so this was our bye-bye party for her. We talked about their kanji, which I forgot, and Lin&amp;rsquo;s kanji, which I remember. Kai showed pictures of their trip to Europe and we compared our experiences in Paris; Kai saw Versaille, which sounds really big and beautiful!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>