<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>soness on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/soness/</link>
    <description>Recent content in soness on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2019 23:59:59 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/soness/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>I performed stand up comedy!</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/09/13/i-performed-stand-up-comedy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2019 23:59:59 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/09/13/i-performed-stand-up-comedy/</guid>
      <description>(adapted from my note last night to Mark)
I went to a stand-up comedy open mic tonight and ended up doing a set (my first ever!)
Several jokes went well, a couple did not; one of those is not recoverable in any way I can think of.
Soness said it was really good that I used contents of the room for several of my bits.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Speaking Journey</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/09/08/my-speaking-journey/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Sep 2018 21:36:59 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/09/08/my-speaking-journey/</guid>
      <description>21:36 Saturday 08 September 2018 JST I have been taking Soness&amp;rsquo;s Step On The Red Dot course, part of https://www.yourspeakingjourney.com/
Today was a normal marathon session of getting stuff done, plus lots of witty anecdotes which I hope are helpful for everyone.
I had to bounce out of the Zoom session after 4.3 hours or so and recorded my second Facebook Live video.
https://www.facebook.com/thunderrabbit/videos/10160860956940716/
Shorter than my first one, yesterday</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>more TED talks</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/05/29/more-ted-talks/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2018 16:07:35 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/05/29/more-ted-talks/</guid>
      <description>16:07 Tuesday 29 May 2018 JST Liz Gilbert Your Elusive Creative Genius  What elements do you think make this a “quintessential” talk?  Not sure what you mean by the talk being quintessential; I think it&amp;rsquo;s inspired and probably true, but it is not better than other talks on TED.
 What’s your opinion on this talk?  Great to see a &amp;ldquo;famous&amp;rdquo; artist be humble and real about her fears and modeling how she intends to continue doing her work because it&amp;rsquo;s her work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>watched some TED talks and answered some questions</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/05/28/watched-some-ted-talks-and-answered-some-questions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2018 16:42:18 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/05/28/watched-some-ted-talks-and-answered-some-questions/</guid>
      <description>16:42 Monday 28 May 2018 JST Actually as I write this, I have only watched the first talk and not answered questions yet, but let&amp;rsquo;s see..
How I teach kids to love science  What elements do you think make this a “solutions” talk?  He presented problems to students who created solutions at least for collecting data in the case of nuclear stuff.
 What’s your opinion on this talk?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>booked to speak in negative one day</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/05/09/booked-to-speak-in-negative-one-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2018 14:38:30 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/05/09/booked-to-speak-in-negative-one-day/</guid>
      <description>14:38 Wednesday 09 May 2018 JST I am not sure how all this works, but I plan to join Soness&amp;rsquo;s Get Booked to Speak in a Week class starting tomorrow. So that means between tomorrow and the week after, I should get booked to speak. Does it count if I get booked today, before the class starts?
It&amp;rsquo;s not really a speaking engagement, but come on out to Bar GariGari on June 1st for story telling night</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>meetings before Toastmasters tonight</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/20/meetings-before-toastmasters-tonight/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Apr 2018 10:30:44 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/20/meetings-before-toastmasters-tonight/</guid>
      <description>10:30 Friday 20 April 2018 JST Several meetings today, including with men&amp;rsquo;s group and Soness and others.
13:33 Friday 20 April 2018 JST So far so good! Good feedback from attendees and should be meeting with Soness soon. Wanna ask her how to prepare for Toastmasters meeting tonight.
Bio
Walking on stage, you immediately notice something .. off. Rob is barefoot! Was it a mistake? Did he lose his shoes?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>draft of mission speech</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/09/draft-of-mission-speech/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2018 10:05:20 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/09/draft-of-mission-speech/</guid>
      <description>10:05 Friday 09 March 2018 JST I sketched out this speech a few days ago as I decided to switch my Complice Goal 0 from &amp;ldquo;Take Counseling Course Online&amp;rdquo; to &amp;ldquo;Speak on stage in Tokyo&amp;rdquo;
What is your mission in life? What is it that drives you, that inspires you to wake up each day, knowing what you plan to do, knowing it might not work out that way TODAY, but knowing that on the whole, you are driving toward something.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Great day</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/04/great-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Mar 2018 20:56:47 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/04/great-day/</guid>
      <description>20:56 Sunday 04 March 2018 JST Went to SOGO for workout with about 50 people in attendance. Great weather and great workout. I met Shell, Koji, Tyler, and others, but cannot remember now.
Went to lunch with Lisa at Laska and chatted with her a bit, and got to see a video of the type of dancing she is doing.
Went down to Tsujido for karaoke after recording video at karaoke with Kai, Mitsue, and Soness as the stars.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Office Hours with Soness</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/13/office-hours-with-soness/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2018 14:23:37 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/13/office-hours-with-soness/</guid>
      <description>14:23 Saturday 13 January 2018 JST Build Your Speaker Bio is Soness&amp;rsquo;s most recent course. It solves the problem of having something to give to TEDx organizers when they ask for a speaker bio which they can use in marketing materials.
Prior to starting this course I did not see myself as a speaker, so why should I write a bio? I still cannot honestly say I see myself as having something worth speaking about, but I can see huge value in the course.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chez Soness</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/12/04/chez-soness/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Dec 2015 11:45:03 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/12/04/chez-soness/</guid>
      <description>11:45 Friday 04 December 2015 JST Headed to Chigasaki to help Soness with her websites; I don&amp;rsquo;t know why her sites keep getting hacked. blarg. I will try moving the sites to new user&amp;hellip;. hmm maybe I&amp;rsquo;ll just start from a fresh Wordpress installation.
17:20 Yay lunch at a nice south indian restaurant!
We worked on Soness&amp;rsquo;s sites some, so saw a bit of progress. Called her friend Ay who is also web savvy to try to work out solutions to script problems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>hung out with Soness</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/11/27/hung-out-with-soness/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Nov 2015 19:24:06 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/11/27/hung-out-with-soness/</guid>
      <description>19:24 Friday 27 November 2015 JST Glad she&amp;rsquo;s doing well! We looked at her websites while in 5th floor cafe above newly renovated Chigasaki station a bit after lunch at Saizeria in Chigasaki.
I told her about men&amp;rsquo;s group starting up on Mondays in Hiroo, and I&amp;rsquo;ll invite Yuji to see if he&amp;rsquo;d be interested.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chez Soness features Studio Soness</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/02/12/chez-soness-features-studio-soness/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2015 09:31:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/02/12/chez-soness-features-studio-soness/</guid>
      <description>##09:31 Thursday 12 February 2015 JST##
Headed to Chez Soness to help her record some videos for her latest project/product. Cool stuff!
##16:39
Fun times! We had lunch and converted Chez Soness into Studio Soness and then recorded several takes of her latest Show-n-Tell US video. Dogs and jets augmented the soundtrack after we got her script tweaked. Try again tomorrow!
Now I&amp;rsquo;m headed to first lesson in Akihabara, which should become a weekly event.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hung out with Soness</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/01/15/hung-out-with-soness/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/01/15/hung-out-with-soness/</guid>
      <description>##20:37 Thursday 15 January 2015 JST##
Went to Soness&amp;rsquo;s house today to help her arrange some lights and have her help me help her file some forms.
Great to get yummy lunch and just hang out having fun, plus mailed some books plus panda shaped chocolate to her friend despite the drippy skies.
And then got lots of goodies from her pantry! She&amp;rsquo;s got lots of healthy stuff from iHerb and gave samples entire containers of everything she recommended.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mailed stuff to Fred and Soness</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/21/mailed-stuff-to-fred-and-soness/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/21/mailed-stuff-to-fred-and-soness/</guid>
      <description>##15:15 Friday 21 November 2014 JST##
I just mailed Fred&amp;rsquo;s calendar and stuff to Soness&amp;rsquo;s accountant.
Afterward, I ate an ankoman, an american dog, and drank piru kuru.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First client for Rapid Rabbit</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/19/first-client-for-rapid-rabbit/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/19/first-client-for-rapid-rabbit/</guid>
      <description>##17:28 Wednesday 19 November 2014 JST##
I&amp;rsquo;m sure Rapid Rabbit is probably taken as a company name and website, but I just thought of something to call my new(!) consulting service. Basically, Soness was like, &amp;ldquo;can you help me organize my stuff?&amp;rdquo; and I was like, &amp;ldquo;maybe!&amp;rdquo; and she was like, &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;ll pay you!&amp;rdquo; and I go &amp;ldquo;hmmmmmmmm!&amp;rdquo; So I went over to her place today and scanned a bunch of business cards which I import into some kind of CSR software (probably monkey mail for now); I&amp;rsquo;m going to go through a bunch of receipts for her and I&amp;rsquo;ll mail some papers to her accountant.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Great help from Soness!</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/14/great-help-from-soness/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/14/great-help-from-soness/</guid>
      <description>##17:33 Friday 14 November 2014 JST##
I feel a lot more confident that I can present something fun and enjoyable for the kindergarten classes on Wednesday! Thanks to Soness for sharing from her years of experience!
She agrees that Dream English Kis is a great resource, and said Matt is a great person for me to model because he&amp;rsquo;s got good gestures and (like me,) isn&amp;rsquo;t over-the-top exuberant (like Soness).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>