<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>language on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/language/</link>
    <description>Recent content in language on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2019 23:05:56 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/language/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>language exchange with Akiko</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/07/11/language-exchange-with-akiko/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2019 23:05:56 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/07/11/language-exchange-with-akiko/</guid>
      <description>23:05 Thursday 11 July 2019 JST Akiko and I went to her train line&amp;rsquo;s side of Akihabara, and ate at the Indian restaurant on the 9th floor of the BIC Camera building. Bottomless cheese nan seems like a good deal until I eat the second one!
We talked about her upcoming trip overseas and pets and other stuff I am too tired to remember, much less write. Oh, we also talked about commas and when to use them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>language exchange with Akiko</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/06/21/language-exchange-with-akiko/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2019 00:06:56 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/06/21/language-exchange-with-akiko/</guid>
      <description>00:06 Friday 21 June 2019 JST Today was the second time for Akiko and I to do a language exchange. She had some good ideas for Marble Track 3 and how to market it. I may end up creating another Instagram account; that is apparently the way to go these days.
So happy to get another subscriber on Youtube, and enthralling to see her enthralled with the process of animating the construction!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter in language</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/03/24/chapter-in-language/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2015 10:11:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/03/24/chapter-in-language/</guid>
      <description>##10:11 Tuesday 24 March 2015 JST##
Finished lesson; &amp;lsquo;twas fine and interesting topic about Paul Allen&amp;rsquo;s team recently finding Battleship Musashi.
Finished the lesson and outside the station I saw two women looking at the local area map. I wasn&amp;rsquo;t able to help them as quickly as they helped themselves (by finding their target on the map before I did) but I was most depressed that I don&amp;rsquo;t know French.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>