<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>workout on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/workout/</link>
    <description>Recent content in workout on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2017 14:46:08 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/workout/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>great hot workout with SOGO</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/08/27/great-hot-workout-with-sogo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2017 14:46:08 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/08/27/great-hot-workout-with-sogo/</guid>
      <description>14:46 Sunday 27 August 2017 JST went to workout with SOGO today in Yoyogi park. So hot! But still fun, though at times I felt kinda close to passing out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SOGO</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/08/13/sogo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2017 13:12:38 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/08/13/sogo/</guid>
      <description>13:12 Sunday 13 August 2017 JST Lin and Ma joined me on the way to SOGO. They watched from a bench across from the tree where SOGO peeps generally meet. Workout was great fun, though a bit hard since I haven&amp;rsquo;t attended in a while. Unfortunately I won&amp;rsquo;t be able to attend for two months starting in October. I&amp;rsquo;m bummed about that, but work is work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Good time at Suns Out Guns Out</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/07/23/good-time-at-suns-out-guns-out/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2017 17:08:41 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/07/23/good-time-at-suns-out-guns-out/</guid>
      <description>17:08 Sunday 23 July 2017 JST I missed SOGO 4 weeks in a row, and will miss it again next week, but I enjoyed being back today! Saw Kai while walking near Harajuku station so got to say HI to her for a bit. Super glad that she has been enjoying the workout as well. She met Tai while there, so they enjoyed having rhyming names.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>workout</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/01/25/workout/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/01/25/workout/</guid>
      <description>##08:55 Monday 26 January 2015 JST##
On Friday or Saturday, Tariq invited me to go to the gym with him on Sunday night. We did; it was pretty well stocked for being cheap as chips!
I used several of the machines, including elliptical &amp;ldquo;running&amp;rdquo; machine (which was a bit weird), treadmill (which was a bit boring), and some non-plastic-enshrouded machines which I can&amp;rsquo;t name.
Back twist, arm push up, arm push out, arm pull down, leg push out, and maybe others.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>