<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>guest writer on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/guest-writer/</link>
    <description>Recent content in guest writer on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2013 18:38:17 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/guest-writer/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>proofread your newsletters before sending them</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2013/04/04/proofread-your-newsletters-before-sending-them/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2013 18:38:17 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2013/04/04/proofread-your-newsletters-before-sending-them/</guid>
      <description>##18:38 Thursday 04 April 2013
6:28pm Thursday 4 April 2013
I got a newsletter from Kii recently. I appreciate that the view online link is nicely mangled, and that I can unsubscribe with a click. Link to funny kii newsletter.
The newsletter I received includes this &amp;ldquo;sample text&amp;rdquo;
 Hi Rob,
 Describe what you have to offer the customer. Why should they read? What did you promise them in the subject line?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>speaking of countdowns</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2012/12/21/speaking-of-countdowns/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Dec 2012 22:40:58 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2012/12/21/speaking-of-countdowns/</guid>
      <description>##22:40 Friday 21 December 2012
Nice job, Ryan!!!
https://www.kickstarter.com/projects/breadpig/to-be-or-not-to-be-that-is-the-adventure
9 minutes to go; click now!!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>From Suzy xx in Palestine</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2008/03/07/from-suzy-xx-in-palestine/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2008 18:08:18 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2008/03/07/from-suzy-xx-in-palestine/</guid>
      <description>##18:08 Friday 07 March 2008
This was actually sent to me a long time ago, but I&amp;rsquo;m just now getting it posted
 Hi All, it&amp;rsquo;s been a while I know! Partly my lack of emails is because i&amp;rsquo;m not very good at keeping in touch (as pointed out very clearly by my sister last week!) and partly because I didn&amp;rsquo;t think I had that much to report. I&amp;rsquo;m settled here now and my life has it&amp;rsquo;s routine just like it did in the UK.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Love-Hate Relationship With English, by Akiko Shimada</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2007/07/15/my-love-hate-relationship-with-english-by-akiko-shimada/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jul 2007 14:04:52 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2007/07/15/my-love-hate-relationship-with-english-by-akiko-shimada/</guid>
      <description>##14:04 Sunday 15 July 2007
Looking back over the years, I&amp;rsquo;m surprised by how much time and how much money I&amp;rsquo;ve devoted to English, the world&amp;rsquo;s most dominant language. Sometimes I love English, but sometimes I really hate it, feeling that my longtime efforts haven&amp;rsquo;t been paying off. I still have difficulty dealing with the language. To begin with, English is illogical and capricious. I don&amp;rsquo;t think I&amp;rsquo;ll be able to understand it completely even if I keep studying it for the rest of my life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oaxaca Report Back in Olympia</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2007/03/06/oaxaca-report-back-in-olympia/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Mar 2007 07:58:16 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2007/03/06/oaxaca-report-back-in-olympia/</guid>
      <description>##07:58 Tuesday 06 March 2007
Hello Family and Friends&amp;hellip;
I am back in the states after my 7 month trip to Southern Mexico where I spent mid July until December learning from and photographing the incredible uprising occurring in Oaxaca followed by two months in Chiapas. In Olympia this week, through photos, video clips, and stories, I hope to share the spirit and creativity of the teachers strike turned full scale popular rebellion that managed to take control of the city for multiple months demanding the resignation of the corrupt state governor, Ulises Ruiz Ortiz.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Report from the Zapatista International Encounter</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2007/02/26/report-from-the-zapatista-international-encounter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2007 23:07:56 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2007/02/26/report-from-the-zapatista-international-encounter/</guid>
      <description>##23:07 Monday 26 February 2007
hello all&amp;hellip;
It has been quite some time since I sent out a report from my time here in Chiapas. I have been working with Frayba, a human rights organization that sends internationals into Zapatista and other indigenous communities to do peace observing work, documenting any threats or actions against the communities by paramilitaries as well as any movement by the Mexican military. It has been an incredible experience and I am hoping to spend two more weeks in a community before I begin the long road home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where Were You That Summer of 2001?</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2007/02/26/where-were-you-that-summer-of-2001/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2007 23:04:10 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2007/02/26/where-were-you-that-summer-of-2001/</guid>
      <description>##23:04 Monday 26 February 2007
This is the kind of info that was floating around before the war in Iraq that everyone ignored and/or discounted, yet now wished they had not. This article is damn well-documented too. if you doubt what he is saying, just click on the links to go directly to the whitehouse website with the quotes he is referencing. Every American in the country should be required to read this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reality strikes my day off...</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2007/01/05/reality-strikes-my-day-off.../</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2007 08:36:05 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2007/01/05/reality-strikes-my-day-off.../</guid>
      <description>##08:36 Friday 05 January 2007
I think I&amp;rsquo;m losing it&amp;hellip;seriously&amp;hellip;i think I&amp;rsquo;m forgetting the meaning of words like &amp;ldquo;peace&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;ceasefire&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;routine&amp;rdquo;. Today I had a day off and went to meet a friend of mine from Bethlehem who has recently started a new job with UNESCO in Ramallah. We met for a long lunch and then went shopping in Ramallah&amp;rsquo;s busy town centre. Then the army arrived. Bulldozers first, shunting parked cars out of the way, some into shop fronts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3G in Japan vs stagnation in the US</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2007/01/03/3g-in-japan-vs-stagnation-in-the-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2007 13:58:57 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2007/01/03/3g-in-japan-vs-stagnation-in-the-us/</guid>
      <description>##13:58 Wednesday 03 January 2007
Regarding WiFi in Japan vs the US, Jesse wrote:
 We already have 4G in Japan&amp;hellip;. and it is already too slow but boasts speeds of 100mbps. 3g is only good for non-mobile systems. It only goes a max of 384kbps for mobile systems, and that is if it has a good connection&amp;hellip;
 Dude explained:
beacause the US is so concerned with &amp;ldquo;preserving the free market&amp;rdquo;, our government refuses to mandate a standard.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>had to flee Oaxaca</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2006/12/15/had-to-flee-oaxaca/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2006 11:08:32 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2006/12/15/had-to-flee-oaxaca/</guid>
      <description>##11:08 Friday 15 December 2006
Hello all&amp;hellip;
So I have been experiencing some sort of writers block. I had intended to send this update last week but ended up needing some time to reflect and decompress. The repression by the Mexican government that I described on the 25th has continued. On October 29th the government leaked that they had compiled a list of 100 internationals from video footage who they alleged were committing vandalism alongside the movement and who they intended to deport.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Life in Walajah</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2006/12/15/life-in-walajah/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2006 10:50:53 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2006/12/15/life-in-walajah/</guid>
      <description>##10:50 Friday 15 December 2006
Hi everyone, It&amp;rsquo;s been a while since my last mass email and I&amp;rsquo;ve had a couple of those &amp;ldquo;are you still alive&amp;rdquo; emails that I love as they prove to me that you all miss me (ie they&amp;rsquo;re good for my ego!) and make me laugh! I have to say that I&amp;rsquo;ve started writing this email a few times, but every time I&amp;rsquo;ve given up as the words seemed a little empty.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The twins in Canada!!</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2006/12/08/the-twins-in-canada/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2006 11:33:46 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2006/12/08/the-twins-in-canada/</guid>
      <description>##11:33 Friday 08 December 2006
Good-oh-my-gosh-it&amp;rsquo;s-cold-here-evening from Canada:
So the twins have safely arrived in Toronto!!!! We had quite a flight to say the least!! Maria managed to get her visa for Canada exactly 6 hours prior to take-off. Check-in became a complete debacle when the ground staff told us that two of our boxes were .5 kilograms over and would need to be repacked. Luckily the pilots for our flight were checking in at the counter beside us&amp;hellip;and offered to carry onto the plane&amp;hellip;the seven packages of Pokari Sweat powder and the one book that was causing the extra weight.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pirates of the Mediterranean</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2006/10/03/pirates-of-the-mediterranean/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2006 01:26:19 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2006/10/03/pirates-of-the-mediterranean/</guid>
      <description>##01:26 Tuesday 03 October 2006
https://www.nytimes.com/2006/09/30/opinion/30harris.html?ei=5087%0A&amp;en;=17f2c99ae7254bfa&amp;ex;=1159761600&amp;pagewanted;=all 
September 30, 2006
Op-Ed Contributor
Pirates of the Mediterranean By ROBERT HARRIS
Kintbury, EnglandIN the autumn of 68 B.C. the world&amp;rsquo;s only military superpower was dealt a profound psychological blow by a daring terrorist attack on its very heart. Rome&amp;rsquo;s port at Ostia was set on fire, the consular war fleet destroyed, and two prominent senators, together with their bodyguards and staff, kidnapped.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rochelle update from oaxaca</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2006/09/18/rochelle-update-from-oaxaca/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2006 10:41:45 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2006/09/18/rochelle-update-from-oaxaca/</guid>
      <description>##10:41 Monday 18 September 2006
Hello family and friends&amp;hellip;
I am sorry it has been awhile since I sent an e-mail. I have been able to get a few pieces published and have been focusing on writing for those. I have thought about sending them out to this list but I fear they would be repetitive. There is so little information out there that each piece I write has a lot of the same background information.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dude on airplane day being an inside job:</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2006/08/27/dude-on-airplane-day-being-an-inside-job/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2006 13:45:56 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2006/08/27/dude-on-airplane-day-being-an-inside-job/</guid>
      <description>##13:45 Sunday 27 August 2006
https://www.cnn.com/2006/EDUCATION/08/06/sept11.theories.ap/index.html
I do not buy that 911 was an inside job by the government. I can buy that the Neocons in the Bush admin potentially knew something was up and did nothing in order to create public sentiment that would rally behind the flag and agree to their extreme foriegn policy agenda, but that&amp;rsquo;s a far cry from orchestrating the event and attacking your own nation with missiles, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oaxaca struggle persists</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2006/08/24/oaxaca-struggle-persists/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2006 11:37:33 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2006/08/24/oaxaca-struggle-persists/</guid>
      <description>##11:37 Thursday 24 August 2006
from Rochelle:
hello all! The teachers and their supporters continue to remain strong in the face of nightly acts of repression. The police and government goons shot up the transmitter for channel 9, shutting down the state tv that the the women from the movement had controlled since the 1st of August. Immediately stations all over the city were taken over. In the last two nights two teachers have been killed by government forces while protecting those stations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rochelle in Oaxaca</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2006/08/13/rochelle-in-oaxaca/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2006 21:43:25 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2006/08/13/rochelle-in-oaxaca/</guid>
      <description>##21:43 Sunday 13 August 2006
Hello all…
So things in Oaxaca are intensifying and fast.
Last week there was a 2000+ womens&amp;rsquo; march of the Popular Assembly of the
State of Oaxaca (APPO). A quick recap, this is the organization that
formed after the June 14th police repression of the striking teachers
union SNTE Section 22. APPO is made up of the teachers as well as a huge
variety of social organizations who support the teachers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s a fucking bus</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2006/08/12/its-a-fucking-bus/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2006 11:14:20 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2006/08/12/its-a-fucking-bus/</guid>
      <description>##11:14 Saturday 12 August 2006
 the civilized hijackings of the seventies are over. if guy says he has a bomb, you&amp;rsquo;re all going to die anyway&amp;ndash;bum rush him. problem solved, just like on united 93. no need for extra security, we can take care of things ourselves.
 That is from a thread between me, Dude and my brother after the announcement that we can&amp;rsquo;t bring drinks onto planes anymore:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fred on 4D coaster</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2006/07/26/fred-on-4d-coaster/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2006 13:03:17 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2006/07/26/fred-on-4d-coaster/</guid>
      <description>##13:03 Wednesday 26 July 2006
Dude:
Rob - Fred called from magic mountain. he said that the 4-D coaster was kick ass. he said that he waited in line for 2.5 hrs and that the ride itself was 3 minutes long, and that it took 4 minutes just to swap seats when the coaster is done (only one coaster per track). he said that the top speed was 70-ish MPH. sounds kick ass, but 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gaza Departure by Serena</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2006/01/06/gaza-departure-by-serena/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2006 20:38:22 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2006/01/06/gaza-departure-by-serena/</guid>
      <description>##20:38 Friday 06 January 2006
By now you may be aware that I am in Jerusalem with the four other delegates from the Olympia-Rafah Sister City Project, and Cindy and Craig Corrie. We chose to leave Gaza Wednesday morning after two men came to our apartment late Tuesday night asking us to go with them under the false pretense that we would be safer staying in their home. Our host in Rafah recognized this as an attempt to kidnap us and cautiously navigated the situation resulting in the bizarre scenario of the men shaking each of our hands and leaving.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rafah Crossing by Serena</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2005/11/28/rafah-crossing-by-serena/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2005 11:34:47 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2005/11/28/rafah-crossing-by-serena/</guid>
      <description>##11:34 Monday 28 November 2005
Below (save for the AP quote) was written by Serena, serene@riseup.net
 RAFAH TERMINAL, Gaza Strip - It was a smooth debut Saturday for the first Palestinian-run border crossing. Hundreds of travelers zipped through passport control without having to submit to Israeli security checks, savoring their new freedom after 38 years of military occupation.
  (Written [27 November 2005 By Ibrahim Barzak, Associated Press](https://www.google.com/custom?domains=robnugen.com&amp;amp;q=%22Palestinian-run+border+crossing.+Hundreds+of+travelers%22&amp;amp;sa=Search&amp;amp;sitesearch=&amp;amp;client=pub-8968158139273573&amp;amp;forid=1&amp;amp;channel=5817411192&amp;amp;ie=ISO-8859-1&amp;amp;oe=ISO-8859-1&amp;amp;cof=GALT%3A%23008000%3BGL%3A1%3BDIV%3A%23336699%3BVLC%3A663399%3BAH%3Acenter%3BBGC%3AFFFFFF%3BLBGC%3A336699%3BALC%3A0000FF%3BLC%3A0000FF%3BT%3A000000%3BGFNT%3A0000FF%3BGIMP%3A0000FF%3BFORID%3A1%3B&amp;amp;hl=en))  Reading the headline news on Rafah Crossing one would conclude that Palestinians are free to come and go as they please with minimal control by Israel over Gaza in general, nothing significantly impeding them from creating a prosperous economy, controlling their borders, air space and sea ports.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>