<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>emotions on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/emotions/</link>
    <description>Recent content in emotions on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2019 11:27:31 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/emotions/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Simple steps for dealing with anger</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/blog/2019/06/27/simple-steps-for-dealing-with-anger/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2019 11:27:31 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/blog/2019/06/27/simple-steps-for-dealing-with-anger/</guid>
      <description>1) breathe. Focus on your breathing until the initial wave of anger has passed. It may help to focus on counting the breaths.
Allow your breathing to deepen and slow.
2) label. Say you yourself, &amp;ldquo;I feel angry.&amp;rdquo; Labeling the emotion brings your thoughtful brain back online.
This helps move beyond the Fight or Flight reaction of the reptilian brain
3) acknowledge. Recognize the steps that brought you into this situation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Save Money Through Meditation</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/blog/2019/06/22/save-money-through-meditation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2019 14:27:22 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/blog/2019/06/22/save-money-through-meditation/</guid>
      <description>My TV says if I buy this or that toothpaste / car / ______ then I will be happy. What TV doesn&amp;rsquo;t tell me is that happiness is temporary. Instead of buying my way into temporary happiness, I can sit my way into lasting happiness.
Sitting allows me to reset my brain to my center, my spirit, my essence. This is where permanent happiness resides. In this moment, sitting in what I call the Ever Present Present, I can just be, happily.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What do emotions tell us</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/blog/2019/06/18/what-do-emotions-tell-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2019 21:22:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/blog/2019/06/18/what-do-emotions-tell-us/</guid>
      <description>Sticking with the basics, we have joy and fear.
Joy is how I feel when I have what I want, or I don&amp;rsquo;t want what I don&amp;rsquo;t have. I am aligned with what is, and have no need or desire to change it.
Fear is the emotion which says I don&amp;rsquo;t have enough information. This is usually about an unknown future. I come to a proverbial fork in the road and could simply choose arbitrarily, but if there is a part of me that wants to choose the &amp;ldquo;right&amp;rdquo; option, I may feel fear about choosing the &amp;ldquo;wrong&amp;rdquo; option.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>(story logging) afraid of getting a drivers license</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/01/06/story-logging-afraid-of-getting-a-drivers-license/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2019 20:25:51 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/01/06/story-logging-afraid-of-getting-a-drivers-license/</guid>
      <description>20:25 Sunday 06 January 2019 JST Write a few sentences about something you did during your ordinary day.  Realized I can get a drivers license
Which one of these simple event of the day had an odd moment? Or evoked an emotion such as aggravation, frustration, surprise, miscommunication. **Name the emotion.**  I realized there was no reason to be a afraid. I wasn&amp;rsquo;t afraid of riding roller coasters (but some people were).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Watched movie Inside Out</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/10/14/watched-movie-inside-out/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2015 18:10:11 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/10/14/watched-movie-inside-out/</guid>
      <description>18:10 Wednesday 14 October 2015 JST Inside Out is the latest Pixar film I&amp;rsquo;ve seen. It hilariously and perfectly describes how emotions seem to work in our minds. Emotions in balance lead to a normal life, while unchecked emotion of any persuasion can lead to a bit of a disaster. I love how it answers so many unasked questions! &amp;ldquo;Ohhh! This explains why that happens!!&amp;rdquo;
Anyway, go see it. I hope to see it with Lin sometime.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>