<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>site on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/site/</link>
    <description>Recent content in site on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2019 23:08:28 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/site/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello Hugo 0.58</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/09/24/hello-hugo-0.58/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2019 23:08:28 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/09/24/hello-hugo-0.58/</guid>
      <description>Hello
I have a rather large Hugo site which I have pared down into one bite sized repository.
I made some tweaks to the top page to only show Page type Blog (in content and in pagination)
There are also page type. journal which I would like to be displayed under /journal
This all worked a few versions of Hugo ago.
I upgraded Hugo to 0.58 recently and it stopped working.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting closer to new site theme, etc</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/06/23/getting-closer-to-new-site-theme-etc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2019 23:30:57 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/06/23/getting-closer-to-new-site-theme-etc/</guid>
      <description>23:30 Sunday 23 June 2019 JST Slept a lot because sick, but I spent some time on getting my site theme figured out.
https://5d0f8601c419c700089949de--zealous-varahamihira-b6564c.netlify.com/
I thought I had removed Professional and Creative from the homepage, but seems they only got removed from the navigation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>new site design</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/06/13/new-site-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2019 13:21:19 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/06/13/new-site-design/</guid>
      <description>13:21 Thursday 13 June 2019 JST New site design coming soon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mt3 site is effed up</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/10/15/mt3-site-is-effed-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2018 15:38:24 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/10/15/mt3-site-is-effed-up/</guid>
      <description>15:38 Monday 15 October 2018 JST Dang marbletrack3.com is broken now. Netlify created the SSL cert and neither of my browsers like it.
I will switch back to hosting on Dreamhost if Netlify cannot sort it out.

I have created a support ticket with Netlify.
And to think I was about ready to shift all my static sites over.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Joel (hopefully) fixed MT3 website top banner</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/09/17/joel-hopefully-fixed-mt3-website-top-banner/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2018 18:08:56 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/09/17/joel-hopefully-fixed-mt3-website-top-banner/</guid>
      <description>18:08 Monday 17 September 2018 JST I chatted with Joel today after doing a livestream on Facebook about work-life-balance. He tweaked the theme for Marble Track 3 to fix the jumbotron at the top! Super awesome. Going to try it out now.
Original:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>fixed my site</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/09/14/fixed-my-site/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 16:12:02 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/09/14/fixed-my-site/</guid>
      <description>16:12 Friday 14 September 2018 JST I broke my upload process, but I think it is fixed now.
Yep. It took 65 seconds to process and upload to my server, but it works.
When trying to get that number down, to a few seconds, I mis-remembered how it was set up and destroyed the public/ directory of my Hugo-controlled site thinking Hugo can rebuild it, but since the Hugo directory is already a Git repo, it was conflating the two, and things got really confuzzed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mt3 dedicated domain</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/05/28/mt3-dedicated-domain/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2018 15:58:32 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/05/28/mt3-dedicated-domain/</guid>
      <description>15:58 Monday 28 May 2018 JST HI Jackie! I would like to make a site for my ongoing project, Marble Track 3. I need some help kinda imagining how is best to present the info+content I have, plus I have a few ideas+constraints of how I think it should go. I think the site can be implemented as a static website with no backend coding required. (Except *possibly* for a section inviting people to get involved with the project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mt3 dedicated domain</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/05/09/mt3-dedicated-domain/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2018 11:57:48 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/05/09/mt3-dedicated-domain/</guid>
      <description>11:57 Wednesday 09 May 2018 JST Hey Nathan I am making a marble track, a.k.a. rolling ball track, similar to this one I made several years ago, visible here https://mt2.robnugen.com/ This time, however, I am not just making the track, I am also making a stop action animation of some characters making the track. Clips of the video so far are here https://mt3s.robnugen.com in a playlist. (No audio nor background yet; that is a whole other project (I asked you about Blender before)) The project is about 5% finished, and has taken a year to get this far.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>cleaning up site</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/09/14/cleaning-up-site/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2016 10:39:20 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/09/14/cleaning-up-site/</guid>
      <description>10:39 Wednesday 14 September 2016 JST I&amp;rsquo;m cleaning up my old user space on dreamhost, culling a lot of stuff, moving some stuff to github, and about to add a few journal entries to my repo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>site is fixed (except where it&#39;s not)</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/07/29/site-is-fixed-except-where-its-not/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2016 09:50:37 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/07/29/site-is-fixed-except-where-its-not/</guid>
      <description>09:50 Friday 29 July 2016 JST It seems like there was something wrong with my rsync command, but I didn&amp;rsquo;t change anything.
I blew away my directory online and rsynced again and it seems to work now.
Huh. I have a ton of files from my journal with messed up dates /1/01/01
https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1/01/01/done-today/ &amp;lt;&amp;ndash; should be https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/02/23/done-today/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Good responsiveness from Soom.la</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/02/02/good-responsiveness-from-soom.la/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2016 07:38:05 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/02/02/good-responsiveness-from-soom.la/</guid>
      <description>07:38 Tuesday 02 February 2016 CST After receiving an email from Emily to see if I was interested in moving ahead with my Soomla account, I wrote to her:
HI Emily! I just looked at your top page (soom.la) and see a weird image near the bottom with significant typo and something that makes no sense to me  both &#39;Welcome Abroad&#39; and &#39;generous today&amp;quot;generous today&#39; seen[sic] strange enough that it reduces the perceived quality of your site and therefore product.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I&#39;m a packrat</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/06/09/im-a-packrat/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2015 11:16:19 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/06/09/im-a-packrat/</guid>
      <description>11:16 Tuesday 09 June 2015 JST I&amp;rsquo;m a packrat; I&amp;rsquo;ve got a bunch of junk strewn across robnugen.com, and I&amp;rsquo;m lazy. I will probably never finish moving everything to www.robnugen.com (via new.robnugen.com), so 80% likely the subdomains of robnugen.com will linger much longer.
I mention this because I just scanned a couple entries at vihart.com. The site is clean and lovely, and though I don&amp;rsquo;t know if it&amp;rsquo;s been pruned, it&amp;rsquo;s at least had some design thought put into it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hugo</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/03/29/hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2015 00:11:18 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/03/29/hugo/</guid>
      <description>00:11 Sunday 29 March 2015 JST So I&amp;rsquo;m looking at Hugo as possibly replacing Middleman.
To do so, I have to change the date format in frontmatter from something like 2015-03-28 10:55 JST to something like 2015-03-29T00:11:18+09:00.
Hopefully the new format will work with Middleman so I can use it in current entries until I can convert the dates in all the previous entries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>plans for images</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/03/24/plans-for-images/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2015 13:13:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/03/24/plans-for-images/</guid>
      <description>##13:13 Tuesday 24 March 2015 JST##
Okay, so my basic plan is to move all my images to b.robnugen.com and hopefully be able to keep the existing links to /?images/path/to/image.png working in my journal pages.
There are several old images on Flickr (which are still there! (oh so happy thank you Flickr!!))&amp;hellip; I plan to move them to b.robnugen.com as well.
I&amp;rsquo;m not sure if I can easily handle redirecting old links to images, but I guess if I can tell robnugen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>adaptive images</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/03/22/adaptive-images/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Mar 2015 23:52:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/03/22/adaptive-images/</guid>
      <description>##23:52 Sunday 22 March 2015 JST##
I just came across a beautiful solution to resizing images on my site. It allows me to keep my existing images&amp;rsquo; filenames, and it just works as a drop-in solution. A single PHP file (plus a few lines of .htaccess to point images through it). The resulting image URLs are unchanged, but the size of the image is adapted per the device size.
Adaptive-Images</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Set up new.robnugen.com on DH</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/03/06/set-up-new.robnugen.com-on-dh/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2015 21:02:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/03/06/set-up-new.robnugen.com-on-dh/</guid>
      <description>##21:02 Friday 06 March 2015 JST##
Set up new domain on DH
How I set up new sites on Dreamhost (shared hosting, not their new Dreamcompute) From their panel -&amp;gt; Domains -&amp;gt; Manage Domains -&amp;gt; Add Hosting to a Domain / Sub-domain
fill in the blanks, including create a new user
Make sure the new user is a shell user at https://panel.dreamhost.com/index.cgi?tree=users.users
Create a new ssh key for the new site</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Journal entry repo</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/02/14/journal-entry-repo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2015 18:22:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/02/14/journal-entry-repo/</guid>
      <description>##18:22 Saturday 14 February 2015 JST##
For years, I have been writing my journal entries in directories based on the date. Originally in YYYY/MM directories, and now (temporarily?) in YYYY/MM/DD directories.
So while recently trying to consolidate all my journal entries, I&amp;rsquo;ve wanted to maintain that directory structure, lest I have several thousand(?) files in one directory.
Travis got me started on Hakyll, but I&amp;rsquo;m too lazy and he&amp;rsquo;s too busy to update the Haskell source with cool bells and whistles.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>