<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>akiko on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/akiko/</link>
    <description>Recent content in akiko on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2019 21:16:44 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/akiko/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Fun last lesson before vacation</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/10/02/fun-last-lesson-before-vacation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2019 21:16:44 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/10/02/fun-last-lesson-before-vacation/</guid>
      <description>Hide and Akiko from 7pm class each needed to make up some lessons, so stayed for the 8pm class featuring Misato and Tatsuya.
I think it worked pretty well; they had not met each other, and they are all pretty much similar personalities so I figured they would get along fine.
After self intros, most of the time they talked about Akiko&amp;rsquo;s challenging business trip to Hydrabad, India. Most of the rest of the time we talked about Hide&amp;rsquo;s work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>lesson with Akiko in CoCos</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/09/12/lesson-with-akiko-in-cocos/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2019 23:11:10 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/09/12/lesson-with-akiko-in-cocos/</guid>
      <description>(written 23:11 Thursday 12 September 2019 JST)
Akiko and I went to CoCo&amp;rsquo;s for our language exchange today and she helped me figure out how the EOS tea business works.
We each ordered drink bar for around 400 yen. As thanks for her business support today, I paid for hers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>language exchange with Akiko</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/07/11/language-exchange-with-akiko/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2019 23:05:56 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/07/11/language-exchange-with-akiko/</guid>
      <description>23:05 Thursday 11 July 2019 JST Akiko and I went to her train line&amp;rsquo;s side of Akihabara, and ate at the Indian restaurant on the 9th floor of the BIC Camera building. Bottomless cheese nan seems like a good deal until I eat the second one!
We talked about her upcoming trip overseas and pets and other stuff I am too tired to remember, much less write. Oh, we also talked about commas and when to use them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>language exchange with Akiko</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/06/21/language-exchange-with-akiko/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2019 00:06:56 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/06/21/language-exchange-with-akiko/</guid>
      <description>00:06 Friday 21 June 2019 JST Today was the second time for Akiko and I to do a language exchange. She had some good ideas for Marble Track 3 and how to market it. I may end up creating another Instagram account; that is apparently the way to go these days.
So happy to get another subscriber on Youtube, and enthralling to see her enthralled with the process of animating the construction!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>studied Japanese with Akiko in Akihabara</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/05/24/studied-japanese-with-akiko-in-akihabara/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 23:10:41 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/05/24/studied-japanese-with-akiko-in-akihabara/</guid>
      <description>23:10 Friday 24 May 2019 JST There are probably errors in the Japanese notes below! Scanned with our new laser printer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Akiko!</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/06/28/akiko/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2017 22:47:30 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/06/28/akiko/</guid>
      <description>22:47 Wednesday 28 June 2017 JST Wow so great to be back in touch with Akiko!
I met her in EV back back in the day, and lost touch after I quit working there and got busy etc etc, but today in the middle of getting to Inbox Zero (I am cleaned out back to 2012 I think), I wrote to her and she wrote back!
AND she says she is interested in teaching me Japanese, which I believe I am more interested now than I was then.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>