<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>mai on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/mai/</link>
    <description>Recent content in mai on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2019 15:16:38 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/mai/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Great timing to see Mai and Richard</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/07/08/great-timing-to-see-mai-and-richard/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2019 15:16:38 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/07/08/great-timing-to-see-mai-and-richard/</guid>
      <description>15:16 Monday 08 July 2019 JST On the way home from Akabanebashi today, I happened to cross paths with Mai, who saw me as she was walking perpendicular to my path of travel, focused on a youtube video about teleportation paradox in Portal.
  Wow! Hi! Headed over to the cafe to chat with Richard and trade travel stories. Great and grateful to see them!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>today</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/22/today/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Apr 2018 00:06:34 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/22/today/</guid>
      <description>00:06 Sunday 22 April 2018 JST oops it is tomorrow already, but today Lin and I had neighbors Richard and Mai over for lunch, and then went for a walk with them and Fitz. We found a geocache.
https://coord.info/GLVJHGHK

I got a sharp flake of plastic splintered into my foot on the way home. Thankfully Lin was able to get it out relatively easily.
Today was the last day for Build Your Speaker Bio course; I will miss everyone and am really thankful for how much Soness helped with my speaker sheet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>toy store</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/06/02/toy-store/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jun 2015 18:41:17 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/06/02/toy-store/</guid>
      <description>18:41 Tuesday 02 June 2015 JST Mai showed me a styrofoam flying wing they had for only 1200 yen! I laughed when she told me the price. She goes, 高い？ Yup. 5 yen each for 3 components plus 1 yen for the rubberband. So 16 yen cost; 10 yen shipping each when in bulk so I&amp;rsquo;d pay 100 or 200 yen, but.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>