<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>synchronicity on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/synchronicity/</link>
    <description>Recent content in synchronicity on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2019 18:19:11 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/synchronicity/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Awesome connection &#43; synchronicity</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/10/03/awesome-connection-synchronicity/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2019 18:19:11 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/10/03/awesome-connection-synchronicity/</guid>
      <description>Wandering a bit aimlessly, I discovered there&amp;rsquo;s a lounge where certain customers can chill and maybe get food and drinks.. I am apparently not one of those customers, so I don&amp;rsquo;t know!
Rejected, but not too dejected, I noticed an information booth so went to talk to them. I found out exactly what kind of customer is allowed (over 50,000 miles), but she wasn&amp;rsquo;t able to look up the mileage I have since I am flying on a different airline.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>met fe18 on the way home today</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/09/27/met-fe18-on-the-way-home-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2019 23:52:11 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/09/27/met-fe18-on-the-way-home-today/</guid>
      <description>fe18 showed some curiosity in my bare feet on the way home today, so we struck up a conversation. Wow I never knew fe stood for Frontend Engineer! Maybe I can get some help on my Marble Track website??</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>met Mark on the way to workshop today</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/09/27/met-mark-on-the-way-to-workshop-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2019 16:56:28 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/09/27/met-mark-on-the-way-to-workshop-today/</guid>
      <description>Mark synchronistically got on the same train car as me and we had a great quick check-in. I was able to dump everything about work and computer things going unexpectedly, and he told me about a cool set of questions he found that may work well in our men&amp;rsquo;s circle.
We did not have long to hang out so just quick stories and then long wave bye as we had to go on separate trains in 代々木上原 station.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>great timing to get my keys</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/06/09/great-timing-to-get-my-keys/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2019 21:26:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/06/09/great-timing-to-get-my-keys/</guid>
      <description>21:26 Sunday 09 June 2019 JST Headed to the station I realized I had left my wallet etc at the workshop location.
Great timing to find them before they got across the street and out of site. Rin let me back in and discovered some of the lights were still on so she got a chance to turn them off. Perfect synchronicity again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>booked to speak in negative one day</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/05/09/booked-to-speak-in-negative-one-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2018 14:38:30 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/05/09/booked-to-speak-in-negative-one-day/</guid>
      <description>14:38 Wednesday 09 May 2018 JST I am not sure how all this works, but I plan to join Soness&amp;rsquo;s Get Booked to Speak in a Week class starting tomorrow. So that means between tomorrow and the week after, I should get booked to speak. Does it count if I get booked today, before the class starts?
It&amp;rsquo;s not really a speaking engagement, but come on out to Bar GariGari on June 1st for story telling night</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>synchronicity</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/09/06/synchronicity/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2017 05:25:10 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/09/06/synchronicity/</guid>
      <description>05:25 Wednesday 06 September 2017 JST Last night one of my friends contacted me. It turned out we were in the same area, so I was able to give her a hug.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Back to my old surgeon</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/06/04/back-to-my-old-surgeon/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jun 2015 11:15:31 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/06/04/back-to-my-old-surgeon/</guid>
      <description>11:15 Thursday 04 June 2015 JST My right elbow has been hurting from too much mousing, I think. I got a recommendation from Tariq, via one of his students.
His name is 吉川泰弘 The nearest station is 駒沢大学駅 His clinic&#39;s name is 駒沢病院 His position there is 整形外科部長  I looked up the hospital and it turns out it&amp;rsquo;s the same one where I had my shoulder surgery done 9 years ago.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stuff</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1987/04/07/stuff/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Apr 1987 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1987/04/07/stuff/</guid>
      <description>(transcribed 6:14pm CST Saturday 25 January 2003)
Tuesday April 7 11:25PM (1987)
I been working out. I&#39;ve been using those hand squeezy things and doin&#39; push-ups. I&#39;m gonna get strong. English - I have a rough draft due Thurs. I need to hurry on it. Ma got a book about Challenger. It will help. I fixed up my Chemistry folder. I need to prove something in Algebra. Somethin&#39; about Hyperbolas, probably.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>