<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>niigata on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/niigata/</link>
    <description>Recent content in niigata on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Jul 2018 16:56:21 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/niigata/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>great beach day</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/07/28/great-beach-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jul 2018 16:56:21 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/07/28/great-beach-day/</guid>
      <description>16:56 Saturday 28 July 2018 JST We got to the beach around 10am and it was warm; by the time we left around 2pm it was hotter than I could stand to walk barefoot on the sand.
We ate at a vegetarian buffet https://yoganiigata.jp/ Good for 1600 yen per person.
23:24 Saturday 28 July 2018 JST We went to see Jurassic World: Fallen Kingdom last night which was pretty good for a fifth installment of a series.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>headed to niigata</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/07/27/headed-to-niigata/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jul 2018 18:14:04 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/07/27/headed-to-niigata/</guid>
      <description>18:14 Friday 27 July 2018 JST Driving to Niigata is taking ages because of the speed limit and stuff, but we are having fun with Mikako in the car with us as Lin drives. I have never gotten a driver&amp;rsquo;s license in Japan, but it is long trips like this that kinda make me want to have one. Highway driving is no problem for me. It&amp;rsquo;s just the squirmy little streets near our house that I don&amp;rsquo;t want to navigate in a car (especially not a relatively big ass mini van like we have).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>swan lake</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/12/24/swan-lake/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2016 15:41:02 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/12/24/swan-lake/</guid>
      <description>15:41 Saturday 24 December 2016 JST We are at Swan Lake in Niigata, where swans apparently gather for the evenings in winter. There are none here now.
17:00 Saturday 24 December 2016 JST Several came back starting around 4:30pm, right when the sky was getting dark.
But even cooler than seeing swans flying was seeing the window through which we could see them! 1.7m tall by 12 meters wide. One pane of glass.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>cacauphany</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/12/24/cacauphany/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2016 06:24:06 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/12/24/cacauphany/</guid>
      <description>06:24 Saturday 24 December 2016 JST There&amp;rsquo;s a huge number of birds outside; I mostly hear crows, but there may be others. They sound a bit far away, but quite plentiful in numbers.. The sound seems to come in waves. Ohh Mikako was saying there are tons of geese or maybe she said swans, for which Niigata is famous. This sound must be coming from them.
10:10 Saturday 24 December 2016 JST Nope; Mikako they were crows!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>