<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>lin on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/lin/</link>
    <description>Recent content in lin on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2019 23:04:28 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/lin/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Lin is late tonight</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/09/24/lin-is-late-tonight/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2019 23:04:28 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/09/24/lin-is-late-tonight/</guid>
      <description>(written 23:04 Tuesday 24 September 2019 JST)
Usually Lin checks in with me on her way home, but she has not checked in with me yet. I wrote this to Mark on LINE:
23:00 barefoot Rob Nugen Just checking in now; Lin is not home and not answering her phone or LINE 23:01 barefoot Rob Nugen It&#39;s possible she is out with friends, but usually she tells me if she will be late 23:01 barefoot Rob Nugen I won&#39;t seriously worry until after last train 23:02 barefoot Rob Nugen I do not need any support now, but I will let you know if I do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>walked around with Lin</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/07/14/walked-around-with-lin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2019 14:37:38 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/07/14/walked-around-with-lin/</guid>
      <description>14:37 Sunday 14 July 2019 JST Lin and I walked around our neighborhood, which couulllddd possibly count as a Walk that I started doing last year and dropped after getting to 14 or so.
During this walk, I practiced a process I heard on an Esther Hicks video recently. &amp;ldquo;You&amp;rsquo;re my favorite rock. You&amp;rsquo;re my favorite leaf. You&amp;rsquo;re my favorite tree.&amp;rdquo; etc
I found the transcription at the bottom of this PDF from a church newsletter(?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>replanted tree today</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/06/15/replanted-tree-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2019 18:18:03 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/06/15/replanted-tree-today/</guid>
      <description>18:18 Saturday 15 June 2019 JST Lin and I replanted the sakura tree which we planted (too close to the wall) last week. There was a slight gap in the rain so we took the chance to move the tree.
I was thankful I had done a careful job of packing mud and nutritious leaves for the tree last week. I was able to dig those up and reuse them today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lin and I removed a tiny stump from our garden.</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/06/08/lin-and-i-removed-a-tiny-stump-from-our-garden./</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2019 11:54:37 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/06/08/lin-and-i-removed-a-tiny-stump-from-our-garden./</guid>
      <description>11:54 Saturday 08 June 2019 JST  
Lin and I removed a tiny stump from our garden. The bush had an infestation of caterpillars with allergenic hairs and
15:43 Saturday 08 June 2019 JST now we have a sakura tree where the bush used to be.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Headed to see my Babychan</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/05/09/headed-to-see-my-babychan/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2019 20:20:30 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/05/09/headed-to-see-my-babychan/</guid>
      <description>20:20 Thursday 09 May 2019 JST Lin said she had an &amp;ldquo;unbelievably hard day at work today&amp;rdquo; so I look forward to listening and hopefully helping her sort out her feelings on the whole thing. New job, new system, steep learning curve; I can relate!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lin&#39;s bag today</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/05/06/lins-bag-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2019 08:54:15 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/05/06/lins-bag-today/</guid>
      <description>08:54 Monday 06 May 2019 JST It turns out I like the bag Lin bought online better than the bag I bought in a shop last year. The wheels on her bag are larger and quieter. That was something I could not test on the linoleum tile floors in the shop. That sounded perfectly smooth there, but out on the street they are raucous.
And this bag has more pockets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Great day today</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/04/21/great-day-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2019 20:00:22 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/04/21/great-day-today/</guid>
      <description>20:00 Sunday 21 April 2019 JST Lin and I enjoyed a great productive day today, starting with a romp after calling my mom on voip.
Main things for me: work on AB, fix bicycles. Lin wanted to clean the house a bit so she did that while I worked on AB.
We walked our decrepit bicycles to a local shop. Mine had to get a new chain; Lin&amp;rsquo;s bicycle needed a new valve stem and new seat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yomiuriland with Lin and Mikarin</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/04/13/yomiuriland-with-lin-and-mikarin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2019 09:13:16 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/04/13/yomiuriland-with-lin-and-mikarin/</guid>
      <description> 09:13 Saturday 13 April 2019 JST Excited to go to Yomiuriland with Lin and Mikarin today!
21:22 Saturday 13 April 2019 JST Just got back home, though we left Yomiuriland around 5pm. Pretty early from my point of view, but they were both tired.
Good times.
       
Francois on Bandit:
  Squealing on waterslide:
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Headed to Narita with Lin</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/03/13/headed-to-narita-with-lin/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2019 16:50:52 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/03/13/headed-to-narita-with-lin/</guid>
      <description>16:50 Wednesday 13 March 2019 JST In preparation for this trip, I started my packing list a few weeks ago.
I had planned to copy it here, but for now, just imagine it.
I pre-packed most of the list a couple days ago, getting down to computer, phone, and other stuff I could not pack because I use it daily.
This morning I woke up early, and repacked everything, doublechecking the list, and taking pictures of all of it, in some kind of just in case scenario that will not happen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lin joined me on my fifth walk</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/08/18/lin-joined-me-on-my-fifth-walk/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Aug 2018 09:19:54 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/08/18/lin-joined-me-on-my-fifth-walk/</guid>
      <description>09:19 Saturday 18 August 2018 JST Lin and I got off to a later start than I had originally planned, but we walked an hour around our neighborhood, finding some new streets we had never used before and arriving via different routes in places we had been before. &amp;ldquo;Oh! we&amp;rsquo;re here!&amp;rdquo; kinda thing.
Wow! 3.9km in 58 minutes, according to Google maps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>headed to niigata</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/07/27/headed-to-niigata/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jul 2018 18:14:04 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/07/27/headed-to-niigata/</guid>
      <description>18:14 Friday 27 July 2018 JST Driving to Niigata is taking ages because of the speed limit and stuff, but we are having fun with Mikako in the car with us as Lin drives. I have never gotten a driver&amp;rsquo;s license in Japan, but it is long trips like this that kinda make me want to have one. Highway driving is no problem for me. It&amp;rsquo;s just the squirmy little streets near our house that I don&amp;rsquo;t want to navigate in a car (especially not a relatively big ass mini van like we have).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>kristen</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/05/27/kristen/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 May 2018 20:30:45 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/05/27/kristen/</guid>
      <description>20:30 Sunday 27 May 2018 JST 私と凛子一緒にクリステンとマーコポーロの動画送ってもらって３−4回猫の話をやりとりした。
Lin and I Marco Poloed with Kristen back and forth a few times tonight, mostly talking about our cats!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>watching Rick and Morty with Lin</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/05/24/watching-rick-and-morty-with-lin/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 May 2018 00:29:01 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/05/24/watching-rick-and-morty-with-lin/</guid>
      <description>00:29 Thursday 24 May 2018 JST We are nearly finished with Season 1. Tonight we watched Season 1 Episode 10 (on Netflix). I paused it a few times to make sure she was catching all the important bits and better jokes, and she understood some of them, so yay. ((( At this point, the first three seasons have been released, and I have seen all the episodes a few times each.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>super great camping weekend</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/25/super-great-camping-weekend/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Mar 2018 20:01:23 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/25/super-great-camping-weekend/</guid>
      <description>20:01 Sunday 25 March 2018 JST Super great night last night watching the moon and stars after dancing Rob&amp;rsquo;s Crazy Dance including with a tennis ball. Created a new piece of art for which Abbie suggested the name Endless Dimensions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>dream scheduling conflict</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/23/dream-scheduling-conflict/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2017 04:49:53 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/23/dream-scheduling-conflict/</guid>
      <description>04:49 Saturday 23 December 2017 -03 I had a schedule conflict that I detected a few days out, but didn&#39;t try to rectify until the day of the conflict. Nate wanted to have me join a late night adventure sneaking into a dark house that only I knew the layout to find some prize close to midnight. I was more interested in joining Lin to meet Travis and Yumi for a roadtrip that started at 11pm, but planned to meet in nearly the same location, an empty field next to the building that Nate and I were going to explore in the dark.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>headed to GRU airport</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/19/headed-to-gru-airport/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2017 10:43:05 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/19/headed-to-gru-airport/</guid>
      <description>10:43 Tuesday 19 December 2017 -02 En route to GRU via taxi from Rodrigo&amp;rsquo;s aparment. I trust we are on time; our flight is at 12:45pm and the airport is apparently 14 kilometers from here. Traffic has started moving briskly; we are traveling at 80 km/h, so we should ostensibly arrive in less than 14 minutes, so I guess we are good. It&amp;rsquo;s a domestic flight so maybe less stringent through security.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>late</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/11/28/late/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2017 22:35:59 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/11/28/late/</guid>
      <description>22:35 Tuesday 28 November 2017 JST Lin&amp;rsquo;s out late tonight with work colleagues. Perfect timing because I stayed out late with peeps from co-gender group. I will still get home before her.
I took the local train tonight so I&amp;rsquo;m actually sitting on the train now as I write this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lins car hit by motorbike guys shoulder</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/10/11/lins-car-hit-by-motorbike-guys-shoulder/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2017 22:47:55 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/10/11/lins-car-hit-by-motorbike-guys-shoulder/</guid>
      <description>22:47 Wednesday 11 October 2017 JST I am at a hospital with Lin after a little fender bender involving a guy&amp;rsquo;s shoulder hitting her mirror hard enough to cut her hand as the glass shattered into her open window.
The police officer came and suggested it will be easiest/cheapest overall if they don&amp;rsquo;t sue each other and just do 50&amp;frasl;50 blame and call it in to their respective insurance companies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>made pottery</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/08/19/made-pottery/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2017 11:04:24 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/08/19/made-pottery/</guid>
      <description>11:04 Saturday 19 August 2017 JST We just made some pottery with an chill old man sensei. I made a mobius strip for Fred, an upside-down plate for me, a dice shaker and two dice for my students.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>pics from Mas third trip to Japan</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/08/18/pics-from-mas-third-trip-to-japan/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2017 00:09:59 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/08/18/pics-from-mas-third-trip-to-japan/</guid>
      <description>2017-08-18 (written 00:09 Friday 06 October 2017 JST)
        
With GG</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SOGO</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/08/13/sogo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2017 13:12:38 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/08/13/sogo/</guid>
      <description>13:12 Sunday 13 August 2017 JST Lin and Ma joined me on the way to SOGO. They watched from a bench across from the tree where SOGO peeps generally meet. Workout was great fun, though a bit hard since I haven&amp;rsquo;t attended in a while. Unfortunately I won&amp;rsquo;t be able to attend for two months starting in October. I&amp;rsquo;m bummed about that, but work is work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>headed to beach with Lisa and Miho</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/07/16/headed-to-beach-with-lisa-and-miho/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2017 10:13:23 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/07/16/headed-to-beach-with-lisa-and-miho/</guid>
      <description>10:13 Sunday 16 July 2017 JST Egad I am missing SOGO again (4 times in a row)
But it&amp;rsquo;s nice to see Lisa and Miho!
Actually only Lisa is with us while Lin is driving, and they are all blah blah blabbin chat chat chattin and missed a turn recommended by GPS. Twice.
11:33 Sunday 16 July 2017 JST Okay we just got Miho yay!
13:07 Sunday 16 July 2017 JST Only 1 hour (4.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hung out with Lisa in July</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/07/16/hung-out-with-lisa-in-july/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2017 00:11:31 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/07/16/hung-out-with-lisa-in-july/</guid>
      <description>2017-07-16T00:11:31+09:00 (written 00:11 Friday 06 October 2017 JST)
This is from when Lisa came over to our house (and stayed the night).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>it became zero</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/07/15/it-became-zero/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2017 18:31:26 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/07/15/it-became-zero/</guid>
      <description>18:31 Saturday 15 July 2017 JST Lin was all set to buy Shungite from Renee, but we ended up with not enough time to do so after going to Haruka lake and shrine. The lake was fine and the shrine was nice, but because we were late leaving because of this extra trip, neither Lin nor I really took the time to enjoy it. I did get a couple of pics, but nothing like wow holy shit this was worth being late.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Great day at the beach</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/07/09/great-day-at-the-beach/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2017 20:58:45 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/07/09/great-day-at-the-beach/</guid>
      <description>20:58 Sunday 09 July 2017 JST I joined Lin who met her co-workers in Kamakura for a going away party for one of the managers. Aki had a Canon film camera with a short little lens, so I offered to give her the slightly longer lens that came with my Canon EOS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>babychan</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/03/06/babychan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2017 22:45:56 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/03/06/babychan/</guid>
      <description>22:45 Monday 06 March 2017 JST Bought an ice cream cake for Lin today. Lovely conversation compared to yesterday. Tomorrow in I-group I will look inside for source of why I get pissed off at people talking over other people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mornin</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/10/12/mornin/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2016 05:56:35 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/10/12/mornin/</guid>
      <description>05:56 Wednesday 12 October 2016 JST Awake now; headed down to breaky.
06:44 Wednesday 12 October 2016 JST Breakfast was lots of veggies for me and a larger variety for Lin. The restaurant had a Pepper robot in front, but it wouldn&amp;rsquo;t follow me when I beckoned it. It faced me, but didn&amp;rsquo;t come with me.
Gotta pack and bounce outta here.
07:53 Wednesday 12 October 2016 JST I&amp;rsquo;m the first person in the departure lounge!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>headed to airport</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/10/11/headed-to-airport/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2016 23:37:54 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/10/11/headed-to-airport/</guid>
      <description>23:37 Tuesday 11 October 2016 JST Lin is driving me to Narita airport because my check-in time is 7:25 tomorrow, and there are no trains that leave early enough to make it on time (if I leave from our house tomorrow).
We&amp;rsquo;re going to stay in a hotel (rar) and after she drops me off at the airport tomorrow, she plans to go back to the hotel to enjoy their onsen, buffet breakfast, etc, before checking out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Valentine&#39;s Day</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/02/15/valentines-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2016 15:39:34 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/02/15/valentines-day/</guid>
      <description>15:39 Monday 15 February 2016 JST Valentine&amp;rsquo;s Day was great; Lin made delicious brownies!!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>wedding ceremony!</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/01/30/wedding-ceremony/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2016 17:17:34 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/01/30/wedding-ceremony/</guid>
      <description>17:17 Saturday 30 January 2016 CST We drove up to Mt Bonnell for marriage ceremony delivered by Ma and witnessed by Jon, kT, and Alicia. Fred couldn&amp;rsquo;t join due to migraine.
Up the steps from the parking lot, I walked barefoot, and asked Lin to take picutres of me for the TV thing.
There were so many people near the top that we couldn&amp;rsquo;t get a very good view, so we headed down the hill a bit and found a stone on which we stood for the ceremony.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ted has started coming back inside</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/12/07/ted-has-started-coming-back-inside/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Dec 2015 01:19:31 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/12/07/ted-has-started-coming-back-inside/</guid>
      <description> 01:19 Monday 07 December 2015 JST </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>date night with Lin!</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/11/27/date-night-with-lin/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Nov 2015 19:31:18 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/11/27/date-night-with-lin/</guid>
      <description>19:31 Friday 27 November 2015 JST Yay! Will meet her at the clock at 7:45!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mikako came over last night</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/06/07/mikako-came-over-last-night/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2015 11:49:57 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/06/07/mikako-came-over-last-night/</guid>
      <description>11:49 Sunday 07 June 2015 JST Lin&amp;rsquo;s friend Mikako came over last night, a night I was originally scheduled to be out at an ET contact event. They made gyoza as I lay on the couch, not feelin&amp;rsquo; all that hot! Not sure why. i&amp;rsquo;m feeling genki 95% this morning, though so I&amp;rsquo;m headed to see Travis, Yumi, Matt, and Calire, and maybe others.
Last night I was also planning to go to Japanese class, but I skipped it to chill with Mika.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lunch at Paola and Jon&#39;s</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/03/07/lunch-at-paola-and-jons/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2015 11:12:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/03/07/lunch-at-paola-and-jons/</guid>
      <description>##11:12 Saturday 07 March 2015 JST##
Lin and I are headed to Paola and Jon&amp;rsquo;s for lunch, and then I&amp;rsquo;m going to meet Nate at 3pm. Skype Nate at 5:30pm.
Unfortunately, I&amp;rsquo;m still grouchy because of infuriating XCode, though I&amp;rsquo;m getting over it by doing something non-Apple related.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream with Lin boat to Japan</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/02/15/dream-with-lin-boat-to-japan/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2015 08:58:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/02/15/dream-with-lin-boat-to-japan/</guid>
      <description>##08:58 Sunday 15 February 2015 JST##
In a school, Lin and I walked up some steps to a counter where we were to pick up our tickets for travel. The guy was like, do you have your stripe card? which I had been given but couldn&#39;t find at that moment. I found it latler in a different pocket of my wallet (change compartnemtn) and moved it to the first plae I had looked for it, while thinking of the LPT I had seen regarding this, though Iit was already a practice I practice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Great day at Fujikyu Highland</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/12/21/great-day-at-fujikyu-highland/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/12/21/great-day-at-fujikyu-highland/</guid>
      <description>##18:25 Sunday 21 December 2014 JST##
Here&amp;rsquo;s the TLDR:
We&amp;rsquo;ve just left on our Shinjuku-bound bus. Basically today was a great day at Fuji-Q Highland, and based on very limited information, I think Fujiyama may be the most popular ride in the park. It seemed to have the longest line at any given time.
We rode big coasters eight times:
Fujiyama * 2 Takabisha * 2 Dodonpa * 1 Eejyanaika * 3  Also rode several rides on time each (capitalized if I know the (romanji) name):</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jennie wrapped and ready to go</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/12/14/jennie-wrapped-and-ready-to-go/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/12/14/jennie-wrapped-and-ready-to-go/</guid>
      <description>##12:45 Sunday 14 December 2014
(written 02:06 Sunday 21 December 2014 JST)
For the party at JB school, we had to wrap some presents. Lin wanted to use this huge bag but I thought it was too big. &amp;ldquo;See? It&amp;rsquo;s big enough for Jennie!!&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>tips when writing a diary</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2013/04/10/tips-when-writing-a-diary/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2013 20:56:37 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2013/04/10/tips-when-writing-a-diary/</guid>
      <description>##20:56 Wednesday 10 April 2013
8:29pm Wednesday 10 April 2013
Lin and I were both feeling kinda sick last week. I&amp;rsquo;ve not meditated in a while, though I might start soon. We&amp;rsquo;re feeling mostly better now, but I&amp;rsquo;ve still got some congestion.
But that&amp;rsquo;s not why I&amp;rsquo;m writing. Lin is talking about starting a diary. I&amp;rsquo;m fully supportive of such things, and hope she gets a lot lot lot and tons of benefit from it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shawshank and A.I. yesterday</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2013/02/17/shawshank-and-a.i.-yesterday/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Feb 2013 09:50:08 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2013/02/17/shawshank-and-a.i.-yesterday/</guid>
      <description>##09:50 Sunday 17 February 2013
When I got home from the iOS meeting, Lin was watching Shawshank Redemption on TV via our video-on-demand service. I joined her once the final rape scene was over; up to that point, I don&amp;rsquo;t really like the movie. When the final credits rolled, I said, &amp;ldquo;oh, I thought that was Tom Hanks,&amp;rdquo; and she was like, &amp;ldquo;no that was Green Mile.&amp;rdquo; I was like, &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;ve never seen Green Mile,&amp;rdquo; and she goes WHAT?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>bad dream Lin upset text message</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2013/01/03/bad-dream-lin-upset-text-message/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2013 07:17:34 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2013/01/03/bad-dream-lin-upset-text-message/</guid>
      <description>##07:17 Thursday 03 January 2013
Lin, Ma, and I went to a university library where we were looking for books or something. I saw Christine and helped her find a book (which was unavailable ever since a KTRU dj had mentioned its greatness on the air). Christine needed the book for a report due in April, but the book cost $91 so she wanted to borrow it from the library.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>thinking about Lin&#39;s trip</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2012/12/25/thinking-about-lins-trip/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Dec 2012 06:27:33 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2012/12/25/thinking-about-lins-trip/</guid>
      <description>##06:27 Tuesday 25 December 2012
Lin and I have been talking a lot about her plan to live/work in Thailand for a year.
Being apart for an extended time will be hard; I know! I see it as an extension of our relationship into a new realm. What&amp;rsquo;s it like to be together and be apart for a decent bit of time?
Lin has &amp;ldquo;always&amp;rdquo; wanted to travel and see other parts of the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>all day Christmas shtuffs with Lin&#39;s family</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2012/12/23/all-day-christmas-shtuffs-with-lins-family/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Dec 2012 00:51:09 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2012/12/23/all-day-christmas-shtuffs-with-lins-family/</guid>
      <description>##00:51 Sunday 23 December 2012
I&amp;rsquo;m still not quite great with the caretaking. For example, when I came up to the table to just sit, they were like, &amp;ldquo;do you want sushi? do you want rice? do you want cake? which do you want?&amp;rdquo; and I was like, &amp;ldquo;no thanks&amp;rdquo; and then boom a plate appeared and food that I didn&amp;rsquo;t want was presented.
Um.
I noticed how spoiled the kids are.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>super proud of Lin!</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2012/12/10/super-proud-of-lin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Dec 2012 22:57:16 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2012/12/10/super-proud-of-lin/</guid>
      <description>##22:57 Monday 10 December 2012
She&amp;rsquo;s making some small and big stretches in her life&amp;hellip; This Christmas she&amp;rsquo;s making some gifts for family (instead of just buying stuff). (that&amp;rsquo;s what I&amp;rsquo;m calling the small stretch.)
The big thing about which I&amp;rsquo;m super impressed: she just applied for a new job &amp;hellip;. in Thailand!! Wow! She&amp;rsquo;s always wanted to travel, and I&amp;rsquo;ve always said, &amp;ldquo;so when are you going to do it?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>date with Lin</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2012/11/27/date-with-lin/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2012 21:53:55 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2012/11/27/date-with-lin/</guid>
      <description>##21:53 Tuesday 27 November 2012
Lin and I went on an impromptu date tonight, first visiting the ramen place adjacent to Kawasaki station, but turning away from its 20 minute line.
We were going to go to the cheap and delicious Chinese place with the cute-nosed waitress, but then I suggested we try Taro&amp;rsquo;s restaurant. Taro stands out on the corner soliciting customers, and has a super genki personality that piqued my curiosity enough to try the place.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Two pix from Christmas at Jill&#39;s 2011</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2011/12/25/two-pix-from-christmas-at-jills-2011/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2011 12:46:02 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2011/12/25/two-pix-from-christmas-at-jills-2011/</guid>
      <description>25 Dec 2011 (written 12:46 Monday 10 July 2017 JST)</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>