<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>barefoot on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/barefoot/</link>
    <description>Recent content in barefoot on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2019 22:40:49 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/barefoot/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Great time hanging out with Max</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/07/05/great-time-hanging-out-with-max/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2019 22:40:49 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/07/05/great-time-hanging-out-with-max/</guid>
      <description>22:40 Friday 05 July 2019 JST Max and I met at The Pink Cow where Lin and I were going to meet, but she ended up heading home instead after work. After filling up on world famous bean burritos at The Pink Cow, we walked to Roppongi Midtown where we spent a considerable amount of time wondering how to measure if the circular glass window over the white not-really-egg-shaped stone is round or not.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>overlooking construction</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/06/27/overlooking-construction/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2019 12:07:03 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/06/27/overlooking-construction/</guid>
      <description>12:07 Thursday 27 June 2019 JST Today on my way back home from lunch, I saw a construction site which was overlookable from a pretty steep hill just beside it.
  
By standing on the guardrail, I could easily have fallen forward over their fence. Nice shot, though!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>crack on ball of my left foot</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/04/14/crack-on-ball-of-my-left-foot/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2019 08:37:04 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/04/14/crack-on-ball-of-my-left-foot/</guid>
      <description>8:37 Sunday 14 April 2019 JST After Yomiuriland yesterday, the skin on the bottom of my left foot split a bit. This morning I superglued it shut and put some tape over it. Seems to be okay.
10:38 Sunday 14 April 2019 JST I put on socks and shoes to take off my shoes as I went into Lantz&amp;rsquo;s office. I left my shoes on during my trip back home as the split is painful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>hugged a woman on the train</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/06/26/hugged-a-woman-on-the-train/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2018 23:26:52 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/06/26/hugged-a-woman-on-the-train/</guid>
      <description>23:26 Tuesday 26 June 2018 JST Tonight in Noborito station, I got off the train to try to figure out which train would be fastest to my station. A woman saw me barefoot and asked where I was going. She kindly looked up my station and confirmed my hunch that the next train was fastest to Shin Yurigaoka.
While riding on the train together, she asked me why I was barefoot, and then what I was doing in Japan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>dream wearing shoes in public</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/05/28/dream-wearing-shoes-in-public/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2018 05:06:16 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/05/28/dream-wearing-shoes-in-public/</guid>
      <description>05:06 Monday 28 May 2018 JST Walking outside, I realized I was wearing hiking boots and was shocked that I was wearing them while walking around on vacation. I asked store owner if I could have a bag to put them in, but he said he could not give me one, but I could not understand the reason why. I walked further and found a place to put my boots in a locker so I did that and saw Yumi there who taking things out of her locker and she said I could put my shoes with her stuff with kinda the implication that her son would be able to wear them when he got older.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My feet on FB</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/05/25/my-feet-on-fb/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2018 20:32:15 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/05/25/my-feet-on-fb/</guid>
      <description>20:32 Friday 25 May 2018 JST Vinod noticed a video of my feet on FB today!
https://www.facebook.com/cschmitz.3009/videos/10156357229678917/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>barefoot in Haneda</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/14/barefoot-in-haneda/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2017 20:43:27 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/14/barefoot-in-haneda/</guid>
      <description>20:43 Thursday 14 December 2017 JST I&amp;rsquo;m barefoot in a cafe in Haneda airport. It&amp;rsquo;s super hot, so I plan not to wear shoes until January when we get back. We shall see how that goes!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>walkin around barefoot</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/06/walkin-around-barefoot/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2017 18:00:36 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/06/walkin-around-barefoot/</guid>
      <description>18:00 Wednesday 06 December 2017 JST 仕事以外どこでも裸足で歩きます。時々誰かが「え、裸足？痛くないの？」その質問聞くと「時々痛いけどしょうがない。」この返事は大丈夫かどか分からない。
Outside work, I walk around barefoot. People sometimes ask if it hurts. I tell them it does sometimes, but it cannot be helped. I wonder if that response is okay.
21:47 Wednesday 06 December 2017 JST 今電車のりながら書いてます。南武線の始発に乗るから次の電車を待つと座れます。
I am writing while sitting on the train. I take Nambu line from its terminal, so if I wait for the next train, I can get a seat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tall man in Ueno station</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/07/27/tall-man-in-ueno-station/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2017 17:58:13 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/07/27/tall-man-in-ueno-station/</guid>
      <description>17:58 Thursday 27 July 2017 JST While I was walking out of Ueno station, a tall man and I did the foreigner nod and then he said he had seen me on TV (for being barefoot). We shook hands and talked for a bit about the importance of doing one&amp;rsquo;s own thing.
He said, &amp;ldquo;I respect you,&amp;rdquo; and I should have said if he sees respectability in me, that means it&amp;rsquo;s in him, too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>stopped by cops</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/06/14/stopped-by-cops/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2016 11:12:03 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/06/14/stopped-by-cops/</guid>
      <description>11:12 Tuesday 14 June 2016 JST I was stopped by the cops in our new neighborhood, ostensibly because I was barefoot, but possibly because I&amp;rsquo;m ostensibly not Japanese.
They asked if I had shoes (no), if I was okay (yes), where I was going (work), what was my job (programmin&amp;rsquo;), where was my job (ebisu), where was my crib (right over there). I offered that I had been barefoot for 7 years in the US and going on year 3 (or is it 4) here, and I was on TV recently, blah blah.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>barefoot pictures</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/02/04/barefoot-pictures/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2016 15:13:06 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/02/04/barefoot-pictures/</guid>
      <description>15:13 Thursday 04 February 2016 JST    
At Karina&amp;rsquo;s wedding
           
Near beach in San Diego
                           
Climbing tree at Dad&amp;rsquo;s house</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>running barefoot to the train</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/12/04/running-barefoot-to-the-train/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Dec 2015 17:18:58 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/12/04/running-barefoot-to-the-train/</guid>
      <description>17:18 Friday 04 December 2015 JST I made it from Chez Soness to Chigasaki in about 13 minutes, running barefoot most of the way! It was a bit spooky in the dark, but I didn&amp;rsquo;t step on many ouchy rocks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GG lesson</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/05/28/gg-lesson/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 May 2015 20:44:31 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/05/28/gg-lesson/</guid>
      <description>20:44 Thursday 28 May 2015 JST Today before GG lesson, T asked A (in English) if she had read M&amp;rsquo;s email. A said she had not.
I used this simple exchange as the basis for fully 45 minutes of lesson:
T: &amp;quot;Did you read M&#39;s email?&amp;quot; A: &amp;quot;No I didn&#39;t.&amp;quot; R: &amp;quot;What did you ask her?&amp;quot; T: &amp;quot;I asked her if she had read M&#39;s email.&amp;quot; R: &amp;quot;and what did she say?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>hiking day</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/04/19/hiking-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Apr 2015 21:37:54 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/04/19/hiking-day/</guid>
      <description>21:37 Sunday 19 April 2015 JST Great fun barefoot hiking today around Mt Mitake! Rohini joined the barefoot lifestyle and we clambored up some rocks, including up the back side!
At the top, oops! I stubbed my toe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jogging with Tariq</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/04/jogging-with-tariq/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/04/jogging-with-tariq/</guid>
      <description>##13:32 Tuesday 04 November 2014 JST##
Went to Tariq&amp;rsquo;s this morning to jog 3.6km around his apartment complex (three laps). He went at my pace, which was a lot slower than his own!
I did relatively well for not having run for ages. About 15 to 20 minutes, though I forgot to time it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>