<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>wende on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/wende/</link>
    <description>Recent content in wende on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2002 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/wende/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>house closing</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/03/19/house-closing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/03/19/house-closing/</guid>
      <description>Date: Tue, 19 Mar 2002 08:15:03 -0800 (PST) From: Rob Nugen thunderrabbit Subject: closing the house To: wende HI Wen Thank you so so so so much for your work and for closing on the house without me there. I shall write you a postcard today. I *might* even call you, but that&#39;s not particularly likely. I love you tons and have had a great time. I&#39;ve learned some about myself, and I see why this travel thing is necessary in my life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>laura!</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/08/31/laura/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/08/31/laura/</guid>
      <description>4:05pm Thursday 31 August 2000
Cute Wende is sleeping on the couch here at work. She now has Thursdays off from work. She brought lunch for us from (guess where?) James Coney Island and then she was lookin&amp;rsquo; pretty sleepy and I encouraged her to sleep. She was thinking 20 minutes, but it&amp;rsquo;s been longer than that now and I don&amp;rsquo;t think she has stirred.
I&amp;rsquo;ve been chatting over AIM with a few youth and all are excited about Tulsa Rally this weekend!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wende</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/05/12/wende/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/05/12/wende/</guid>
      <description>Me and Wende 2:17pm CDT Saturday 13 May 2000
Last night Wende and I had a great heart-to-heart conversation. Short version is that I tend to bottle my anger when she gets bitchy when she&amp;rsquo;s hungry or tired. She&amp;rsquo;ll snap, and I won&amp;rsquo;t respond at all. I&amp;rsquo;m afraid that if I do say something it will be really mean, so I just don&amp;rsquo;t say it.
We agreed last night that I would say it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wende</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/05/06/wende/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/05/06/wende/</guid>
      <description>Wende 10:20am CDT Saturday 6 May 2000
Today is my 11,000th day. Bigger celebration than any birthday. Even 30th. When I got out of the shower, I found a card from Wende on the sink. Inside is a Classic Pooh card.
&amp;ldquo;We&amp;rsquo;ll be friends forever, won&amp;rsquo;t we, Pooh?&amp;rdquo; asked Piglet.
&amp;ldquo;Even longer,&amp;rdquo; Pooh answered.
I cried.
- - -
I&amp;rsquo;m sad that Wende is unavailable for the celebrations today.
- - -</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aggie Ring</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/02/18/aggie-ring/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Feb 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/02/18/aggie-ring/</guid>
      <description>Friday 18 February 2000
A month ago or so, someone broke into Wende&amp;rsquo;s apartment and stole most of her jewelry, including her Aggie Ring. Of all the items, she says, there&amp;rsquo;s only 4 that she really really wants to have back. Her Aggie Ring is one of them.
Yesterday, she got a call from the Aggie Ring Office; her ring has been found!
A (homeless?) woman tried to sell it so she could feed her kids.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>late</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1999/12/07/late/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 1999 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1999/12/07/late/</guid>
      <description>23:47 Tuesday 7 December 1999
Wende and I spent the greater portion of today down south of downtown, mostly at Ares Robotics where we are working on all four different altars. When we arrived, the table for the water altar had no legs and no top. It was just a frame of two-by-fours. A man named Terry worked on it, adding the legs, reinforcing them, then adding the top.
During this time Wende and I spray painted our mountain fountain, first with a rust proof primer, and then with two different colors of fleck paint.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>