<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>jb on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/jb/</link>
    <description>Recent content in jb on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2019 16:58:39 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/jb/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>worked at SCC</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/07/18/worked-at-scc/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2019 16:58:39 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/07/18/worked-at-scc/</guid>
      <description>16:58 Thursday 18 July 2019 JST Today Naoko worked on introducing the history zone, including teacup carrying dolls, perpetual clock, and the early days of electricity in Japan.
What was it like back in the day when a simple thing like a few candle power light bulb could be so impressive?
Yasu talked about the Meissner effect and flux pinning. I would like to do an experiment.. will the Meissner effect keep a thing suspended above the magnetic table or is that only do to flux pinning?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fun 3rd of 4th lesson at BP</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/06/21/fun-3rd-of-4th-lesson-at-bp/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2019 00:03:56 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/06/21/fun-3rd-of-4th-lesson-at-bp/</guid>
      <description>00:03 Friday 21 June 2019 JST JB got me 8 hours of lessons at BP over the 4 Thursdays in June. This was the 3rd lesson, during which we practiced taking taxis, ordering in a restaurant, and something else.
Yoko M wasn&amp;rsquo;t there, but she will be back next week. Yoko N volunteered a couple of times to go first!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Work at SCC</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/04/18/work-at-scc/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2019 20:34:39 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/04/18/work-at-scc/</guid>
      <description>20:34 Thursday 18 April 2019 JST Back at SCC today with four student for 30 minutes each. Hitomi came in for Lily, who could not come.
I bought Cast Arrows, a new Hanayama puzzle because I could not solve it in 20 minutes. (not that I can solve most of them in 20 minutes, but this one looked like I could solve it and then I was like &amp;ldquo;woah that&amp;rsquo;s not going to work?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Closing out 2018</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/12/19/closing-out-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Dec 2018 21:30:39 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/12/19/closing-out-2018/</guid>
      <description>21:30 Wednesday 19 December 2018 JST I am on the way home after my last 2018 lesson at JB. I thought we had lessons next week, but apparently not! I kinda sorta wish we did have to work next week; the monies would be nice, but I guess I can work on AB during that time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>headed to work</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/08/08/headed-to-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Aug 2018 13:00:33 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/08/08/headed-to-work/</guid>
      <description>13:00 Wednesday 08 August 2018 JST Headed to JB now soon; hopefully no big concern from the typhoon. I will bring my rain coat, but I ain&amp;rsquo;t too worried.
21:35 Wednesday 08 August 2018 JST The typhoon has been like a typhoon for ants.
But my train is nearly empty because apparently nobody came to work. Or at least everyone left work early.
I&amp;rsquo;m just finishing work and heading home now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>work</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/06/06/work/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2018 21:33:07 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/06/06/work/</guid>
      <description>21:33 Wednesday 06 June 2018 JST I worked for JB at three different locations around Kawasaki Station today, as I do every Wednesday, at Solid Square, SSC, and JB main office. Solid Square lesson went pretty well; we drew mind maps of our favorite places and then said a few sentences about them. Then I had a break during which I Marco Poloed with Richard from ae911truth a bit and then worked on AB, nearly finishing this ticket since it received a bit higher priority at our last meeting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>work work work</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/02/28/work-work-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2018 18:36:47 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/02/28/work-work-work/</guid>
      <description>18:36 Wednesday 28 February 2018 JST I&amp;rsquo;m on break now at JB, listening to the other class, where the teacher&amp;rsquo;s Japanesey English always kinda bugs me. But the students seem happy and have been in the class for a long time.
This morning thinking about C who apparently took my investment advice before bitcoin blew up. She quit her job and is overseas now. hahahah nice!
Then working on AB, getting three alleged issues sorted.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>work day</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/02/13/work-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2018 16:21:31 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/02/13/work-day/</guid>
      <description>16:21 Tuesday 13 February 2018 JST Worked at IL for ist today, and then with CE for MR, and then talked to Chika at B for JB.
Now going to AB to talk to T and S-san.
Tired, I would rather go home.
Oh, but I got past the tween issue I had with Godot 3
Yay!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>headed to BRIDGE</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/02/06/headed-to-bridge/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2018 13:49:03 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/02/06/headed-to-bridge/</guid>
      <description>13:49 Tuesday 06 February 2018 JST This is the fourth to last lesson at BRIDGE. They started off strong, but then started to get busy quite quickly last summer. Two hours of lessons went down to 1 hour which sucked considering it took 3 hours round trip travel. But I kept at it. During December they cancelled January saying they will be too busy. So I had a nice break during January, during which they said the will end at the end of February.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>headed to work at SCC</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/26/headed-to-work-at-scc/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2018 12:55:17 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/26/headed-to-work-at-scc/</guid>
      <description>12:55 Friday 26 January 2018 JST Three hours of lessons in SCC today; looking forward to it!
On the way there, I hope to figure out why my local version of mypowercircle.org will not compile with Hugo. bah. it was supposed to be easy!!
Ah. I had gotten stuck trying to add Japanese language version of the site, but never got it working. It&amp;rsquo;s better to just have an actual Japanese speaker make the Japanese site, so I cut out the Japanese content from the site and now it&amp;rsquo;s working again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>work</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/17/work/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2018 18:34:31 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/17/work/</guid>
      <description>18:34 Wednesday 17 January 2018 JST First three classes were fine today, though I have been asked to blow through a book super fast to let one class catch up with another class. I don&amp;rsquo;t think that&amp;rsquo;s how it works.
In other news, JB has a new owner, who seems nice enough that I can keep working here. Really curious as to how much they paid!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>work yesterday</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/16/work-yesterday/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2018 08:39:06 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/16/work-yesterday/</guid>
      <description>08:39 Tuesday 16 January 2018 JST I worked for four companies yesterday. First was my lesson in Akabanebashi for Tariq. Then walked to Nishi Azabu for MR Laboratories client (company DNE yet). Then walked across the Nishi Azabu intersection to a lesson for TESS. Then bus and train to Kawasaki for 2 hours of lessons at my favorite, SCC. Came home and had one more lesson for MR Laboratories.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>five hours of work at SCC</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/13/five-hours-of-work-at-scc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2018 02:33:31 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/13/five-hours-of-work-at-scc/</guid>
      <description>02:33 Saturday 13 January 2018 JST Today was the first time I worked five hours at SCC. Due to a schedule snafu, 1.5 hours with Liliko chatting about her trip to Sydney and my trip to OZ, then Rick and Morty and Lucifer. I didn&amp;rsquo;t think of Dirk Gently, but she considered getting Netflix to see the others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Akihabara for GG lesson</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/11/akihabara-for-gg-lesson/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2018 18:02:54 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/11/akihabara-for-gg-lesson/</guid>
      <description>18:02 Thursday 11 January 2018 JST Now I am in Akihabara, across the street from GG lesson which starts at 18:30.
I bought a trackball mouse to replace the one I had before which seems to just mysteriously and annoyingly not work anymore. This time I will keep the receipt because I think the old one konked out before its warranty was up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>two hour lesson with Tomoko</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/11/two-hour-lesson-with-tomoko/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2018 17:59:27 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/11/two-hour-lesson-with-tomoko/</guid>
      <description>17:59 Thursday 11 January 2018 JST Today was the first of five 2-hour lessons this month at SCC. Today I helped Tomoko by making corrections to her written English. She plans to present the features of some of her company&amp;rsquo;s products. Pretty cool stuff like elevators and batteries, and elevators that run on batteries. We studied up in their cafeteria on the 4th floor, and then I went down the escalator to the third floor and went out the exit I had never gone out before (but had seen many times).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>morning lesson</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/10/25/morning-lesson/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2017 09:13:23 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/10/25/morning-lesson/</guid>
      <description>09:13 Wednesday 25 October 2017 JST Good lesson today, full of the word &amp;ldquo;full of&amp;rdquo; and after filling the paper with examples, &amp;ldquo;this page is full&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>three lessons</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/10/11/three-lessons/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2017 17:37:38 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/10/11/three-lessons/</guid>
      <description>17:37 Wednesday 11 October 2017 JST The kids lessons were pretty good today. The two new students (one in each of my first two classes) are still not speaking, and I can&amp;rsquo;t tell if they are acting shy or don&amp;rsquo;t understand.. anytime they speak, they get the right answer, but getting them to speak is a stretch. esp with the other kids being so chatty. I ain&amp;rsquo;t sure how to handle it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JB</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/05/03/jb/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2017 19:38:26 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/05/03/jb/</guid>
      <description>19:38 Wednesday 03 May 2017 JST Looks doable. ギリギリ but doable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Former student now present student</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/03/24/former-student-now-present-student/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2015 11:32:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/03/24/former-student-now-present-student/</guid>
      <description>##11:32 Tuesday 24 March 2015 JST##
Actually I don&amp;rsquo;t know if she&amp;rsquo;ll be here, but one of my former students at Nova contacted me on FB saying that she&amp;rsquo;s in the Tuesday version of my Thursday class with GG. Well, I&amp;rsquo;m teaching the Tuesday lesson today at 12, so I may see her soon! I don&amp;rsquo;t honestly remember her just from FB photo, but we&amp;rsquo;ll see if some memories return after actually chatting with her.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Early Thursday lesson</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/06/early-thursday-lesson/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/06/early-thursday-lesson/</guid>
      <description>##09:41 Thursday 06 November 2014 JST##
Chapter with Chika, Ayano, and Yohei runs from 7:50 to 8:50. Maybe it&amp;rsquo;s a bit early; the first to arrive today (besides me, running a little late and arriving at 8:50:30) arrived at 8:05.
Everyone presented trip reports and we&amp;rsquo;ll get back to the book next week!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kids classes (a.k.a. O_o)</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/05/kids-classes-a.k.a.-o_o/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/05/kids-classes-a.k.a.-o_o/</guid>
      <description>##10:58 Wednesday 05 November 2014 JST##
Wow. Well, I survived the first day teaching a group of kids, they seemed to have fun overall, and there was some semblence of learning involved.
To be more specific, I just &amp;ldquo;taught&amp;rdquo; two classes of around 20 kids each, the first group being a bit younger than the second; I&amp;rsquo;d guess 5 and 6 years old, but I heard they were 4 and 5 years old respectively.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JB lesson this morning</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/10/30/jb-lesson-this-morning/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/10/30/jb-lesson-this-morning/</guid>
      <description>##09:03 Thursday 30 October 2014 JST##
I&amp;rsquo;ve been teaching a lesson each Thursday morning for JB at a company office near Kawasaki station. Today new student Yohei arrived, though Chika, one of my &amp;ldquo;regulars&amp;rdquo; wasn&amp;rsquo;t there, so still just two students, including Ayano.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>