<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>dreams on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/dreams/</link>
    <description>Recent content in dreams on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2019 12:14:13 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/dreams/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>different types of dreams</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/08/07/different-types-of-dreams/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2019 12:14:13 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/08/07/different-types-of-dreams/</guid>
      <description>12:14 Wednesday 07 August 2019 JST Just this morning I realized I have at least two different types of dreams. One type seems to just be my brain sorting stuff out. I dream about work or mundane things like that.
Another type seems to be a place that I go. The scenes are always filled with friends living together in a building with multiple rooms, a campground with multiple cabins, multiple levels with stairs and stuff, and a lot of different activity happening.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to have lucid dreams</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/blog/2019/08/07/how-to-have-lucid-dreams/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2019 07:59:41 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/blog/2019/08/07/how-to-have-lucid-dreams/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever found yourself flying like a bird, only to later realize it was a dream?
Have you been chased by &amp;ldquo;bad guys&amp;rdquo; or haunted by scary situations in your dreams?
&amp;ldquo;Lucid dreaming&amp;rdquo; is a state of dreaming while being aware that you are dreaming. Lucid dreaming allows me to have more fun flying dreams and fewer scary dreams. This is how I got started:
There are a few techniques I have used at different times of my life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>dreams, including being rich</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/03/07/dreams-including-being-rich/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2015 06:01:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/03/07/dreams-including-being-rich/</guid>
      <description>##06:01 Saturday 07 March 2015 JST##
I needed a red mat for the kitchen like a non slip mat and went up a long road loooking forw one and found one up a long hallway curivng to the right in a hotel and found one outisde a house, so I took it and walked back and then got all the way back and asked a guy if he new knew where I could buy it and he goes yeah my brother and called his brother down and I bought a mat from him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Awake early</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/12/15/awake-early/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/12/15/awake-early/</guid>
      <description>##03:47 Monday 15 December 2014 JST##
I woke up around 2:30am and have written a few journal entries, including the dream I had when I woke up, but am going back to bed.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>