<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>class on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/class/</link>
    <description>Recent content in class on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2017 17:47:10 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/class/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>students leveled up real quick</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/06/students-leveled-up-real-quick/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2017 17:47:10 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/06/students-leveled-up-real-quick/</guid>
      <description>17:47 Wednesday 06 December 2017 JST At my third of three kids classes here at JB, we had a new student, 4 or 5 years older than the others. The two previously-oldest girls in the class suddenly stopped messing around and tried significantly harder than usual. Such a nice change of pace! I used a technique I learned from Tariq: keep having them switch conversation partners and repeat the same conversation with a new partner.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>last class for B-group</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/06/17/last-class-for-b-group/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2015 18:52:09 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/06/17/last-class-for-b-group/</guid>
      <description>18:52 Wednesday 17 June 2015 JST Today was the last class for the B-group. Takahiro informed me as he came in. I had heard it would be ending soon but didn&amp;rsquo;t know today was the day. They requested &amp;ldquo;small talk&amp;rdquo; so I invited each person in turn to ask another &amp;ldquo;how was your weekend?&amp;rdquo; and I made corrections as appropriate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AM Thursday class</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/06/04/am-thursday-class/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jun 2015 07:04:09 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/06/04/am-thursday-class/</guid>
      <description>07:04 Thursday 04 June 2015 JST Headed to Kawasaki station
09:00 Class was as great as possible with three students arriving at three different times! (one of whom hasn&amp;rsquo;t attended in so long that I had forgotten his name)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Good time in Japanese class</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/06/03/good-time-in-japanese-class/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2015 22:43:41 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/06/03/good-time-in-japanese-class/</guid>
      <description>22:43 Wednesday 03 June 2015 JST Just attended Japanese class in 80&amp;rsquo;s Cafe. It&amp;rsquo;s the third time リサさん has attended, and the third time I&amp;rsquo;ve sat next to her. I like her piercings and smile. :-)
Today she asked me if it rained much in Houston, and I showed her the pictures of recent flooding there. I actually didn&amp;rsquo;t really know just how bad (and quickly) it flooded. wow. I hope everyone is okay, though I know flood damage suuucckks.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>