<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>sick on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/sick/</link>
    <description>Recent content in sick on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2019 13:18:47 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/sick/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>barefoot in Yurigaoka</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/08/24/barefoot-in-yurigaoka/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2019 13:18:47 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/08/24/barefoot-in-yurigaoka/</guid>
      <description>13:18 Saturday 24 August 2019 JST Today I met a woman who asked if I was from New Zealand. We were in a clinic for meds; Lin and I are sick; the woman had hives. She said she had just started studying English, but I didn&amp;rsquo;t think quickly enough to see if she&amp;rsquo;d like to take lessons with me.
Email me at rob α𝐭 robnugen.com, if you like!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lazy day</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/07/15/lazy-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2019 17:41:43 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/07/15/lazy-day/</guid>
      <description>17:41 Monday 15 July 2019 JST Today after being out late last night at Lin&amp;rsquo;s sister&amp;rsquo;s place, I was happy that today is a holiday. I slept a good bit of the day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hanging out with Michael Monkey</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/03/20/hanging-out-with-michael-monkey/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2019 23:27:39 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/03/20/hanging-out-with-michael-monkey/</guid>
      <description>23:27 Wednesday 20 March 2019 PDT Been sick as a dog for most of it, but I have had a great time hanging out at Michael Monkey&amp;rsquo;s in Houston. Thanks to Great Granny Good Witch for driving me to the store today to buy clothes and toiletries which should last a good while.
She has a lot lot lotta masks from around the world!
I have made a good start on the puzzle in the dining room, first expanding the table, then adding more white backing, then rotating the inner white backing to reduce waste.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>was sick during BC NWTA</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/03/18/was-sick-during-bc-nwta/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2019 01:10:32 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/03/18/was-sick-during-bc-nwta/</guid>
      <description>01:10 Monday 18 March 2019 PDT I felt sad to have to check out for a significant portion of the NWTA this past weekend. So annoying, and certainly not what I had in mind for my trip!
Was great to meet awesome men. I stayed with Steve R in Vancouver the night before the weekend, and am now staying with Dave M in Victoria the night after the weekend. Headed to Houston tomorrow via Calgary.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>coughy so went to clinic</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/07/21/coughy-so-went-to-clinic/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2017 10:24:44 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/07/21/coughy-so-went-to-clinic/</guid>
      <description>10:24 Friday 21 July 2017 JST Lin drove me to a clinic today because I got some kinda cold, and have been coughing for a while. Doc said it isn&amp;rsquo;t contageous, but gave me four (4) different meds to take 3 times a day for 5 days.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>sick sick sick</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/12/31/sick-sick-sick/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2016 17:38:11 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/12/31/sick-sick-sick/</guid>
      <description>17:38 Saturday 31 December 2016 JST Sick yesterday and today but getting better and going to Lin&amp;rsquo;s family&amp;rsquo;s party.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>sick day</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/12/29/sick-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2016 22:40:45 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/12/29/sick-day/</guid>
      <description>22:40 Thursday 29 December 2016 JST I woke up feeling a bit sick and Lin drove me to the clinic for fever, nausea, headache, etc. They stuck the long stick in my sinus to test for influenza. It was negative, but they said it because it&amp;rsquo;s only been a day, it might just not be influenzy enough for the test to detect it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>sick of being sick</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/03/19/sick-of-being-sick/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2016 16:33:53 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/03/19/sick-of-being-sick/</guid>
      <description>16:33 Saturday 19 March 2016 JST blah
this is day 6 of Influenza B, which started on Monday officially. A couple days ago on Thursday the doctor predicted I&amp;rsquo;d be able to work on Tuesday, and even didn&amp;rsquo;t give me any more medication. Yay, but now booo because I can&amp;rsquo;t tell that I&amp;rsquo;m realllllly getting better.
My voice isn&amp;rsquo;t fully back, but it isss better a bit, but I&amp;rsquo;ve had no voice for like 3 or 4 days now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Influenza B - day 4</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/03/17/influenza-b-day-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2016 08:02:32 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/03/17/influenza-b-day-4/</guid>
      <description>08:02 Thursday 17 March 2016 JST yeah wow this is my first entry in a while; I&amp;rsquo;ve had influenza (type B, not that I think I&amp;rsquo;d know the difference) and it&amp;rsquo;s taken my voice somewhere for going on 40 hours now. I&amp;rsquo;m barely beginning to get it back; there seems to be one pitch that works but the rest are just raspy air.
I&amp;rsquo;m going to the clinic today, but I can&amp;rsquo;t speak!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>moe joe i&#39;m sick</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/02/09/moe-joe-im-sick/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2016 21:42:57 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/02/09/moe-joe-im-sick/</guid>
      <description>21:42 Tuesday 09 February 2016 JST Bluh I&amp;rsquo;m sick today, and took the day off from CB and Saru work.
Went to a local clinic and got some meds; was feeling better during the day after sleeping, and then started &amp;ldquo;working&amp;rdquo; on AB site.
Streamed my socked feet online, but no one joined the fun.
Kinda got back into the Ghost Inspector AB groove, but not totally sure why some tests are not passing while others are.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Illin</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/07/01/illin/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2015 15:36:11 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/07/01/illin/</guid>
      <description>15:36 Wednesday 01 July 2015 JST My tonsils hurt a bit yesterday, so I did neti and gargled with warm salt water, drank loads of orange juice and went to bed as soon as I got home. Still felt a bit ooky this morning so I went to a clinic near our house. Thanks to rain, there weren&amp;rsquo;t many people in the waiting room, so I got checked (red tonsils, slight fever), prescribed (antibiotics for 6 days (which I will finish perfectly)), billed (1200 yen), and outta there pretty quickly.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>