<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>book on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/book/</link>
    <description>Recent content in book on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Aug 2018 09:46:31 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/book/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>todo book</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/08/10/todo-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Aug 2018 09:46:31 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/08/10/todo-book/</guid>
      <description>09:46 Friday 10 August 2018 JST I bought a book that has become my todo book. It&amp;rsquo;s as portable as my phone and even more reliable in terms of battery power. I bought it on Tuesday and have used it daily since then. Wow four days in total.
So far I have used a single page per day. (It&amp;rsquo;s 91mm x 160mm x 6mm, featuring 96 pages and two covers within the 6mm thickness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Finally sent book back to Margaret</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/07/11/finally-sent-book-back-to-margaret/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2017 16:32:52 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/07/11/finally-sent-book-back-to-margaret/</guid>
      <description>16:32 Tuesday 11 July 2017 JST I finally got Margaret&amp;rsquo;s book on its way back to her. She lent it to me years ago.. like 8 years and said she would like to have it back sometime.. and then our group ended and she left the country.
Funny that after I reached her and got her address yesterday, I suddenly had the desire to read the book to my GG class.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Received Rollerdog from Krimms</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/05/28/received-rollerdog-from-krimms/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 May 2015 16:57:07 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/05/28/received-rollerdog-from-krimms/</guid>
      <description>16:57 Thursday 28 May 2015 JST I received via snail mail the hardcopy version of Rollerdog I purchased from Krimms. It looks beautiful in its pristine packaging. I haven&amp;rsquo;t opened it yet, and probably won&amp;rsquo;t open it until further notice&amp;hellip; though I&amp;rsquo;ll email him and ask if there&amp;rsquo;s anything he put in the book specifically for me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>book review The Last</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/05/03/book-review-the-last/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 May 2015 17:45:24 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/05/03/book-review-the-last/</guid>
      <description>17:45 Sunday 03 May 2015 JST I just finished Mike&amp;rsquo;s latest book, The Last. It&amp;rsquo;s a really interesting story set in the real world, just three years from now. Quite an easy read except for the queasy parts which I almost had to put down! The story leaves some unanswered questions, and lends itself to more books, which I hope he writes soon!
I was surprised by the plot twists; it seemed so simple at first!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>