<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>fun on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/fun/</link>
    <description>Recent content in fun on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2019 21:16:44 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/fun/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Fun last lesson before vacation</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/10/02/fun-last-lesson-before-vacation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2019 21:16:44 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/10/02/fun-last-lesson-before-vacation/</guid>
      <description>Hide and Akiko from 7pm class each needed to make up some lessons, so stayed for the 8pm class featuring Misato and Tatsuya.
I think it worked pretty well; they had not met each other, and they are all pretty much similar personalities so I figured they would get along fine.
After self intros, most of the time they talked about Akiko&amp;rsquo;s challenging business trip to Hydrabad, India. Most of the rest of the time we talked about Hide&amp;rsquo;s work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Helping people see past lives?</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/blog/2019/09/07/helping-people-see-past-lives/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2019 17:26:33 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/blog/2019/09/07/helping-people-see-past-lives/</guid>
      <description>I put a question mark on the title because I cannot really prove the visions are related to past lives, but this is a fun way to guide people through a process to see what could be their past lives.
Each participant gets into a relaxed position, usually either sitting in a chair, or laying down, or otherwise sitting against something comfortable. Spend a few minutes leading the participants through a relaxation process, whereby they let their bodies relax and keep their minds awake.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fun time badminton</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/08/31/fun-time-badminton/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2019 01:25:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/08/31/fun-time-badminton/</guid>
      <description>01:25 Saturday 31 August 2019 JST Just now home and ready for bed after playing badminton with peeps from Tomoko&amp;rsquo;s badminton club.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>today</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/08/30/today/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 16:45:26 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/08/30/today/</guid>
      <description>16:45 Friday 30 August 2019 JST Several different things on my day off today. Mostly related to work, where I realized the value of having a staging server with non-live data. &amp;ldquo;Ohhh that is right; I tested saving data as well..&amp;rdquo; when AB was like, &amp;ldquo;Um, where is the Azabujuban record?&amp;rdquo; which had been renamed to &amp;ldquo;Doraemon 5e5433a38e2b035689a75c9ed11ffb0e&amp;rdquo;
Once I fixed all of those (about 8 different records) based on the old live DB which is still available at cli with mysql as root, I watched episode 3 of The Naked Director.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grinpa</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/07/22/grinpa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2019 14:53:37 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/07/22/grinpa/</guid>
      <description>(actually written 14:12 Wednesday 24 July 2019 JST)
After getting a photo with Kanauknot, we headed toward the roller coaster, but were sidetracked by a tiny house that offered free entry.
(It was inside the house that I took off my shoes; they felt so uncomfortably hot!)
Lin and Mikarin were like かわいいいいい at everything as I looked to see where I could explore. I considered using the upright piano to access the loft, but decided not to.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Great time hanging out with Max</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/07/05/great-time-hanging-out-with-max/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2019 22:40:49 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/07/05/great-time-hanging-out-with-max/</guid>
      <description>22:40 Friday 05 July 2019 JST Max and I met at The Pink Cow where Lin and I were going to meet, but she ended up heading home instead after work. After filling up on world famous bean burritos at The Pink Cow, we walked to Roppongi Midtown where we spent a considerable amount of time wondering how to measure if the circular glass window over the white not-really-egg-shaped stone is round or not.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Great SOGO and ultimate</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/06/16/great-sogo-and-ultimate/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2019 14:14:37 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/06/16/great-sogo-and-ultimate/</guid>
      <description>14:14 Sunday 16 June 2019 JST Fun in the sun today at SOGO Bootcamp. We had to adjust our normal workout area due to puddles, but all good and lots of fun. I remet Anuj, Valeria, Lisa, Alex, Ben. Got to see Haruo and Jim again as they led ultimate frisbee after bootcamp.
We played until about 1:18pm with about 6 on 6 down to 4 on 4 as people had to go.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>benefits of leaving an airport at 00:01</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/05/09/benefits-of-leaving-an-airport-at-0001/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2019 22:00:16 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/05/09/benefits-of-leaving-an-airport-at-0001/</guid>
      <description>22:00 Thursday 09 May 2019 JST My friend wanted to buy a ticket to leave on Saturday and accidentally bought a ticket that leaves at 00:01am (one minute after midnight) Saturday morning. (26 hours from now as I write this)
I challenged him to write 25 benefits of such a situation. Here are mine:
 have a funny story be awake with nothing to do but watch digital clock turn from 23:59:59 to 00:00:00 arrive at airport when it&amp;rsquo;s relatively quiet get a chance to see behind-the-scenes stuff they only do at night at airports not have to wake up early for a flight have already halfway solved the jetlag issue get to really ponder the human construct of tracking time have a chance to put a smile on face of staff working late save time shopping for souvenirs save money on buying souvenirs have moving walkway all to yourself get to wonder if other passengers made the same mistake get to joke about how early the flight is easy chance to sleep late on Saturday no worries about a large choice of food vendors in airport immediate night mode on plane so can sleep quickly &amp;ldquo;I leave tonight&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;I leave tomorrow&amp;rdquo; are both true passport stamps says you left the day before you actually leave opportunity for taking nighttime photos at airport can play in kids zone because no kids will be there can say &amp;ldquo;good evening&amp;rdquo; to one seatmate immediately before &amp;ldquo;good morning&amp;rdquo; to next seatmate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>walk number nine during typhoon</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/08/24/walk-number-nine-during-typhoon/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Aug 2018 07:47:34 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/08/24/walk-number-nine-during-typhoon/</guid>
      <description>07:47 Friday 24 August 2018 JST This morning I walked during the typhoon that passed by Tokyo today. I saw some interesting effects of water rushing down the hill near よみうりランド前駅 I captured them on vertical video on Marco Polo to send to Lin, who stayed home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>fun at SOGO</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/08/fun-at-sogo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Apr 2018 15:18:30 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/08/fun-at-sogo/</guid>
      <description>15:18 Sunday 08 April 2018 JST Great fun at SOGO today and not too hot, but a bit tiring. It&amp;rsquo;s apparently Alisha&amp;rsquo;s last day. Chatted with Thanuja at the Mexican restaurant for lunch; 12 SOGO peeps at our table. Leo and Lydia reminded me about geocaching.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>pool play</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/27/pool-play/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2017 19:51:32 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/27/pool-play/</guid>
      <description>19:51 Wednesday 27 December 2017 -02 Played with the nephews in the pool for a couple of hours. Activities included:
 entering the pool with various techniques counting consecutive successful toy catches bouncing an empty 2 liter bottle launching said bottle riding on jacuzzi cover like a raft filling 2 liter bottle with bubbles from jacuzzi jumping into pool for distance  But most importantly, no one got hurt</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>lukewarm jacuzzi</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/25/lukewarm-jacuzzi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Dec 2017 23:30:40 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/25/lukewarm-jacuzzi/</guid>
      <description>23:30 Monday 25 December 2017 -03 I just got out of the lukewarm jacuzzi because it just didn&amp;rsquo;t seem to be getting any hotter. The thermostat or something is broken so it won&amp;rsquo;t heat, so we taped a hose to the nearby shower faucet and put it on full hot, which was too hot to touch at first, but then seemed to get asymptotically close to the jacuzzi temperature, which never broke 32 degrees C.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kai and Mika tonight</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/11/25/kai-and-mika-tonight/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Nov 2017 00:42:59 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/11/25/kai-and-mika-tonight/</guid>
      <description>00:42 Saturday 25 November 2017 JST Hung out with Kai and Mika near Mika&amp;rsquo;s work tonight. They gave me a stack of flyers to hand out for a show that Mika and Kai will be staffing on Monday. Thanks to Mika for sending my medium rare burger back to be recooked to well done as I had ordered! Thanks to Mama for snacks she brought back today from her trip.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>walked 2 hours to Yoyogi Park</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/08/30/walked-2-hours-to-yoyogi-park/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2017 01:41:52 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/08/30/walked-2-hours-to-yoyogi-park/</guid>
      <description>01:41 Wednesday 30 August 2017 JST I walked for 2 hours from NB lesson to Yoyogi Park. I had 2 hours total and Google said it would take 1 hour and 45 minutes. I stopped once to get a snack and a drink (and to change from pants to shorts) and then stopped again to buy a 2 liter bottle of tea. Made it to Yoyogi Park with 2 minutes to spare.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>made pottery</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/08/19/made-pottery/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2017 11:04:24 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/08/19/made-pottery/</guid>
      <description>11:04 Saturday 19 August 2017 JST We just made some pottery with an chill old man sensei. I made a mobius strip for Fred, an upside-down plate for me, a dice shaker and two dice for my students.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JB party</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/12/11/jb-party/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2016 22:02:54 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/12/11/jb-party/</guid>
      <description>22:02 Sunday 11 December 2016 JST Great time at the party; talked to a lot of people and met Chris&amp;rsquo; friend Becca. Afteward, Chris and Becca invited Lin and me to karaoke with them. Super great fun! Chris loves karaoke. He said his record is 14 hours in one session, and then 6 hours the next day!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>physics lesson</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/06/30/physics-lesson/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2016 17:53:29 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/06/30/physics-lesson/</guid>
      <description>17:53 Thursday 30 June 2016 JST Physics Girl reminded me of the fun that can be had with magnets.
Today before my (ostensibly English) lesson with GG, I bought a meter of thin, shielded copper wire, a couple magnets, and a little light (emitting diode).
I brought with me a 1.5 volt AA battery and a ferrous, though magnetically neutral Allen wrench hex driver which will act as my electro magnet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Climbing trees in Yoyogi Park</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/08/08/climbing-trees-in-yoyogi-park/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2015 20:49:44 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/08/08/climbing-trees-in-yoyogi-park/</guid>
      <description>20:49 Saturday 08 August 2015 JST Satomi said her friend Kenji liked to climb trees so we should all do so! Today was the day; we met in Yoyogi Park at 4pm. At first it was Satomi and Zakky, and then I showed up and we went into Yoyogi. Kenji and his wife Sherry (sp) came as well, and their friend Ozan lives nearby so joined the fun. He said he wasn&amp;rsquo;t good at climbing trees, but we had fun playing badmitton and throwing a hard tennis ball at velcro mitts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>fun working day and met Scean</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/04/13/fun-working-day-and-met-scean/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Apr 2015 18:30:10 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/04/13/fun-working-day-and-met-scean/</guid>
      <description>18:30 Monday 13 April 2015 JST Just finished eating sakura ice cream with Scean, Kasagawa, and another guy whose name I didn&amp;rsquo;t get. We talked a lot (though I didn&amp;rsquo;t ask for permission to transcribe his interesting stories)!
This was all after about 6 hours of group lessons, all coordinated from the front of the room; basically the lesson content wasn&amp;rsquo;t difficult but all the coordination took a bit of focus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Studio Soness</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/02/13/studio-soness/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2015 20:54:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/02/13/studio-soness/</guid>
      <description>##20:54 Friday 13 February 2015 JST##
Full day of shooting at Studio Soness! In 8 hours, we got about 1 hour of video recorded.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mikako and Seo over for dinner</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/12/29/mikako-and-seo-over-for-dinner/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/12/29/mikako-and-seo-over-for-dinner/</guid>
      <description>##19:25 Monday 29 December 2014 JST##
Mikako and Seo came over today for なべ with me, Lin, and ママ. Jennie is here in the living area; Ted is hiding in the cat room, though he didn&amp;rsquo;t totally panic when Lin and Mika went to visit him.
Seo and I are playing Say Cheese. I&amp;rsquo;ve solved up through level 20 in the required number of moves; he has done most of them except the pesky level 10.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Made toy car at toy store</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/12/16/made-toy-car-at-toy-store/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/12/16/made-toy-car-at-toy-store/</guid>
      <description>##18:45 Tuesday 16 December 2014
(written 03:06 Sunday 21 December 2014 JST)
Went to the toy store in Harajuku and made two cars (but only photographed one)

The car pictured was made with some plastic toys that feature magnets which hold the pieces together.
The other car was made with plastic pieces held together with ball and socket joints.
柴田さん was there, but she was busy with another customer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>solved puzzles at toy store</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/12/02/solved-puzzles-at-toy-store/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/12/02/solved-puzzles-at-toy-store/</guid>
      <description>##18:38 Tuesday 02 December 2014 JST##
I&amp;rsquo;ve been stopping by the toy store on the way to M&amp;amp;M lesson on Tuesdays. It&amp;rsquo;s mostly kids&amp;rsquo; stuff, but they&amp;rsquo;ve got a few challenging puzzles, including three linked &amp;ldquo;ring&amp;rdquo; puzzles that can be taken apart. I solved two of them today after having solved the third (first?) last week. I put together a round plastic jigsaw puzzle, which I guess was made with a laser cutter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Schlitterbahn in New Braunfels</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1997/06/28/schlitterbahn-in-new-braunfels/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 1997 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1997/06/28/schlitterbahn-in-new-braunfels/</guid>
      <description>Saturday 28 June 1997
(transcribed out of my diary)
 Wende and I are in New Braunfels at her parents&amp;rsquo; house. We went to Schlitterbahn today&amp;ndash;my first time there&amp;ndash;and had a ton of fun. There are 3 separate parks.  I was most technologically impressed with the water coaster. The water pressure accelerated the tube boats up up up so they could slide down then up then down and the key was (of all things) large holes in the bottom of the up ramps which let out the water that was no longer going up so that it wouldn&amp;rsquo;t slow the boat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spring Break Science Trip</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1987/03/22/spring-break-science-trip/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Mar 1987 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1987/03/22/spring-break-science-trip/</guid>
      <description>(transcribed 5:50pm CST Monday 20 January 2003 - 11:ish Wednesday 22 January 2003)
(reformatted for Hugo 20 October 2017)
Mr. Hamm Mr. Cowan Beth Ahlborn Renae Ahlborn Pam Tacquard Julia Eckhardt Trace&#39; Dutson David Osborne Kevin Hollenshead Wade Johnson Barry Nelson Robert Nugen David Osborne Gary Picou Eric Shafer Brian Thigpen Allen Torgesen Carl Torgesen Charles Mike Hurt Glen Wilson Eric Likins John Tim Oestrich Doug ITINERARY Spring Trip Sunday-March 22: 11:00 AM-leave Tomball 2:00 PM-snack-roadside park near Bastrop 4:00 PM-supper in Austin 5:30 PM-arrive Inks Lake State Park.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>