<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>weather on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/weather/</link>
    <description>Recent content in weather on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2018 14:03:42 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/weather/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>lovely day</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/25/lovely-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2018 14:03:42 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/25/lovely-day/</guid>
      <description>14:03 Thursday 25 January 2018 JST Great online Integration Group today. Just six men in the call (we recently have had as many as 11 or 12). I was asked to facilitate twice (joy for me) and both men said it was very helpful. yay!
Headed to work now, slightly later than my arrive-early target, but still early enough to be on time. The weather is clear blue chilly with snow melting in the sun and frozen solid in the shade.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>rain wow</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/10/15/rain-wow/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2016 01:22:48 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/10/15/rain-wow/</guid>
      <description>01:22 Saturday 15 October 2016 AWST Super interesting rain here. It&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;partly cloudy&amp;rdquo; but with each cloud there&amp;rsquo;s like a decent rain shower. Then clear for 20 minutes and then rain like boom and then clear and then rain. It&amp;rsquo;s been happening basically all day. We never got storms like that in Houston, where it&amp;rsquo;s like boooooom rain and then clear for the rest of the week or month.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Warm storm</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/12/11/warm-storm/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2015 09:35:56 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/12/11/warm-storm/</guid>
      <description>09:35 Friday 11 December 2015 JST Lin and I slept late, wrapped up in blankets, trying to fend off the cold weather. She remembered that it&amp;rsquo;s trash day and upon opening the door to check if it had been collected, discovered the storm wind is relatively warm! I guess it&amp;rsquo;s a typhoon, though I haven&amp;rsquo;t been watching the weather / news at all.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>