<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>pk on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/pk/</link>
    <description>Recent content in pk on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2016 14:21:14 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/pk/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Drian helped tweak some of the transitions</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/11/23/drian-helped-tweak-some-of-the-transitions/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2016 14:21:14 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/11/23/drian-helped-tweak-some-of-the-transitions/</guid>
      <description>14:21 Wednesday 23 November 2016 JST Thanks to Drian for helping me clean up some of the transitions and tying up some loose ends on my Pecha Kucha presentation. He helped connect the thread of marriage back to the main theme, and helped tighten up the ending so it would be more impactful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>pk presentation pretty perfectly planned</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/11/22/pk-presentation-pretty-perfectly-planned/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2016 23:40:21 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/11/22/pk-presentation-pretty-perfectly-planned/</guid>
      <description>23:40 Tuesday 22 November 2016 JST I plan to speak at PechaKucha on 24 November!
These are the pictures I&amp;rsquo;ve submitted, and pretty much what I plan to say for each picture.
                 0:00 HI! I&amp;rsquo;m Rob! As you may have noticed, I like to walk around barefoot! I like to feel connected to the earth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>pecha kucha presentation plan</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/11/19/pecha-kucha-presentation-plan/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Nov 2016 18:54:11 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/11/19/pecha-kucha-presentation-plan/</guid>
      <description>18:54 Saturday 19 November 2016 JST I plan to speak at PechaKucha on 24 November!
These are the pictures I&#39;ve submitted, and sorta-kinda what I plan to say for each picture. Thanks to Soness for helpng me make a coherent story that people will hopefully be able to apply to their own lives!                   0:00 HI!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pecha Kucha?</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/12/15/pecha-kucha/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2015 11:10:56 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/12/15/pecha-kucha/</guid>
      <description>11:10 Tuesday 15 December 2015 JST Hmmm. Last night the idea of presenting at Pecha Kucha came to mind. Could be a good place to speak about authenticity
Some fragments came to mind while walking to the station
 I like walking barefoot (on beach) Not just on the beach but everwhere I can (collage of barefeet walking) Don&amp;rsquo;t worry about what people think Just be happy Not always happy Sometimes life can be surprising (surprise snake) What if we could talk about it?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>