<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>first on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/first/</link>
    <description>Recent content in first on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2019 22:12:09 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/first/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Arrived in Sugarland</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/10/04/arrived-in-sugarland/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2019 22:12:09 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/10/04/arrived-in-sugarland/</guid>
      <description>(written 22:12 Friday 04 October 2019 CDT)
Ma and I chatted while waiting for Nico to arrive and clear customs. Fun chatting with her and nearly finished solving the latest NYT crossword puzzle. I can see how it would be a good way to keep the ol&amp;rsquo; left brain sharp.
I chatted with the nice driver of the shuttle bus as she drove us to the IAH parking lot a couple miles away from the airport.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Headed to second eye gazing workshop</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/09/28/headed-to-second-eye-gazing-workshop/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2019 12:38:22 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/09/28/headed-to-second-eye-gazing-workshop/</guid>
      <description>Today is the second time for me to lead an eye gazing workshop. This will be in the same location in Dogenzaka.
It will be my first time to meet Yuna face to face! We have been doing lessons online for a while (since July 2018), so we know each other pretty well, but we have never met!
Currently 4 people are scheduled to attend, which is better than the Past Lives workshop!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I performed stand up comedy!</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/09/13/i-performed-stand-up-comedy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2019 23:59:59 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/09/13/i-performed-stand-up-comedy/</guid>
      <description>(adapted from my note last night to Mark)
I went to a stand-up comedy open mic tonight and ended up doing a set (my first ever!)
Several jokes went well, a couple did not; one of those is not recoverable in any way I can think of.
Soness said it was really good that I used contents of the room for several of my bits.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>studied Japanese with Akiko in Akihabara</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/05/24/studied-japanese-with-akiko-in-akihabara/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 23:10:41 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/05/24/studied-japanese-with-akiko-in-akihabara/</guid>
      <description>23:10 Friday 24 May 2019 JST There are probably errors in the Japanese notes below! Scanned with our new laser printer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>laser printer</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/05/24/laser-printer/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 23:05:51 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/05/24/laser-printer/</guid>
      <description>23:05 Friday 24 May 2019 JST Until now, we have always had inkjet printers. Our inkjet printer ran out of ink again, and I was like ef this. We are buying a laser printer.
It arrived today.
It is thrice as heavy as the inkjet and ten times as fast, a lot more crisp, and omg super great.
It scans like a champ (with its autofeeder that even worked with somewhat not-flat pages).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First session with Dane Dormio</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/05/22/first-session-with-dane-dormio/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2019 11:54:11 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/05/22/first-session-with-dane-dormio/</guid>
      <description>11:54 Wednesday 22 May 2019 JST I just finished a two hour session with Dane Dormio, during which we got a high level look at how I am doing in different areas of my life versus how I want to be doing in those areas. Then identified some action and habit I can implement in the next week.
Action: clear space for new printer
Habit: continue exercises from A Course in Miracles</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>onsen with Robert Golden</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/05/09/onsen-with-robert-golden/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2019 13:47:47 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/05/09/onsen-with-robert-golden/</guid>
      <description>13:47 Thursday 09 May 2019 JST Robert Golden and I enjoyed chatting at the onsen near Minami-tama station on JR Nambu line. Great to get to know each other better. I told him about how I ended up in Japan, including Tammy, Bonnie, Wende, janette, Lin. We talked about MKP Japan and the work we are doing here. I learned how he ended up in Hawaii.
I wished we could hang out longer at the onsen; I did not finish all my lunch and did not finish sitting in all the pools + both saunas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rode bicycle to station</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/05/08/rode-bicycle-to-station/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2019 06:34:01 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/05/08/rode-bicycle-to-station/</guid>
      <description>06:34 Wednesday 08 May 2019 JST I rode TJ Bike to the bicycle parking lot today. This is the first time I have done so for work, given that we got our bicycle parking passes during Golden Week, and this is the first day that I have to work outside the house.
I usually allow 24 minutes to walk leisurely to the station. Riding TJ Bike &amp;ldquo;leisurely&amp;rdquo; down a big hill, I arrived at the bicycle parking area in 8 minutes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with Mark soon: Behavioral OS</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/05/07/working-with-mark-soon-behavioral-os/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2019 21:58:06 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/05/07/working-with-mark-soon-behavioral-os/</guid>
      <description>21:58 Tuesday 07 May 2019 JST I found out that Mark is a trainer for Behavioral OS, something I have been interested in for a while. They are launching a course this year and I am excited to join!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>guest magician Robert Golden</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/04/30/guest-magician-robert-golden/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 21:52:55 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/04/30/guest-magician-robert-golden/</guid>
      <description>21:52 Tuesday 30 April 2019 JST Tonight, on the last day of Heisei, Robert Golden attend our men&amp;rsquo;s circle as a guest magician. It was really great to see his facilitation, and to see how closely it meshes with what we have already been doing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>urbit ~rabsef-linmyn</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/04/12/urbit-~rabsef-linmyn/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2019 14:10:53 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/04/12/urbit-~rabsef-linmyn/</guid>
      <description>14:10 Friday 12 April 2019 JST I got my urbit planet running the other day on my local machine. After some playing around I determined that I should be able to run it on AWS on a t2.micro which fits within their free tier.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>;join ~dopzod/urbit-help ... but still not connected to talk</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/04/10/join-~dopzod/urbit-help-...-but-still-not-connected-to-talk/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2019 23:14:08 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/04/10/join-~dopzod/urbit-help-...-but-still-not-connected-to-talk/</guid>
      <description>23:14 Wednesday 10 April 2019 JST I tried ;join /urbit-talk
I then followed this tweet ;join ~dopzod/urbit-help
But when I type in the talk&amp;gt; field, I do not see my posts anywhere.
Later I saw
[%dead-request [i=//http/0v14.urbt1/36/1 t=~]]  log is below:
$ urbit rabsef-linmyn/ ~ urbit 0.7.3 boot: home is /Users/thunderrabbit/urbit/rabsef-linmyn loom: mapped 2048MB boot: protected loom live: loaded: MB/254.885.888 boot: installed 258 jets arvo: time: ~2019.4.10..13.36.55..1b86 rest: checkpoint at event 13.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>prepping to talk to F</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/02/21/prepping-to-talk-to-f/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Feb 2019 07:35:38 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/02/21/prepping-to-talk-to-f/</guid>
      <description>07:35 Thursday 21 February 2019 JST Marble Track 3 is not my #1 priority; I am happy to work on it slowly.
*) Rewriting in Gatsby / React makes sense if I can learn along the path to creating it. How do you feel about going slowly, to help an old newbie learn along the way?
Basically, I do the work, learning along the way, you get a per month retainer, for minimum 5 months?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>effin around with gatsby</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/02/14/effin-around-with-gatsby/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2019 20:17:37 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/02/14/effin-around-with-gatsby/</guid>
      <description>20:17 Thursday 14 February 2019 JST A man named Fust has recommended a new stack for Marble Track 3: Airtable as backend, Gatsby as frontend, and some other things I have not heard of. Actually I had not heard of Gatsby.
I have an old VirtualBox sitting around so I spun it up and loaded a Gatsby demo. It pooped out a bunch of deprecation warnings, so I am loathe to really dig into this thing if it will be an ongoing battle against a bunch of deprecations ongoing during the project, as well as making the marble track itself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>work today</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/01/16/work-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2019 22:00:54 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/01/16/work-today/</guid>
      <description>22:00 Wednesday 16 January 2019 JST tired
8am - 9am Shukoh, then 4 hours of AB in internet cafe, TY called in the middle, then JB lessons from 3:30 to 9pm</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>working with a designer on Marble Track 3</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/12/31/working-with-a-designer-on-marble-track-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2018 03:57:19 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/12/31/working-with-a-designer-on-marble-track-3/</guid>
      <description>21:14 Sunday 30 December 2018 JST Dear Rob, Glad to see you email. I have gone through the website and there are a lot of improvement which can be done. Please check one of our Hugo based website - https://www.nathanaherne.com – If you’ll see on Home page – we have shown important section of the site briefly and with pictures. Same I’ll propose for this website i.e. we can show 3 or 6 Workers with Images, 3-6 Tracks, One Step with picture.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SOGO Ultra Radio Taiso</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/11/12/sogo-ultra-radio-taiso/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 06:19:54 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/11/12/sogo-ultra-radio-taiso/</guid>
      <description>06:19 Monday 12 November 2018 JST There is a morning exercise routine used by Japan to help build community and health and prepare everyone for the day. Even though it has been used in Japan for a minute, it has not spread outside Japan.
Today after SOGO, Menya and Risa led us through the first stages of changing all that. They had multiple cameras and awesome music. Video is coming Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Great hanging out with Mark</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/11/12/great-hanging-out-with-mark/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 06:11:31 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/11/12/great-hanging-out-with-mark/</guid>
      <description>06:11 Monday 12 November 2018 JST Mark rode 4km from the 古民家公園 to our house yesterday to meet Lin and see Marble Track 3 in person. He had some great ideas for MT3:
 Encourage teambuilding among youth by giving them a certain set of track pieces, tools, and time limit to make a track that fits a certain set of requirements. Set my camera so the whole set is in focus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>conswi dipendra</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/11/02/conswi-dipendra/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2018 17:26:01 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/11/02/conswi-dipendra/</guid>
      <description>17:26 Friday 02 November 2018 JST Today I met with Tariq and Dipendra to talk about ConSwi. They are all excited about the graphics and I am in the camp of getting a minimum viable product out. I want to empower Dipendra to update the graphics in the app. He got a copy of Conswi from Github. Instead of giving him write access to the app, I had him create his own account and push to his own ConSwi.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scuttlebutt reminds me of BBS days</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/10/22/scuttlebutt-reminds-me-of-bbs-days/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Oct 2018 21:29:41 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/10/22/scuttlebutt-reminds-me-of-bbs-days/</guid>
      <description>21:29 Monday 22 October 2018 JST This description of scuttlebutt reminds me of BBS days. I think I will dip a toe into this.
https://www.scuttlebutt.nz/
00:13 Tuesday 23 October 2018 JST 3 hours later&amp;hellip;. was dragged under by the current and oh man I gotta go to bed!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>cCCC with Shraddhan</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/10/22/cccc-with-shraddhan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Oct 2018 20:00:33 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/10/22/cccc-with-shraddhan/</guid>
      <description>20:00 Monday 22 October 2018 JST I met Shraddhan in Iidabashi to hear about his Creative Capitalism game. I don&amp;rsquo;t have a full sense of how to play it, but we had fun playing a small version which resulted in six piles of 72 yen each, plus a 5 yen coin in the center.
The idea is that these will be seed money for six different projects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>walking while talking to Dora</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/10/22/walking-while-talking-to-dora/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Oct 2018 16:03:33 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/10/22/walking-while-talking-to-dora/</guid>
      <description>16:03 Monday 22 October 2018 JST I chatted with Dora for 1.75 hours on the phone. She had some amazing insights on my presentation for MKP stuff. Plus a course she has enjoyed taking, designed to help people start their business projects.
While talking, I walked from Nishi-Azabu to the other end of Yoyogi Park before realizing I had intended to turn right before Yoyogi Park, or actually maybe even turn at Omotesando.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>blue car</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/10/21/blue-car/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Oct 2018 15:59:04 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/10/21/blue-car/</guid>
      <description>15:59 Sunday 21 October 2018 JST On my way to SOGO there was a blue car amongst the stalls where people were selling bread and beads and stuff. Huh. Old car looks new. It was old, and I asked the guy how old it was. Older than me by 2 years.
After SOGO I talked to him (in English) for about 20 minutes, and met his daughter, who has an accupuncture place nearby.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yoyogi Park day SOGO, Movement, Yuka &#43; Michael party</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/10/14/yoyogi-park-day-sogo-movement-yuka-michael-party/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Oct 2018 19:03:07 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/10/14/yoyogi-park-day-sogo-movement-yuka-michael-party/</guid>
      <description>19:03 Sunday 14 October 2018 JST (written Monday 2pm)
SOGO was a lot easier for me this weekend probably because it was not so blasting hot as it&amp;rsquo;s been during the summer. I was basically able to do most of the exercises without giving up partway through as I have done in the past.
After the workout, I joined a small group for lunch at a Thai restaurant. At my table: Asaad, Kino, Alex, Rafaela, Tatsuya, and maybe someone else.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chihomi came to SOGO</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/09/23/chihomi-came-to-sogo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Sep 2018 13:34:58 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/09/23/chihomi-came-to-sogo/</guid>
      <description>13:34 Sunday 23 September 2018 JST Long time no see for Mike, and not-so-long no see for Brad, but I had to ask their names again. Re-met Haruna as well; will remember all three in two weeks when I go back to SOGO! Today Chihomi came and said she enjoyed it enough to come back. Today was also Kevin&amp;rsquo;s first day. Kevin, beard freshly levin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>met Tariq and Dipendra</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/09/21/met-tariq-and-dipendra/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2018 09:24:08 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/09/21/met-tariq-and-dipendra/</guid>
      <description>09:24 Friday 21 September 2018 JST I met Dipendra today, a young man with design chops that far exceed my own, and even Tariq&amp;rsquo;s. He is interested in doing the images for ConSwi, our swipe game we are making in Godot.
We met in a room that used to be a car showroom, but now features a coffee shop because the car showroom was not making enough money.
I showed Dipendra how to get started with Godot and git.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SOGO me too</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/09/16/sogo-me-too/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2018 12:31:33 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/09/16/sogo-me-too/</guid>
      <description>12:31 Monday 16 September 2018 JST Funny thing at SOGO today. Sakura asked me how long I&amp;rsquo;ve been in Japan.
15 years.
She goes &amp;ldquo;Wow, me too, almost.&amp;rdquo; She is 17 years old. hahaha</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Go is great</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/08/31/go-is-great/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Aug 2018 21:50:51 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/08/31/go-is-great/</guid>
      <description>21:50 Friday 31 August 2018 JST Wow Go is great. The compiler doesn&amp;rsquo;t let you fuck around too much. &amp;ldquo;Hey you&amp;rsquo;re wasting variables!&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Hey those are different!&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Hey you already did that!&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Don&amp;rsquo;t include it if you don&amp;rsquo;t need it!&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Don&amp;rsquo;t use it if you didn&amp;rsquo;t include it&amp;rdquo;
I can imagine what Travis meant when he said if a Hakyll Haskell program compiles, it probably works correctly. Even with all the side effects available in Go, I am much more confident that my code works than with any PHP code.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Passion Test results</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/08/20/passion-test-results/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Aug 2018 17:42:15 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/08/20/passion-test-results/</guid>
      <description>17:42 Monday 20 August 2018 JST Today I took the Passion Test with Eri (, who is still looking for participants, if you&amp;rsquo;re interested).
I came up with the following visions and SMART goals
 Leading (by example) and teaching men to live their life mission
Have grandfathered 20 healthy men&amp;rsquo;s circles in Japan that run without me.
 Creating passionate community around detailed art.
Have 50,000 followers online and 500 live watchers of my livestreams</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lin joined me on my fifth walk</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/08/18/lin-joined-me-on-my-fifth-walk/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Aug 2018 09:19:54 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/08/18/lin-joined-me-on-my-fifth-walk/</guid>
      <description>09:19 Saturday 18 August 2018 JST Lin and I got off to a later start than I had originally planned, but we walked an hour around our neighborhood, finding some new streets we had never used before and arriving via different routes in places we had been before. &amp;ldquo;Oh! we&amp;rsquo;re here!&amp;rdquo; kinda thing.
Wow! 3.9km in 58 minutes, according to Google maps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>stomach camera</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/08/17/stomach-camera/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Aug 2018 09:31:45 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/08/17/stomach-camera/</guid>
      <description>9:31 Friday 17 August 2018 JST I just finished having my stomach checked. It was different than I expected. They put some kind of anesthetic in my mouth which for a moment maybe not be able to swallow which was weird. I couldn&amp;rsquo;t breathe through my mouth.
It was a little frightening that I couldn&amp;rsquo;t breathe through my mouth, but I was able to breathe through my nose so I was able to maintain and calm demeanor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>fantastic first walk (1)</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/08/14/fantastic-first-walk-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Aug 2018 11:05:38 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/08/14/fantastic-first-walk-1/</guid>
      <description>11:05 Tuesday 14 August 2018 JST I have decided to wake up at 5am each day, and on the five days I do not have to immediately go to work (for which I have already been waking up at 5am), I will go for a brisk walk around the neighborhood.
Today I went up the hill and along the ridge and up left on a street I had never walked before, then up a hill into a park and then omg down a spooky mossy staircase with spiderweb strands hitting my face and cicadas buzzing my ears and mosquitoes chomping my legs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>hugged a woman on the train</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/06/26/hugged-a-woman-on-the-train/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2018 23:26:52 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/06/26/hugged-a-woman-on-the-train/</guid>
      <description>23:26 Tuesday 26 June 2018 JST Tonight in Noborito station, I got off the train to try to figure out which train would be fastest to my station. A woman saw me barefoot and asked where I was going. She kindly looked up my station and confirmed my hunch that the next train was fastest to Shin Yurigaoka.
While riding on the train together, she asked me why I was barefoot, and then what I was doing in Japan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>geocache dekita</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/06/24/geocache-dekita/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jun 2018 10:17:06 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/06/24/geocache-dekita/</guid>
      <description>10:17 Sunday 24 June 2018 JST 昨日、初めのジオキャッシュを作って隠した。 Yesterday I made my first geocache and hid it.
https://geocaching.comで登録したけど、まだハンネイしていない。I registered it on https://geocaching.com, but it hasn&amp;rsquo;t been published yet.
先輩は新しキャッシュを確認してハンネイします。 Some senior member will check it and then publish the cache online.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mak^Hde first geocache</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/06/23/makhde-first-geocache/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Jun 2018 11:26:07 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/06/23/makhde-first-geocache/</guid>
      <description>11:26 Saturday 23 June 2018 JST I plan to placed my first geocache today.
I got support from Turbo-7, who sent me links to English and Japanese notes to place on the cache.
I tweaked the notes to include my email address, but have not put them online yet because they break the CSS of my site when displayed in the index, and I cannot figure out how to override the Hugo index the way I want.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>work</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/06/20/work/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jun 2018 15:14:48 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/06/20/work/</guid>
      <description>15:14 Wednesday 20 June 2018 JST Lunched with Tomoko and Yukiko (first time to meet her) at SCC, talking about movies and fears (acrophobia, claustrophobia, arachnophobia) and then lesson with Midori, talking about spot AC units which do not need ducts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>15 men in Tokyo Integration group</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/06/06/15-men-in-tokyo-integration-group/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2018 06:51:49 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/06/06/15-men-in-tokyo-integration-group/</guid>
      <description>06:51 Wednesday 06 June 2018 JST I did not keep careful track, but I believe we had 15 men in Tokyo men&amp;rsquo;s circle (Integration group) last night. According to A Circle of Men we should think about splitting the group if the group is larger than about 12 men.
I wonder about splitting the circle into two groups on the same evenings, or possible begin a circle on another evening of the week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keith Corrigan</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/05/31/keith-corrigan/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2018 08:24:25 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/05/31/keith-corrigan/</guid>
      <description>08:24 Thursday 31 May 2018 JST Keith Corrigan contacted me on FB, and I thought it was a fake account trying to lure money out of me, but now I am not so sure. I still have a guess that is the case, but it&amp;rsquo;s not as blatant as others I have seen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mt3: introducing spoonhead</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/05/30/mt3-introducing-spoonhead/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 May 2018 05:15:44 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/05/30/mt3-introducing-spoonhead/</guid>
      <description> 05:15 Wednesday 30 May 2018 JST I spent a couple hours on MT3 yesterday, culminating in introducing a new character whose job is to carry marbles onto the stage. On his way out, he hit the switch to reverse the stage rotation, so Squarehead will fall because he is just about to jump off the stage onto the ramp, but the stage is just about to reverse direction.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>sogo with Aki</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/05/27/sogo-with-aki/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 May 2018 20:28:49 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/05/27/sogo-with-aki/</guid>
      <description>20:28 Sunday 27 May 2018 JST Lin&amp;rsquo;s friend Aki joined SOGO today and had a lot of fun! Lin may attend as well next week; Aki plans to go again. Yay!
I got a bit sunburned, but should not be too bad tomorrow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Great co-gender group tonight</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/05/14/great-co-gender-group-tonight/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 May 2018 22:49:18 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/05/14/great-co-gender-group-tonight/</guid>
      <description>22:49 Monday 14 May 2018 JST Two new members today. Great connection and hopefully many more to come.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>health update</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/05/11/health-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 May 2018 11:20:51 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/05/11/health-update/</guid>
      <description>6 May or so 2018 I got a weird bump on my leg. Doctor gave some antibiotics.
  
11:20 Friday 11 May 2018 JST Today is my first health update my journal. I&amp;rsquo;m actually writing via voice recognition because I am not supposed to use my left wrist right now.
I went to the clinic and the doctor took x-rays and said there is some calcification on the bones in my wrist.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mt3 whats on the ramp</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/05/10/mt3-whats-on-the-ramp/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2018 09:34:25 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/05/10/mt3-whats-on-the-ramp/</guid>
      <description> 09:34 Thursday 10 May 2018 JST Neat neat neat I just discovered some new characters who should prove to be pretty useful as well as squirmy and maybe giving heebee jeebees!
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SOGO 2 year anniversary today</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/22/sogo-2-year-anniversary-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Apr 2018 20:01:24 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/22/sogo-2-year-anniversary-today/</guid>
      <description>20:01 Sunday 22 April 2018 JST SOGO is 2 years old today, so the organizers suggested a picnic in Yoyogi after the workout. Great workout and picnic with maybe 100 peeps and 80 peeps in attendance, respectively. I chatted with Hide, who has come for quite a while, and some first timers, Kino, Anna, and Laurie. Actually I don&amp;rsquo;t know if it was Kino&amp;rsquo;s first time, but it was my first time to meet her.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>today</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/22/today/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Apr 2018 00:06:34 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/22/today/</guid>
      <description>00:06 Sunday 22 April 2018 JST oops it is tomorrow already, but today Lin and I had neighbors Richard and Mai over for lunch, and then went for a walk with them and Fitz. We found a geocache.
https://coord.info/GLVJHGHK

I got a sharp flake of plastic splintered into my foot on the way home. Thankfully Lin was able to get it out relatively easily.
Today was the last day for Build Your Speaker Bio course; I will miss everyone and am really thankful for how much Soness helped with my speaker sheet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>geocache</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/08/geocache/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Apr 2018 19:27:37 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/08/geocache/</guid>
      <description>19:27 Sunday 08 April 2018 JST Lin joined me today as I found my first geocache
I want to place my own cache, but the site suggests finding between 20 and 100 caches before placing my own. Bah. I guess I will find a couple others before I place one. But the other crummy thing is the place I wanted to place a cache is apparently too close to the cache I found.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Met Felix</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/08/met-felix/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Apr 2018 07:53:16 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/08/met-felix/</guid>
      <description>07:53 Sunday 08 April 2018 JST Sarus Mama and Papa invited Lin and I to meet Felix and Koko last night. Great time with great peeps!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Met Dipika</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/04/met-dipika/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Apr 2018 12:45:01 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/04/met-dipika/</guid>
      <description>12:45 Wednesday 04 April 2018 JST Today while I was in the cafe below Muza, a woman came up and asked if I could speak English. I drew her a map to a bank on the other side of the station, but had a slightly bad feeling about sending her on a possible wild goose chase. Her name is Dipika, and she&amp;rsquo;s been in Japan just a little bit and will be here for 2 more weeks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>new man in mens circle last night</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/04/new-man-in-mens-circle-last-night/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Apr 2018 07:03:25 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/04/new-man-in-mens-circle-last-night/</guid>
      <description>07:03 Wednesday 04 April 2018 JST Nice synchronicity brought two old friends together on the train just in time for one to invite the other two men&amp;rsquo;s group last night, the first Tuesday of the month, when new men are welcome to join.
Six men in the circle last night. Good strong container in which we did a lot of good work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No のの</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/02/no-%E3%81%AE%E3%81%AE/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Apr 2018 23:48:51 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/02/no-%E3%81%AE%E3%81%AE/</guid>
      <description>15:48 Monday 02 April 2018 JST While walking from Roppongi down to my lunchtime lesson, I walked past a woman (after admiring her tattoo), and then she walked past me and said, &amp;ldquo;hey I like your style,&amp;rdquo; referring to my bare feet. Turns out she works at Gonpachi, aka the Kill Bill restaurant. She invited me to come by, so I did around 1:45pm.

She must have been busy or the message did not get to her, but no Nono.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mt3: hmm is the stage slowing down?</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/20/mt3-hmm-is-the-stage-slowing-down/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Mar 2018 15:22:32 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/20/mt3-hmm-is-the-stage-slowing-down/</guid>
      <description>15:22 Tuesday 20 March 2018 JST (written 09:25 Wednesday 21 March 2018 JST)
In a single day, I can take maybe 20 or 30 frames, which adds a couple of seconds to the final movie.
Yesterday, I worked 2 hours on Marble Track 3, including adding a new dimension of planning to the project:
  
I wrote notes to script out the next 5 weeks (or so) for the Reversable Guy (character whose head looks largely the same when facing forward or backward) as he debugs why the stage is slowing down.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>recreation</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/13/recreation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Mar 2018 01:46:35 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/13/recreation/</guid>
      <description>01:46 Tuesday 13 March 2018 JST 09:46 Monday 12 March 2018 Portland Recreational marijuana is legal in Oregon. I took advantage of this fact last night and had a really overall positive experience with several experiencial teachings I gained.
I am still a bit affected as I write this, sitting in the airport in Portland, waiting for my flight back to Narita.
The most interesting aspect about the experience itself was the time stretching.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Great LT1 weekend</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/11/great-lt1-weekend/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Mar 2018 16:05:39 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/11/great-lt1-weekend/</guid>
      <description>16:05 Sunday 11 March 2018 JST 23:05 Saturday 10 March 2018 JST Bunch of great guys here in Oregon for the LT1 and ST1 dual training. I attended ST1 (Staff Training 1) in Perth last year and am attending LT1 (Leadership Training 1) in Oregon this weekend. Got to meet Alan who I know from my online men&amp;rsquo;s circle, and met Mike P with dredlocks who I had met online as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Headed to Portland</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/09/headed-to-portland/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2018 12:16:24 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/09/headed-to-portland/</guid>
      <description>12:16 Friday 09 March 2018 JST I&amp;rsquo;m leaving in about an hour for a weekend in Portland. It&amp;rsquo;s for a training called The Container of Leadership. I will be challenged to look deeply at myself, really digging down into my -isms and other thoughts which unconsiously underly my perception of the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>first draft bio</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/05/first-draft-bio/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Mar 2018 15:34:49 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/05/first-draft-bio/</guid>
      <description>15:34 Monday 05 March 2018 JST To pursue his dream of travel, Rob gave up his comfortable life in Texas, including house, car, cat, and fiance. Just to see what else is out there. Fascinated with time, Rob has started a stop-motion animation project, likely to take ten years. He has also started writing a novel, which is being presented backwards, one word at a time. Walking around barefoot as often as possible, Rob hopes to inspire others to do what they like, regardless of what other people may think.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Great day</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/04/great-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Mar 2018 20:56:47 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/04/great-day/</guid>
      <description>20:56 Sunday 04 March 2018 JST Went to SOGO for workout with about 50 people in attendance. Great weather and great workout. I met Shell, Koji, Tyler, and others, but cannot remember now.
Went to lunch with Lisa at Laska and chatted with her a bit, and got to see a video of the type of dancing she is doing.
Went down to Tsujido for karaoke after recording video at karaoke with Kai, Mitsue, and Soness as the stars.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>first session with Daeryl Holzer</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/30/first-session-with-daeryl-holzer/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2018 16:53:18 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/30/first-session-with-daeryl-holzer/</guid>
      <description>16:53 Tuesday 30 January 2018 JST My homework after my session with Daeryl is to look up hypnotherapy training. She said I cannot finish reading books because I get started reading, remember the rest, and don&amp;rsquo;t need to read the rest of the book.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>headed to work at SCC</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/26/headed-to-work-at-scc/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2018 12:55:17 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/26/headed-to-work-at-scc/</guid>
      <description>12:55 Friday 26 January 2018 JST Three hours of lessons in SCC today; looking forward to it!
On the way there, I hope to figure out why my local version of mypowercircle.org will not compile with Hugo. bah. it was supposed to be easy!!
Ah. I had gotten stuck trying to add Japanese language version of the site, but never got it working. It&amp;rsquo;s better to just have an actual Japanese speaker make the Japanese site, so I cut out the Japanese content from the site and now it&amp;rsquo;s working again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>speaker bio draft</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/17/speaker-bio-draft/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2018 13:14:08 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/17/speaker-bio-draft/</guid>
      <description>13:14 Wednesday 17 January 2018 JST Often seen walking barefoot around Tokyo, Rob likes baring his soles as well as his soul. &amp;ldquo;The long term goal is to reduce the suicide rate in Tokyo&amp;rdquo; he says with a wistful gaze. &amp;ldquo;It just seems like such a waste of human potential for someone to kill themselves instead of talk about their problems.&amp;rdquo;
To facilitate talking about problems, he leads peer counseling circles in Tokyo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>five hours of work at SCC</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/13/five-hours-of-work-at-scc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2018 02:33:31 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/13/five-hours-of-work-at-scc/</guid>
      <description>02:33 Saturday 13 January 2018 JST Today was the first time I worked five hours at SCC. Due to a schedule snafu, 1.5 hours with Liliko chatting about her trip to Sydney and my trip to OZ, then Rick and Morty and Lucifer. I didn&amp;rsquo;t think of Dirk Gently, but she considered getting Netflix to see the others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Met Lin&#39;s aunt and uncle 2</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/17/met-lins-aunt-and-uncle-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2017 16:33:10 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/17/met-lins-aunt-and-uncle-2/</guid>
      <description>16:33 Sunday 17 December 2017 -02 Met A-ni-su and A-ni-su-mei at their restaurant and then went to a bbq party on the other side of town. I chatted with 三木（みき）in English, and his friend talked about the organization whose name includes a pronunciation pun on the phrase &amp;ldquo;innovate yourself&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>bought 2 orgonite pyramids</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/16/bought-2-orgonite-pyramids/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2017 11:43:56 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/16/bought-2-orgonite-pyramids/</guid>
      <description>11:43 Saturday 16 December 2017 -02 Walking by a street vendor, I liked the look of items on this table
 
and ended up buying two.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>my first flight in an Airbus A-380</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/16/my-first-flight-in-an-airbus-a-380/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2017 07:37:40 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/16/my-first-flight-in-an-airbus-a-380/</guid>
      <description>07:37 Saturday 16 December 2017 -02 Last night was my (and Lin&amp;rsquo;s) first time to travel in an Airbus A380. Our flight was around 15 hours from Dubai to São Paulo on Emirates, which is apparently Airbus&amp;rsquo; largest A380 customer.
I was impressed with how relatively quiet the plane was during the entire flight. (I had a window seat just at the trailing edge of the wings.)
We had a hard landing with a bounce, but the aircraft came to a stop very quickly and smoothly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>saikin (recently)</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/03/saikin-recently/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2017 15:06:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/03/saikin-recently/</guid>
      <description>15:06 Sunday 03 December 2017 JST There are likely myriad errors in the Japanese below! 俺の最近の世界  これは初めの「俺の最近の世界」と言う日記の文書です。 パソコンで書けますけど、今度読めますか？ 今日十時間ぐらい仕事できました。 メル先生から優しいメールをもらいました。 最近じゃないけど、毎日裸足で歩きます。 さっき、あんの人は私の裸足にさせて、微笑んだ。私「裸足」言うって、 彼は「なぜ」言うった。「気持ちから」言うった。彼がまた微笑んだ。 それはフォンで、只今電車に座りながら、書きます。 新宿まで乗るけどローマンスカーは２０分しかかからない。 日本語を喋りたいけど、「マットリクス」と言う映画見たい勉強しないすむがいいと思う。 まだ毎年新しものを勉強しますかな。 メーロを書く年あるし これは私のメーロのサイートです。 https://www.amazeaweek.net/ たくさんビットコインの記事を読んだし ３５分後、英語のレッスンが始まります。その前に２５版までを終わらせちゃう。 今日もっと寒かったけど裸足で歩きました。 妻にごぼうもらった。美味しいです。 食べたいけどもう歯を磨きました。 明日またMT3の作る事を続きたいです。 MT3のサイトは https://mt3.robnugen.com です。 友達の　ジェニファーから取って、うちの猫をジェニーと名付けた。 今日、友達の古いフィットビットをもらいました。 今チャージ中です。 部屋を素地しました時リップ５本を見つけた。 うちの猫ジェニーには友達のためジェニーって呼ぶ 今週末は忙しかったですけど仕事のやつできました。 よくできました！  English versions of the sentences above, just in case they are needed.
 This is the first time I have written an SOML in Japanese.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mt3: mt3.robnugen.com</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/11/18/mt3-mt3.robnugen.com/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Nov 2017 15:00:18 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/11/18/mt3-mt3.robnugen.com/</guid>
      <description>15:00 Saturday 18 November 2017 JST During the livestream today, I watched the (5) clips so far to see which characters have had the ability to pass through tracks. Basically it&amp;rsquo;s easier to let characters pass through tracks, but I think it would be a good subtle thing if some characters (consistently) can, and some (consistently) cannot.
Anyway, I took notes and pinned them to the blue fabric which makes the floor of the set.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>new style TS lessons</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/11/16/new-style-ts-lessons/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2017 17:56:10 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/11/16/new-style-ts-lessons/</guid>
      <description>17:56 Thursday 16 November 2017 JST Mutsumi introduced a new style lesson format where the guides sit down together with me instead of just having individual lessons. Hopefully this will help them improve listening skills by listening to other people have conversations in English.
I showed mt3s.robnugen.com to Miyako and Ayaka. Miyako showed me pics from her trip to the US with Haruka.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting started in Godot Engine</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/11/12/getting-started-in-godot-engine/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2017 06:37:40 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/11/12/getting-started-in-godot-engine/</guid>
      <description>06:37 Sunday 12 November 2017 JST Godot Engine would display its windows at the wrong zoom level so I couldn&amp;rsquo;t even use it&amp;hellip; so I was like bah at first, but so many people kept liking it, so I kept at it and discovered it was an issue with different monitor pixel densities. Aha! Looks like Godot is reading the pixel density on my main monitor even though it is open on a second monitor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shimoda Weekend</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/11/07/shimoda-weekend/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2017 13:39:45 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/11/07/shimoda-weekend/</guid>
      <description>13:39 Tuesday 07 November 2017 JST Okay it&amp;rsquo;s been a couple days, but we had a lovely weekend in Shimoda. So glad that Lin joined us! She said she had a great time. The weekend schedule was kinda freestyle, which caused a bit of consternation for some, but did not affect things too badly. I enjoyed getting to know everyone a bit better.
Yoga on Saturday morning was originally led by Lisa, but turned into acro yoga with people being angels, superman, partners, flippers, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Liz English School</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/10/24/liz-english-school/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2017 13:05:14 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/10/24/liz-english-school/</guid>
      <description>13:05 Tuesday 24 October 2017 JST Met Yaw for the first time at Liz English School. He and I got on quite well, and even shared a prayer for world peace and supporting our community and family. I look forward to working closely with him in the future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mt3 first roll celebration</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/10/10/mt3-first-roll-celebration/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2017 13:11:43 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/10/10/mt3-first-roll-celebration/</guid>
      <description>13:11 Tuesday 10 October 2017 JST   yay they rolled a marble!
Live stream in two parts today.
 Up to the first roll https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BjtpiRxoxvU The first roll https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=i9gCFg5TpqQ  I have spent 73 hours on MT3 so far.
10:23 Wednesday 11 October 2017 JST Oh wow I really love it. The characters manically run around for a bit and it&amp;rsquo;s hard to tell what&amp;rsquo;s going on, but then they all line up for the first roll; I think it looks pretty good.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mt3： first rolling marble</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/09/27/mt3-first-rolling-marble/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2017 00:06:51 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/09/27/mt3-first-rolling-marble/</guid>
      <description>00:06 Wednesday 27 September 2017 JST   It does not honestly make a lot of sense, but the marble rolled on the stage and the guys ran around while it spun.
Livestream is here https://youtu.be/UAhlgQTAN4U
I have spent 66 hours on MT3 so far.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paola and Jon came over</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/09/23/paola-and-jon-came-over/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2017 20:20:27 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/09/23/paola-and-jon-came-over/</guid>
      <description>20:20 Saturday 23 September 2017 JST Today was the first time for Paola and Jon to come visit our house since we moved last summer. Lovely time including delicious salmon quiche, indian graham crackers (my name), plum pie, and two different salads. Oh, and we played the ball game that I do not have a name for yet, but which I got from the shop in Harajuku. Everyone played and enjoyed it!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>zeronet.io</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/09/17/zeronet.io/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2017 01:41:38 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/09/17/zeronet.io/</guid>
      <description>01:41 Sunday 17 September 2017 JST Huh. Zeronet seems interesting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>weights</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/09/16/weights/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2017 18:50:13 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/09/16/weights/</guid>
      <description>18:50 Saturday 16 September 2017 JST Simon gave me a set of weights, including one which he found discarded on a hiking trail. We hiked up the trail, found the weight still there, collected it and cleaned it up in his shower.
He wanted to give me dumbells, but after I asked what would be good for my lower back, he suggested a T-bar kettlebell.
 
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=427hjj0ZRDc
At one point we got a pic at the supermarket while he bought us beef for steak and potatoes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>rafting yesterday with Simon</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/09/16/rafting-yesterday-with-simon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2017 08:35:37 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/09/16/rafting-yesterday-with-simon/</guid>
      <description>08:35 Saturday 16 September 2017 JST Arms are sore after rafting yesterday, but generally had a great time. Got dumped a couple of times, and banged up my knees a bit on rocks, but I was wearing a helmet, so no worries.
I am thankful my phone is waterproof!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>hung out with Michael near Noborito</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/09/09/hung-out-with-michael-near-noborito/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2017 00:08:05 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/09/09/hung-out-with-michael-near-noborito/</guid>
      <description>00:08 Saturday 09 September 2017 JST First time to hang out with Michael one on one. We ate at a cafe in the station and then went barefoot out on a balcony where we talked to a mom waiting for her kid to come back from school. Michael chatted with her a bit, introducing us.. I was kinda amazed because even though my Japanese is better, I&amp;rsquo;m not as willing to break the ice with people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>beads for sale</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/08/18/beads-for-sale/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2017 19:30:48 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/08/18/beads-for-sale/</guid>
      <description>19:30 Friday 18 August 2017 JST This is the first time I have worked with glass. Basically melted the end of a glass rod and tacked some colors onto it after the sensei wrapped it onto some sort of ceramic to which the glass apparently won&amp;rsquo;t adhere.
Lin took pictures during the process and then when I finished was like お疲れ様です。 and I was like まだまだ and asked the sensei if I could make another.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mt3：skeleton arrives</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/08/08/mt3skeleton-arrives/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2017 11:33:46 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/08/08/mt3skeleton-arrives/</guid>
      <description>11:33 Tuesday 08 August 2017 JST   This is the first time the skeleton has been seen in a scene of Marble Track 3.
The livestream was 3 hours; it got split in the middle
https://youtu.be/9mEeIYsISLk
https://youtu.be/AALQGwA44Gc
video time: 68 seconds so far
video making time: 69001 seconds ( 19 hours) so far.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>new lesson</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/07/18/new-lesson/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 17:52:31 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/07/18/new-lesson/</guid>
      <description>17:52 Tuesday 18 July 2017 JST Met new students for a first lesson in Nihonbashi. Five beginner students who all seem pretty genki. Some are more beginner than others.
JB was there to do the introduction and everything went smoothly. See you guys again next week! &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m glad to hear that!&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>connection</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/01/08/connection/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2017 14:29:24 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/01/08/connection/</guid>
      <description>14:29 Sunday 08 January 2017 JST Then on the way home a met a couple on the train who have lived in the same area for 20 years. It&amp;rsquo;s not amazing for Japanese, but he is an English speaker, and isn&amp;rsquo;t from Japan.
They live kinda kinda close to us
Same line at least
He seemed really nice so I hope we can hang out more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>met Hanako and Christy</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/10/08/met-hanako-and-christy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2016 23:52:45 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/10/08/met-hanako-and-christy/</guid>
      <description>23:52 Saturday 08 October 2016 JST (names changed)
Hanako and Christy are over from Austin at Hanako&amp;rsquo;s parents, who happen to be our neighbors across the street. Mom came over at 9pm or so and was like, &amp;ldquo;Rob! come over!&amp;rdquo;
After hugging Hanako and Christy I talked to them and ignored Hanako&amp;rsquo;s siblings who were there with family because I was in new-people-overload (doesn&amp;rsquo;t take much, I guess) and selfishly wanted to talk to Americans.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Climbing trees in Yoyogi Park</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/08/08/climbing-trees-in-yoyogi-park/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2015 20:49:44 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/08/08/climbing-trees-in-yoyogi-park/</guid>
      <description>20:49 Saturday 08 August 2015 JST Satomi said her friend Kenji liked to climb trees so we should all do so! Today was the day; we met in Yoyogi Park at 4pm. At first it was Satomi and Zakky, and then I showed up and we went into Yoyogi. Kenji and his wife Sherry (sp) came as well, and their friend Ozan lives nearby so joined the fun. He said he wasn&amp;rsquo;t good at climbing trees, but we had fun playing badmitton and throwing a hard tennis ball at velcro mitts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>first lesson</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/06/03/first-lesson/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2015 12:23:15 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/06/03/first-lesson/</guid>
      <description>12:23 Wednesday 03 June 2015 JST Today is my first lesson with TEM in Lazona. Apparently low level so I brought Side by Side.
14:14 Lesson went well I think, but she said 難しい instead of 楽しかった so I hope she enjoyed it!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kusk Studio</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/05/18/kusk-studio/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 May 2015 22:15:06 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/05/18/kusk-studio/</guid>
      <description>22:15 Monday 18 May 2015 JST Wow cool! I met a guy in Akihabara station as he was looking at the train map. I happened to know he could get to Kichijoji station on the Sobu Line so I walked him upstairs to it.
He described having been to an interesting sounding workshop thing, and gave me a sticker from there.
DMM.make  Wow what? This DMM is the logo of an adult video company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>slow day today</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/03/22/slow-day-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Mar 2015 20:35:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/03/22/slow-day-today/</guid>
      <description>##20:35 Sunday 22 March 2015 JST##
Today has seemed very slow because Lin and I are fasting! Looks like we survived; she&amp;rsquo;s in gettin&amp;rsquo;-ready-for-bed mode, and I&amp;rsquo;m like meh; not that hungry anymore.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Met Daisuke</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/12/13/met-daisuke/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/12/13/met-daisuke/</guid>
      <description>##00:45 Saturday 13 December 2014 JST##
I met Lin in Tokyo so we could meet her friend Daisuke. He&amp;rsquo;s got a job interview for which he needs to speak a bit of English. Lin and I gave him a few lines which will hopefully help him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First 赤羽橋 lesson</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/11/first-%E8%B5%A4%E7%BE%BD%E6%A9%8B-lesson/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/11/first-%E8%B5%A4%E7%BE%BD%E6%A9%8B-lesson/</guid>
      <description>##10:20 Tuesday 11 November 2014 JST##
Today was my first lesson in 赤羽橋, a station whose kanji I cannot really read yet, though I know each kanji individually if I read slowly.
The lesson is a beginner level lesson, though I think the article I brought was a bit too difficult for the level. I&amp;rsquo;ll bring an easier article next time.
Only two students: A on the left wearing a necklace made by her friend ten years ago, and A on the right with all his mobile devices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>three lessons at Toshiba</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/11/three-lessons-at-toshiba/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/11/three-lessons-at-toshiba/</guid>
      <description>##18:43 Tuesday 11 November 2014 JST##
Another first lesson today: &amp;lsquo;twas the first time I taught at Toshiba science museum near Lazona in Kawasaki.
I taught three lessons to three individuals, all of whom wore the same uniform, so I&amp;rsquo;m not sure I could readily identify them in a lineup, but the lessons were fun and I hope I will get to go back after tomorrow, when I&amp;rsquo;m scheduled to be there for three hours.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kids classes (a.k.a. O_o)</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/05/kids-classes-a.k.a.-o_o/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/05/kids-classes-a.k.a.-o_o/</guid>
      <description>##10:58 Wednesday 05 November 2014 JST##
Wow. Well, I survived the first day teaching a group of kids, they seemed to have fun overall, and there was some semblence of learning involved.
To be more specific, I just &amp;ldquo;taught&amp;rdquo; two classes of around 20 kids each, the first group being a bit younger than the second; I&amp;rsquo;d guess 5 and 6 years old, but I heard they were 4 and 5 years old respectively.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>it all started here</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2007/06/27/it-all-started-here/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2007 10:07:34 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2007/06/27/it-all-started-here/</guid>
      <description>27 June 2007 JST (written 10:11 Monday 25 September 2017 JST)
Okay so it all started ten years ago. I made Marble Track 2 during my free time at work and then made this video.
  People asked how I made the marble track. It&amp;rsquo;s a simple question without a simple answer. &amp;ldquo;I glued sticks together..&amp;rdquo;
I decided I should answer by showing the pipe cleaner characters making the track.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ConCon first am</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/08/04/concon-first-am/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Aug 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/08/04/concon-first-am/</guid>
      <description>Con Con
11:30am Tuesday 4 August 1998

transcribed from my diary
Woke up and read part of Shield and talked to Torger and Galen and others on staff out on our cabin porch. Then breakfast and sat at the same table with mostly the same group as dinner last night. We talked and chilled a bit and bounced a plastic ring from a coke bottle plastic cap. At the Spirt Circle I sat between Carol and Jeremy who sang &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>