<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>anger on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/anger/</link>
    <description>Recent content in anger on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2019 11:27:31 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/anger/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Simple steps for dealing with anger</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/blog/2019/06/27/simple-steps-for-dealing-with-anger/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2019 11:27:31 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/blog/2019/06/27/simple-steps-for-dealing-with-anger/</guid>
      <description>1) breathe. Focus on your breathing until the initial wave of anger has passed. It may help to focus on counting the breaths.
Allow your breathing to deepen and slow.
2) label. Say you yourself, &amp;ldquo;I feel angry.&amp;rdquo; Labeling the emotion brings your thoughtful brain back online.
This helps move beyond the Fight or Flight reaction of the reptilian brain
3) acknowledge. Recognize the steps that brought you into this situation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What do emotions tell us</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/blog/2019/06/18/what-do-emotions-tell-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2019 21:22:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/blog/2019/06/18/what-do-emotions-tell-us/</guid>
      <description>Sticking with the basics, we have joy and fear.
Joy is how I feel when I have what I want, or I don&amp;rsquo;t want what I don&amp;rsquo;t have. I am aligned with what is, and have no need or desire to change it.
Fear is the emotion which says I don&amp;rsquo;t have enough information. This is usually about an unknown future. I come to a proverbial fork in the road and could simply choose arbitrarily, but if there is a part of me that wants to choose the &amp;ldquo;right&amp;rdquo; option, I may feel fear about choosing the &amp;ldquo;wrong&amp;rdquo; option.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>shaking with anger</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/10/05/shaking-with-anger/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2017 13:10:30 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/10/05/shaking-with-anger/</guid>
      <description>13:10 Thursday 05 October 2017 JST written 21:59 Thursday 05 October 2017 JST
Still fucking shaking with anger. I saw an old man grab a woman&#39;s ass just as her train arrived. He tried to run so I grabbed him and brought him back to her. She was like thank you and got on the train! Yo lady don&#39;t leave me hanging with this fucker; he grabbed your ass. so I yelled at him and let him go, never to see her again and a bunch people wondering wtf crazy barefoot mf yelling about.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>dream rage at a guy</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/08/09/dream-rage-at-a-guy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2017 07:46:17 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/08/09/dream-rage-at-a-guy/</guid>
      <description>07:46 Wednesday 09 August 2017 JST Driving Mr Van with some friends, including Natalie from PB, I learned that one of my friends was able to start Mr Van with a lockpick key that worked very easily. He wanted to drive, but because he wasn&#39;t on our insurance, I said it was illegal and asked him not to.
He distracted me with a puzzle and then when I looked up, I disocvered he was driving the van!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>