<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>unicycle on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/unicycle/</link>
    <description>Recent content in unicycle on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2000 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/unicycle/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Unicycle</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/06/22/unicycle/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/06/22/unicycle/</guid>
      <description>8:35am CDT Thursday 22 June 2000
Before work today, enjoying the early morning sun, I unicycled outside our house. I stayed close by the driveway (and phone); I was waiting for Alisa (Elisa?) to come sleep on our couch between work ending at 8am and beginning at noon. (E/Alisa is my dad&amp;rsquo;s girlfriend&amp;rsquo;s daughter)
In order to stay close by the house, I practiced fine tune stuff: tight turns within the width of the street!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>unicycle</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/06/20/unicycle/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/06/20/unicycle/</guid>
      <description>9:55pm CDT Tuesday 20 June 2000
Tonight is 1 day away from Summer Solstice!! For some strange reason, this fact has totally been escaping me&amp;hellip; I&amp;rsquo;ve been wasting precious daylight!
After eating at Mission Burrito with Deborah (sp) and Wende, I rode my (borrowed) unicycle a total of about 13 blocks! All the way from our house to the middle of the American General parking lot (4 blocks or so), then a few short rides in the parking lot, then several false starts when leaving the parking lot, but once I got started, I rode 4 blocks along West Dallas (4 lane street) to the Chevron station at the corner of Montrose and W Dallas (including going up their little driveway ramp!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>unicycle</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/05/19/unicycle/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/05/19/unicycle/</guid>
      <description>Unicyclin&amp;rsquo; 6:20pm CDT Friday 19 May 2000
I just unicycled around the block!! I did it in only 2 starts!! Actually it took 4 starts, but 2 of them resulted in immediately dismounting (falling off;-).
ps: I have noticed that a lot of my journal entries are short, and I think it would be much nicer for you, my lovely reader, if links to [prev] and [next] journal entries were at the bottom of each entry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>unicycle</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/05/11/unicycle/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/05/11/unicycle/</guid>
      <description>Unicycle 7:05pm CDT Thursday 11 May 2000
Wow. In one hour I unied (past tense of &amp;ldquo;rode my (borrowed) unicycle&amp;rdquo;) from our house, three blocks to the gas station, put air in the tire (it was a little flat) and rode almost all the way back. On the way back, I found it so much easier! Note to fellow uniers: keep your tire inflated!
(oh! At the gas station I saw Meek from Saturday Night Ultimate!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>unicycle</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/05/10/unicycle/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/05/10/unicycle/</guid>
      <description>Unicycle till I sweat 10:01pm CDT Wednesday 10 May 2000
So I didn&amp;rsquo;t go to ultimate after all. Got downstairs and thought&amp;hellip; &amp;ldquo;unicycle&amp;rdquo; because I haven&amp;rsquo;t ridden in a while and my (borrowed) unicycle is right here in my trunk, while ultimate is way over there in a field.
I did relatively great! I successfully turned 360 degrees within the radius of our street (3 cars wide) plus sidewalk (including going up and back down the slight driveway slope)!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>unicycle</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/04/28/unicycle/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/04/28/unicycle/</guid>
      <description>Unicycle 7:44am CDT Friday 28 April 2000
Last night I pulled out (from my trunk) the old unicycle. It&amp;rsquo;s been since my last journal entry that I&amp;rsquo;ve ridden it; I&amp;rsquo;m guessing over a month, maybe two months ago.
Delightfully enough, I have discovered that unicycling is just like riding a bike; once I&amp;rsquo;ve learned how, I didn&amp;rsquo;t forget. Granted, I wasn&amp;rsquo;t great at it, but last night I rode just as well as I had the last time!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>unicycle</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/03/09/unicycle/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/03/09/unicycle/</guid>
      <description>unicycle 8:33pm CST Thursday 9 March 2000
Yesterday I purchased gas for Scott. $1.51 per gallon!! Depending on where you live, this may seem like nothin&amp;rsquo;, but it&amp;rsquo;s fully 22 cents higher than it was last week. Yipes!
^^^^^ That&amp;rsquo;s just a side note.
I&amp;rsquo;m feeling antsy right now; just like gotta go do something!
So I&amp;rsquo;m going to ride my unicycle to the bank. I got a check in the mail today for some computer work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>unicycle2</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/03/09/unicycle2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/03/09/unicycle2/</guid>
      <description>10:05pm CST Thursday 9 March 2000
Wow. I am officially tired.
This was certainly a feat of persistence. On the way to the bank, I essentially didn&amp;rsquo;t walk at all. At each point that I fell (stepped) off the unicycle, I started from that same point, or at an easier-to-start point (telephone pole, for example) behind where I stepped off.
I deposited the check at 9:41pm (according to the bank).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ultimate Unicycle</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/02/17/ultimate-unicycle/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/02/17/ultimate-unicycle/</guid>
      <description>Ultimate and Unicycling 1:57am CST Thursday 17 February 2000
Ultimate was great fun tonight! Now I know how some of the guys (John) who play Saturday night have gotten so much better! On Wednesdays the field is huge and everyone runs! The structure of play is different, too: instead of playing a game to a certain number of points, we just play one point at a time. We maintain 7 or 8 people on each team, and as people get tired of play, they swap with people on the sidelines.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>unicycling</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/01/20/unicycling/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/01/20/unicycling/</guid>
      <description>Unicycling 8:46pm CST Thursday 20 January 2000
Today I unicycled over 200 feet! I first started practicing when my brother bought a unicycle around December. He and I were each able to go about 30 feet, and he could sometimes go 40 feet. I was so thrilled by my improvement that I borrowed a unicycle and today after practicing less than 2 hours, I went 226 feet!
I borrowed it on Tuesday from a guy (Scott) who skates on Tuesday and Thursday nights.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>