<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>babychan on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/babychan/</link>
    <description>Recent content in babychan on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2019 18:18:03 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/babychan/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>replanted tree today</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/06/15/replanted-tree-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2019 18:18:03 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/06/15/replanted-tree-today/</guid>
      <description>18:18 Saturday 15 June 2019 JST Lin and I replanted the sakura tree which we planted (too close to the wall) last week. There was a slight gap in the rain so we took the chance to move the tree.
I was thankful I had done a careful job of packing mud and nutritious leaves for the tree last week. I was able to dig those up and reuse them today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>chillin with Travis and them</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/04/30/chillin-with-travis-and-them/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 17:39:23 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/04/30/chillin-with-travis-and-them/</guid>
      <description>17:39 Tuesday 30 April 2019 JST Today Lin and I drove to Travis and Yumi&amp;rsquo;s place to hang out with them and Sakura. Johan was already there and Deji came a bit later. Nice to see everyone again, though in some ways it&amp;rsquo;s like the tribe is getting smaller (and larger!)
No BBQ today due to rain, but we made 手巻き with chicken, eggs, salad, and then ice cream at the end.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>free bus ride with babychan</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/02/17/free-bus-ride-with-babychan/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2018 21:17:27 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/02/17/free-bus-ride-with-babychan/</guid>
      <description>21:17 Saturday 17 February 2018 JST After work today, Lin and I met at the station and as a little &amp;ldquo;romantic&amp;rdquo; gift, I bought reserved seats so we could take Romance Car to our station. It was nice to just be able to relax all the way home. Curiously, when Lin tried to pay for my bus fare, it wouldn&amp;rsquo;t go through so the driver just let us on the bus free.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shimoda Weekend</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/11/07/shimoda-weekend/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2017 13:39:45 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/11/07/shimoda-weekend/</guid>
      <description>13:39 Tuesday 07 November 2017 JST Okay it&amp;rsquo;s been a couple days, but we had a lovely weekend in Shimoda. So glad that Lin joined us! She said she had a great time. The weekend schedule was kinda freestyle, which caused a bit of consternation for some, but did not affect things too badly. I enjoyed getting to know everyone a bit better.
Yoga on Saturday morning was originally led by Lisa, but turned into acro yoga with people being angels, superman, partners, flippers, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>today</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/09/12/today/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2017 23:57:26 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/09/12/today/</guid>
      <description>23:57 Tuesday 12 September 2017 JST Just got home via taxi with Lin after eating ice cream with her near our station. I got Ben and Jerry&amp;rsquo;s cotton candy (which was similar to Baskin Robbin&amp;rsquo;s Popping Shower), and she got cherry by some other premium brand, the name of which escapes me now.
Lin and I took the same train from Noborito to our station. She had gotten on near Shinjuku, and we did not specifically plan to take the same train, but it worked out that way.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>