<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>fix on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/fix/</link>
    <description>Recent content in fix on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2019 07:46:38 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/fix/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How Netlify helped me fix my website</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/09/25/how-netlify-helped-me-fix-my-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2019 07:46:38 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/09/25/how-netlify-helped-me-fix-my-website/</guid>
      <description>My website stopped working recently. More accurately, Hugo stopped rendering the /blog and /journal portions of my website. The last time it worked was 2 weeks ago. I noticed that my local version of Hugo had gotten updated (*) and checked the releases.. sure enough there was a change to something related to that I had tweaked regarding indices.
The problem languished for a while until I remembered that Netlify allows choosing which version of Hugo to use.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>reboot fixed USB yay</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/09/23/reboot-fixed-usb-yay/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2019 06:20:40 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/09/23/reboot-fixed-usb-yay/</guid>
      <description>Actually I am writing this before the reboot. Let&amp;rsquo;s see&amp;hellip;
17:39 next day The reboot didn&amp;rsquo;t help, but turning off one of my USB cameras helped. Hard to know what is causing the issue.
It seems like it might be this USB 4-splitter I got. What types of things would cause it to suddenly fail?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Joel (hopefully) fixed MT3 website top banner</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/09/17/joel-hopefully-fixed-mt3-website-top-banner/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2018 18:08:56 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/09/17/joel-hopefully-fixed-mt3-website-top-banner/</guid>
      <description>18:08 Monday 17 September 2018 JST I chatted with Joel today after doing a livestream on Facebook about work-life-balance. He tweaked the theme for Marble Track 3 to fix the jumbotron at the top! Super awesome. Going to try it out now.
Original:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fixed my jetlag</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/16/fixed-my-jetlag/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2017 07:29:30 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/16/fixed-my-jetlag/</guid>
      <description>07:29 Saturday 16 December 2017 -02 Good morning from São Paulo! My jetlag seems fine, though we are in a timezone opposite that of Japan, where it is 6:30pm Saturday according to https://time.is/Tokyo
My techique is to switch my clocks to my destination time as soon as I get onto the airplane, and then sleep or stay awake during the flight according to the target schedule.
The more timezones changed, the longer the flight and therefore more time available to do the switch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fixed AB site issue that got delayed</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/21/fixed-ab-site-issue-that-got-delayed/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/21/fixed-ab-site-issue-that-got-delayed/</guid>
      <description>##12:16 Friday 21 November 2014 JST##
I finished the request that was made in August. It took close to 12 hours + 3 months. Oops.
Though the repo is currently private, the git hash is 04d5f55b8f0fcb3508920331858df0f89dee745e, in case someone comes across it later.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>