<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>back on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/back/</link>
    <description>Recent content in back on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 08:30:57 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/back/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>back in Japan</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/04/05/back-in-japan/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 08:30:57 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/04/05/back-in-japan/</guid>
      <description>08:30 Friday 05 April 2019 JST Back in Japan as of Wednesday and still a bit jet lagged. Today I plan to call AB and get back in the groove with them.
I have been reading Urbit docs and considering starting one of my planets on my local machine here. Gotta get that figured out before I try to start my star, ~wanbus.
Lesson in Akihabara was fine last night.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>back in Tokyo</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/13/back-in-tokyo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Mar 2018 16:02:27 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/13/back-in-tokyo/</guid>
      <description>16:02 Tuesday 13 March 2018 JST Back in Japan now, on a bus headed to Tokyo from Narita airport. This bus is cheap and does not include electrical outlets like some airport trains do, but I have a bit of charge available on my computer (74% (was 79% when I started))
Ah; I can write Japanese for my lesson on Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>getting back to work in 2018</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/10/getting-back-to-work-in-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2018 08:44:46 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/10/getting-back-to-work-in-2018/</guid>
      <description>08:44 Wednesday 10 January 2018 JST I worked yesterday for the first time in 2018. Monday was a holiday, and my
13:41 Wednesday 10 January 2018 JST I am on the train and the above is as far as I got before sidetracking myself with something before having a meeting with TY at 9am then lunch with Lin.
Today:
 I got my AWS account switched to JPY instead of USD so I can pay more efficiently.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Headed back</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/01/18/headed-back/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/01/18/headed-back/</guid>
      <description>##09:40 Monday 19 January 2015 JST##
We ate at Gusto yesterday morning, where I got some mushroom + rice soup. Mark asked how it was and I go, &amp;ldquo;It tastes like&amp;hellip; mushroom soup&amp;rdquo; and Asuka added, &amp;ldquo;with rice,&amp;rdquo; which I really appreciated her dry sense of humor. (is &amp;ldquo;dry&amp;rdquo; the right term?)
Sumiyaki left before the rest of us; he has to work on Sundays.
Mark, Asuka, and I walked back toward the contact site, and up a short ridge that looked down on the area.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>