<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>health on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/health/</link>
    <description>Recent content in health on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2019 15:29:42 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/health/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Brain pounding eyes vibrating too much computer</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/09/03/brain-pounding-eyes-vibrating-too-much-computer/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2019 15:29:42 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/09/03/brain-pounding-eyes-vibrating-too-much-computer/</guid>
      <description>Last night when I finally went to sleep around 11 pm my brain was pounding headachey and my eyes were vibrating in a strange way like, not in a good way.
I chalk it up to too much time spent on my computer.
it kept me awake for a while, but I was finally able to calm myself down into sleep.
I&amp;rsquo;m on my way to the dentist now, recording this with voice transcription.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Headed to Nathans Dentist</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/09/03/headed-to-nathans-dentist/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2019 14:54:20 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/09/03/headed-to-nathans-dentist/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m headed to Nathan&amp;rsquo;s dentist which is now my dentist.
I like this dentist because he didn&amp;rsquo;t waste time checking my teeth three (3) appointments in a row without doing anything.
First appointment: &amp;ldquo;I recommend you fix this; wanna do it now?&amp;rdquo;
Yes!
16:49 He worked on two teeth, and best I can understand, he filled a filling on the left lower third from back tooth, which also suffers from gum disease (receding gum).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>fasted yesterday</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/09/02/fasted-yesterday/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2019 07:55:10 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/09/02/fasted-yesterday/</guid>
      <description>07:55 Monday 02 September 2019 JST After having eaten extra ice cream and stuff late at night on the 31st, I fasted yesterday. Pretty easy, though I worked out at SOGO. Usually that would make me woozy if I hadn&amp;rsquo;t eaten, but yesterday seemed fine.
I have a bit of a headache now, which may be related to fast, or eat, or not enough water, or upcoming (first) session with Dean</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>health update</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/05/11/health-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 May 2018 11:20:51 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/05/11/health-update/</guid>
      <description>6 May or so 2018 I got a weird bump on my leg. Doctor gave some antibiotics.
  
11:20 Friday 11 May 2018 JST Today is my first health update my journal. I&amp;rsquo;m actually writing via voice recognition because I am not supposed to use my left wrist right now.
I went to the clinic and the doctor took x-rays and said there is some calcification on the bones in my wrist.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ate after 10pm last night</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/02/22/ate-after-10pm-last-night/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2018 09:02:06 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/02/22/ate-after-10pm-last-night/</guid>
      <description>09:02 Thursday 22 February 2018 JST Yeah so last night against my better judgement, I ate at night. I mean it wasn&amp;rsquo;t a ton, but maybe 1&amp;frasl;2 kg, including a bunch of sugar.
This morning my stomach is like &amp;ldquo;ugh with a big fat ball of fat&amp;rdquo;
Lin felt about the same, so I made a contract with her to not eat after 9pm, 32 times in the next 38 days.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>