<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>reiki on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/reiki/</link>
    <description>Recent content in reiki on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Nov 2015 19:49:42 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/reiki/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Fun day at reiki and wandering around Asakusa</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/11/08/fun-day-at-reiki-and-wandering-around-asakusa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Nov 2015 19:49:42 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/11/08/fun-day-at-reiki-and-wandering-around-asakusa/</guid>
      <description>19:49 Sunday 08 November 2015 JST We attended a reiki share in Asakusa, featuring a reiki master from Kyoto. He was quite friendly and chatty, both in English and Japanese. It was the second time or Lin and I to join this particular reiki share.
Afterward, we wandered around Asakusa with Jon, had sushi at a 回転 sushi shop, went to an English book store where we bought a total of three books, and then walked to Tokyo Sky Tree where I got a bunch of gifts for Fred (in a pay-by-the-container system).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>reiki class</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/04/24/reiki-class/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2015 16:23:28 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/04/24/reiki-class/</guid>
      <description>16:23 Friday 24 April 2015 JST Just said bye to Tomoko after reiki class in Matsudo. We took the same train from Matsudo to Kita-Senju and now I&amp;rsquo;m headed back to Ye Olde Kawasaki, though this train terminates in Shinagawa. I imagine I could have waited longer in Matsudo in order to get a seat all the way, but there were no such trains on the marquee when we left.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reiki meetup in Matsudo</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/01/25/reiki-meetup-in-matsudo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/01/25/reiki-meetup-in-matsudo/</guid>
      <description>##16:09 Sunday 25 January 2015 JST##
Thanks to Nobuko for organizing a Reiki class, and thanks to Meetup for showing it to me. It&amp;rsquo;s nice to reconnect with Reiki energy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Going to Reiki workshop</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/12/13/going-to-reiki-workshop/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/12/13/going-to-reiki-workshop/</guid>
      <description>##11:27 Saturday 13 December 2014 JST##
Via meetup.com, I found a reiki group. They&amp;rsquo;ve had 37 meetups so far; this will be my first to join.
##5pm
Had a good time chatting with Nobuko and Keiko; essentially the event was canceled because the space was taken over by some event.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>