<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>swuusi on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/swuusi/</link>
    <description>Recent content in swuusi on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Aug 1998 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/swuusi/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>nominating committee</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/08/02/nominating-committee/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Aug 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/08/02/nominating-committee/</guid>
      <description>I made the district nominating committee!
Date:Sun, 02 Aug 98 19:24:52 CDT From:Penny Ramsdale Subject:RE: SWD Nomination Committee To:rob nugen   Rob, I wanted to tell you that you have been elected by the district board to the district nominating committee. Congratulations, and thank you again for being willing to serve! __________ is chairperson of the nominating committee, and she will let you know what needs to happen when. I will be sending an e-mail to everyone on the new committee soon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>swuusi 1998 completion</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/07/31/swuusi-1998-completion/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/07/31/swuusi-1998-completion/</guid>
      <description>SWUUSI
12:13pm Friday 31 July 1998
transcribed from my diary Welp, we&#39;re on the way back home from SWUUSI. I was kinda in a grouchy mood when I woke up this morning after missing the talent show last night. Fricke et.al. had written a song for SWUUSI and fuck I missed it and they are graduating. But I felt way better with all the love and hugs and happy happy joy joy throughout the camp, and signing mugbooks and taking pictures and all the fun.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>swuusi 1998 Worship</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/07/31/swuusi-1998-worship/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/07/31/swuusi-1998-worship/</guid>
      <description>SWUUSI
3am Friday 31 July 1998
transcribed from my diary I got super hugs when I went back to the main cabin after &#34;my first shower since Sunday morning!&#34; &#34;Yay Rob!&#34; and hugs all around. Played koosh with Clark, Jessica, Nathan Sexton, and Bryn and others before dinner. Gave advisors Mary Angel and Dorian back massages and then it was time for worship. I had been asked to lead a senior circle through some type of guided mediation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>swuusi 1998 social</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/07/30/swuusi-1998-social/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/07/30/swuusi-1998-social/</guid>
      <description>SWUUSI
early Thursday 30 July 1998
transcribed from my diary Super tired waking up this morning but opening circle and then breakfast was good pancakes and stuff then I couldn&#39;t stay awake for Drake&#39;s Theme Workshop so I went back to bed. Woke up for lunch around 2pm, missing &#34;Whack The YAC&#34; which I didn&#39;t entirely mind since I didn&#39;t want to get whacked, whatever that might entail. Then the themed Gansta Lunch, serving Soup Doggie Dog, Method Manwich, Notorious BLT, and to drink Wu-Tang and Ice-T with Ice Cubes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>swuusi 1998 visitors</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/07/30/swuusi-1998-visitors/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/07/30/swuusi-1998-visitors/</guid>
      <description>SWUUSI
7pm Thursday 30 July 1998
transcribed from my diary Wow holy cow went to breakfast and then Drake&#39;s workshop and back to the cabin and was just about to hop into the shower when someone walked in. I went to see who it was: a woman, a new face, so I said &#34;HI&#34; and then realized holy cow it&#39;s Karen!! big big big hugs and we briefed one another on our respective weeks so far and sat down to talk and stuff and after about 5 or 8 minutes she said simply, &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>swuusi 1998 dorian</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/07/28/swuusi-1998-dorian/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/07/28/swuusi-1998-dorian/</guid>
      <description>SWUUSI
11pm Tuesday 28 July 1998
transcribed from my diary During Sean&#39;s Hair and Foot Washing Workshop, I got my hair washed by Anna Magwood and Katy Robinson and my feet washed by Josh Voyles. The nurturing attention was wonderful. I was pretty well sunburned today with all my time spent at the lake, even though I started the day with SPF 50. Maybe it wasn&#39;t as waterproof as I hoped.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>swuusi 1998 geology</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/07/28/swuusi-1998-geology/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/07/28/swuusi-1998-geology/</guid>
      <description>SWUUSI
4pm Tuesday 28 July 1998
transcribed from my diary Missed Spirit Circle tody and I certainly didn&#39;t want to do that; I had wanted to compliment the youth on how well they are drinking plenty of water and to keep it up. I did make breakfast though, and then Drake Baer (theme speaker) workshop, during which I wrote a mythical story about how The Feel Good Net got started. Morning workshops and then I went swimming from 1:25pm to essentially now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>swuusi 1998 water</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/07/28/swuusi-1998-water/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/07/28/swuusi-1998-water/</guid>
      <description>SWUUSI
2:30am Tuesday 28 July 1998
transcribed from my diary This morning, Jason and I played lots in the lake again, chicken fights and acrobatics of whatever sort we could come up with including Jessica on Jason&#39;s shoulders while Jason on my shoulders. We tried some 6-person pyramids, but couldn&#39;t get them to work. We played keep away from Maia with Maia&#39;s hat and sunglasses. Actually I did play a bit, but tried to keep the group to remain respectful of her stuff.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>swuusi 1998 scorpion</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/07/27/swuusi-1998-scorpion/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jul 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/07/27/swuusi-1998-scorpion/</guid>
      <description>SWUUSI
am Monday 27 July 1998
transcribed from my diary The same night after Jessica hit her head and we sent her to bed, Elizabeth (an advisor) asked if I would shave the back of her head with my clippers. No problem! I clipped it as she requested and was walking in the dark toward the bushes to throw it away when BAM!! something clamped onto my toe and burning poison seared through like red hot electrocuting pliers biting through OHMYGOD that hurts get-it-off-get-it-off and I scraped my foot upside down to knock off whatever animal had so effectively stung me DAMN!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>swuusi 1998 hydrator</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/07/26/swuusi-1998-hydrator/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jul 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/07/26/swuusi-1998-hydrator/</guid>
      <description>SWUUSI
6:45pm Sunday 26 July 1998
transcribed from my diary I am the Head Hydrator. I got the job after taking it upon myself to hand people glasses of water with a simple smile and, &#34;drink this.&#34; I like the job because the youth really appreciate it when I give them water even before they realize how much they want it. Or before they can work up the energy to get up in this heat and get it for themselves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>swuusi 1998 jessica</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/07/26/swuusi-1998-jessica/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jul 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/07/26/swuusi-1998-jessica/</guid>
      <description>SWUUSI
11pm Sunday 26 July 1998
transcribed from my diary After dinner I watched youth swim, but I didn&#39;t swim at first since I hadn&#39;t brought my swim trunks to the lake. (it was a 7 minute walk each direction from the camp to the lake) I went and got my trunks and Jason Fricke and I had fun wrestling and goofing around in the water. At one point we were standing back to back with our arms interlocked and trying to essentially do flips while staying in this position.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>swuusi 1998 travel</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/07/26/swuusi-1998-travel/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jul 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/07/26/swuusi-1998-travel/</guid>
      <description>SWUUSI
am Sunday 26 July 1998
transcribed from my diary After saying HI and bye to Amanda, and being up on my computer I went to bed at 4am and slept 30 minutes until Wende called. During that sleep I experienced my soul perfectly existing in this continuous moment. Beautiful. Wende said she was coming right over and she finally came over so very much later than I wanted and she wanted me to take some boxes to my back porch to be recycled and I ran to do it so as to not be late and holy shit I lost my toe ring.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SWUUSI by Maia Cudhea</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/07/25/swuusi-by-maia-cudhea/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jul 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/07/25/swuusi-by-maia-cudhea/</guid>
      <description>1998 SWUUSI Review by Maia Cudhea
  i can&#39;t believe no one reviewed swuusi. so i&#39;ll do it belatedly. okay, here&#39;s what i remember several months later. i got to camp really late saturday night, and the rest of staff was way already there. my hair was all done up from my sister&#39;s wedding (why i was late) and i was so tired. so we had this quick meeting and said we&#39;d do everything else tomorrow and i went to sleep on a table.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SWUUSI</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1997/08/02/swuusi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 1997 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1997/08/02/swuusi/</guid>
      <description>1997 SWUUSI review by Rob   SWUUSI 1997 by Rob
 26 July 1997  Drove up here after Bobby, Erika, and Nathan drove to Houston and spent the night at our apartment. Altogether we had Me, Jason Fricke, Mike Noyse, Bobby Hall, Erika Hewitt, and Nathan Ryan. Stopped a couple times along the way and Nathan needed a white t-shirt, so we stopped in at Albertson&amp;rsquo;s in Denton. Found a package that was open, so we got two shirts for two bucks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SWUUSI by Dane Dormio</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1997/08/02/swuusi-by-dane-dormio/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 1997 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1997/08/02/swuusi-by-dane-dormio/</guid>
      <description>1997 SWUUSI review by Dane Dormio   Saturday
7/26/96
10:06 pm
  SWUUSI hasn&#39;t even started, but I&#39;ve already had a lot of fun. After a relatively short trip, I got here at about 4:00 pm. I came early because my mom&#39;s on staff. There was a staff meeting going on when we arrived, but I passed the time talking with Nathan Ryan, who was in the same predicament as me.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>