<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>git on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/git/</link>
    <description>Recent content in git on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2019 06:22:49 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/git/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>rewrote history of journal entry commit messages</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/06/17/rewrote-history-of-journal-entry-commit-messages/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2019 06:22:49 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/06/17/rewrote-history-of-journal-entry-commit-messages/</guid>
      <description>06:22 Monday 17 June 2019 JST I wanted to swap the commas a bit so I rewrote the commit messages with git rebase 68a8c08. Now the top of git log --oneline --graph --decorate --all looks like this (sans colorization):
* 7dc0917 (HEAD -&amp;gt; master) back * 10b1b54 some, * 35be077 well, * 0bd1c8b several | * 84efab7 (norigin/master, github/master, bitbucket/master) some | * 143640e well, | * a8b25db several, |/ * 68a8c08 years * 34b1460 ago * b62b05e when * 8f33818 he * 7ce3602 was  After writing this, I started composing a message on english.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>fixed my site</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/09/14/fixed-my-site/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 16:12:02 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/09/14/fixed-my-site/</guid>
      <description>16:12 Friday 14 September 2018 JST I broke my upload process, but I think it is fixed now.
Yep. It took 65 seconds to process and upload to my server, but it works.
When trying to get that number down, to a few seconds, I mis-remembered how it was set up and destroyed the public/ directory of my Hugo-controlled site thinking Hugo can rebuild it, but since the Hugo directory is already a Git repo, it was conflating the two, and things got really confuzzed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>git out</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/19/git-out/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2018 00:15:53 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/19/git-out/</guid>
      <description>00:15 Thursday 19 April 2018 JST  39c7bfa recent entries 17a339c removed : from titles 70ec6d3 TEMPoRARY commit, not including all years, and not cleaned up filenames 6086901 Added README 354c77e (bitbucket/master) p 1fbcd35 s c385ebb colon 492f2fc slash 3b91dec slash 40ba10c w ce5271f w 8be74d2 w afebd29 dot  The above shows a weird thing that happened to my git repo while I was messing with Fossil. The commit 6086901 is the first, and the commit 354c77e is the last, but it was shown right in a row.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>today</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/18/today/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2018 10:22:13 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/18/today/</guid>
      <description>10:22 Wednesday 18 April 2018 JST New regular students in SS lesson this morning; Kaede stopped coming relatively soon after joining last year, and Chika apparently took my bitcoin advice (whereas I did not haha) so she moved overseas. Satoshi has not come recently, and Sayuri said she was busy today, plus said Ayano something something so could not come. Nonoka and Ai came today. Ai helped Nonoka with some phrases and months of the year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>wow wow fossil is awesome</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/11/wow-wow-fossil-is-awesome/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 10:58:04 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/11/wow-wow-fossil-is-awesome/</guid>
      <description>10:58 Wednesday 11 April 2018 JST Fossil is awesome, but I am not ready to switch quite yet.
Can I get Fossil to host my journal like I have Hugo doing now? Should I? The point was to have it as a static site, so I guess not, but it seems weird to use something that can host sites just to track the site content and not host the site.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>git commit -m commit</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/11/25/git-commit-m-commit/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Nov 2017 17:33:39 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/11/25/git-commit-m-commit/</guid>
      <description> 17:33 Saturday 25 November 2017 JST git commit -m commit  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>git is neat</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/06/22/git-is-neat/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2016 21:31:32 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/06/22/git-is-neat/</guid>
      <description>21:31 Wednesday 22 June 2016 JST I created a subdirectory in my git repo, initiated a git repo in it, then added the subdirectory to the parent repo. Boom it looks like it&amp;rsquo;s a submodule.
Hmm but wait it&amp;rsquo;s not listed in the parent git repo&amp;rsquo;s config file. hmmm.
git is still neat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Netlify doesn&#39;t git clone --recursive</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/03/03/netlify-doesnt-git-clone-recursive/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2015 22:25:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/03/03/netlify-doesnt-git-clone-recursive/</guid>
      <description>##22:25 Tuesday 03 March 2015 JST##
I got my repos sorted today; all the journal entries have had frontmatter lobotomies if Middleman can&amp;rsquo;t deal with the different dates, and my main Middleman repo includes the journal entry repo as a submodule.
However, turns out netlify doesn&amp;rsquo;t clone recursively (yet). I mentioned this to Mathias and he was like, &amp;ldquo;hmm you&amp;rsquo;re right&amp;rdquo; and said he would look into it. But, he said politely, he was planning to go home for the night and didn&amp;rsquo;t want to push any possibly-breaking changes before going to bed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>done today</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/02/23/done-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2015 23:07:37 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/02/23/done-today/</guid>
      <description>23:07 Monday 23 February 2015 JST Today I made a repo to help find particular md5 strings for Counting with md5sum. It&amp;rsquo;s my live md5 command line cheater.
Also gave 10000 bit tip to a man who announced his wife was pregnant.
And am working on a maze for Angelos, and printed a logo for a photo at Shibuya Crossing tomorrow.
Okay good night!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Broke the crap out of my local hakyll repo</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/02/19/broke-the-crap-out-of-my-local-hakyll-repo/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2015 17:36:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/02/19/broke-the-crap-out-of-my-local-hakyll-repo/</guid>
      <description>##17:36 Thursday 19 February 2015 JST##
Oops.
I thought it would be a good idea to hardcode my directory into my Hakyll binary, so now, until I remember how to build the Hakyll binary, I have to have it work from the ~/journal directory. However, I now want my ~/journal directory to be my new repo consisting of only journal entries.
I moved the Hakyll version of ~/journal to ~/journal-hakyll and moved my real journal to ~/journal, then added ~/journal as a subrepository of the Hakyll journal in ~/hakyll-journal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>install.sh</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/26/install.sh/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/26/install.sh/</guid>
      <description>##20:35 Wednesday 26 November 2014 JST##
I spent most of the day working on installing a website from git; it has symlinks to a config directory and a vendor directory. We&amp;rsquo;re not just updating an existing directory, but cloning the repo from git each time.
I made a little install.sh file:
#!/bin/bash read -p &amp;quot;This will install the latest version from git!! Are you sure? (n) &amp;quot; -n 1 if [[ !</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>