<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>fack on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/fack/</link>
    <description>Recent content in fack on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2017 17:50:49 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/fack/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>timing</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/10/29/timing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2017 17:50:49 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/10/29/timing/</guid>
      <description>17:50 Sunday 29 October 2017 JST I don’t know why all this shit is piling up and the timing got fucked up so I lost 2 hours today. Lin is fighting with her family because they are doing shit that reminds her of old shit. I am supposed to be doing shit for work but cannot concentrate with her being so loud talking to her family about how crazy her family is.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>good i-group</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/10/12/good-i-group/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2017 14:09:20 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/10/12/good-i-group/</guid>
      <description>14:09 Thursday 12 October 2017 JST Great I-group today; I had chills from within when I got to yell at my dad from when I was 7 years old.
He said &amp;ldquo;if there were 100 people from your class all in a line, you would be the smartest.&amp;rdquo;
He meant it well, but it&amp;rsquo;s like hey fuck you don&amp;rsquo;t put that on a 7 year old! what is he going to do with that info?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>holy shit what a morning</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/06/06/holy-shit-what-a-morning/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2017 09:13:19 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/06/06/holy-shit-what-a-morning/</guid>
      <description>09:13 Tuesday 06 June 2017 JST Lin cooked lovely breakfast for me, by cooking an egg into some already-made vegetable soup.
The soup was too hot to eat immediately (because it had just been boiling), and it reminded me of all the times she has reheated food to scalding temperature.
From my point of view, the food is already cooked; there is no reason to reheat it at all, much less beyond the point that it can be eaten.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>