<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>liliko on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/liliko/</link>
    <description>Recent content in liliko on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2019 17:05:31 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/liliko/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Two lessons at SCC</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/09/12/two-lessons-at-scc/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2019 17:05:31 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/09/12/two-lessons-at-scc/</guid>
      <description>Had an hour lesson with Liliko, during which we double checked the English for an AI game they are developing. For some reason they keep asking for confirmation of stuff on paper but it has gotten to the point that we would prefer to see the real thing in action in order to really make sure it&amp;rsquo;s all correct.
Also had a lesson with Azusa, during which we clarified some of her translation into English, changing the word &amp;ldquo;become&amp;rdquo; into &amp;ldquo;because&amp;rdquo; and stuff like replacing &amp;ldquo;addition and multiplication are done by turning the handle outside&amp;rdquo; with &amp;ldquo;to add and multiply numbers, we turn the handle clockwise,&amp;rdquo; partially because she could not consistently say &amp;ldquo;multiplication.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>good lessons at SCC</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/08/08/good-lessons-at-scc/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2019 17:05:58 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/08/08/good-lessons-at-scc/</guid>
      <description>17:05 Thursday 08 August 2019 JST Liliko and I talked about the best way to support one of her staff who wants to guide tours in English, but does not yet have the basics of English conversation down. In the past some guides just straight memorize the scripts but do not fully understand what they are saying. We are trying to avoid that if possible. I suggested er-central.com and mylanguageexchange.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>lessons at SCC</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/02/21/lessons-at-scc/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Feb 2019 17:29:51 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/02/21/lessons-at-scc/</guid>
      <description>17:29 Thursday 21 February 2019 JST Today (and most Thursdays) I taught at SCC in Kawasaki. Naoko reviewed for her test next week. Yasu reviewed the same material for his test sometime in the future. Azusa did much better with her fluency and intonation for her presentation. Liliko asked about the brochure that has to change soon to accomodate new opening times.
After the lessons I went to say HI to Tomoko and Midori, but Midori had the day off.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>headed to work at SCC</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/26/headed-to-work-at-scc/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2018 12:55:17 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/26/headed-to-work-at-scc/</guid>
      <description>12:55 Friday 26 January 2018 JST Three hours of lessons in SCC today; looking forward to it!
On the way there, I hope to figure out why my local version of mypowercircle.org will not compile with Hugo. bah. it was supposed to be easy!!
Ah. I had gotten stuck trying to add Japanese language version of the site, but never got it working. It&amp;rsquo;s better to just have an actual Japanese speaker make the Japanese site, so I cut out the Japanese content from the site and now it&amp;rsquo;s working again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>five hours of work at SCC</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/13/five-hours-of-work-at-scc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2018 02:33:31 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/13/five-hours-of-work-at-scc/</guid>
      <description>02:33 Saturday 13 January 2018 JST Today was the first time I worked five hours at SCC. Due to a schedule snafu, 1.5 hours with Liliko chatting about her trip to Sydney and my trip to OZ, then Rick and Morty and Lucifer. I didn&amp;rsquo;t think of Dirk Gently, but she considered getting Netflix to see the others.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>