<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>con-con on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/con-con/</link>
    <description>Recent content in con-con on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Aug 1998 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/con-con/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>ConCon first am</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/08/04/concon-first-am/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Aug 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/08/04/concon-first-am/</guid>
      <description>Con Con
11:30am Tuesday 4 August 1998

transcribed from my diary
Woke up and read part of Shield and talked to Torger and Galen and others on staff out on our cabin porch. Then breakfast and sat at the same table with mostly the same group as dinner last night. We talked and chilled a bit and bounced a plastic ring from a coke bottle plastic cap. At the Spirt Circle I sat between Carol and Jeremy who sang &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kathryn</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/08/04/kathryn/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Aug 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/08/04/kathryn/</guid>
      <description>Con Con
4pm Tuesday 4 August 1998

transcribed from my diary
Lunch then chilled and we had a fire drill, bringing everyone to the volley ball court downhill from all the cabins. The fire drill was also a sneaky way to get us all assembled for a big ConCon group photo (which I should most certainly scan and put on the web!) for which Jeremy sat on my shoulders. Then I arrived late for the adult check-in meeting but it was all good and afterward I said HI and talked to Kathryn, advisor from this area.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Airplane to ConCon</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/08/03/airplane-to-concon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Aug 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/08/03/airplane-to-concon/</guid>
      <description>Con Con
9:20am Monday 3 August 1998

transcribed from my diary
I&#39;m in seat 24A of Continental flight 1989 about to leave for ConCon. Celine Dion&#39;s &#34;My heart will go on&#34; is playing quietly over the speakers as two boys with English accents talk with their parents behind me, including &#34;if I sit heah, I con&#39;t see tha TV.&#34; This weekend I got all my planned activities complete, including transcribing all my SWUUSI journal entries, updating the Houston YRUU (pronounced &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>arrival ConCon</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/08/03/arrival-concon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Aug 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/08/03/arrival-concon/</guid>
      <description>Con Con arrival
11pm Monday 3 August 1998

transcribed from my diary
Arrived at the airport from Phoenix after 1 hour flight during which I slept most of the way. I woke at the end to see Ian F (I like the pun &#34;E &#39;n F&#34;) who I met at GA and his sister Kathleen. Bryan Beck said HI while we were waiting for baggage and then we sat with the pile of youth after collecting Ian and Kathleen&#39;s stuff.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flight to ConCon</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/08/03/flight-to-concon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Aug 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/08/03/flight-to-concon/</guid>
      <description>Con Con flyin there
Monday 3 August 1998

transcribed from my diary
On the ground below I can see huge block letters of green (trees?) on brown dirt background: LUECKI I wonder what the heck it means (city name?) or where it is... We&#39;ve been flying for about an hour and I&#39;m seeing some intricate roadways that look like an old circuit board. Pretty cool, but the weird thing is they don&#39;t see to go anywhere.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>