<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>michael on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/michael/</link>
    <description>Recent content in michael on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 23:56:03 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/michael/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>snack with Michael</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/04/30/snack-with-michael/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 23:56:03 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/04/30/snack-with-michael/</guid>
      <description>23:56 Tuesday 30 April 2019 JST At Mark&amp;rsquo;s suggestion, Michael and I ate at a restaurant in Noborito where we talked about Marble Track 3. I showed him the secret backend of Marble Track 3 where I have &amp;ldquo;episodes&amp;rdquo; showing the 300+ hours of livestreams for creating the animation of the construction..</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>with Kai and Mika met Mike at The Pink Cow</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/05/18/with-kai-and-mika-met-mike-at-the-pink-cow/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2018 08:06:12 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/05/18/with-kai-and-mika-met-mike-at-the-pink-cow/</guid>
      <description>08:06 Friday 18 May 2018 JST 昨日ピンクカウ美佳さんと佳依さんと会って楽しみました。　Had a good time chilling with Kai and Mika at The Pink Cow last night.
マイケルさんも会った。彼が世界の1番よくなバーテンダーでしたって。We also met Michael. He said he&amp;rsquo;s the worlds best bartender.
そうでもそうでもないわからないけど、彼と面白い話できた。I don&amp;rsquo;t know if that&amp;rsquo;s true, but we had a good time talking to him.
美佳さんと佳依さんと日本語でも英語でも喋りました。I spoke in Japanese and English with Kai and Mika.
戸からピンポン音はピッザヂリベリかたが来た。みんながびっくりした。笑 Everyone was surprised when we heard a knock at the door; it was a pizza delivery guy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shimoda Weekend</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/11/07/shimoda-weekend/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2017 13:39:45 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/11/07/shimoda-weekend/</guid>
      <description>13:39 Tuesday 07 November 2017 JST Okay it&amp;rsquo;s been a couple days, but we had a lovely weekend in Shimoda. So glad that Lin joined us! She said she had a great time. The weekend schedule was kinda freestyle, which caused a bit of consternation for some, but did not affect things too badly. I enjoyed getting to know everyone a bit better.
Yoga on Saturday morning was originally led by Lisa, but turned into acro yoga with people being angels, superman, partners, flippers, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>hung out with Michael near Noborito</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/09/09/hung-out-with-michael-near-noborito/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2017 00:08:05 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/09/09/hung-out-with-michael-near-noborito/</guid>
      <description>00:08 Saturday 09 September 2017 JST First time to hang out with Michael one on one. We ate at a cafe in the station and then went barefoot out on a balcony where we talked to a mom waiting for her kid to come back from school. Michael chatted with her a bit, introducing us.. I was kinda amazed because even though my Japanese is better, I&amp;rsquo;m not as willing to break the ice with people.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>