<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>lesson on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/lesson/</link>
    <description>Recent content in lesson on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2019 21:16:44 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/lesson/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Fun last lesson before vacation</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/10/02/fun-last-lesson-before-vacation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2019 21:16:44 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/10/02/fun-last-lesson-before-vacation/</guid>
      <description>Hide and Akiko from 7pm class each needed to make up some lessons, so stayed for the 8pm class featuring Misato and Tatsuya.
I think it worked pretty well; they had not met each other, and they are all pretty much similar personalities so I figured they would get along fine.
After self intros, most of the time they talked about Akiko&amp;rsquo;s challenging business trip to Hydrabad, India. Most of the rest of the time we talked about Hide&amp;rsquo;s work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Great lesson with Yuna</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/09/14/great-lesson-with-yuna/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2019 09:26:43 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/09/14/great-lesson-with-yuna/</guid>
      <description>(written 09:26 Saturday 14 September 2019 JST)
Today I was five minutes late to (teach) my lesson with Yuna; I excitedly told her about going to see 叶結（Kanauknot) today in 豊島園after having seen them in ぐりんぱ.
I was so excited that I explained &amp;ldquo;hh hh hh hh hh&amp;rdquo;, from The Castle of Dreams
I was so excited that for 30 minutes, this overshadowed my news about having done my first stand up comedy last night after being invited by Soness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>lesson with Akiko in CoCos</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/09/12/lesson-with-akiko-in-cocos/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2019 23:11:10 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/09/12/lesson-with-akiko-in-cocos/</guid>
      <description>(written 23:11 Thursday 12 September 2019 JST)
Akiko and I went to CoCo&amp;rsquo;s for our language exchange today and she helped me figure out how the EOS tea business works.
We each ordered drink bar for around 400 yen. As thanks for her business support today, I paid for hers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>lesson in Akihabara</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/05/09/lesson-in-akihabara/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2019 20:18:11 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/05/09/lesson-in-akihabara/</guid>
      <description>20:18 Thursday 09 May 2019 JST Today I showed students in Akihabara the website and snippets for Marble Track 3. They were like &amp;ldquo;waow&amp;rdquo; etc. I love the project and felt a bit guilty for taking up a significant amount of class time with it. We have had lessons for years though, so I don&amp;rsquo;t think they will mind.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>last lesson with Sweets Party Attendants</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/03/06/last-lesson-with-sweets-party-attendants/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2019 21:33:17 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/03/06/last-lesson-with-sweets-party-attendants/</guid>
      <description>21:33 Wednesday 06 March 2019 JST Today was the last lesson with Sweets Attendants. (Their office is being shut down at the end of this month, but I am leaving next week for three weeks overseas.)
I met Tomoko at CPK at 11am and helped her carry pizza to their office where we had a party, including candy I bought from the conveni ond 3F.
The party was fun, but afterward I unfortunately let myself get sidetracked into dealing with some work related Excel spreadsheet crap, but got it sorted out by moving the spreadsheet into Google Sheets, where I can use the =FILTER() function.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Second to last lesson with Sweets Party Attendants</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/02/13/second-to-last-lesson-with-sweets-party-attendants/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2019 21:26:23 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/02/13/second-to-last-lesson-with-sweets-party-attendants/</guid>
      <description>21:26 Wednesday 13 February 2019 JST Sweets Party Attendants had their second to last lesson with me today. The mood was both somber and joyful; it has been great working with them over the years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hanayama Marble at Wednesday morning lesson</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/10/31/hanayama-marble-at-wednesday-morning-lesson/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 09:16:11 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/10/31/hanayama-marble-at-wednesday-morning-lesson/</guid>
      <description>09:16 Wednesday 31 October 2018 JST The lessons I teach on Wednesday morning used to be on Thursday mornings. They were one of the first lessons I taught for JB. Pretty convenient when Lin and I lived near Kawasaki station, but now it takes over an hour to go each way for an hour lesson.
Once I win the lottery, this will be one of the first lessons I release because I have to leave the house by 5:45 to get a seat on the train on the way there (or leave by 6:15 and stand for 40 minutes total on (two) trains).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>morning lessons</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/09/18/morning-lessons/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 12:19:03 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/09/18/morning-lessons/</guid>
      <description>12:19 Tuesday 18 September 2018 JST Good lesson this morning with just two students. We talked about rental おっさん in Japan. Interesting concept of renting old men because they are older and presumably wiser. They? We?
Walked with Tariq from Akabanebashi to Shibashi while we talked about future plans for our swipe game. He found a designer who can create excellent graphics.
Did not end up needing my computer, but I have my rolly bag so no worries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>good lesson before holidays</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/23/good-lesson-before-holidays/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Apr 2018 09:57:28 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/23/good-lesson-before-holidays/</guid>
      <description>09:57 Monday 23 April 2018 JST Good lesson at IL this morning, though only two students attended. I praised the student who came 35 minutes late to thank her for attending even though it was apparently a challenge to join.
Next week&amp;rsquo;s lesson is canceled due to a week of holidays, so on May 7th, I will invite them to talk about their holidays in English.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>today</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/18/today/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2018 10:22:13 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/18/today/</guid>
      <description>10:22 Wednesday 18 April 2018 JST New regular students in SS lesson this morning; Kaede stopped coming relatively soon after joining last year, and Chika apparently took my bitcoin advice (whereas I did not haha) so she moved overseas. Satoshi has not come recently, and Sayuri said she was busy today, plus said Ayano something something so could not come. Nonoka and Ai came today. Ai helped Nonoka with some phrases and months of the year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>last lesson this session</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/09/last-lesson-this-session/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2018 14:21:38 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/09/last-lesson-this-session/</guid>
      <description>14:21 Monday 09 April 2018 JST Today was the last lesson for Ushigoro. We had finished up everything last week, having done their exams, so today we just did lots of Q and A sessions, first with the class split into two groups, and then with all students asking questions of one student.
I offered my LINE QR code in case they want to ask questions or continue practicing their English.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Great day</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/04/great-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Mar 2018 20:56:47 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/04/great-day/</guid>
      <description>20:56 Sunday 04 March 2018 JST Went to SOGO for workout with about 50 people in attendance. Great weather and great workout. I met Shell, Koji, Tyler, and others, but cannot remember now.
Went to lunch with Lisa at Laska and chatted with her a bit, and got to see a video of the type of dancing she is doing.
Went down to Tsujido for karaoke after recording video at karaoke with Kai, Mitsue, and Soness as the stars.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Akihabara for GG lesson</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/11/akihabara-for-gg-lesson/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2018 18:02:54 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/11/akihabara-for-gg-lesson/</guid>
      <description>18:02 Thursday 11 January 2018 JST Now I am in Akihabara, across the street from GG lesson which starts at 18:30.
I bought a trackball mouse to replace the one I had before which seems to just mysteriously and annoyingly not work anymore. This time I will keep the receipt because I think the old one konked out before its warranty was up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>two hour lesson with Tomoko</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/11/two-hour-lesson-with-tomoko/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2018 17:59:27 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/11/two-hour-lesson-with-tomoko/</guid>
      <description>17:59 Thursday 11 January 2018 JST Today was the first of five 2-hour lessons this month at SCC. Today I helped Tomoko by making corrections to her written English. She plans to present the features of some of her company&amp;rsquo;s products. Pretty cool stuff like elevators and batteries, and elevators that run on batteries. We studied up in their cafeteria on the 4th floor, and then I went down the escalator to the third floor and went out the exit I had never gone out before (but had seen many times).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>in Akihabara for last lesson of 2017</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/14/in-akihabara-for-last-lesson-of-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2017 17:54:40 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/14/in-akihabara-for-last-lesson-of-2017/</guid>
      <description>17:54 Thursday 14 December 2017 JST After working 3 hours (5 lessons) near Lazona, I&amp;rsquo;m eating cold lunch in Akihabara across the street from GG lesson. I have Lin&amp;rsquo;s sister&amp;rsquo;s heavy-as-hell suitcase. (Now I know why gorillas cannot break them)
19:41 Lesson was great; everyone was there! Yoko, Maki, and Atusko all brought sweets! Mayumi and Toshie both did homework!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>new style TS lessons</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/11/16/new-style-ts-lessons/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2017 17:56:10 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/11/16/new-style-ts-lessons/</guid>
      <description>17:56 Thursday 16 November 2017 JST Mutsumi introduced a new style lesson format where the guides sit down together with me instead of just having individual lessons. Hopefully this will help them improve listening skills by listening to other people have conversations in English.
I showed mt3s.robnugen.com to Miyako and Ayaka. Miyako showed me pics from her trip to the US with Haruka.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>lesson at TB</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/10/11/lesson-at-tb/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2017 17:34:45 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/10/11/lesson-at-tb/</guid>
      <description>13:54 Wednesday 11 October 2017 JST Good lesson today at TB; they had just redone the place so I got a grand tour of the show room. Midori talked to some clients while Tomoko gave me the tour. They didn&amp;rsquo;t have anything to check yet, but I saw lots of word-for-word translations which we will have to clean up later.
They actually had to leave 10 minutes earlier than normal, so I headed out at 1:50pm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1.5 hour lesson in Azabu Juban</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/10/02/1.5-hour-lesson-in-azabu-juban/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2017 12:54:30 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/10/02/1.5-hour-lesson-in-azabu-juban/</guid>
      <description>(written 12:54 Friday 06 October 2017 JST)
On Monday I got my bag back from ML, where I had left it the previous week while substituting on the 7th floor. I found out then that they have a show room and after I got my bag, I went to it. They have a lock which can be reset with one key and relocked with any 1 of another set of keys, which then becomes the only key which can unlock it (except the reset key, of course).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>first official NA lesson</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/09/25/first-official-na-lesson/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2017 10:14:06 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/09/25/first-official-na-lesson/</guid>
      <description>10:14 Monday 25 September 2017 JST NA is the two letter designation for a new lesson I will be teaching on Mondays. It is within walking distance of the Monday morning lesson, but there is a bit of a gap in between so I am chilling at a restaurant in Tokyo Tower.
15:35 Monday 25 September 2017 JST Lesson was tough at first when I tried terribly to explain my intention to the group of quietly patient students.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>lesson</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/08/03/lesson/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2017 21:25:43 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/08/03/lesson/</guid>
      <description>21:42 Thursday 03 August 2017 JST Hopefully I have learned all the lessons I need to learn from this situation. I considered documenting everything in my journal, or a gist,.. but a bunch of deleted lines in git will have to do.
Let&amp;rsquo;s just say &amp;ldquo;Buffer 03s-effect.md has shrunk a lot; auto save disabled in that buffer until next real save&amp;rdquo;
I am going to go meditate now to regain some sanity and hopefully shine some good light on all this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>internetty lesson</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/07/26/internetty-lesson/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2017 09:07:29 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/07/26/internetty-lesson/</guid>
      <description>09:07 Wednesday 26 July 2017 JST Lesson at Zavas featured a high level discussion of two different peering arrangements (p2p vs centralized) and the concept of protocols. I was planning to talk about Bitcoin, but the word &amp;ldquo;peer&amp;rdquo; in the whitepaper started the discussion we ended up having.
I had a distinct sense of inadequacy when describing layers of protocols that make up the internet, but that may be because when I hear the phrase &amp;ldquo;the internet&amp;rdquo; in my mind, my mind replies with &amp;ldquo;the internet is made of cats, the internet is made of cats, cats!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>tweaked Kai&#39;s presentation</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/07/24/tweaked-kais-presentation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2017 14:15:33 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/07/24/tweaked-kais-presentation/</guid>
      <description>14:15 Monday 24 July 2017 JST Met Kai today at 1pm to edit her presentation which she translated from Japanese. It was pretty decent actually, with just a few wonky sentence structures and some punctuation typos. It was so easy that it did not take the 2 hours we had allocated, but boom done in an hour sitting at (&amp;ldquo;Fresh like a box of _______ ______&amp;ldquo;) down near Azalea.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>new lesson</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/07/18/new-lesson/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 17:52:31 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/07/18/new-lesson/</guid>
      <description>17:52 Tuesday 18 July 2017 JST Met new students for a first lesson in Nihonbashi. Five beginner students who all seem pretty genki. Some are more beginner than others.
JB was there to do the introduction and everything went smoothly. See you guys again next week! &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m glad to hear that!&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>morning lesson</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/07/18/morning-lesson/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 09:04:57 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/07/18/morning-lesson/</guid>
      <description>9am Tuesday 18 July 2017 JST (written 17:54 Tuesday 18 July 2017 JST)
Lesson at Il was okay but not great. I had what I thought was a good plan, but it resulted in silence during the latter half. Hmmm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>late and early</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/12/19/late-and-early/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2016 19:40:28 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/12/19/late-and-early/</guid>
      <description>19:40 Monday 19 December 2016 JST I have Japanese lessons until 11:30pm tonight, and then have to leave the house at 6:30am tomorrow.
Tonight will be my first lesson with 文子先生, though I&amp;rsquo;m not sure if that&amp;rsquo;s the correct kanji for her name.
20:27 Monday 19 December 2016 JST Ah, it&amp;rsquo;s 史子.
23:33 Tuesday 20 December 2016 JST Fantastic lesson with 史子先生.
I&amp;rsquo;m not sure what the core difference is, but I somehow learned more than in my other lessons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>sweet suite</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/10/27/sweet-suite/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2016 18:25:50 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/10/27/sweet-suite/</guid>
      <description>18:25 Thursday 27 October 2016 JST I&amp;rsquo;m in Akihabara for my Thursday evening lesson, but some people are still in a meeting in the room where the lesson is usually held. One of the other students is here, so I imagine we will get to kick them out soon.
Because of my sweet drink, she asked if I like sweets / sweet drinks.
I started to explain the difference between the sweet adjective and sweets as nouns.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>lesson</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/10/03/lesson/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2016 09:21:11 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/10/03/lesson/</guid>
      <description>9:21 Monday 03 October 2016 JST Great lesson this morning. M and N each gave presentations on the voting age in Japan. We cleaned up the presentations and they got progressively more coherent, though still not perfect. This is the second week for us on the topic, so next week will be a new topic: compulsory vacation days in Japan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>lesson in Akihabara</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/09/29/lesson-in-akihabara/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2016 17:33:42 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/09/29/lesson-in-akihabara/</guid>
      <description>17:33 Thursday 29 September 2016 JST Now I&amp;rsquo;m headed to Akiba to teach as many as five students in one lesson.
I&amp;rsquo;m a bit tired because I was up a bit late adding the days old counter to my website.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>morning lesson</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/09/29/morning-lesson/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2016 07:48:47 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/09/29/morning-lesson/</guid>
      <description>07:48 Thursday 29 September 2016 JST Just met Tim at the clock in Kawasaki so he can cover for Matt here in what I call the Zavas building.
As predicted, our students are not yet here, but they still have 1 second by my.. nevermind, now they&amp;rsquo;re late.
09:11 Lesson was good; we somehow got onto the subject of web security; I encouraged them to use a password manager like Lastpass or 1Password</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>morning lesson</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/09/27/morning-lesson/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2016 10:10:48 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/09/27/morning-lesson/</guid>
      <description>10:10 Tuesday 27 September 2016 JST I taught a lesson this morning for Matt in Marunochi. Three students, relatively high level.
Here&amp;rsquo;s my report on the lesson:
 Topics included introductions (given that it was our first lesson together), differences in culture between the US and Japan, and (after the women left at 8:55 for an accounting class,) finance. The students did not have any books nor topics, so it might be valuable to have something available to give a bit of direction to the class.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SS lesson</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/09/20/ss-lesson/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2016 22:00:27 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/09/20/ss-lesson/</guid>
      <description>22:00 Tuesday 20 September 2016 JST Had lessons with Sarus Mama and Papa today in Shibuya. We set up Skype on Sarumama&amp;rsquo;s machine so she and I can skype next week. Then lesson with both of them again in two weeks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>good lesson</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/06/20/good-lesson/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2016 10:36:09 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/06/20/good-lesson/</guid>
      <description>10:36 Monday 20 June 2016 JST Had a good lesson with 3 students this morning; they are working on their presentations, and progressing quite nicely! Right now we are just memorizing, but in the future I will show them how to speak &amp;lsquo;off the cuff&amp;rsquo; about any topic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Good lesson with GG</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/06/16/good-lesson-with-gg/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2016 20:33:39 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/06/16/good-lesson-with-gg/</guid>
      <description>20:33 Thursday 16 June 2016 JST Today&amp;rsquo;s lesson with GG was Part II of hard drive disassembly. We opened the outer case in Part I, and have now opened the hard drive itself. &amp;ldquo;The platters are like mirrors!&amp;rdquo; and the warranty is officially void.
Headed home now on Odakyu Line from Shinjuku.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SS lesson canceled today</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/06/14/ss-lesson-canceled-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2016 07:55:44 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/06/14/ss-lesson-canceled-today/</guid>
      <description>07:55 Tuesday 14 June 2016 JST They told me weeks ago, and the timing is great; I wanna work on AB site instead!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>lesson with Mutsumi</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/03/08/lesson-with-mutsumi/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2016 21:49:36 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/03/08/lesson-with-mutsumi/</guid>
      <description>21:49 Tuesday 08 March 2016 JST Mutsumi told me she&amp;rsquo;d like to be pera pera in English by 2020 for the Olympics in Tokyo. I told her it&amp;rsquo;s quite a good goal and I&amp;rsquo;ll support her in doing it! The first (four) steps are to practice practice practice practice.
I told her I&amp;rsquo;m taking 3 Japanese lessons per week because I really wanna improve my Japanese (until I change my mind again　かな。。) but for now, fuckit, three lessons a week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SS lesson</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/03/01/ss-lesson/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2016 12:07:18 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/03/01/ss-lesson/</guid>
      <description>12:07 Tuesday 01 March 2016 JST At SS lesson, we described a picture, and practiced asking questions based on the descriptions. We then played a game where teams created questions for a new picture and then took turns asking as the other team answered (without looking at the picture).
That took most of the time. Focus was on correctly using is/are appropriately, and use of the phrase &amp;ldquo;at least&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Early lesson</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/02/16/early-lesson/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2016 08:46:48 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/02/16/early-lesson/</guid>
      <description>08:46 Tuesday 16 February 2016 JST Today at 9:30, I&amp;rsquo;m substitute teaching 6 9 students who are apparently up-n-coming stars or at least wannabe stars. There&amp;rsquo;s a non zero chance I might teach them again; we shall see!
I just need to stay awake until then! (I&amp;rsquo;m in a nearby convenience store.)
The class was fun! Their band is Silent Siren; we did an adjective-opposites game and then practiced English phrases they can use on stage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>pretty great GG lesson</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/01/21/pretty-great-gg-lesson/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2016 20:44:25 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/01/21/pretty-great-gg-lesson/</guid>
      <description>20:44 Thursday 21 January 2016 JST I&amp;rsquo;m enjoying my recent lessons a lot more by being more focused on having the students speak instead of correcting their errors. I pick out a few points perhaps, but basically allow them to chatter away as long as I can essentially understand what they mean.
Today with GG, I did the same exercise as I did down in Fukuura: gave instructions for drawing some lines, circles and dots.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Class with GG</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/01/07/class-with-gg/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2016 20:29:38 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/01/07/class-with-gg/</guid>
      <description>20:29 Thursday 07 January 2016 JST Extracted from emails to Mayumi:
Thank you for sending the lesson notes! I&#39;m glad you like yesterday&#39;s lesson style. I hope to give all of you more speaking time! If you think of any activities which might be fun, feel free to let me know. :-) I will be thinking of ways to make the lessons more interesting. one idea I have is to break up in pairs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Class with GG</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/01/07/class-with-gg/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2016 20:29:38 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/01/07/class-with-gg/</guid>
      <description>20:29 Thursday 07 January 2016 JST Extracted from emails to Mayumi:
At this point, I&#39;ve only solved one puzzle. I tried briefly to solve one of the others, but was unable to do so after a few minutes. But, more importantly, yes you guys certainly made great progress on the one I finished for you! It&#39;s a variant of one of my grandad&#39;s old puzzles. In a way, it&#39;s mathematically a variant of the round black puzzle I showed you (with pegs that move in and out).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GG lesson</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/12/17/gg-lesson/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Dec 2015 20:32:34 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/12/17/gg-lesson/</guid>
      <description>20:32 Thursday 17 December 2015 JST Good last lesson of the year with GG, featuring only M and Te because Y had to leave for a 忘年会 (end of year party).
Actually M was quite late, but she brought back the Digits in a Box puzzle, which I think I&amp;rsquo;ve written about before. She wasn&amp;rsquo;t able to solve it without looking it up online. I plan to give it to Fred not just unsolved, but without the containing box, so he won&amp;rsquo;t immediately know how small it can be made.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First lesson with N</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/12/17/first-lesson-with-n/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Dec 2015 16:48:10 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/12/17/first-lesson-with-n/</guid>
      <description>16:48 Thursday 17 December 2015 JST Met a new student who would like to practice presentations for his new business. When I heard that, I remembered all the times I&amp;rsquo;ve heard that before, and all the times the students have quickly given up. (80% ?)
I&amp;rsquo;d like to think it&amp;rsquo;s not completely my fault, but in any case, I have a good feeling about this particular person, except that he seems to have a pretty busy schedule, and would like to have lessons on an ad hoc basis, which I can imagine may become less and less frequent.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Good lesson for JB</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/12/16/good-lesson-for-jb/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2015 18:23:51 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/12/16/good-lesson-for-jb/</guid>
      <description>18:23 Wednesday 16 December 2015 JST Lesson tonight featured four students, including Bob, Michael, George, and Edgar, the English names of Yuta, Hirofumi, Ryo, and Masao. We reviewed &amp;ldquo;pumped&amp;rdquo; and Bob practiced answering &amp;ldquo;it was fine&amp;rdquo; for some questions of the form &amp;ldquo;how was (it)?&amp;rdquo; because when I asked &amp;ldquo;How was the party?&amp;rdquo; he originally answered, &amp;ldquo;I was fun.&amp;rdquo;
Homework will be for each of them to create something and bring it (or a picture) to show and talk about it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Headed to lesson for JB</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/12/02/headed-to-lesson-for-jb/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2015 15:54:15 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/12/02/headed-to-lesson-for-jb/</guid>
      <description>15:54 Wednesday 02 December 2015 JST Headed to lesson, bitching to Fred about Apple. He has lost a hard drive due to the same problem, but was able to recover it by sending to his local admins at UT.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First lesson in Tennozu Aisle</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/11/13/first-lesson-in-tennozu-aisle/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2015 21:20:37 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/11/13/first-lesson-in-tennozu-aisle/</guid>
      <description>21:20 Friday 13 November 2015 JST It was a trial lesson, and before the lesson started, I was pretty well set on not accepting it: I have to wear a suit; it&amp;rsquo;s on Friday night; etc.
But, it was fine; the students seem earnest, eager, etc.. plus it&amp;rsquo;s only a 3 month contract, so I can survive that long, じゃない？</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>last lesson かな</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/11/10/last-lesson-%E3%81%8B%E3%81%AA/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2015 10:59:28 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/11/10/last-lesson-%E3%81%8B%E3%81%AA/</guid>
      <description>10:59 Tuesday 10 November 2015 JST Today C indicated she would probably not join the lesson next time because she&amp;rsquo;s tired. I&amp;rsquo;m sorry to hear that; I imagine I could have done something different so that she would have enjoyed the lessons more, but maybe not.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GG lesson</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/07/30/gg-lesson/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2015 20:34:37 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/07/30/gg-lesson/</guid>
      <description>20:34 Thursday 30 July 2015 JST Talking about puzzles near the end of our lesson, I remembered the word puzzles with five houses, five owners, five colors, five pets, and five jobs.
Several clues are given and then the question: &amp;ldquo;Who likes fishing?&amp;rdquo; can be solved with a little logic.
SO, I attempted to create such a puzzle for GG, but with only 3 houses because I only had 5 minutes to do it:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>fourth of 4 lessons at JB</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/07/17/fourth-of-4-lessons-at-jb/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jul 2015 12:21:48 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/07/17/fourth-of-4-lessons-at-jb/</guid>
      <description>12:21 Saturday 18 July 2015 JST Last night I taught the fourth of four lessons at JB. I hope they&amp;rsquo;ll continue, but not sure, and will probably never know why, if not.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GG lesson</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/07/16/gg-lesson/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jul 2015 12:14:48 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/07/16/gg-lesson/</guid>
      <description>12:14 Saturday 18 July 2015 JST GG lesson that night featured a discussion of Airplane Day; they were all shocked to know three towers had fallen that day. I&amp;rsquo;m curious if they&amp;rsquo;ll do some research on their own. T told me after class she couldn&amp;rsquo;t believe it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kaori lesson</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/07/16/kaori-lesson/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jul 2015 12:07:42 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/07/16/kaori-lesson/</guid>
      <description>12:07 Saturday 18 July 2015 JST On Thursday, Kaori came to the lesson near Zavas in Kawasaki because no one else came. It seems she doesn&amp;rsquo;t like to come if anyone else attends. We talked about focused on a couple of grammar structures that were useful in the conversation, but I don&amp;rsquo;t remember what they were.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>lesson at hs</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/07/11/lesson-at-hs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jul 2015 09:44:45 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/07/11/lesson-at-hs/</guid>
      <description>09:44 Saturday 11 July 2015 JST I had the smart idea of making teams to create and ask questions instead of just boring-lecturing today&amp;rsquo;s topic. Two team captains self-selected and then chose the first 2 peeps on their team, and then I arbitrarily divided the rest so there would be no last person selected.
11:50am During the third hour, in which we were asked to talk about the new WTC complex, I spoke about the events on the day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>lesson at jhs</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/07/10/lesson-at-jhs/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2015 13:10:21 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/07/10/lesson-at-jhs/</guid>
      <description>13:10 Friday 10 July 2015 JST Just finished lunch with Kazu, Tony, Tomomi, Stuart, and Tyrell at a pizza place apparently rated the 2nd best pizza in Tokyo. I thought it was as good as CPK, but not as good as Star Pizza (of course!?) I had a four cheese pizza to myself, while the others shared things with spicey sauce, tomatos, meat, more meat, and some sea food.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>lesson in Akihabara</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/07/06/lesson-in-akihabara/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jul 2015 21:52:01 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/07/06/lesson-in-akihabara/</guid>
      <description>21:52 Monday 06 July 2015 JST Today&amp;rsquo;s topic was 七夕 （たなばた）the holiday(?) which is tomorrow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lesson</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/07/01/lesson/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2015 18:32:12 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/07/01/lesson/</guid>
      <description>18:32 Wednesday 01 July 2015 JST Lesson was good; same company, but new class with seven students, who were willing to use the idea I got from my Spanish teacher back in the day: use a new target-language name&amp;hellip; basically take a new name, move to a new city, get a new job. So I&amp;rsquo;m Rob from Sydney, and, to honor my Spanish teacher having been a payaso, am a clown.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New JB lesson on Friday nights</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/06/26/new-jb-lesson-on-friday-nights/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jun 2015 20:08:45 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/06/26/new-jb-lesson-on-friday-nights/</guid>
      <description>20:08 Friday 26 June 2015 JST Though the weekly lessons are only scheduled for a month, but I&amp;rsquo;m optimistic that the students (FS) had enough fun tonight and will continue enjoying their fun learning adventure enough to continue after the initial period.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>YM lesson</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/06/16/ym-lesson/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jun 2015 21:49:17 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/06/16/ym-lesson/</guid>
      <description>21:49 Tuesday 16 June 2015 JST Good lesson today with Y and M and (the other) M&amp;rsquo;s office.
But my right elbow hurts now from typing up on the table; I should have used my keyboard. Dang.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>headed to GG class now</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/06/11/headed-to-gg-class-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2015 17:15:43 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/06/11/headed-to-gg-class-now/</guid>
      <description>17:15 Thursday 11 June 2015 JST I&amp;rsquo;m about an hour early; I&amp;rsquo;m going to look at laptops to see what I can see. I should prolly also jump on TLUG list or go to a meeting before buying anything&amp;hellip;
18:15 I wandered around a bit and couldn&amp;rsquo;t find anything good in any of the smaller shops. Even when I found things that seemed basically good, they had Japanese keyboards, which aren&amp;rsquo;t good for me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GG lesson</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/05/28/gg-lesson/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 May 2015 20:44:31 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/05/28/gg-lesson/</guid>
      <description>20:44 Thursday 28 May 2015 JST Today before GG lesson, T asked A (in English) if she had read M&amp;rsquo;s email. A said she had not.
I used this simple exchange as the basis for fully 45 minutes of lesson:
T: &amp;quot;Did you read M&#39;s email?&amp;quot; A: &amp;quot;No I didn&#39;t.&amp;quot; R: &amp;quot;What did you ask her?&amp;quot; T: &amp;quot;I asked her if she had read M&#39;s email.&amp;quot; R: &amp;quot;and what did she say?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>lesson</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/05/26/lesson/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2015 10:11:12 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/05/26/lesson/</guid>
      <description>10:11 Tuesday 26 May 2015 JST Lesson with C in Akabanebashi went well today. She&amp;rsquo;s got great fluency but chaotic grammar, featuring lots of instances of &amp;ldquo;is&amp;rdquo; in place of a variety of verbs in a variety of tenses.
For example, &amp;ldquo;lesson with C is good today. She is fluency and bad grammar is lots of is to any verb any time.&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>lesson went well</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/05/20/lesson-went-well/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2015 10:11:44 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/05/20/lesson-went-well/</guid>
      <description>10:11 Wednesday 20 May 2015 JST Yesterday&amp;rsquo;s lesson went well today. Tariq gave me some suggestions for how to adjust the student&amp;rsquo;s transcript, and it all seemed to work as he guessed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>great GG class</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/05/14/great-gg-class/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 May 2015 20:21:42 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/05/14/great-gg-class/</guid>
      <description>20:21 Thursday 14 May 2015 JST Great lesson with GG tonight; after discussing customs related to death in Japan (put money in the box so the person can cross The Styx, but don&amp;rsquo;t put coins cause they don&amp;rsquo;t burn), we primarily reviewed their homework on reported speech. I had asked them to use reported speech for a picture in their textbook, and they were great! T had the great idea of writing the original speech from which she created the reported speech.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Good GG class</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/05/07/good-gg-class/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2015 20:30:24 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/05/07/good-gg-class/</guid>
      <description>20:30 Thursday 07 May 2015 JST Nice class in Akihabara tonight; five pages of notes including a coloring page which T will color and bring back next week.
Homework was pretty focused: write a sentence for each little picture on page 49, using reported speech, &amp;ldquo;while&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;during&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;because&amp;rdquo;, and any preposition, respectively.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tuesday morning lesson shakeup</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/04/22/tuesday-morning-lesson-shakeup/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2015 10:28:33 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/04/22/tuesday-morning-lesson-shakeup/</guid>
      <description>10:28 Wednesday 22 April 2015 JST Today was M&amp;rsquo;s last lesson as he&amp;rsquo;s leaving the company. He&amp;rsquo;s been my only student in that timeslot, so I&amp;rsquo;m not sure what&amp;rsquo;s going to happen regarding future lessons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>lesson with GG was great</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/04/16/lesson-with-gg-was-great/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Apr 2015 07:36:41 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/04/16/lesson-with-gg-was-great/</guid>
      <description>07:36 Friday 17 April 2015 JST Lesson with GG last night was great as usual. They all did good homework, and I got good feedback that the previous homework had been too difficult.
T gave good reasoning, and I was like, &amp;ldquo;hmmm you&amp;rsquo;re right!!&amp;rdquo; and explained that in my Japanese &amp;ldquo;book&amp;rdquo; (Textfugu), the author said he has cut out all the Japanese that we don&amp;rsquo;t really need, just focusing on the 20%.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>first lesson in Lazona</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/04/11/first-lesson-in-lazona/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Apr 2015 08:14:03 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/04/11/first-lesson-in-lazona/</guid>
      <description>08:14 Saturday 11 April 2015 JST Through a school called Temperance and Effort I&amp;rsquo;m scheduled to have a first lesson today in Lazona. I don&amp;rsquo;t have any details on the student, but we&amp;rsquo;ll see how it goes!
11:30 Nice lesson; she&amp;rsquo;s recently been inspired to study, so I look forward to helping her!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>lesson tonight</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/04/08/lesson-tonight/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2015 18:50:40 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/04/08/lesson-tonight/</guid>
      <description>18:50 Wednesday 08 April 2015 JST Francine and I are headed to Japanese class after teaching down on the south side.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mutsumi lesson</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/04/07/mutsumi-lesson/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Apr 2015 21:48:40 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/04/07/mutsumi-lesson/</guid>
      <description>21:48 Tuesday 07 April 2015 JST Good lesson with Mutsumi; her English is certainly improving, though she doesn&amp;rsquo;t see it! We&amp;rsquo;ve been working on past perfect / past continuous / present continuous.
Her husband joined us near the end of the lesson and gave me a cool navy/dark gray/olive camouflage suit jacket! wow! It&amp;rsquo;s barely too small for me, but definitely wearable!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>super fun lesson with GG</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/04/02/super-fun-lesson-with-gg/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2015 20:50:47 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/04/02/super-fun-lesson-with-gg/</guid>
      <description>20:50 Thursday 02 April 2015 JST Super fun lesson today with GG; just going in to the room, just before which time I had purchase a poor-me chocolate bar, I felt all my grouchiness lift away and no need to chow chocolate!
We laughed a lot and they said they learned a lot; it&amp;rsquo;s really a great class.
This is the day I paid 100 yen each of two times that GGE translated something into Japanese unnecessarily.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Great lesson with GG tonight</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/03/26/great-lesson-with-gg-tonight/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Mar 2015 20:35:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/03/26/great-lesson-with-gg-tonight/</guid>
      <description>##20:35 Thursday 26 March 2015 JST##
Tonight&amp;rsquo;s lesson in Akihabara was great as always. The students are all eager and do lots of homework, try hard to speak and ask lots of questions. I love &amp;lsquo;em!
Speaking (indirectly) of them, I haven&amp;rsquo;t studied J in two days, even though they inspired me to start again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nice lesson</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/03/12/nice-lesson/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2015 20:31:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/03/12/nice-lesson/</guid>
      <description>##20:31 Thursday 12 March 2015 JST##
Just had a fun lesson with GG in Akihabara! Seven pages of written notes, using a slowly dying marker..
So honored that M said she scanned my notes and used them in her portable reader thing!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>great GG lesson</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/02/19/great-gg-lesson/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2015 20:28:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/02/19/great-gg-lesson/</guid>
      <description>##20:28 Thursday 19 February 2015 JST##
Great lesson with GG in Akihabara! They are so inquisitive, creative, inspiring, understanding, and thankful! And I&amp;rsquo;m thankful for such a fun time in lessons with them.
M asked how I met Lin so I got to tell them that story.
I just gotta be careful to let them speak as well!!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AM lesson</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/02/17/am-lesson/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2015 10:30:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/02/17/am-lesson/</guid>
      <description>##10:30 Tuesday 17 February 2015 JST##
Finished my AM lesson with only M in attendance. We talked about paid vacation days. The article mentioned France with people taking 93% of their 37 available vacation days. In Japan people took 50% of their 18 vacation days.
M took 5% of his vacation days, and seemed pretty O_o when hearing about other cultures.
&amp;ldquo;I thought vacation days were just for emergencies!&amp;rdquo;
hmm..</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>great lesson</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/02/12/great-lesson/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2015 20:23:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/02/12/great-lesson/</guid>
      <description>##20:23 Thursday 12 February 2015 JST##
Such a nice lesson tonight! This was my first time to meet these students; they are three lovely women, two of whom are retired, one of whom does not have a computer nor TV! Wow!
We laughed a lot and they asked lots of questions and tried lots of speaking; I need to learn from them!
Also great: there are plenty of seats on the train on the way back.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AC lesson</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/02/12/ac-lesson/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2015 09:26:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/02/12/ac-lesson/</guid>
      <description>##09:26 Thursday 12 February 2015 JST##
I was a minute late to A and C&amp;rsquo;s lesson, but they were 5 and 20 minutes late, respectively. whew!
We hadn&amp;rsquo;t seen C in three weeks so I asked A to ask some questions about C&amp;rsquo;s latest adventures. I took notes on two separate sheets of paper on which I made corrections and then had them do the same conversation again, but using the new phrases.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>fun lesson and dinner</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/01/13/fun-lesson-and-dinner/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/01/13/fun-lesson-and-dinner/</guid>
      <description>##23:03 Tuesday 13 January 2015 JST##
Fun lesson with Yoshi today, and then went to dinner with Yoshi and Mutsumi. Yummy and great plus we got free drinks because I found a fish scale in the liver pâté.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>teaching at Toshiba</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/12/25/teaching-at-toshiba/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/12/25/teaching-at-toshiba/</guid>
      <description>##00:09 Sunday 28 December 2014 JST##
Yay! for the first time I got to have a bit of a tour in Toshiba Science Museum on Christmas day.
It&amp;rsquo;s actually quite interesting; they&amp;rsquo;ve got a couple of presentations every half hour, at least one of which involves materials cooled with liquid nitrogen for super conductive levitation around a small circular track.
I hope I can get them to put Francois on the hovering block some time!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>thursday lesson at Kawasaki Daishi</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/12/11/thursday-lesson-at-kawasaki-daishi/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/12/11/thursday-lesson-at-kawasaki-daishi/</guid>
      <description>##19:40 Thursday 11 December 2014 JST##
Tonight was my second night to teach at Kawasaki Daishi. It&amp;rsquo;s great; the lessons are casual and it&amp;rsquo;s only a 12 minute TJ Bike ride from our house. We practiced using &amp;ldquo;I would like&amp;rdquo; for ordering at restaurants and reserving airline tickets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Good morning lesson</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/12/09/good-morning-lesson/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/12/09/good-morning-lesson/</guid>
      <description>##10:29 Tuesday 09 December 2014 JST##
Chapter only with Mizuno today. The article we used was a good length for us. We had a good laugh when we realized the guy started his project in Mexico because that&amp;rsquo;s where he&amp;rsquo;s from.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin lesson this morning</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/12/04/bitcoin-lesson-this-morning/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/12/04/bitcoin-lesson-this-morning/</guid>
      <description>##09:26 Thursday 04 December 2014 JST##
It wasn&amp;rsquo;t really a &amp;ldquo;bitcoin lesson&amp;rdquo;, but when my one (1) student showed up fifteen (15) minutes late, I had been reading posts in /r/bitTippers (and for the first time published a link to my subreddit /r/consecutiveNaturals) and Bitcoin was on my brain so I asked if she had heard of it. She had, but didn&amp;rsquo;t have access to any, so I suggested change tip to help her get started.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Good lesson in Fukuura</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/12/03/good-lesson-in-fukuura/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/12/03/good-lesson-in-fukuura/</guid>
      <description>##18:38 Wednesday 03 December 2014 JST##
Met Yuuji in Kawasaki and he introduced me to the class in Fukuura where I taught tonight. They did a great job in role play buying some clothes. Next week: Christmas party!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>easy lesson</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/12/02/easy-lesson/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/12/02/easy-lesson/</guid>
      <description>##10:07 Tuesday 02 December 2014 JST##
Only one student at my lesson this morning. We were therefore able to go over the material exactly at his preferred rate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nice lesson with M and M</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/12/02/nice-lesson-with-m-and-m/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/12/02/nice-lesson-with-m-and-m/</guid>
      <description>##21:41 Tuesday 02 December 2014 JST##
I enjoy lessons with M and M because they both do lots of homework so we can focus on exactly what they want to do, and between lessons I can focus on exactly what I want to do.
Before the lesson, we agreed on the schedule for February, when I&amp;rsquo;m planning to go to Kagoshima for 2 weeks.
After the lesson, M asked me when she&amp;rsquo;ll become fluent&amp;hellip; and I told her that she will need to practice speaking if she wants to speak English more fluently.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fine lesson</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/27/fine-lesson/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/27/fine-lesson/</guid>
      <description>##09:22 Thursday 27 November 2014 JST##
Chapter with Chika and Ayano today. No Onoue nor Yohei. We practiced using prepositions to locate things in time and space.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Good MM lesson</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/25/good-mm-lesson/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/25/good-mm-lesson/</guid>
      <description>##21:36 Tuesday 25 November 2014 JST##
M did good homework.
M was pretty chill; she wasn&amp;rsquo;t feeling 100% so we didn&amp;rsquo;t do a ton, but had fun. I&amp;rsquo;m so lucky. :-)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter this morning</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/20/chapter-this-morning/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/20/chapter-this-morning/</guid>
      <description>##08:32 Thursday 20 November 2014 JST
On the way to my lesson this morning, I snapped a snap of this tree inside the lobby of the building.

Onoue joined the lesson today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quick lesson last night</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/20/quick-lesson-last-night/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/20/quick-lesson-last-night/</guid>
      <description>##18:30 Thursday 20 November 2014 JST
(written 10:54 Friday 21 November 2014 JST)
Last night JB school called me, &amp;ldquo;hey can you teach tonight??&amp;rdquo; and I go &amp;ldquo;sure!&amp;rdquo; even though it was raining.
Got dressed, including a tie, rain pants, rain jacket, and even my waterproof hiking boots. Took Lin&amp;rsquo;s bicycle because its seat is waterproof.
Smart me: I had my phone earphones in my ears (that&amp;rsquo;s right, future-people, we haven&amp;rsquo;t had them permanently attached yet!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>And the kids class was fine</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/19/and-the-kids-class-was-fine/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/19/and-the-kids-class-was-fine/</guid>
      <description>##10:19 Wednesday 19 November 2014 JST##
Thanks to Soness helping me prepare, I was well enough prepared for the kids lesson even though I felt crazy afraid before the lesson. I believed I wasn&amp;rsquo;t prepared; I had forgotten to bring Johnny (the stuffed bear) who I planned to use as a teaching assistant; I didn&amp;rsquo;t have a way to play music in the class, and I was just a frazzled nut before the lesson.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Early lesson in Akabanebashi</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/18/early-lesson-in-akabanebashi/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/18/early-lesson-in-akabanebashi/</guid>
      <description>##07:55 Tuesday 18 November 2014 JST##
I brought an article by Sophia Yan about Schragels bagels in Hong Kong.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Morning lesson</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/13/morning-lesson/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/13/morning-lesson/</guid>
      <description>##9:22 Thursday 13 November 2014 JST##
Chapter with Chika and Ayano was pretty great, actually; they both improved during the lesson and I think I helped in some way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>nice lesson with the Ms</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/11/nice-lesson-with-the-ms/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/11/nice-lesson-with-the-ms/</guid>
      <description>##21:30 Tuesday 11 November 2014 JST##
M has been studying hard; he prepared a presentation of his company&amp;rsquo;s products. Really neat to hear how gpleats are created!
M brought blueberry flavored chocolate balls! She explained how her other teacher didn&amp;rsquo;t check her homework, so I checked it for her.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>three lessons at Toshiba</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/11/three-lessons-at-toshiba/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/11/three-lessons-at-toshiba/</guid>
      <description>##18:43 Tuesday 11 November 2014 JST##
Another first lesson today: &amp;lsquo;twas the first time I taught at Toshiba science museum near Lazona in Kawasaki.
I taught three lessons to three individuals, all of whom wore the same uniform, so I&amp;rsquo;m not sure I could readily identify them in a lineup, but the lessons were fun and I hope I will get to go back after tomorrow, when I&amp;rsquo;m scheduled to be there for three hours.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Early Thursday lesson</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/06/early-thursday-lesson/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/06/early-thursday-lesson/</guid>
      <description>##09:41 Thursday 06 November 2014 JST##
Chapter with Chika, Ayano, and Yohei runs from 7:50 to 8:50. Maybe it&amp;rsquo;s a bit early; the first to arrive today (besides me, running a little late and arriving at 8:50:30) arrived at 8:05.
Everyone presented trip reports and we&amp;rsquo;ll get back to the book next week!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>M and M lesson</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/04/m-and-m-lesson/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/04/m-and-m-lesson/</guid>
      <description>##18:40 Tuesday 04 November 2014 JST##
About to have a lesson with M and then another lesson with the other M. Special thanks to M for introducing M!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JB lesson this morning</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/10/30/jb-lesson-this-morning/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/10/30/jb-lesson-this-morning/</guid>
      <description>##09:03 Thursday 30 October 2014 JST##
I&amp;rsquo;ve been teaching a lesson each Thursday morning for JB at a company office near Kawasaki station. Today new student Yohei arrived, though Chika, one of my &amp;ldquo;regulars&amp;rdquo; wasn&amp;rsquo;t there, so still just two students, including Ayano.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>