<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>late on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/late/</link>
    <description>Recent content in late on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2019 23:04:28 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/late/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Lin is late tonight</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/09/24/lin-is-late-tonight/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2019 23:04:28 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/09/24/lin-is-late-tonight/</guid>
      <description>(written 23:04 Tuesday 24 September 2019 JST)
Usually Lin checks in with me on her way home, but she has not checked in with me yet. I wrote this to Mark on LINE:
23:00 barefoot Rob Nugen Just checking in now; Lin is not home and not answering her phone or LINE 23:01 barefoot Rob Nugen It&#39;s possible she is out with friends, but usually she tells me if she will be late 23:01 barefoot Rob Nugen I won&#39;t seriously worry until after last train 23:02 barefoot Rob Nugen I do not need any support now, but I will let you know if I do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fun time badminton</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/08/31/fun-time-badminton/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2019 01:25:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/08/31/fun-time-badminton/</guid>
      <description>01:25 Saturday 31 August 2019 JST Just now home and ready for bed after playing badminton with peeps from Tomoko&amp;rsquo;s badminton club.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>headed home</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/07/11/headed-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2019 23:35:43 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/07/11/headed-home/</guid>
      <description>23:35 Thursday 11 July 2019 JST I&amp;rsquo;m on a local train in Shinjuku which will leave in less than a minute from now. I could have taken an express train which would get to our station faster, but would not have afforded me a seat to write.
23:59 Thursday 11 July 2019 JST Just woke up in Kyodo. Soshigaya-Okura now. Super tired. Too tired to write kanji.
00:02 Friday 12 July 2019 JST Express train.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>almost late</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/06/almost-late/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Apr 2018 23:45:28 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/06/almost-late/</guid>
      <description>23:45 Friday 06 April 2018 JST Not as late as last night, but may not get to bed by my target of midnight.
Watched too much damn ER with Lin, but I gotta admit it&amp;rsquo;s a good show. We are at Season 5 Episode 3 or so.
Had three meetings this morning, getting off to a great start, but did not do any paid work. Did do 1.3 hours of MT3, but have not uploaded the results yet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>late</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/06/late/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Apr 2018 00:54:06 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/06/late/</guid>
      <description>00:54 Friday 06 April 2018 JST Just watched a couple episodes of Rick and Morty on Netflix. From season 1, the Zigerian scammers, and then the Mr Needful half of the Pluto episode (, fast forwarding through the Pluto parts).
This was after Japanese lesson with Mel, who often gives me bonus time yay! We read a few pages of a Doraemon book with 100 four-kanji words.
All that was after eating chocolate on the way home from the station after reading Planet on Purpose after talking to Yoko after the lesson after receiving the remainder of the chocolate rabbit she brought to class after she arrived late after we had been talking about Planet on Purpose after talking about Skype after having talked about the lesson from last week after Mayumi asked me about it after not having been there then.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dirk Gently and the focused binge</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/13/dirk-gently-and-the-focused-binge/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2018 02:29:22 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/13/dirk-gently-and-the-focused-binge/</guid>
      <description>02:29 Saturday 13 January 2018 JST Heh. Well, it was pretty great. Dirk Gently&amp;rsquo;s Holistic Detective Agency was good enough that I just watched the last four (4) episodes in a row. At 40+ minutes each that&amp;rsquo;s 160+ minutes or about oh my god I have to go to bed.
https://news.newonnetflix.info/news/dirk-gentlys-holistic-detective-agency-season-2-date-for-netflix-uk/
Now it is apparently canceled, but I hope not. https://variety.com/2017/tv/news/dirk-gently-2-1202644035/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>arrived in Japan</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/01/arrived-in-japan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2018 23:56:26 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/01/arrived-in-japan/</guid>
      <description>23:56 Monday 01 January 2018 JST We have arrived back in Haneda and are in a taxi back home. Didn&amp;rsquo;t realize trains would not be running very late so yay for 12000 yen for stale smoke flavored taxi.
Last train was at 11:51 and would require two transfers, including from KQ Kawasaki to JR Kawasaki station.
I get to work on MT3 tomorrow yayyy!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>11pm dinner</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/27/11pm-dinner/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2017 23:17:52 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/27/11pm-dinner/</guid>
      <description>22:17 Wednesday 27 December 2017 -02 Though I thought things would be winding down here this evening, the table is being set and everyone is having fun.
23:20 Wednesday 27 December 2017 -02 Dinner was delicious, especially the dessert consisting of condensed milk, coconut milk, and prunes as topping.
I am falling asleep here, but I wanted to attend I-group. I think most men have checked out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>late</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/11/28/late/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2017 22:35:59 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/11/28/late/</guid>
      <description>22:35 Tuesday 28 November 2017 JST Lin&amp;rsquo;s out late tonight with work colleagues. Perfect timing because I stayed out late with peeps from co-gender group. I will still get home before her.
I took the local train tonight so I&amp;rsquo;m actually sitting on the train now as I write this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>late for class near C&#39;s place</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/11/13/late-for-class-near-cs-place/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2017 16:51:07 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/11/13/late-for-class-near-cs-place/</guid>
      <description>16:51 Monday 13 November 2017 JST TL;DR: Would you like donuts delivered to your place on Monday morning Nov 20th? details: Story time! Today I was inexplicably late for class which happens to be near your place. I told them I would get donuts before class next week. I found a donut place, checked Google Maps to see how to get to the class... and the track goes right by your house!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Japanese notes from a month ago</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/03/26/japanese-notes-from-a-month-ago/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2017 23:45:11 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/03/26/japanese-notes-from-a-month-ago/</guid>
      <description>23:45 Sunday 26 March 2017 JST Japanese notes from over four weeks ago, but just posting now.
https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/02/24/%E6%97%A5%E6%9C%AC%E8%AA%9E%E3%82%92%E5%8B%89%E5%BC%B7%E3%81%97%E3%81%BE%E3%81%97%E3%81%9F/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Charu&#39;s painting</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/12/10/charus-painting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2016 01:38:33 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/12/10/charus-painting/</guid>
      <description>01:38 Saturday 10 December 2016 JST Only 4 or 5 years in the making, I finished Charu&amp;rsquo;s painting today. Picture coming in less than 5 years!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tiny bit late</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/06/23/tiny-bit-late/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2015 18:45:22 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/06/23/tiny-bit-late/</guid>
      <description>18:45 Tuesday 23 June 2015 JST Good thing I&amp;rsquo;ve padded a lot of free time into my normal schedule; I was later than normal leaving work so had to crop my free time at the toy store. I basically went in, said HI, spun two tops, said BYE, and left while the tops were still spinning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>At Fujizakurasou</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/12/21/at-fujizakurasou/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/12/21/at-fujizakurasou/</guid>
      <description>##03:18 Sunday 21 December 2014 JST##
This place is nice and quiet; I think there may be only one other couple here. We had each hot spring bath to ourselves, the entire lobby to ourselves, the entire hall to ourselves.
We took a bus from Shinjuku to Kawaguchiko, and then the hotel sent a shuttle to shuttle us to the hotel. The driver reeked of cigarette smoke, and the van was equally bad.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Catching up on AB site</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/13/catching-up-on-ab-site/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/13/catching-up-on-ab-site/</guid>
      <description>##13:24 Thursday 13 November 2014 JST##
A request got lost in the shuffle, and I&amp;rsquo;ve now got it working, but the CSS is still messed up. I got it working in Chrome, but not in Firefox. Bah.
 
While making a ticket for the above request, I found an old request intended for me but not assigned to me, so I never saw it. I got it sorted today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Did some coding for AB site</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/10/did-some-coding-for-ab-site/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/10/did-some-coding-for-ab-site/</guid>
      <description>##Monday 10 November 2014 JST##
(written 10:24 Tuesday 11 November 2014 JST)
I&amp;rsquo;m late writing this entry, but really late with the code. It was around the time that I was leaving the language school in Ebisu that AB client requested a change. The paper on which the request was made got moved by over-eager cleaning and I just found it on Sunday, whereas I think I had the meeting in August.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>