<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>igroup on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/igroup/</link>
    <description>Recent content in igroup on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2019 13:11:01 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/igroup/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>let loose in my online men&#39;s circle</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/07/18/let-loose-in-my-online-mens-circle/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2019 13:11:01 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/07/18/let-loose-in-my-online-mens-circle/</guid>
      <description>13:11 Thursday 18 July 2019 JST I have been doing MKP stuff for a while. Today I expressed in my online group that I did not want to be there and I do not always want to be there. I am so thankful that I could just let loose with a barrage|littany of the stuff rolling through my mind and the men could be there just to hear me. It was stuff like</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>today</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/11/29/today/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 17:24:13 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/11/29/today/</guid>
      <description>17:24 Thursday 29 November 2018 JST Just finished four lessons at SCC: Naoko, Liliko, Hitomi, and Yasu each had 30 minute lessons, practicing various parts of their presentations.
During the first two lessons, my nose was running like yuck. I used a bunch of toilet paper and tissues blowing all the snot out.
This morning I worked on MT3 for 1.5 hours or so, getting maybe 8 frames taken. At this point, I am working on version 2 of the website, which focuses on the characters making the track instead of me making the characters make the track.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>last virtual I-group</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/08/25/last-virtual-i-group/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2017 11:35:22 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/08/25/last-virtual-i-group/</guid>
      <description>11:35 Friday 25 August 2017 JST Today was the fifth of five virtual I-groups designed to give leadership practice to men in the group. Just five men in the group, one night each gives a sense of what it&amp;rsquo;s like and lets men see other men leading the calls.
So I will be the leader leader of the next set of calls, planned for 6 calls starting in October.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Integration Group</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/03/24/integration-group/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2017 14:30:38 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/03/24/integration-group/</guid>
      <description>14:30 Friday 24 March 2017 JST Okay so for a long time I have used &amp;ldquo;I-group&amp;rdquo; or igroup or some variant to describe my men&amp;rsquo;s circle. This nomenclature might be confusing, so I shall now call it Integration Group.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>two new men in Tokyo men&#39;s circle</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/02/07/two-new-men-in-tokyo-mens-circle/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2017 09:05:23 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/02/07/two-new-men-in-tokyo-mens-circle/</guid>
      <description>09:05 Friday 10 February 2017 JST We had two new men in I-group on Tuesday. Awesome. I&amp;rsquo;m now suggesting that we meet every week, instead of just twice a month. I&amp;rsquo;ve emailed Prentiss to see about running the initial 6 week I-group protocols.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>