<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2019 21:42:22 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>I can choose to do anything (and no one really cares)</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/blog/2019/09/18/i-can-choose-to-do-anything-and-no-one-really-cares/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2019 21:42:22 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/blog/2019/09/18/i-can-choose-to-do-anything-and-no-one-really-cares/</guid>
      <description>So long as I do stuff within a normalized range, no one really cares what I do.
I can spend all day trying to figure out one bug, or ignore it. No one will know the difference. I could even quit my job, and just a few people will notice. (some people very much so, but 99+% will not)
Re-reading the above sounds like I am suicidal, but I am not.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Helping people see past lives?</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/blog/2019/09/07/helping-people-see-past-lives/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2019 17:26:33 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/blog/2019/09/07/helping-people-see-past-lives/</guid>
      <description>I put a question mark on the title because I cannot really prove the visions are related to past lives, but this is a fun way to guide people through a process to see what could be their past lives.
Each participant gets into a relaxed position, usually either sitting in a chair, or laying down, or otherwise sitting against something comfortable. Spend a few minutes leading the participants through a relaxation process, whereby they let their bodies relax and keep their minds awake.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Affirmations 101</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/blog/2019/08/29/affirmations-101/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 13:21:24 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/blog/2019/08/29/affirmations-101/</guid>
      <description>Growing up, we are taught various things in order to guide us toward being a fully functioning adult. Some of the messages we got as children do not serve us as adults (and some didn&amp;rsquo;t serve us a children!) so affirmations are an easy way to help retrain our brain to have positive messages rolling through.
I had heard of affirmations many times before, but my coaching sessions with Rin really helped me see the value of affirmations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Law of Attraction is real</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/blog/2019/08/25/the-law-of-attraction-is-real/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2019 19:23:58 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/blog/2019/08/25/the-law-of-attraction-is-real/</guid>
      <description>draft: true
The Law of Attraction is real, but maybe not in the way you&amp;rsquo;ve heard portrayed. &amp;ldquo;Think of something and it comes to you&amp;rdquo; brings to mind people thinking of a new fancy car, but still not see it in their driveway so assume LoA is a LoAd of Hooey.
But let&amp;rsquo;s go to a more subtle level. In the same way that my focus matters, I tend to bring experiences to myself based on my intention or attention.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to have lucid dreams</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/blog/2019/08/07/how-to-have-lucid-dreams/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2019 07:59:41 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/blog/2019/08/07/how-to-have-lucid-dreams/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever found yourself flying like a bird, only to later realize it was a dream?
Have you been chased by &amp;ldquo;bad guys&amp;rdquo; or haunted by scary situations in your dreams?
&amp;ldquo;Lucid dreaming&amp;rdquo; is a state of dreaming while being aware that you are dreaming. Lucid dreaming allows me to have more fun flying dreams and fewer scary dreams. This is how I got started:
There are a few techniques I have used at different times of my life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eye Gazing Workshop - 17 August 2019</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/blog/2019/08/05/eye-gazing-workshop-17-august-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2019 09:33:44 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/blog/2019/08/05/eye-gazing-workshop-17-august-2019/</guid>
      <description>In two weeks I will be leading an Eye Gazing Workshop near Shibuya station.
To help plan my first workshop, Rin asked me to choose something that made me really excited.
I told her I would have to think about it, and a couple days later it suddenly came to me as the perfect workshop.
After determining what I wanted the final outcome to be, the workshop plan went through a few iterations, with support from Georgie, Mark Wild, Soness, Kevin Turner, and others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Self care must come first (usually)</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/blog/2019/07/18/self-care-must-come-first-usually/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2019 13:28:41 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/blog/2019/07/18/self-care-must-come-first-usually/</guid>
      <description>In relationships where everyone is equally able to take care of themselves, you need to take care of yourself first. In general, you are the only person who truly knows what you need, and everyone else is too busy taking care of themselves to take care of you.
(And to be clear, I am speaking to you, dear reader, not just the generalized &amp;ldquo;you&amp;rdquo; which really means &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rdquo;.)
Today I learned the value of taking care of myself as related to my (online) men&amp;rsquo;s group.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>See more by walking slowly</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/blog/2019/07/10/see-more-by-walking-slowly/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2019 11:50:50 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/blog/2019/07/10/see-more-by-walking-slowly/</guid>
      <description>When out and about, I like to allow plenty of time between clients so I can be relaxed while in transit. Today I took it a step (ha) further by walking quite slowly.
After slowing myself down physically, I noticed a sense of peace come over me. An awareness of joyful awareness like a tautology of being happy because you&amp;rsquo;re happy.
Time lost its meaning as I simply walked step by step, aware of the surroundings like being there for the first time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>my focus matters</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/blog/2019/07/08/my-focus-matters/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2019 12:49:16 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/blog/2019/07/08/my-focus-matters/</guid>
      <description>Where I place the focus my attention makes a difference in how I experienced my life.
Have you seen the basketball video? If not, have a look:
  If I&amp;rsquo;m in a bad mood I tend to see things that are likewise bad. If I&amp;rsquo;m in a good mood I tend to see things that are likewise good.
This causes a natural feedback loop that tends to amplify itself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rubber ducking ftw</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/blog/2019/07/04/rubber-ducking-ftw/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2019 12:08:07 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/blog/2019/07/04/rubber-ducking-ftw/</guid>
      <description>Recently, I have had a big server upgrade that has been challenging me on how to finish it. Yesterday I asked a friend of mine if he could look over my plan for the upgrade.
He agreed, and I began to write the email that articulated my plan.
Just in writing out the email I recalled the value of rubber ducking.
The idea is that you explain the problem to a rubber duck, giving enough information so that the rubber duck can understand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maintaining state in long projects</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/blog/2019/07/03/maintaining-state-in-long-projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2019 18:42:57 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/blog/2019/07/03/maintaining-state-in-long-projects/</guid>
      <description>As a programmer, I often want things to be just right, finding that balance between maintainability, extensibility, and plain ol&amp;rsquo; get-&amp;lsquo;er-done. Today, banging my head against unexpected walls while trying to spin up a virtual machine with Vagrant, I had to keep my focus on the goal at hand: Keep the website up while migrating from PHP 5.7 on Ubuntu 14 to PHP 7.2 on Ubuntu 18.
In this case, the task seemed simple.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Insanity and exponential curves</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/blog/2019/07/02/insanity-and-exponential-curves/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2019 09:27:05 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/blog/2019/07/02/insanity-and-exponential-curves/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;ve all heard the quote something like
Insanity is repeating the same thing and expecting a different result.  I just realized that I have been trying to apply that quote too strongly in my life. I have low-key assumed I have to make some huge radical change in my life in order to have anything different.
That belief was blocking my ability to make lasting change. I don&amp;rsquo;t have to take on a huge change or multiple changes all at once.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simple steps for dealing with anger</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/blog/2019/06/27/simple-steps-for-dealing-with-anger/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2019 11:27:31 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/blog/2019/06/27/simple-steps-for-dealing-with-anger/</guid>
      <description>1) breathe. Focus on your breathing until the initial wave of anger has passed. It may help to focus on counting the breaths.
Allow your breathing to deepen and slow.
2) label. Say you yourself, &amp;ldquo;I feel angry.&amp;rdquo; Labeling the emotion brings your thoughtful brain back online.
This helps move beyond the Fight or Flight reaction of the reptilian brain
3) acknowledge. Recognize the steps that brought you into this situation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Save Money Through Meditation</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/blog/2019/06/22/save-money-through-meditation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2019 14:27:22 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/blog/2019/06/22/save-money-through-meditation/</guid>
      <description>My TV says if I buy this or that toothpaste / car / ______ then I will be happy. What TV doesn&amp;rsquo;t tell me is that happiness is temporary. Instead of buying my way into temporary happiness, I can sit my way into lasting happiness.
Sitting allows me to reset my brain to my center, my spirit, my essence. This is where permanent happiness resides. In this moment, sitting in what I call the Ever Present Present, I can just be, happily.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What do emotions tell us</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/blog/2019/06/18/what-do-emotions-tell-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2019 21:22:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/blog/2019/06/18/what-do-emotions-tell-us/</guid>
      <description>Sticking with the basics, we have joy and fear.
Joy is how I feel when I have what I want, or I don&amp;rsquo;t want what I don&amp;rsquo;t have. I am aligned with what is, and have no need or desire to change it.
Fear is the emotion which says I don&amp;rsquo;t have enough information. This is usually about an unknown future. I come to a proverbial fork in the road and could simply choose arbitrarily, but if there is a part of me that wants to choose the &amp;ldquo;right&amp;rdquo; option, I may feel fear about choosing the &amp;ldquo;wrong&amp;rdquo; option.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>