<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>laura on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/laura/</link>
    <description>Recent content in laura on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Jun 2015 07:12:00 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/laura/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>dream youth group</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/06/16/dream-youth-group/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jun 2015 07:12:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/06/16/dream-youth-group/</guid>
      <description>##07:12 Monday 16 June 2015 JST##
Playing silent football, with Nick and Laura D, they kept footballing to each other and then Nick sent it to me and expected me to send it to her, so I made a big show of finding a way to measure the distance to her: I searched in my pockets for a measuring device and found a short length of string and began to measure the distance to her, but it was more than 5 string lengths to get just to the next person so I dramatically tossed it over my shoulder and pulled out a pantomime string and measure one unit for each person away, and determined that Laura was in fact 4 people away from me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>laura!</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/08/31/laura/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/08/31/laura/</guid>
      <description>4:05pm Thursday 31 August 2000
Cute Wende is sleeping on the couch here at work. She now has Thursdays off from work. She brought lunch for us from (guess where?) James Coney Island and then she was lookin&amp;rsquo; pretty sleepy and I encouraged her to sleep. She was thinking 20 minutes, but it&amp;rsquo;s been longer than that now and I don&amp;rsquo;t think she has stirred.
I&amp;rsquo;ve been chatting over AIM with a few youth and all are excited about Tulsa Rally this weekend!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>