<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>money on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/money/</link>
    <description>Recent content in money on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2019 14:27:22 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/money/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Save Money Through Meditation</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/blog/2019/06/22/save-money-through-meditation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2019 14:27:22 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/blog/2019/06/22/save-money-through-meditation/</guid>
      <description>My TV says if I buy this or that toothpaste / car / ______ then I will be happy. What TV doesn&amp;rsquo;t tell me is that happiness is temporary. Instead of buying my way into temporary happiness, I can sit my way into lasting happiness.
Sitting allows me to reset my brain to my center, my spirit, my essence. This is where permanent happiness resides. In this moment, sitting in what I call the Ever Present Present, I can just be, happily.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>life changing work</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/01/17/life-changing-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jan 2019 18:02:33 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/01/17/life-changing-work/</guid>
      <description>18:02 Thursday 17 January 2019 JST It has taken me a long time to reach this point, but from being afraid of men in 1997, I am now facilitating deep emotional work in men&amp;rsquo;s circles every week, both online and face to face in Tokyo.
I want to deepen my skills as a facilitator and have decided to step more fully into this emotional awareness work. To improve my facilitation skills, I plan to staff two (2) New Warrior Training Adventure weekends, back to back in March and April.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>investment Club</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/02/25/investment-club/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/02/25/investment-club/</guid>
      <description>No sleep till&amp;hellip;Brooklyn 5:36am CST Friday 25 February 2000
I couldn&amp;rsquo;t sleep after I wrote the previous message.. not out of astonishing giddiness, but more of a nagging things-to-do-list. I remembered I still had to research online brokerages for our investment club meeting this Saturday!
Since the meeting is tomorrow, I figured I oughta get the research out of the way ahead of time. Instead of doing full blown tons of info research, I looked for basics: minimum balance, cost per trade, can we fund the account with cash or checks?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>credit cards ii</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1999/10/09/credit-cards-ii/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Oct 1999 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1999/10/09/credit-cards-ii/</guid>
      <description>9 october 1999
Hmmm.
Card A said it might take 2 weeks to make the balance transfers, but I called them tonight anyway to see what was up. Turns out that neither one was processed; it would have put me over my credit limit. Doh. I think a finance charge was applied to Card A and the balance transfers would have therefore put me over my limit. They were carefully measured to put me right exactly at my limit.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>