<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>lessons on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/lessons/</link>
    <description>Recent content in lessons on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 May 2019 17:19:56 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/lessons/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>great lessons at SCC</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/05/09/great-lessons-at-scc/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2019 17:19:56 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/05/09/great-lessons-at-scc/</guid>
      <description>17:19 Thursday 09 May 2019 JST Four lessons at SCC today. One was shorter than expected due to a (hopefully small) medical emergency. Third lesson on the third floor featured discussions of the other three lessons and hearing they students really enjoy my passion for the topics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>lessons today</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/02/13/lessons-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2019 21:30:48 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/02/13/lessons-today/</guid>
      <description>21:30 Wednesday 13 February 2019 JST In the first adult lesson at JB, we flexed some reported speech muscles with Side By Side book 1, where the target language is &amp;ldquo;This is a photograph of my son Bart. He is riding a skateboard outside our house.&amp;rdquo;
We changed it to be &amp;ldquo;This is a photograph of me riding a skateboard in from of my house&amp;rdquo; and then &amp;ldquo;That is a photograph of him riding a skateboard in from of his house.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>assuming the worst</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/09/27/assuming-the-worst/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2018 23:01:12 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/09/27/assuming-the-worst/</guid>
      <description>23:01 Thursday 27 September 2018 JST I do not normally catastrophize things, but I am assuming my favorite Japanese teacher got fed up with me not studying much the past few weeks. At the same time, I didn&amp;rsquo;t notice that our lesson package on iTalki had run out of lessons, so (even though she had said this timeslot was always reserved for me) that was not the case today, it seems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>easy lessons</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/18/easy-lessons/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2018 17:37:46 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/18/easy-lessons/</guid>
      <description>17:37 Wednesday 18 April 2018 JST Easy lessons today because Patrick was out. After combining the 4:30 classes, we played a game with target language &amp;ldquo;May I have a card, please?,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m ＿＿＿＿-ing,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;We&amp;rsquo;re ＿＿＿＿-ing,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Hey ＿＿＿＿, let&amp;rsquo;s go ＿＿＿-ing,&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Sorry I can&amp;rsquo;t. I&amp;rsquo;m busy.&amp;rdquo;
Matt is also out today, so I&amp;rsquo;ll teach his 6pm lesson.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>three lessons</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/10/11/three-lessons/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2017 17:37:38 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/10/11/three-lessons/</guid>
      <description>17:37 Wednesday 11 October 2017 JST The kids lessons were pretty good today. The two new students (one in each of my first two classes) are still not speaking, and I can&amp;rsquo;t tell if they are acting shy or don&amp;rsquo;t understand.. anytime they speak, they get the right answer, but getting them to speak is a stretch. esp with the other kids being so chatty. I ain&amp;rsquo;t sure how to handle it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>T lessons near Lazona</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/09/29/t-lessons-near-lazona/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2016 17:29:45 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/09/29/t-lessons-near-lazona/</guid>
      <description>17:29 Thursday 29 September 2016 JST Just taught three lessons at T near Lazona. I really enjoy these lessons because the students always have questions / topics / something to practice. The first two lessons were 30 minutes each. The first student talked about a wooden doll which carries tea cups. The next student talked about a record player. The third lesson was scheduled to be an hour, but there was a bit of miscommunication and we ended up starting 15 minutes late.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>lessons with Sarutachi</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/06/14/lessons-with-sarutachi/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2016 23:04:50 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/06/14/lessons-with-sarutachi/</guid>
      <description>23:04 Tuesday 14 June 2016 JST I was a bit late to lesson with Sarupapa tonight on account of not having been to this particular location before, getting lost on the way there, and being late to start heading that direction because I was begging the Softbank guy to give me the code to let me change my phone number to a new carrier.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Good lessons with SS</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/12/15/good-lessons-with-ss/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2015 21:44:30 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/12/15/good-lessons-with-ss/</guid>
      <description>21:44 Tuesday 15 December 2015 JST The timeslot used to be for MM but now is for SS, Sarupapa and Sarumama. They&amp;rsquo;re both progressing nicely, nearly enough for me to be inspired to study Japanese but gah I&amp;rsquo;m soo dumb (that I don&amp;rsquo;t).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Good lesson with SP and SM</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/11/24/good-lesson-with-sp-and-sm/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Nov 2015 21:48:56 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/11/24/good-lesson-with-sp-and-sm/</guid>
      <description>21:48 Tuesday 24 November 2015 JST Nice lessons with Sarupapa and Sarumama. They&amp;rsquo;re both so lovely!
And I learned from Lin that Sarupapa is a good person to describe with the word 渋い　(しぶい)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>time and money and money and time</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/11/19/time-and-money-and-money-and-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2015 17:22:37 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/11/19/time-and-money-and-money-and-time/</guid>
      <description>17:22 Thursday 19 November 2015 JST Asking for more money seems challenging to me, but it looks like it will be worth the fear.
It helps that I&amp;rsquo;m gainfully employed already. I can afford for them to say &amp;ldquo;nope&amp;rdquo; and find somebody else.
Saturday yep; I got it. Yay!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MM lessons and Thai dinner</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/11/10/mm-lessons-and-thai-dinner/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2015 22:27:14 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/11/10/mm-lessons-and-thai-dinner/</guid>
      <description>22:27 Tuesday 10 November 2015 JST During the first half of his lesson, Sarupapa asked me about MKP and I told him as much as I was able with my broken Japanese and English hybrid sentences. He said it seemed interesting; I wonder if he&amp;rsquo;d eventually be interested in attending I-group with us.
Sarumama came after that and we went over her homework. She&amp;rsquo;s really improving and would be a great inspiration if I wasn&amp;rsquo;t so frickin&amp;rsquo; lazy to study Japanese!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>lessons in Shinagawa</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/07/16/lessons-in-shinagawa/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jul 2015 12:11:03 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/07/16/lessons-in-shinagawa/</guid>
      <description>12:11 Saturday 18 July 2015 JST I taught two lessons in Shinagawa. First was a private lesson where I asked questions about her hobby: birdwatching. She seems pretty dedicated to birdwatching and was pretty good speaking once she spoke, but seemed really shy.
Second lesson featured two chatty women, who were relatively low, but really tried hard. I know logically this is what I need to do to improve my Japanese: speak, speak, speak, and speak!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MM lessons</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/05/26/mm-lessons/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2015 21:33:52 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/05/26/mm-lessons/</guid>
      <description>21:33 Tuesday 26 May 2015 JST Had lessons with both M &amp;amp; M tonight. During both lessons I tried to do more role play than I normally do with them. They tend to veer toward just checking homework instead of actually practicing English. M had done a huge amount of homework (as she usually does), but I didn&amp;rsquo;t check it all tonight; I was like, &amp;ldquo;okay, let&amp;rsquo;s practice this part.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>nice lessons</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/04/14/nice-lessons/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2015 21:44:33 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/04/14/nice-lessons/</guid>
      <description>21:44 Tuesday 14 April 2015 JST Great! It seems I hae three consistent lessons on Tuesdays now. Thanks to Mutsumi and Mutsumi, and K and Y. There&amp;rsquo;s a bit of tag team between Mutsumi and Y but Mutsumi and K are planning to study each week.
Glad and happy yay!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>lessons</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/03/24/lessons/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2015 23:34:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/03/24/lessons/</guid>
      <description>##23:34 Tuesday 24 March 2015 JST##
Chapters with Muchan and Muchan were great tonight; Mucchan has been working hard on his stuff and Muchan always works hard so it&amp;rsquo;s lovely. Sarupapa joined Muchan and explained some of the requirements for his fabric designs. I&amp;rsquo;m actually writing with the design in front of my screen now so I can only see part of what I&amp;rsquo;m typing. Hmm maybe I will use this as the first chance to take a photo that will be only available on b.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>lessons</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/03/03/lessons/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2015 22:34:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/03/03/lessons/</guid>
      <description>##22:34 Tuesday 03 March 2015 JST##
Yoshie may introduce a friend for lessons with me. Yay!
Mutsumi recently asked if I could create a vector pattern, and I spent some time looking at weaving software packages&amp;hellip; but it appears that it will require more conventional image software.. I plan to use Artboard, which I&amp;rsquo;ve had for a while but not really used (nor registered). This project would give me an excuse to do both!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapters at Toshiba</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/02/17/chapters-at-toshiba/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2015 17:21:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/02/17/chapters-at-toshiba/</guid>
      <description>##17:21 Tuesday 17 February 2015 JST##
I love teaching at Toshiba because the topics are so sciencey and interesting! Today Tomomi met me in Kawasaki station and introduced me to some new people at Toshiba. I had gone in earlier, thinking I would have lessons with the attendants, but they were all like, &amp;ldquo;ummm not today!&amp;rdquo;
Good thing I called JB, who was like, &amp;ldquo;don&amp;rsquo;t worry. Wait for Tomomi and she&amp;rsquo;ll get you sorted.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>surprise lessons!</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/02/11/surprise-lessons/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/02/11/surprise-lessons/</guid>
      <description>##09:40 Thursday 12 February 2015 JST##
Yesterday around 17:43, JB called me all, &amp;ldquo;yeah can you come teach from 6pm to 9pm today?&amp;rdquo;
That worked out nicely! I had asked JB for a single lesson off yesterday, so I could go to Kagoshima. I was therefore scheduled not to work, but got 3 hours instead of 1. Thank you, angels!
While there, JB offered me 1.5 hours of lessons on Thursday nights.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>