<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>tedx on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/tedx/</link>
    <description>Recent content in tedx on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2018 22:27:39 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/tedx/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>today / recently</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/08/06/today-/-recently/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2018 22:27:39 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/08/06/today-/-recently/</guid>
      <description>22:27 Monday 06 August 2018 JST I contacted the organizer of TEDx Roppongi, which is scheduled for November 3rd of this year. I&amp;rsquo;m not sure if I will end up helping with that, but I&amp;rsquo;m interested, because eventually I would like to speak on stage at a TEDx event.
In other news, I&amp;rsquo;m preparing for a workshop to be held on November 23rd, which will be an introduction to the men&amp;rsquo;s group work that we do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TEDx Waseda 2016</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/06/25/tedx-waseda-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2016 21:12:09 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/06/25/tedx-waseda-2016/</guid>
      <description>21:12 Saturday 25 June 2016 JST So today was the big day! Got to assist Soness at TEDx Waseda as she assisted all the speakers in the event. I helped Alan by recording some audience reactions during the presentations. I couldn&amp;rsquo;t do many because the camera couldn&amp;rsquo;t discern much of the audience in the dark. He recorded all the presenters and some audience reactions after the show.
All the presentations were great!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Headed to TEDx Waseda today</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/06/25/headed-to-tedx-waseda-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2016 08:06:30 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/06/25/headed-to-tedx-waseda-today/</guid>
      <description>08:06 Saturday 25 June 2016 JST Going to assist Soness with her presentation and have my first experience at TED-anything!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TEDx clarity</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/03/06/tedx-clarity/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2016 12:30:47 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/03/06/tedx-clarity/</guid>
      <description>12:30 Sunday 06 March 2016 JST Soness has spoken at a couple TEDx events, and given her extensive training and experience on stage, I figure she can help me figure out how to speak at Pecha Kucha, where I&amp;rsquo;d like to present a presentation on authenticity.
Synchronistically, Soness is leading an online workshop thing called TED Worth Application, which I&amp;rsquo;m taking!
Question 1:
Who are you? What&#39;s your message worth spreading?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>