<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>beach on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/beach/</link>
    <description>Recent content in beach on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Jul 2018 16:56:21 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/beach/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>great beach day</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/07/28/great-beach-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jul 2018 16:56:21 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/07/28/great-beach-day/</guid>
      <description>16:56 Saturday 28 July 2018 JST We got to the beach around 10am and it was warm; by the time we left around 2pm it was hotter than I could stand to walk barefoot on the sand.
We ate at a vegetarian buffet https://yoganiigata.jp/ Good for 1600 yen per person.
23:24 Saturday 28 July 2018 JST We went to see Jurassic World: Fallen Kingdom last night which was pretty good for a fifth installment of a series.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>dug a hole on the beach</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/23/dug-a-hole-on-the-beach/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2017 14:53:59 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/23/dug-a-hole-on-the-beach/</guid>
      <description>23 December 2017 -02 (transcribed 14:54 Sunday 31 December 2017 -02)
Dug a hole for myself on the beach but it was too far from the waves to bury me in the sand. Headed down to the water a bit more and meditated with Lin. Kept moving down toward the water so I was in the waves from 0 to 40cm deep, avg 2~10cm. たのしかった
Got Godot app to highlight clicked items today and got it to highlight subsequent mouseovered items and unswipe backtracked items.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ate churascos</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/23/ate-churascos/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2017 14:19:30 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/23/ate-churascos/</guid>
      <description>14:19 Saturday 23 December 2017 -03 Lin and I just walked along the beach from the restaurante de churrascos (sp) after pretty much gorging on all the offerings.
I saw some really neat rivulets on the beach (but forgot to take a picture) where water seems to just spring from the beach. I guess that is exactly what&amp;rsquo;s happening; water within the sand works its way out and then comes down to the ocean.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>beach day</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/21/beach-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2017 22:12:06 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/21/beach-day/</guid>
      <description>(transcribed 22:12 Monday 01 January 2018 JST)
evening 21 December 2017 Great view of semi-fragile sand dunes, but not safe to climb ざんねん. Hot girls including one with braces. OMG why do so many adults have braces here?
Finished algorithm for the app (LeSwipe / ConSwi) to deal with linking swipes to shapes while chilling in a self made hole in the beach.
(pictures coming soon?)
Quite interesting to see the waves coming in over the very-flat beach, so it came up significantly farther and farther with each passing unit of time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Relaxing on the beach in Fortaleza</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/20/relaxing-on-the-beach-in-fortaleza/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2017 14:46:04 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/20/relaxing-on-the-beach-in-fortaleza/</guid>
      <description>14:46 Wednesday 20 December 2017 -03 Relaxing on the beach, we got some delicious drinks: manga con leche (sp) for me and acerola for Lin. Mine was sweeet and muito deliciouso (sp).
A man came by with a young boy in his arms, and we ended up giving him R10 $3. Then other guys selling shirts, cashews, art, and maybe one more before we ended up just leaving instead of saying no no no no.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>headed to beach with Lisa and Miho</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/07/16/headed-to-beach-with-lisa-and-miho/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2017 10:13:23 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/07/16/headed-to-beach-with-lisa-and-miho/</guid>
      <description>10:13 Sunday 16 July 2017 JST Egad I am missing SOGO again (4 times in a row)
But it&amp;rsquo;s nice to see Lisa and Miho!
Actually only Lisa is with us while Lin is driving, and they are all blah blah blabbin chat chat chattin and missed a turn recommended by GPS. Twice.
11:33 Sunday 16 July 2017 JST Okay we just got Miho yay!
13:07 Sunday 16 July 2017 JST Only 1 hour (4.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Great day at the beach</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/07/09/great-day-at-the-beach/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2017 20:58:45 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/07/09/great-day-at-the-beach/</guid>
      <description>20:58 Sunday 09 July 2017 JST I joined Lin who met her co-workers in Kamakura for a going away party for one of the managers. Aki had a Canon film camera with a short little lens, so I offered to give her the slightly longer lens that came with my Canon EOS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>going to the beach</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/08/17/going-to-the-beach/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2016 08:48:22 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/08/17/going-to-the-beach/</guid>
      <description>08:48 Wednesday 17 August 2016 JST Lin and I went before, and it&amp;rsquo;s just an hour from my work. I think we&amp;rsquo;re going to Miura Beach. (三浦海岸)</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>