<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>sad on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/sad/</link>
    <description>Recent content in sad on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2019 01:10:32 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/sad/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>was sick during BC NWTA</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/03/18/was-sick-during-bc-nwta/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2019 01:10:32 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/03/18/was-sick-during-bc-nwta/</guid>
      <description>01:10 Monday 18 March 2019 PDT I felt sad to have to check out for a significant portion of the NWTA this past weekend. So annoying, and certainly not what I had in mind for my trip!
Was great to meet awesome men. I stayed with Steve R in Vancouver the night before the weekend, and am now staying with Dave M in Victoria the night after the weekend. Headed to Houston tomorrow via Calgary.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>lost my FitBit</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/08/lost-my-fitbit/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2017 01:53:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/08/lost-my-fitbit/</guid>
      <description>01:53 Friday 08 December 2017 JST I cannot understand how I could have lost my fitbit in two days. I received it from Prentiss on Monday night; I charged it the next day; I wore it for two days, and now I cannot find it.
I didn&amp;rsquo;t put it anywhere specific; it should be clipped to the pants I was wearing. Where did it go?
So sad.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gunma weekend</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/07/30/gunma-weekend/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2017 18:47:31 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/07/30/gunma-weekend/</guid>
      <description>18:47 Sunday 30 July 2017 JST Thanks to Rohini for inviting all the beautiful people who joined the Gunma adventure staying at Renee&amp;rsquo;s place.
Yesteray morning Lisa led yoga and later in the day she played an instrument with four strings. We tried doing some chanting with it, but no one knew the chants.
We went to the caves apparently dug by hand with a bunch of different statues (33?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>bitching</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/04/23/bitching/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2017 22:01:20 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/04/23/bitching/</guid>
      <description>22:01 Sunday 23 April 2017 JST Moe Joe
Lin is bitching at her mom. In me it&amp;rsquo;s triggering anger. I just want to yell SHUT THE FUCK UP GODDAMMIT because with them bitching I can&amp;rsquo;t work, nor sleep.
I know this reaction is my problem. I am going to sit (and meditate) a bit.
09:46 Monday 24 April 2017 JST Meditation worked wonders. My feelings shifted from &amp;ldquo;fuck you&amp;rdquo; to understanding that they have needed to get this fight out for a long time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>tough call</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/02/04/tough-call/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2017 17:43:37 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/02/04/tough-call/</guid>
      <description>17:43 Saturday 04 February 2017 JST Three hour wake-up call had me angry at one point and sad at the end. Headache now, but not sure if it&amp;rsquo;s from too much computer moreso than the conversation. Lots of attacks on the way my life is going: no kids equals alone in the end.
05:50 Sunday 05 February 2017 JST Yeah so what I&amp;rsquo;ve come to recognize is that I trust my intuition / future abilities to take care of myself and my relationship.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>