<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>old on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/old/</link>
    <description>Recent content in old on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Nov 2018 22:22:36 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/old/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>noisy fan on macbook</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/11/17/noisy-fan-on-macbook/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Nov 2018 22:22:36 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/11/17/noisy-fan-on-macbook/</guid>
      <description>22:22 Saturday 17 November 2018 JST Yuck. One of the fans on my Macbook is clattering as it spins.
I do not know how to estimate decibels, but it is annoying. It sounds about like an old hard drive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>transcribed old corrected Japanese</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/05/01/transcribed-old-corrected-japanese/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2018 08:45:33 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/05/01/transcribed-old-corrected-japanese/</guid>
      <description>early 2016 今日品川で英語の授業を四つ教えた。
Today I had four lessons in Shinagawa.
一番目は生徒一人三才の男の子こう君がいました。
一番さいしょの授業の生徒は一人3才の男の子こう君がいました。
In the first lesson, there was a three year old boy named Ko.
初めの時彼はちょっと恥ずかしいと思ったけど
When the lesson started, he was shy,
時間とともに彼は元気になった。
but he got better as it went on.
二番目のレッスンに三人の６才の男の子と一人の女の子がいました。
The second lesson had three six-year-old boys and a girl.
四人は元気だったし英語喋るの頑張ったからもっと楽しかった。
These four students were excited and did their best to speak so the lesson was more fun.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>recently</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/11/28/recently/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2017 13:43:23 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/11/28/recently/</guid>
      <description>13:43 Tuesday 28 November 2017 JST Recently,
 An elderly man fell as he was getting off the bus with an elderly woman. Everyone on the bus exclaimed, but the bus driver took off before anyone moved. I nearly completed the M Splitter on Marble Track 3. I tried getting Netlify CMS working, but still have a few bits missing, starting with authentication. I failed an test at TY. There will be other chances, but I felt sad because I had thought I would do better.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>