<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>travis on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/travis/</link>
    <description>Recent content in travis on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 17:39:23 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/travis/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>chillin with Travis and them</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/04/30/chillin-with-travis-and-them/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 17:39:23 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/04/30/chillin-with-travis-and-them/</guid>
      <description>17:39 Tuesday 30 April 2019 JST Today Lin and I drove to Travis and Yumi&amp;rsquo;s place to hang out with them and Sakura. Johan was already there and Deji came a bit later. Nice to see everyone again, though in some ways it&amp;rsquo;s like the tribe is getting smaller (and larger!)
No BBQ today due to rain, but we made 手巻き with chicken, eggs, salad, and then ice cream at the end.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Got mypowercircle to trigger Travis deploys</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/07/21/got-mypowercircle-to-trigger-travis-deploys/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2017 10:26:25 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/07/21/got-mypowercircle-to-trigger-travis-deploys/</guid>
      <description>10:26 Friday 21 July 2017 JST When I git push the source docs for Tokyo Men&amp;rsquo;s Group to the Github repo for Tokyo Men&amp;rsquo;s Group, it triggers a Travis build.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>hang out with Travis and Yumi</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/12/03/hang-out-with-travis-and-yumi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2016 23:08:49 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/12/03/hang-out-with-travis-and-yumi/</guid>
      <description>23:08 Saturday 03 December 2016 JST Sweet! Lin and I hung out with Yumi and Travis, respectively, in Shinjuku for a couple of hours, and an hour, respectively.
(as I write this, the above sentence seems comprehensible)
Lin called me while I was working at home, and kinda in a break-needing stage, so I jumped at the chance to meet Travis, for what I suspect is the last time before he starts his new project(s).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maki, Kaori, Yohan, Yukari, Yumi, Lin, and I</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/10/18/maki-kaori-yohan-yukari-yumi-lin-and-i/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2016 13:56:06 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/10/18/maki-kaori-yohan-yukari-yumi-lin-and-i/</guid>
      <description>13:56 Tuesday 18 October 2016 JST Maki, Kaori, Yohan, Yukari, Yumi, Lin, and I went to a Nepalese restaurant called Nepalico behind Cerulean Tower in Shibuya. Quite good and about half the price I had expected.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trying Debian</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/05/22/trying-debian/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 May 2015 11:50:01 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/05/22/trying-debian/</guid>
      <description>11:50 Friday 22 May 2015 JST At Travis&amp;rsquo; suggestion, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna try Debian on the new (old) machine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>chillin with Travis and Yumi</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/05/04/chillin-with-travis-and-yumi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 May 2015 15:09:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/05/04/chillin-with-travis-and-yumi/</guid>
      <description>15:09 Monday 04 May 2015 JST We are in Yakushiikekoen (sorry about romanji) chillin&amp;rsquo; under a wooden roof thing that looks vaguely new like they might rebuild it every couple of years.
Lin&amp;rsquo;s enjoying Yumi&amp;rsquo;s camera as they pose like apes in Yumi&amp;rsquo;s natural state.
We were originally scheduled to go to Kids Country, but when I saw the hordes headed that direction, I suggested we might do that on a different day, perhaps?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream baseball with Travis</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/04/11/dream-baseball-with-travis/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Apr 2015 07:59:35 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/04/11/dream-baseball-with-travis/</guid>
      <description>07:59 Saturday 11 April 2015 JST In a slightly enclosed area, Travis and I were playing a version of baseball. We would each take one turn at bat, and keep track of where our ghost players had made it around the bases. We were pretty well tied, though we kept getting hits. It was my turn at bat, and someone gave me a broken bat as a joke, so I used it as a joke and got a pretty good hit, making it to third base, though Travis tagged home base before my ghost runner would have made it there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream virtual room with Travis</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/03/23/dream-virtual-room-with-travis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2015 06:39:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/03/23/dream-virtual-room-with-travis/</guid>
      <description>##06:39 Monday 23 March 2015 JST##
Travis and I were in a virtual reality on my computer. He showed me a room that was similar to what I had seen before, so I almost didn&#39;t go inside to explore. Then I was like, &#34;wait if Travis showed me this, it must be cool&#34; so I went inside to check the place out. It was *amazing* with 3D virtual games inside the groom, a hologram which could be manipulated by touching the screen and project into the room; and some hidden rooms behind the walls with hinged doors on mirrors that caused the hologram to reflect &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yay Travis and Yumi are staying in Tokyo!</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/06/yay-travis-and-yumi-are-staying-in-tokyo/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/06/yay-travis-and-yumi-are-staying-in-tokyo/</guid>
      <description>##11:58 Thursday 06 November 2014 JST##
Yay! Travis and Yumi are staying in Tokyo!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>pre pre-release of hakyll-journal</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/05/pre-pre-release-of-hakyll-journal/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/05/pre-pre-release-of-hakyll-journal/</guid>
      <description>##20:12 Wednesday 05 November 2014 JST##
I&amp;rsquo;m so lucky to have an awesome programmer friend like Travis. :-)
Over the past few days we have been emailing back and forth, mostly with me going &amp;ldquo;uh huh&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;yeah&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;that&amp;rsquo;s right&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;great!&amp;rdquo; as he explains the intricacies of the best way to create a haskell library.
I&amp;rsquo;ve been studying Learn You a Haskell and considering buying Graham Hutton&amp;rsquo;s book, and am excited to have my static journal back, very excited to have Travis making a kick-ass library to seamlessly(?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thanks to Travis for refactoring the code!</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/01/thanks-to-travis-for-refactoring-the-code/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/01/thanks-to-travis-for-refactoring-the-code/</guid>
      <description>##02:12 Sunday 02 November 2014 JST##
Got an email from Travis today indicating that he refactored my Hakyll installation. Whoohoo!!
The refactorization he&amp;rsquo;s done so far is visible here.
The biggest changes (in terms of me not understanding them well) are in one file. https://github.com/TravisCardwell/hakyll-journal/commit/05416e71fbbf0f910bcc19717ee88d7ae810c9bd.
I&amp;rsquo;m going to put all his changes into the &amp;lsquo;master&amp;rsquo; branch, merge them into my recently created &amp;lsquo;rob&amp;rsquo; branch, then replace my personalized content in master with some generic stuff so it&amp;rsquo;s easier for people to use this repo for their own Hakyll installations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Installing journal with Travis</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/10/31/installing-journal-with-travis/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/10/31/installing-journal-with-travis/</guid>
      <description>##14:04 Friday 31 October 2014 JST##
Travis helped me (into and) out of Cabal Hell on my mac. heehee
cd ~ rm -rf .ghc rm -rf .cabal rm -rf ~/Library/Haskell cabal update cabal install cabal-install  Building cabal took a few minutes, even on my SSD-filled MBP. bah.
mkdir journal cd journal cabal sandbox init  Now need to create journal.cabal like this:
name: journal version: 0.1.0.0 build-type: Simple cabal-version: &amp;gt;=1.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>