<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>yruu on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/yruu/</link>
    <description>Recent content in yruu on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2018 05:03:46 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/yruu/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>YRUU dream oh my darlin clementine</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/07/02/yruu-dream-oh-my-darlin-clementine/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2018 05:03:46 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/07/02/yruu-dream-oh-my-darlin-clementine/</guid>
      <description>05:03 Monday 02 July 2018 JST It&amp;rsquo;s been a while since I woke up with a YRUU dream in my mind.
We were somewhere and someone sang some made up lyrics There was a new attendee from Colorado, and we jokingly said we had not heard of their football team, the California Nuggets. As an apology, someone sang Oh my darling, oh my darling
Oh my darling, Clementine
We don&#39;t know the football team name</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>doug conversation</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/10/24/doug-conversation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2002/10/24/doug-conversation/</guid>
      <description>10:34am CDT Thursday 24 October 2002
I have just called Doug and scheduled a talk with him at 1:pm ish.
yammering about japan
there are adults in the district who think it&amp;rsquo;s time for you to move on.
&amp;ldquo;yeah well fuck them&amp;rdquo; I&amp;rsquo;m thinking.
Gail didn&amp;rsquo;t know about dedication to me so maybe it&amp;rsquo;s not a done deal
he&amp;rsquo;s repeating a story about about japan that he already told me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>note from Bryn</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/06/04/note-from-bryn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/06/04/note-from-bryn/</guid>
      <description>Rob, OKC rally Sat 4 June 2000
Over the past three-ish years, i have met many people and done many things unlike any of my dreams. through all of these things, one person has always suported me, always comforted me, and always brought so much light to my life. rob, you&amp;rsquo;ve beAn so incredible. thank you for being my friend. when i think of not seeing you for VERY long times, it&amp;rsquo;s super sad.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OKC</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/06/04/okc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/06/04/okc/</guid>
      <description>4:30pm Friday 2 June 2000
Wende and I were late to the meeting spot; (supposed to meet here at 4pm) I felt pretty angry and yelled a bit. That felt better and we processed our feelings on the way here. Ironically, not everyone is here yet, so we are waiting... Happy random conversations--Wende is describing our home purchase to one of the parents. Ryan is doing some sort of magic card trick for Christina who just hollered, &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>pre Dallas rally</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/02/04/pre-dallas-rally/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/02/04/pre-dallas-rally/</guid>
      <description>12:43pm Friday 4 February 2000
Rally begins tonight!! This time in Dallas, a relatively short-ish drive once we get out of Houston traffic. We&amp;rsquo;re leaving at 7pm &amp;ndash; Wende and I driving separate vehicles full of youth. Big big fun!!
I hope I&amp;rsquo;ll be able to write some during the weekend.
Yay!!
With Love - Rob</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HoustonRally</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/01/16/houstonrally/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/01/16/houstonrally/</guid>
      <description>Houston Rally 2000 10:02pm CST Sunday 16 January 2000
(adapted from my diary)
Friday 14 January 2000 9pm
Houston Rally 2000. Bang we are here after such a short drive! We in this case = me, kT, and her sister Allison. Upon arrival, they bounced out of the car and I sat gently munching my chicken sandwich from Sonic. This is one of the first rallies in a long time that I also didn&amp;rsquo;t bounce out of the car.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>pre-rally</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/01/14/pre-rally/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/01/14/pre-rally/</guid>
      <description>Before Rally 6:31pm Friday 14 January 2000
Rally this weekend! And I haven&amp;rsquo;t been in charge at all! So weird. I haven&amp;rsquo;t packed at all! That&amp;rsquo;s not so weird.
I think FINALLY Jason will be at a rally with me so we can do our bubble gum skit, which I am sure will be more funny to people who are there than people who don&amp;rsquo;t see it, and probably more funny to Jason and I than anyone else at all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>san antonio rally</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1999/10/29/san-antonio-rally/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Oct 1999 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1999/10/29/san-antonio-rally/</guid>
      <description>(transcribed from my diary) [except for text in brackets]
29-31 october 1999
5:31am Saturday 30 October 1999
Oh my god it&amp;rsquo;s 5:21 am. I&amp;rsquo;m at San Antonio Rally. After work I was all &amp;ldquo;Ohshit! I didn&amp;rsquo;t get the van!&amp;rdquo; [it would be a very unfortunate situation to have 12 youth ready to go to San Antonio and me have to say, &amp;ldquo;um, I forgot to pick up the van from the rental place.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>pre youth council</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1999/07/23/pre-youth-council/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jul 1999 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1999/07/23/pre-youth-council/</guid>
      <description>8:22pm Friday 23 July 1999
In 12 hours I leave for 2 weeks in Iowa. I haven&amp;rsquo;t packed yet. The first week I&amp;rsquo;ll be an adult-at-large on Youth Council, and the second week I&amp;rsquo;ll be an advisor at Con Con. Each of these events are youth empowering, youth organized, youth everything, and I&amp;rsquo;m proud to be a part of the wonderfulness.
I do not have a laptop yet (haven&amp;rsquo;t had the proper cashflow for one) so I may write a mega entry at the end of it all, but maybe will figure out a way to write while I&amp;rsquo;m there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>general assembly</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1999/06/26/general-assembly/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 1999 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1999/06/26/general-assembly/</guid>
      <description>26-30 (or so) june 1999
written 7 July 1999
&amp;ldquo;How was Utah?&amp;rdquo;
This is a common question posed by my friends, and I&amp;rsquo;ve not yet written my official definitive answer.
For those of you thinking, &amp;ldquo;Utah?&amp;rdquo; here you go: I attended General Assembly, the largest Unitarian Universalist convention of the year. This year it was held in Salt Lake City. The week consists of lots of workshops, some worship, and plenary, where we as a democratic group decide what issues to focus our collective resources on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>youth council</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1999/04/14/youth-council/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Apr 1999 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1999/04/14/youth-council/</guid>
      <description>Subject:congrats Date:Wed, 14 Apr 1999 22:39:35 -0500 From:Tera Little To:Rob Nugen   ROB!!!!!! YOU&#39;RE ON YOUTH COUNCIL!!!! WHOOPPIEEEE!!!!!!!!!!! YOU DID IT!!! :) :) :) :) :) There. I&#39;m so excited for you. it will be an amazing, affirming, life-changing experience. Concon isnt&#39; a requirement, but it&#39;s so easy to go since your travel to YC is covered by the youth office, and con con will be just an hour or so away.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>little rock rally</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/12/05/little-rock-rally/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Dec 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/12/05/little-rock-rally/</guid>
      <description>Little Rock Rally
4-6 December 1998
Leaving Houston at 9:30am, I drove kT Hammons and Nicole Mauldin up to Tulsa to pick up Frank Roesler and Eryn Pope. I had forgotten to get a map to the Tulsa church, but we stopped by a McDonald&#39;s and used their phone book and figured it out. Said HI to Ashley Robinson, Stacey Craig, and a couple others after I took a quick nap at the Tulsa church.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>youth caucus</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/11/15/youth-caucus/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Nov 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/11/15/youth-caucus/</guid>
      <description>Youth Caucus
15 November 1998
(transcribed from my diary) En route to Tulsa. I&#39;m driving Denise&#39;s van, and Denise &amp; kT are asleep. Adam is silently reading in the back. I&#39;m in a reflective mood... healthy contemplation of my life after reading so much of Science of the Gods. OKC is 48 miles away. The book describes a physics that I don&#39;t really care about but I&#39;ve been enjoying the paranormal and unusual events and stuff it has described.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>San Antonio by Annie Bricker</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/11/02/san-antonio-by-annie-bricker/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/11/02/san-antonio-by-annie-bricker/</guid>
      <description>1998 San Antonio rally review by Annie Bricker
 
Damn, over a hundred people going to your average rally and not one of them has written a review since OKC 98. That&amp;rsquo;s terrible people!
anyway, got back from the San An Rally yesterday so I am going to write about it before the memories begin to fade. And yes, contrary to popular belief, i do more at rallies than just stay with Nick Carter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>San Antonio by Nancy Deardorff</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/11/02/san-antonio-by-nancy-deardorff/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/11/02/san-antonio-by-nancy-deardorff/</guid>
      <description>1998 San Antonio rally review by Nancy Deardorff
 
so i got inspired
leaving school on friday was a pain in the ass, but katie and danny k and i got through it. (don&amp;rsquo;t get confused, danny k was just visiting, he doesn&amp;rsquo;t go to my school) there was some craziness getting everyone together and into the van, but we(me, katie carson, danny k, ian coward, and matt luria, and me momma) finally left tulsa at about 4:00 in the nippy grayness of afternoon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>san antonio rally</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/11/02/san-antonio-rally/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/11/02/san-antonio-rally/</guid>
      <description>San Antonio Rally
2 November 1998
Here is my version of this past weekend lock-in at San Antonio with 120+ youth and a ton of fun! Here are pics from the rally.  How incredible to think that just counting from memory, we brought more than 25 youth from Houston! Yay! This whole Houston Network thing is working wonderfully! Youth from Emerson church collected at Emerson and waited for youth from First Church to arrive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>halloween carnival</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/10/25/halloween-carnival/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Oct 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/10/25/halloween-carnival/</guid>
      <description>Halloween Carnival
25 October 1998
Today at church we had our annual carnival with proceeds benefitting UNICEF. The youth group had two tables set up: one for face painting and stuff, and the other for fake blood and bandages. They also were in charge of the jail; people could pay to have others arrested, and those who were arrested could pay to get out. At one point I was arrested &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Construct-O-Con</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/10/18/construct-o-con/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Oct 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/10/18/construct-o-con/</guid>
      <description>Construct-O-Con
Sunday 18 October 1998
What a wild weekend! To give you a visual of sorts, let me say that on Friday, I shaved my head. I shaved it again Saturday morning and again this afternoon. The bulk of this weekend I spent at First UU Church of Houston with youth for Construct-O-Con, where Houston area youth gathered to design a much larger conference that will be held at my church in January.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>pre haunted house</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/10/02/pre-haunted-house/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/10/02/pre-haunted-house/</guid>
      <description>Before Haunted House
2 October 1998
I&#39;m right now listening to nine inch nails&#39; &#34;the downward spiral&#34; on _downward spiral_ CD. As soon as the CD ends I&#39;m leaving to go check out a haunted house with the youth group! There are 3 houses super close to each other near downtown on Fannin Street. Haunted Hotel, Haunted Hotel 2, and Fear Factory. Earlier today I cruised out there to see where to park and stuff before they get all crowded.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Airplane to ConCon</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/08/03/airplane-to-concon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Aug 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/08/03/airplane-to-concon/</guid>
      <description>Con Con
9:20am Monday 3 August 1998

transcribed from my diary
I&#39;m in seat 24A of Continental flight 1989 about to leave for ConCon. Celine Dion&#39;s &#34;My heart will go on&#34; is playing quietly over the speakers as two boys with English accents talk with their parents behind me, including &#34;if I sit heah, I con&#39;t see tha TV.&#34; This weekend I got all my planned activities complete, including transcribing all my SWUUSI journal entries, updating the Houston YRUU (pronounced &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flight to ConCon</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/08/03/flight-to-concon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Aug 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/08/03/flight-to-concon/</guid>
      <description>Con Con flyin there
Monday 3 August 1998

transcribed from my diary
On the ground below I can see huge block letters of green (trees?) on brown dirt background: LUECKI I wonder what the heck it means (city name?) or where it is... We&#39;ve been flying for about an hour and I&#39;m seeing some intricate roadways that look like an old circuit board. Pretty cool, but the weird thing is they don&#39;t see to go anywhere.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>nominating committee</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/08/02/nominating-committee/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Aug 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/08/02/nominating-committee/</guid>
      <description>I made the district nominating committee!
Date:Sun, 02 Aug 98 19:24:52 CDT From:Penny Ramsdale Subject:RE: SWD Nomination Committee To:rob nugen   Rob, I wanted to tell you that you have been elected by the district board to the district nominating committee. Congratulations, and thank you again for being willing to serve! __________ is chairperson of the nominating committee, and she will let you know what needs to happen when. I will be sending an e-mail to everyone on the new committee soon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>swuusi 1998 completion</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/07/31/swuusi-1998-completion/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/07/31/swuusi-1998-completion/</guid>
      <description>SWUUSI
12:13pm Friday 31 July 1998
transcribed from my diary Welp, we&#39;re on the way back home from SWUUSI. I was kinda in a grouchy mood when I woke up this morning after missing the talent show last night. Fricke et.al. had written a song for SWUUSI and fuck I missed it and they are graduating. But I felt way better with all the love and hugs and happy happy joy joy throughout the camp, and signing mugbooks and taking pictures and all the fun.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>swuusi 1998 Worship</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/07/31/swuusi-1998-worship/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/07/31/swuusi-1998-worship/</guid>
      <description>SWUUSI
3am Friday 31 July 1998
transcribed from my diary I got super hugs when I went back to the main cabin after &#34;my first shower since Sunday morning!&#34; &#34;Yay Rob!&#34; and hugs all around. Played koosh with Clark, Jessica, Nathan Sexton, and Bryn and others before dinner. Gave advisors Mary Angel and Dorian back massages and then it was time for worship. I had been asked to lead a senior circle through some type of guided mediation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>swuusi 1998 social</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/07/30/swuusi-1998-social/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/07/30/swuusi-1998-social/</guid>
      <description>SWUUSI
early Thursday 30 July 1998
transcribed from my diary Super tired waking up this morning but opening circle and then breakfast was good pancakes and stuff then I couldn&#39;t stay awake for Drake&#39;s Theme Workshop so I went back to bed. Woke up for lunch around 2pm, missing &#34;Whack The YAC&#34; which I didn&#39;t entirely mind since I didn&#39;t want to get whacked, whatever that might entail. Then the themed Gansta Lunch, serving Soup Doggie Dog, Method Manwich, Notorious BLT, and to drink Wu-Tang and Ice-T with Ice Cubes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>swuusi 1998 visitors</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/07/30/swuusi-1998-visitors/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/07/30/swuusi-1998-visitors/</guid>
      <description>SWUUSI
7pm Thursday 30 July 1998
transcribed from my diary Wow holy cow went to breakfast and then Drake&#39;s workshop and back to the cabin and was just about to hop into the shower when someone walked in. I went to see who it was: a woman, a new face, so I said &#34;HI&#34; and then realized holy cow it&#39;s Karen!! big big big hugs and we briefed one another on our respective weeks so far and sat down to talk and stuff and after about 5 or 8 minutes she said simply, &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>swuusi 1998 dorian</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/07/28/swuusi-1998-dorian/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/07/28/swuusi-1998-dorian/</guid>
      <description>SWUUSI
11pm Tuesday 28 July 1998
transcribed from my diary During Sean&#39;s Hair and Foot Washing Workshop, I got my hair washed by Anna Magwood and Katy Robinson and my feet washed by Josh Voyles. The nurturing attention was wonderful. I was pretty well sunburned today with all my time spent at the lake, even though I started the day with SPF 50. Maybe it wasn&#39;t as waterproof as I hoped.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>swuusi 1998 geology</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/07/28/swuusi-1998-geology/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/07/28/swuusi-1998-geology/</guid>
      <description>SWUUSI
4pm Tuesday 28 July 1998
transcribed from my diary Missed Spirit Circle tody and I certainly didn&#39;t want to do that; I had wanted to compliment the youth on how well they are drinking plenty of water and to keep it up. I did make breakfast though, and then Drake Baer (theme speaker) workshop, during which I wrote a mythical story about how The Feel Good Net got started. Morning workshops and then I went swimming from 1:25pm to essentially now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>swuusi 1998 water</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/07/28/swuusi-1998-water/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/07/28/swuusi-1998-water/</guid>
      <description>SWUUSI
2:30am Tuesday 28 July 1998
transcribed from my diary This morning, Jason and I played lots in the lake again, chicken fights and acrobatics of whatever sort we could come up with including Jessica on Jason&#39;s shoulders while Jason on my shoulders. We tried some 6-person pyramids, but couldn&#39;t get them to work. We played keep away from Maia with Maia&#39;s hat and sunglasses. Actually I did play a bit, but tried to keep the group to remain respectful of her stuff.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>swuusi 1998 scorpion</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/07/27/swuusi-1998-scorpion/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jul 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/07/27/swuusi-1998-scorpion/</guid>
      <description>SWUUSI
am Monday 27 July 1998
transcribed from my diary The same night after Jessica hit her head and we sent her to bed, Elizabeth (an advisor) asked if I would shave the back of her head with my clippers. No problem! I clipped it as she requested and was walking in the dark toward the bushes to throw it away when BAM!! something clamped onto my toe and burning poison seared through like red hot electrocuting pliers biting through OHMYGOD that hurts get-it-off-get-it-off and I scraped my foot upside down to knock off whatever animal had so effectively stung me DAMN!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>swuusi 1998 hydrator</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/07/26/swuusi-1998-hydrator/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jul 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/07/26/swuusi-1998-hydrator/</guid>
      <description>SWUUSI
6:45pm Sunday 26 July 1998
transcribed from my diary I am the Head Hydrator. I got the job after taking it upon myself to hand people glasses of water with a simple smile and, &#34;drink this.&#34; I like the job because the youth really appreciate it when I give them water even before they realize how much they want it. Or before they can work up the energy to get up in this heat and get it for themselves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>swuusi 1998 jessica</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/07/26/swuusi-1998-jessica/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jul 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/07/26/swuusi-1998-jessica/</guid>
      <description>SWUUSI
11pm Sunday 26 July 1998
transcribed from my diary After dinner I watched youth swim, but I didn&#39;t swim at first since I hadn&#39;t brought my swim trunks to the lake. (it was a 7 minute walk each direction from the camp to the lake) I went and got my trunks and Jason Fricke and I had fun wrestling and goofing around in the water. At one point we were standing back to back with our arms interlocked and trying to essentially do flips while staying in this position.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>swuusi 1998 travel</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/07/26/swuusi-1998-travel/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jul 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/07/26/swuusi-1998-travel/</guid>
      <description>SWUUSI
am Sunday 26 July 1998
transcribed from my diary After saying HI and bye to Amanda, and being up on my computer I went to bed at 4am and slept 30 minutes until Wende called. During that sleep I experienced my soul perfectly existing in this continuous moment. Beautiful. Wende said she was coming right over and she finally came over so very much later than I wanted and she wanted me to take some boxes to my back porch to be recycled and I ran to do it so as to not be late and holy shit I lost my toe ring.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SWUUSI by Maia Cudhea</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/07/25/swuusi-by-maia-cudhea/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jul 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/07/25/swuusi-by-maia-cudhea/</guid>
      <description>1998 SWUUSI Review by Maia Cudhea
  i can&#39;t believe no one reviewed swuusi. so i&#39;ll do it belatedly. okay, here&#39;s what i remember several months later. i got to camp really late saturday night, and the rest of staff was way already there. my hair was all done up from my sister&#39;s wedding (why i was late) and i was so tired. so we had this quick meeting and said we&#39;d do everything else tomorrow and i went to sleep on a table.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>beach cleanup</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/07/18/beach-cleanup/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jul 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/07/18/beach-cleanup/</guid>
      <description>lock-in and beach cleanup
Saturday 18 July 1998
Last night Wende and I went to the Post GA Participant Party and it was cool. 10 of us were there, and I felt a nice balance between talkative and listenative. When we left the weather was storming and I came home and turned off my PC in case the power went out. Then I cruised to the youth lock-in at First Church.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Orleans Rally by Sean Murray</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/07/04/new-orleans-rally-by-sean-murray/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jul 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/07/04/new-orleans-rally-by-sean-murray/</guid>
      <description>1998 New Orleans rally review by Sean Murray 
Well it was 3 months ago but I&amp;rsquo;ll try to remember it since obviously nobody else did. Well. all of the OKC people met at the church at 11:00 on thursday night. It took a while to leave though because we had this big ordeal because some people from Tulsa and Maia were supposed to come with us and there wasn&amp;rsquo;t enough room, but I made some calls and 15 minutes before we were supposed to leave Eryn Pope&amp;rsquo;s mom said she&amp;rsquo;d drive to New Orleans.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>general assembly 3</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/06/27/general-assembly-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jun 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/06/27/general-assembly-3/</guid>
      <description>General Assembly
General Assembly 
transcribed from my diary
10:03am Saturday 27(?) June 1998
Yesterday I started at a workshop on how to get grants from an private grant giving organization. They give away millions of dollars each year and I nearly snoozed through the workshop (guess who was up late?) but I got their &#34;how to apply&#34; packet at the end and it was all good. That was after $6.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>general assembly 2</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/06/25/general-assembly-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jun 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/06/25/general-assembly-2/</guid>
      <description>General Assembly
General Assembly transcribed from my diary 11:30 AM Thursday 25 June 1998
Just went with Drake, Tera, Wende to the mall and Drake and I bought swim trunks for $10 each. Met Jo Victoria! How cool to meet her after knowing her name from emails on YRUU-L mailing list! Met youth Tim Wing and Stephanie something and Mandy Jacobson. Tim had rainbow colored cloth sections added to the pant legs of his pants, making what we call in Southwest District &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>general assembly 1</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/06/24/general-assembly-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/06/24/general-assembly-1/</guid>
      <description>General Assembly
General Assembly 24 June 1998
Wende and I were 40 minutes late flying out of Hobby Airport for Detroit. That wasn&#39;t so bad; I was in a great mood and not in a tremendous rush to get anywhere.. I was in vacation mode. Whee! Got to Detroit at 1:15pm and easily made our connecting flight that was to leave at 1:45. Yup, we made the flight. Sat in our seats.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>adam beach house</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/05/10/adam-beach-house/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 May 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/05/10/adam-beach-house/</guid>
      <description>10 May 1998
This Sunday at church was the 8th graders&amp;rsquo; Affirmation Sunday, honoring their place in the church and welcoming them into the high school program.
We had a slightly different preparation process this year; the youth paired up with adult mentors who worked with them in various fields of growth, from creating a personal view of God and religion, to doing some service work for the community.
The youths&amp;rsquo; speeches were beautiful; I could hear sniffling noses in the audience behind me and my sniffling nose.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>cluster kickoff</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/05/10/cluster-kickoff/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 May 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/05/10/cluster-kickoff/</guid>
      <description>10 May 1998
Today was Flower Communion at my church. The service stems from way back in Czechloslavakia when Norbert Capek (The &#39;C&#39; character is actually a C with a v on it.) a Unitarian minister, wanted to have a communion but not using bread and wine. That&#39;s the short version of the story.
But that&#39;s not why I&#39;m writing. Today after church, Mary McCuen and I, en route to Einstein Bros.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>lry chuck e cheese 2</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/05/06/lry-chuck-e-cheese-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/05/06/lry-chuck-e-cheese-2/</guid>
      <description>Chuck E. Cheese
Wednesday 6 May 1998
Dinner this night was at Chuck E. Cheese&#39;s and we had 14 youth show up! That&#39;s the most we&#39;ve had at any Wednesday night dinner. We had representation from 3 or 4 churches! A great time was had by all, I believe. I mostly didn&#39;t spend many tokens. Probably about 1 dollar worth and then I just watched the youth doing various games and stuff.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OKC Rally by Bryn Cain</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/04/24/okc-rally-by-bryn-cain/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/04/24/okc-rally-by-bryn-cain/</guid>
      <description>1998 Oklahoma City Rally (in) review by Bryn &#34;Bean&#34; Cain
 Its beAn two weeks, but I&#39;ll start from Friday night and see where it gets me. First thing I remember was Eryn Pope, Austin Roth, Nora and I were all sitting outside in the courtyard around 8-8:30 just layin on each others tummies talkin, Nora is from Germany (as you all know) so we were askinh er all sorts of silly questions about Germany, and Austin was talkin about tummies, and it was just jolly fun.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>lry ninfas</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/04/22/lry-ninfas/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/04/22/lry-ninfas/</guid>
      <description>dinner at Ninfa&amp;rsquo;s
Wednesday 22 April 1998
 This night the LRY met at Ninfa&#39;s for dinner. As we arrived there were no parking spaces available in two parking lots; I dropped off Wende and parked across 8-lane Westheimer. Just as I got back, millions and millions of men (well, maybe fifty) came out, all comfortably wearing white shirts, khaki pants, work boots! Most had pagers, cell phones, and/or tape measures!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ministry with youth</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/04/03/ministry-with-youth/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/04/03/ministry-with-youth/</guid>
      <description>Ministry With Youth
Friday 3 April 1998
 Tonight began Renaissance Module: Ministry With Youth, a weekend workshop designed for Unitarian Universalist religious educators to learn how to support youth and youth advisors in creating a safe space to empower youth.  Tera Little and Lisa Rubens are the facilitators for the weekend, and that&#39;s cool because Tera is an advisor/DRE from my district and she&#39;s really great! We went as advisors to many rallies last year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>lry chuck e cheese</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/04/01/lry-chuck-e-cheese/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/04/01/lry-chuck-e-cheese/</guid>
      <description>Chuck E. Cheese
Wednesday 1 April 1998
 At Chuck E. Cheese&#39;s Magical Satanical Pizza Place, the goal for the night was to acquire enough tickets to trade in for a lava lamp, lofting large purple wax bubbles bathed in soft light behind the counter.  We included &#34;Satanical&#34; in the name because their phone number includes &#34;666&#34; but the recording we hear when we dial the number says something like, &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>lry house of pies</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/03/25/lry-house-of-pies/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/03/25/lry-house-of-pies/</guid>
      <description>LRY dinner at Houst of Pies
25 March 1998
 The LRY dinner was at House of Pies tonight. Because it was my birthday, my mom, her husband Jon and his daughter Alicia were all there. Jon&#39;s friend Donna showed up just because, and LRY youth Paul, Elaine, Laura, kT, Dennis were there and Wende got there a bit late because of work.  I had big fun and enjoyed briefly describing my college experience to Elaine, who plans to attend Texas A&amp;M in the fall.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>lry macaroni grill</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/03/18/lry-macaroni-grill/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/03/18/lry-macaroni-grill/</guid>
      <description>Journal
18 March 1998
 This night the LRY met at Macaroni Grill for dinner. Adam , kT , Laura , Wende  and I were all there. Actually, Wende got there a little late since she had been stuck at work.  The most fun thing about Macaroni Grill is they cover the tables with white paper and give crayons so patrons can express their artistic talents. kT and I expressed our talents maliciously at each other, resulting in an illegible scrawl of color in our corner.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Austin Rally by Sean Murray</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/03/09/austin-rally-by-sean-murray/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/03/09/austin-rally-by-sean-murray/</guid>
      <description>1998 Austin rally review by Sean Murray  
Well we left OKC Friday night at about 6:00 which put us in austin around 2 in the am. Even though it was a real long drive and Adam kept flicking me in the back of the head on the way there and Susanne kept sticking her toes in my ear, it was all worth it to see everybody that I hadn&amp;rsquo;t seen since Dallas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>rally dallas 1998</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/02/07/rally-dallas-1998/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/02/07/rally-dallas-1998/</guid>
      <description>Dallas Rally 1998
6-8 February 1998
 Dallas Rally was last weekend!  Once we got a bit more than halfway to Dallas, kT and I thoroughly confounded Laura and Adam with a nice long game of Ceiling Wall Floor.  I was pleased that I didn&#39;t have to consult the map to get to the church. I&#39;ve been to Dallas Rally a few times!  We got there with bouncy happy anticipation, signed in, dumped our stuff, got mugbook pictures taken (I wore my rainbow striped stocking cap over my face for the picture), and I walked around saying HI to everyone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Houston Rally by Jason Fricke</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/01/19/houston-rally-by-jason-fricke/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/01/19/houston-rally-by-jason-fricke/</guid>
      <description>1998 Houston rally review by Jason  
I slept. I slept. I slept. I slept. I went to the bad ass flag workshop. I slept. I slept I slept. I slept. I slept. I slept. I slept. I slept. I slept. I slept. I slept. I slept. I slept. I slept. I slept. I slept. I slept. I slept. I slept. I slept. I slept. I slept. I slept. I slept.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>rally houston 1998</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/01/18/rally-houston-1998/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/01/18/rally-houston-1998/</guid>
      <description>Houston Rally 1998
16-18 January 1998
 After a few weeks of receiving registrations via mail and phone and fax and email, we had 111 youth registrations and 22 adult registrations. I received 7 registrations on the Friday the rally began. Holy cow what a huge rally!  Friday morning I picked up the T-shirts bearing our controversial &#34;Imagine the Cat in the Hat Burning the Flag&#34; title and image of a seedy looking cat holding a lighter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Little Rock Rally</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1997/12/08/little-rock-rally/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 1997 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1997/12/08/little-rock-rally/</guid>
      <description>1997 Little Rock rally review by Rob   5 - 007 December 1997  The Little Rock Rally was, of course, absolutely incredible.
 I didn&amp;rsquo;t look forward to the 9.5 hour drive, but as I expected, the conversation was plenty invigorating to keep us chatting the entire way up there. In the rental car was Cathy S, KT H and I. I brought up a question that&amp;rsquo;s been bouncing through my head for a while.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Little Rock Rally by Cathy Saur</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1997/12/08/little-rock-rally-by-cathy-saur/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 1997 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1997/12/08/little-rock-rally-by-cathy-saur/</guid>
      <description>1997 Little Rock rally review by Cathy  
woke up and went to lamar with my mom to get my college day shit out of the way; wrote a review of scrooge for my brother, and bitched at my boss for scheduling me to work sunday. rode to houston, cruzed rob&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;hood with my parents waiting for him to get home; got to his house and saw ROB IN PANTS!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LRY dinner at Chuck E. Cheese!</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1997/12/03/lry-dinner-at-chuck-e.-cheese/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 1997 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1997/12/03/lry-dinner-at-chuck-e.-cheese/</guid>
      <description>Wednesday 3 December 1997
 For our Wednesday Night LRY dinner outing, we collected at Chuck E. Cheese&amp;rsquo;s Magical (Satanical) Pizza Place.  KT and I decided it was satanical because their phone number starts with 666. We decided it was magical because their phone message says so! (Those reading who don&amp;rsquo;t know me or us: don&amp;rsquo;t take it seriously.)  Jon W and Sean C were already there when Wende and I arrived.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Houston Construct-O-Con Rally</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1997/11/22/houston-construct-o-con-rally/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 1997 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1997/11/22/houston-construct-o-con-rally/</guid>
      <description>weekend of 21-23 November 1997
 This weekend we had our Construct-O-Con planning rally for the full blown rally in January.
Anna M, Charlotte B, Christina L, Jason F, Jim M, Jon M, Jon W, KT H, Nick C, Rob N and Wende W were all there for most of the weekend.  We were way more productive than I had expected. The first night we got the theme figured out: &amp;ldquo;Imagine The Cat in the Hat (burning the flag)&amp;rdquo; (or something like that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>San Antonio</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1997/11/01/san-antonio/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 1997 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1997/11/01/san-antonio/</guid>
      <description>1997 San Antonio rally review by Rob   The slugless San Antonio Rally, 31 October - 2 November 1997 was a most entirely excellent rally.  Special guests Drake Baer and Gregor Faron were flown in from Metro New York District to attend as normal advisor and youth, as part of a &amp;ldquo;district exchange&amp;rdquo; program to encourage communication in YRUU between the districts.  The first night was normal high energy rally bounciness, with PHUUFs for some of the rally virgins, toe tags to identify touch group affiliation, Surge, chocolate, mugbook picture taking and everything else that starts a rally.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>San Antonio Rally by Mike Moren</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1997/11/01/san-antonio-rally-by-mike-moren/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 1997 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1997/11/01/san-antonio-rally-by-mike-moren/</guid>
      <description>1997 San Antonio rally review by Mike  
Ok, first tera little picked me up at my house in plano at about 4 pm friday.  Then tera and nathan sexton and i drove down to san antonio. it was kinda bad though cuz tera&amp;rsquo;s car doesn&amp;rsquo;t have a clock or a radio, but we survived. Anyway, this is a good part. right before we got to the church, we called from the texaco station and got bryan beck on the phone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taco Cabana</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1997/10/29/taco-cabana/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 1997 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1997/10/29/taco-cabana/</guid>
      <description>29 October 1997
 This evening at Taco Cabana for our weekly LRY Dinner Hangout, Jon W was already there when we arrived. He showed off his new braces and new pager; &amp;ldquo;what&amp;rsquo;s different about me?&amp;rdquo; he asked as I greeted him.  We ordered and Paul R arrived as our food appeared on the counter. I got a Suicide as my tasty beverage and we sat outside to chat and chew.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Halloween Carnival!</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1997/10/26/halloween-carnival/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Oct 1997 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1997/10/26/halloween-carnival/</guid>
      <description>Sunday 26 October 1997
 At 5:45 in the am, after we had slept about 3 or 4 hours, the lights flashed on and immediately back off as Gerald came in to set up the chairs for the day.  I popped awake and hopped up and went to talk with him. &amp;ldquo;Um, we spent the night here last night, can you open the LRY room so we can sleep in there instead?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Haunted House LRY Lock-in!</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1997/10/25/haunted-house-lry-lock-in/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 1997 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1997/10/25/haunted-house-lry-lock-in/</guid>
      <description>Saturday 25 October 1997
 This day the LRY helped the Schweitzer Club with building their haunted house for the younger kids at church! Normally this project belongs to the Schweitzer Club, but they have only a few members this year and asked for our help.  My task included bringing big boxes for building whatever they wanted to build. Wende had brought a large box from work a few days previously, which stood grandly in our living room until Saturday morning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taco Cabana</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1997/10/22/taco-cabana/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 1997 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1997/10/22/taco-cabana/</guid>
      <description>Wednesday 22 October 1997
 Wende and I went to Taco Cabana for our Weekly LRY Hangout thingy. I was amazed that we made it on time; Wende had been in College Station about an hour previously. She said, &amp;ldquo;I didn&amp;rsquo;t exactly get here legally.&amp;rdquo;  Paul R arrived essentially on time and we waited for a few minutes for any stragglers. We talked physics and about the Mars Sojourner and the Mars Sample Return programs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>rally approval spirituality</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1997/10/20/rally-approval-spirituality/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 1997 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1997/10/20/rally-approval-spirituality/</guid>
      <description>Monday 20 October 1997
 This night Jon W and I went to the Board meeting at church to request permission to hold the Houston Rally at Emerson Church this year (well, January 1998). I let Jon do essentially all the talking and he did great and we got it!  Pam B said &amp;ldquo;Yes!&amp;rdquo; before he even finished asking the request; she helped the rest of the members understand the value of the event.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Youth planning and dinner</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1997/10/17/youth-planning-and-dinner/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 1997 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1997/10/17/youth-planning-and-dinner/</guid>
      <description>17 October 1997
 Today at work I talked with Marc Loustau of the youth office, and he more fully described to me the ConCon staff position for which he had encouraged me to apply.  Turns out the position is not just advisor, but adult coordinator, the one and only adult who acts as advisor for all the other adult advisors. (Does that make sense?)
 It makes sense to me, and I feel greatly excited about the possibility of holding that position.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CiCis Pizza</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1997/10/15/cicis-pizza/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 1997 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1997/10/15/cicis-pizza/</guid>
      <description>16 October 1997
 Last night Wende and I went to CiCi&amp;rsquo;s Pizza, and invited our youth group to join just for fun. Laura was there promptly at 7. We talked about school and her trips to Disney World and stuff. Actually Wende had more to say than I; I&amp;rsquo;ve never been to Disney World. sniff!  I encouraged Laura to get involved with Houston Rally planning, telling her how awesome the experience has been for many youth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>lry plans</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1997/10/05/lry-plans/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 1997 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1997/10/05/lry-plans/</guid>
      <description>5 October 1997
 Today at church, the youth group got some great plans underway for this year&amp;rsquo;s activities. First on our calendar is planning for a church-wide fund raising (for Unicef) Talent Show!  I absolutely love how the youth are brainstorming, planning, organizing all their own activities. Wende and I are just there to help guide them but let them pretty much do their own thing.  Next planned thing (which will actually occur before the talent show) is a lock-in / haunted house creating day on the weekend of the 26 of October.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>after YAC lock-in</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1997/09/29/after-yac-lock-in/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 1997 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1997/09/29/after-yac-lock-in/</guid>
      <description>29 September 1997
 This past weekend I met with the rest of the district YAC and Marc Loustau for our Summit pre-planning meeting. We completed all our goals and had a great time to boot. Marc&amp;rsquo;s knowledge and experience proved to be a great asset to our cause.  We met at Horizon Church in Carrollton, TX. Jason Fricke and I drove up there together. Well, I drove, and he offered to drive anytime I got tired.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>before YAC lock-in</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1997/09/25/before-yac-lock-in/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 1997 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1997/09/25/before-yac-lock-in/</guid>
      <description>Thursday 25 September 1997
 I&amp;rsquo;m not totally sure what I&amp;rsquo;m doing with this webpage; it&amp;rsquo;s been idle for a while. I haven&amp;rsquo;t been working on my novel, or writing Wild Skating Adventures, or out of body adventures, or much of anything.  So what have I been doing?  I&amp;rsquo;ve been working at work as a professional programmer, but that is not what I want to do all my life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SWUUSI</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1997/08/02/swuusi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 1997 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1997/08/02/swuusi/</guid>
      <description>1997 SWUUSI review by Rob   SWUUSI 1997 by Rob
 26 July 1997  Drove up here after Bobby, Erika, and Nathan drove to Houston and spent the night at our apartment. Altogether we had Me, Jason Fricke, Mike Noyse, Bobby Hall, Erika Hewitt, and Nathan Ryan. Stopped a couple times along the way and Nathan needed a white t-shirt, so we stopped in at Albertson&amp;rsquo;s in Denton. Found a package that was open, so we got two shirts for two bucks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SWUUSI by Dane Dormio</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1997/08/02/swuusi-by-dane-dormio/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 1997 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1997/08/02/swuusi-by-dane-dormio/</guid>
      <description>1997 SWUUSI review by Dane Dormio   Saturday
7/26/96
10:06 pm
  SWUUSI hasn&#39;t even started, but I&#39;ve already had a lot of fun. After a relatively short trip, I got here at about 4:00 pm. I came early because my mom&#39;s on staff. There was a staff meeting going on when we arrived, but I passed the time talking with Nathan Ryan, who was in the same predicament as me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Orleans Rally</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1997/07/07/new-orleans-rally/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 1997 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1997/07/07/new-orleans-rally/</guid>
      <description>1997 New Orleans rally review by Rob Nugen   Wow  Jason Fricke, Mike Noyse, and Tony Salinas and I all drove from my apartment toward Beaumont to pick up Cathy Saur along the way to New Orleans. Wende could not go, though she wanted to; she was sick.  We picked up Cathy after not being able to find the house and having to call her on the car phone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Orleans Rally by Dane Dormio</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1997/07/07/new-orleans-rally-by-dane-dormio/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 1997 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1997/07/07/new-orleans-rally-by-dane-dormio/</guid>
      <description>1997 New Orleans rally review by Dane Dormio   I have never been to the New Orleans rally before, but from what I have heard about it, this year&#39;s Fire-themed get-together lived up to the New Orleans UU church&#39;s reputation of a great rally. This year I rode with my mom and brought along with me a new guy, AJ, who will be a fellow student with me next year at the Arkansas School for Mathematics and Sciences.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tulsa Rally</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1997/06/16/tulsa-rally/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 1997 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1997/06/16/tulsa-rally/</guid>
      <description>1997 Tulsa rally review by Rob Nugen   Wow.  9 hours is not so bad if you have 3 drivers. However, it&amp;rsquo;s kinda cramped when you have 8 people in a 7 passenger minivan. But for a rally, we&amp;rsquo;ll do anything. On the way up from Houston to Tulsa were 3 advisors: Rob Nugen (that&amp;rsquo;s me), Wende Whitlock, and Dierdre Hammons, and 5 youth: Mike Noyse, Charlotte Benbenek-Price, Jon Whitten-Lege, Tony Salinas, and April Ambrose.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tulsa Rally by Dane Dormio</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1997/06/16/tulsa-rally-by-dane-dormio/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 1997 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1997/06/16/tulsa-rally-by-dane-dormio/</guid>
      <description>1997 Tulsa rally review by Dane dormio  Well, two years, twelve rallies and two SWUUSIs later, I finally got to go back to the site of my first rally, the All Souls UU church in Tulsa. I&amp;rsquo;m sure anyone who has been going to rallies for a while will understand how special a place this was for me. It was great to see the old church again and think about how completely different a person I am now than I was then.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fort Worth Rally</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1997/05/12/fort-worth-rally/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 1997 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1997/05/12/fort-worth-rally/</guid>
      <description>1997 Fort Worth rally review by Rob  Driving up from Houston in my truck were just Cathy Saur and myself.
The entire way up there we talked about what is most important in the world. The discussion resulted in us defining 4 types of love:   Love, the emotion, that people have when they fall in love with other people. This is the type of love people usually mean when they say, &amp;ldquo;I love you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fort Worth Rally by Dane Dormio</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1997/05/12/fort-worth-rally-by-dane-dormio/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 1997 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1997/05/12/fort-worth-rally-by-dane-dormio/</guid>
      <description>1997 Ft Worth rally review by Dane Dormio  Ft. Worth, rally number eleven for me, and the last one for a lot of seniors. This fact perhaps made it a little more emotional than most. At the end, though, I was surprised that almost nobody cried.
Last year, I remember, there was a lot of crying at the end. I was told that by the time it&amp;rsquo;s time for seniors to leave, they are about ready to move on anyway.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OKC Rally</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1997/04/14/okc-rally/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 1997 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1997/04/14/okc-rally/</guid>
      <description>OKC RALLY 11-13 APRIL 1997   What a drive! I thought it was like 10 hours, so psychologically I made it longer than it actually was- only 7. Wende, co-advisor with me at Emerson UU in Houston and I drove, while quietly talking or sleeping in the back were Cathy Saur and Ben Atkinson.  Got there about 1:30 in the AM and had apparently just missed opening circle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OKC Rally by Dane Dormio</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1997/04/14/okc-rally-by-dane-dormio/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 1997 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1997/04/14/okc-rally-by-dane-dormio/</guid>
      <description>1997 OKC rally as seen through the eyes of Dane Dormio.   We left as soon as we could Friday and stopped in Conway to pick up Meghan Rose and Nick Grunewald. Meghan had hurt her knee really bad in a soccer game right after the Little Rock rally, but she was almost healed and only had to use crutches a little. Nick was hyper and kept us all awake whenever he was around us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Houston Rally 1997</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1997/01/19/houston-rally-1997/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 1997 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1997/01/19/houston-rally-1997/</guid>
      <description>SECOND ANNUAL HOUSTON RALLY 17-19 JANUARY 1997
 Way back in like May 1996, I was called by Jason Fricke, and/or Nick Devereux to see if I would act as adult host for the Houston Rally in January. I was extremely flattered and accepted immediately.
 Jason Fricke was the youth dean of the rally. We called him The Dean on th&amp;rsquo; Scene. I was the Host with the Most.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>host with the most</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1996/01/17/host-with-the-most/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 1996 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1996/01/17/host-with-the-most/</guid>
      <description> The HOST with the MOST Houston Rally 17-19 Jan 1996  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dallas Rally</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1990/02/11/dallas-rally/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 1990 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1990/02/11/dallas-rally/</guid>
      <description>(transcribed 2:29am CST Monday 27 January 2003)
(not proofread)
Sunday 11 February 1990
I just got back today from the 1990 Dallas Rally. On Friday I picked up Fred (my brother) from his house &amp; we met Rick E and Mike O at 6pm. We left in Rick&#39;s truck shortly afterward. We got there at about 10:something &amp; not many people were there. I got a mesage to call my mom (She&#39;s going to school at SMU, which is very close to the church).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ConCon</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1988/08/23/concon/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 1988 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1988/08/23/concon/</guid>
      <description>(transcribed 2:22am CST Monday 27 January 2003)
(not finished nor proofread)
23 August 1988
 I got back from ConCon 2 days ago. It was so incredible. There is simply no way of fully describing ConCon - so I won&#39;t do it. But I will of course tell about some of the stuff I did.  On August 15 my flight was at 12:20PM and I got there with 45 minutes to spare.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>YRUU</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1987/05/24/yruu/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 May 1987 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1987/05/24/yruu/</guid>
      <description>(transcribed 8:59am CST Friday 31 January 2003)
Sunday 6:10AM May 24, 1987
I don&#39;t know why I woke up early. I got a letter from Shay Pickerell yesterday. It was short but nice. She hasn&#39;t been to church since I met her at the OKC Rally. Kelly has not written to me yet. I will write to her and give her the details on the Houston Rally. Church today will be fun.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>YRUU</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1987/05/21/yruu/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 May 1987 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1987/05/21/yruu/</guid>
      <description>(transcribed 8:56am CST Friday 31 January 2003)
10:30 PM May 21, 1987 Thursday
We had no meeting yesterday. It will be Tuesday. I need to practice rifles more than I have been. I need to bring a poster on something for the NUTS Room. Spuds Mackenzie probably. I want a whole lot of pillows for that room. It will be great. Bryn wrote me a letter, but it was very short and she didn&#39;t put our usual pictures at the end.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spring Conference Baton Rouge</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1987/04/29/spring-conference-baton-rouge/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 1987 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1987/04/29/spring-conference-baton-rouge/</guid>
      <description>(transcribed 7:29pm CST Saturday 25 January 2003)
10:40 Wednesday the 29 of April, 1987.
The Rally was awesome. Cheri had fun. I am glad. Debbie Wagner went with me and mom there. When we got to the hotel, no youth were around. They had gone to the youth hopitality houses. Debbie found Rusty Cockrell&#39;s room. (he is sort of out of the teen group) We talked some and then Cheri &amp; Emily came.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OKC Rally</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1987/04/11/okc-rally/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Apr 1987 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1987/04/11/okc-rally/</guid>
      <description>(transcribed 6:35pm CST Saturday 25 January 2003)
8:15am Saturday 11 April 1987
We got here at 12:30 this morning during opening ceremony. We sang songs and went around the circle telling our names, where we were from and stuff. We split up after the rules and I played hackey sack, frisbee, and Margaret and I had a pillow fight with a big dude named Monte. We worked on a puzzle and I slept at 4:00AM.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>