<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Peace Boat on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/peace-boat/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Peace Boat on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2005 02:18:15 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/peace-boat/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Life onboard</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2005/07/19/life-onboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2005 02:18:15 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2005/07/19/life-onboard/</guid>
      <description>##02:18 Tuesday 19 July 2005
We 16 GET Teachers (GET stands for Global English/Espanol Training) all teach two classes a day on 35 days of the voyage. During our free time we have the option of being quite busy with lectures and myriad activities on the ship. (( One of the biggest &amp;ldquo;problems&amp;rdquo; on the ship is deciding what to do next! Every room usually teems with activity. )) Somewhere during all that (usually at night when we&amp;rsquo;ve got several hours before classes) we plan lessons, with each teacher designing his or her own curriculum to fit the students and hopefully coordinate with the ports we&amp;rsquo;re visiting, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Le Havre, France</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2005/07/02/le-havre-france/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2005 05:33:46 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2005/07/02/le-havre-france/</guid>
      <description>##05:33 Saturday 02 July 2005
Hello from Le Havre, France! This city of 100,000 features some museums and gardens, and old architecture that I can&amp;rsquo;t name, but reminds me of old paintings. I&amp;rsquo;ve written more detail about our Le Havre wanderings in my journal dated July 2nd.
I think the last time I wrote was in Egypt (Port Said) after we saw the three Great Pyramids and Sphinx in Cairo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sri Lanka</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2005/06/06/sri-lanka/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2005 05:45:52 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2005/06/06/sri-lanka/</guid>
      <description>##05:45 Monday 06 June 2005
Not just Sri Lanka, but Columbo, which is the largest city (though not the capital) in this beautiful friendly country. The people are as friendly as in Vietnam, and the traffic is about as crazy, but with more trucks and 3-wheelers (little three wheel trucks they use as taxis).
The homes here are often covered in corrugated sheet metal, with patchwork quilt appearance from above. We got a tour through a university (possibly named Kabilla) and it started raining (we&amp;rsquo;re in monsoon season now) so little red muddy rivers formed between the trees.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Viet Nam</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2005/06/01/viet-nam/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2005 05:40:09 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2005/06/01/viet-nam/</guid>
      <description>##05:40 Wednesday 01 June 2005
Vietnam has been the best stop so far (Hong Kong, Danang, Singapore). People were friendly, roads were bumpy and chaotic, little 8 to 12 year old kids hardselling postcards, silk things, tiger balm, .. anything they could carry around. I must say they were quite well practiced with quick lines and little pouty faces that could wrench money from the coldest heart.
I bought custom made sandals for 95,000 d.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>