<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ssc on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/ssc/</link>
    <description>Recent content in ssc on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2019 22:07:47 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/ssc/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>lunch with Tomoko</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/02/27/lunch-with-tomoko/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2019 22:07:47 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/02/27/lunch-with-tomoko/</guid>
      <description>22:07 Wednesday 27 February 2019 JST Actually not lunch, but after the NWTA meeting, I worked on AB and then hung out with Tomoko from 2:05pm to 2:50pm. Midori was off today, so I didn&amp;rsquo;t get to see her. We talked about badminton and Mari-chan, who is in the badmintion group and happened to be with Tomoko when she let me in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>work</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/06/06/work/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2018 21:33:07 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/06/06/work/</guid>
      <description>21:33 Wednesday 06 June 2018 JST I worked for JB at three different locations around Kawasaki Station today, as I do every Wednesday, at Solid Square, SSC, and JB main office. Solid Square lesson went pretty well; we drew mind maps of our favorite places and then said a few sentences about them. Then I had a break during which I Marco Poloed with Richard from ae911truth a bit and then worked on AB, nearly finishing this ticket since it received a bit higher priority at our last meeting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Great lesson in SSC after lunch</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/02/14/great-lesson-in-ssc-after-lunch/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2018 17:58:12 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/02/14/great-lesson-in-ssc-after-lunch/</guid>
      <description>17:58 Wednesday 14 February 2018 JST Tomoko did well in our lessons in the SSC. She had to give a presentation in English today. Midori does not have to present as soon so she is trying to memorize more, it seems.
Lessons were after we ate lunch together on the 4th floor. I still kinda feel like an outsider there, as if my face and Visitor badge are flashing beacons.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>