<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>funny on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/funny/</link>
    <description>Recent content in funny on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 May 2019 08:54:15 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/funny/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Lin&#39;s bag today</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/05/06/lins-bag-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2019 08:54:15 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/05/06/lins-bag-today/</guid>
      <description>08:54 Monday 06 May 2019 JST It turns out I like the bag Lin bought online better than the bag I bought in a shop last year. The wheels on her bag are larger and quieter. That was something I could not test on the linoleum tile floors in the shop. That sounded perfectly smooth there, but out on the street they are raucous.
And this bag has more pockets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>tomato harvest</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/05/23/tomato-harvest/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 May 2018 12:07:53 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/05/23/tomato-harvest/</guid>
      <description>12:07 Wednesday 23 May 2018 JST コンプリスにタイマーがあります。　There is a timer on Complice.
タイマーが終わったら、トマトをもらいます。　Every time the timer finishes, I get a tomato.
今日、タイマーの時間を０秒に設定しました。 Today I set the timer for 0 seconds.

０秒で、５千個以上トマトをもらった。 I got over 5000 tomatos.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>woke up in Noborito</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/04/woke-up-in-noborito/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Apr 2018 07:05:45 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/04/woke-up-in-noborito/</guid>
      <description>07:05 Wednesday 04 April 2018 JST This morning I woke up with a start in Noborito, where I transfer between lines from Odakyu main line to JR Nambu line.
&amp;ldquo;Oh snap my stop!&amp;rdquo; and bounced out of my seat, got off the train and was confused about how far down the platform I was.
&amp;ldquo;Where am I? This is&amp;hellip; ohhhh&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo; and went back in the train and sat back down in my seat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>you guys are the best at making hot air</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/21/you-guys-are-the-best-at-making-hot-air/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2018 09:59:20 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/21/you-guys-are-the-best-at-making-hot-air/</guid>
      <description>09:59 Wednesday 21 March 2018 JST This was from 2017, maybe December..</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>git commit -m commit</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/11/25/git-commit-m-commit/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Nov 2017 17:33:39 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/11/25/git-commit-m-commit/</guid>
      <description> 17:33 Saturday 25 November 2017 JST git commit -m commit  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>pizza jam</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/10/08/pizza-jam/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2017 23:32:12 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/10/08/pizza-jam/</guid>
      <description>23:32 Sunday 08 October 2017 JST Yay Chris uploaded the pictures of us in blankets after we our pizza was delivered.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>automatic gate immigration</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/10/06/automatic-gate-immigration/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2017 08:29:14 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/10/06/automatic-gate-immigration/</guid>
      <description>08:29 Friday 06 October 2017 JST Here is my QR code which apparently lets me through the immigration gate in a breeze. So nice that they have this service! On my way out of Narita, the lines to go through the human powered checkpoints were quite long compared to the lack of lines in the automated gates. Hmmm&amp;hellip; so I went over there and they helped me get registered free of charge!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cookie Clicker bugs</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/07/09/cookie-clicker-bugs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2017 08:09:01 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/07/09/cookie-clicker-bugs/</guid>
      <description>08:09 Sunday 09 July 2017 JST Haha from Cookie Clicker (beta):
some old bugs were phased out and replaced by new ones</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>janette</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/09/14/janette/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2016 11:38:29 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/09/14/janette/</guid>
      <description> 11:38 Wednesday 14 September 2016 JST I just found some text messages between janette and I after I first moved to Japan. She knit a hat for me, and this was my reply:
you _-*! MADE !*-_ this hat??? Like with a long piece of yarn, wiggle wiggle wiggle presto a hat????  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No seat for you</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/12/16/no-seat-for-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/12/16/no-seat-for-you/</guid>
      <description>##11:00 Tuesday 16 December 2014 JST##
I walked into a restaurant featuring curry and naan, but they apparently didn&amp;rsquo;t open for 8 minutes. The guy spoke English, but said I couldn&amp;rsquo;t sit for 8 minutes until they open. Oh Japan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Showed Lin my new site tonight!</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/06/showed-lin-my-new-site-tonight/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/06/showed-lin-my-new-site-tonight/</guid>
      <description>##22:51 Thursday 06 November 2014 JST##
Tonight I showed Lin this new website (hakyll.robnugen.com). Not joking, she goes,
I was like, &amp;ldquo;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo;
As she realized her mistake, I explained that it wasn&amp;rsquo;t, and then I said, &amp;ldquo;wait wait this is you&amp;rdquo; and I made this image.
We LOLed for several minutes! It was great.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A funny thing happened during my lesson</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/10/28/a-funny-thing-happened-during-my-lesson/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/10/28/a-funny-thing-happened-during-my-lesson/</guid>
      <description>During my lesson with Mogi-san, I got a call from AB saying their image system wasn&amp;rsquo;t working. Hmmm. I asked them to create a ticket and she was like &amp;ldquo;okay&amp;rdquo; while I sent a quick email to Alfonzo because he&amp;rsquo;s the one who deals with the image system.
_______ says she can&#39;t upload images. I haven’t confirmed; I’m in a lesson. I aksed her to make a redmine ticket, but she can’t select you as the Assignee.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>funny</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/05/10/funny/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/05/10/funny/</guid>
      <description>This is so funny! 5:28pm CDT Wednesday 10 May 2000
Oh my gosh you have to try this!!!!!!!
Items you need: Small packet of Pop Rocks candy (or equivalent) 1 cup of tasty beverage (your choice) 1 stethoscope (optional)
What to do: Put all the Pop Rocks in your mouth Wash them down with tasty beverage Listen carefully to your stomach! 
I just did this to see what would happen, and I could clearly hear the Pop Rocks popping inside my stomach!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Margins</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/01/22/margins/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jan 2000 17:59:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/01/22/margins/</guid>
      <description>Margins
5:59pm CST Saturday 22 January 2000 How difficult could it be to write a message that automatically justifies its own margins? By &#39;automatic justification&#39; I mean that each line of a message would have the same number of characters in it. Then, viewing an automatically self-justifying message (with a fixed-width font), like the one you are reading now, results in an aesthetically pleasing experience. I saw such a message in 1994 during my days at University of Houston.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>pixels</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/09/30/pixels/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Sep 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/09/30/pixels/</guid>
      <description>Pixels!
30 September 1998
Things are going pretty great lately. Just last night, after 2 weeks of using my display at 640x480 pixels and 16 colors, Thomas was able to come over and fix it. I needed a PCIIX driver and a S3 Virge/DX driver and I just didn&#39;t have the expertise to get everything set. But now it&#39;s 1024x768 and 24 bit color and it&#39;s great!!! I&#39;m actually pleased with Windows right about now.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>