<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>coursera on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/coursera/</link>
    <description>Recent content in coursera on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2016 09:46:58 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/coursera/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Discuss people with high IQs are good language learners</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/01/03/discuss-people-with-high-iqs-are-good-language-learners/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2016 09:46:58 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/01/03/discuss-people-with-high-iqs-are-good-language-learners/</guid>
      <description>09:46 Sunday 03 January 2016 JST In the TESOL course, they just presented a story about a smart guy who tried to learn a language just from books, and no practice. I can&amp;rsquo;t imagine it&amp;rsquo;s as literally true as they&amp;rsquo;ve presented it, but the point is clear. Books don&amp;rsquo;t talk back. (*)
(*) Yes, I mean the old kind of books, the ones that were just made of paper and stuff.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is taught is what is learned</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/01/02/what-is-taught-is-what-is-learned/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2016 08:15:58 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/01/02/what-is-taught-is-what-is-learned/</guid>
      <description>08:15 Saturday 02 January 2016 JST Here&amp;rsquo;s my answer to the statement &amp;ldquo;What is taught is what is learned&amp;rdquo;
What is taught is definitely not what is learned. Students focus on whatever they focus on. The instructor may be talking about blah blah blah, but the student might be focusing on their navel, their cellphone, etc. In this case, what is taught is for naught. As we learned early in this course, students are busy forming their opinions about the teacher&#39;s ability to teach instead of the topic itself, and that&#39;s just in the first 6 seconds of class.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>started learning how to learn</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/07/11/started-learning-how-to-learn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jul 2015 07:37:42 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/07/11/started-learning-how-to-learn/</guid>
      <description>07:37 Saturday 11 July 2015 JST I started the Learning how to Learn course on Coursera this morning, and was able to correctly answer most of the questions without watching the videos. I queued three videos to watch while out at Higashi-Nakano today, but forgot my earphones, so might not be able to (unless I do it between lessons, which I might).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>