<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>great on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/great/</link>
    <description>Recent content in great on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2019 00:07:01 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/great/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Super great day with Colleen</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/10/04/super-great-day-with-colleen/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2019 00:07:01 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/10/04/super-great-day-with-colleen/</guid>
      <description>(written 00:07 Friday 04 October 2019 PDT)
Colleen had to wait an extra hour for me to go through immigration and customs in Seattle. Once we hung out, though, it was like no time had passed!
                          
Lively laughy fun dinner with Colleen and Ryan at their house while eating pizza.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Great day so far</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/06/18/great-day-so-far/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2019 15:29:01 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/06/18/great-day-so-far/</guid>
      <description>15:29 Tuesday 18 June 2019 JST I got 1.5 hours of livestream done on MT3 and about an equal amount of work done on AB. Plus spent time ostensibly studying Japanese by watching Kakegurui in Japanese. (Season 2 now has subtitles in English.)
Anndd had a nice nap.
Rode TJ Bike to the station and am now on my way to 麻布十番 for my third session with Rin.
We are going to work on my first workshop together as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>great timing to catch the train</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/06/11/great-timing-to-catch-the-train/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2019 15:45:05 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/06/11/great-timing-to-catch-the-train/</guid>
      <description>15:45 Tuesday 11 June 2019 JST I walked gently toward our station while repeating the lesson for today. I included &amp;ldquo;I am determined to see time differently&amp;rdquo; an was intrigued as I walked past a man who was walking slowly; it felt right / fine to do so.
Arrived at the train station and just missed the local train, but whatdya know the next train was a Hakone Limited Express (or something) and the next stop is Shinjuku, and I got a seat (for 410 yen).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>super cool Netflix</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/09/18/super-cool-netflix/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 15:51:09 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/09/18/super-cool-netflix/</guid>
      <description>15:51 Tuesday 18 September 2018 JST I got an email from Netflix saying they are going to raise prices starting soon. They did not list the options that were available, but had some indication that I could change my plan or cancel if I wanted. I was not logged in to Netflix on my mobile phone so I left the email in my inbox to deal with later.
Sat down to Netflix and chill today and a new dialog box popped up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Go is great</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/08/31/go-is-great/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Aug 2018 21:50:51 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/08/31/go-is-great/</guid>
      <description>21:50 Friday 31 August 2018 JST Wow Go is great. The compiler doesn&amp;rsquo;t let you fuck around too much. &amp;ldquo;Hey you&amp;rsquo;re wasting variables!&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Hey those are different!&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Hey you already did that!&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Don&amp;rsquo;t include it if you don&amp;rsquo;t need it!&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Don&amp;rsquo;t use it if you didn&amp;rsquo;t include it&amp;rdquo;
I can imagine what Travis meant when he said if a Hakyll Haskell program compiles, it probably works correctly. Even with all the side effects available in Go, I am much more confident that my code works than with any PHP code.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Great co-gender group tonight</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/05/14/great-co-gender-group-tonight/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 May 2018 22:49:18 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/05/14/great-co-gender-group-tonight/</guid>
      <description>22:49 Monday 14 May 2018 JST Two new members today. Great connection and hopefully many more to come.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>great co-gender circle tonight</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/05/07/great-co-gender-circle-tonight/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 May 2018 22:31:25 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/05/07/great-co-gender-circle-tonight/</guid>
      <description>22:31 Monday 07 May 2018 JST So thankful for my group tonight who were able to help me look at my income problem, pick me up out of the proverbial quicksand, and open me up to no limits for my business plan.
Not that I actually knew I was in proverbial quicksand, nor that I had unconsciously put limits on my possible business. Great to have great feedback from them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>integration group council meeting</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/26/integration-group-council-meeting/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2018 11:38:53 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/26/integration-group-council-meeting/</guid>
      <description>11:38 Friday 26 January 2018 JST Great integration group council meeting today. I got some great ideas for how to help invite new men into the work. I mean the same type of work in The Work.
Blessings to all the men who make this work possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Godot is so great</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/24/godot-is-so-great/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2017 14:02:33 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/24/godot-is-so-great/</guid>
      <description>14:02 Sunday 24 December 2017 Godot is super great for fast and easy development. I haven&amp;rsquo;t gotten to the export stage yet, but hopefully that will be as easy. I was able to add a queue to display the upcoming pieces in about an hour, including distractions.
https://github.com/thunderrabbit/robdot_conswi to see the latest.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>