<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>group on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/group/</link>
    <description>Recent content in group on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2019 13:28:41 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/group/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Self care must come first (usually)</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/blog/2019/07/18/self-care-must-come-first-usually/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2019 13:28:41 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/blog/2019/07/18/self-care-must-come-first-usually/</guid>
      <description>In relationships where everyone is equally able to take care of themselves, you need to take care of yourself first. In general, you are the only person who truly knows what you need, and everyone else is too busy taking care of themselves to take care of you.
(And to be clear, I am speaking to you, dear reader, not just the generalized &amp;ldquo;you&amp;rdquo; which really means &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rdquo;.)
Today I learned the value of taking care of myself as related to my (online) men&amp;rsquo;s group.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First co-gender group after initial 8 meetings</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/09/27/first-co-gender-group-after-initial-8-meetings/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2017 00:10:34 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/09/27/first-co-gender-group-after-initial-8-meetings/</guid>
      <description>00:10 Wednesday 27 September 2017 JST Tonight the co-gender group had its first meeting after our initial 8 meetings. Two new people came and seemed keen enough that they will attend again. I did a process which helped people see the value of emotional clearing work:
Feeling: anger at my wife because she buys crap she won&#39;t use for long Anger source: helpless, feeling sadness that consumerism is polluting earth Feel sadness where: actually not in my body, like it&#39;s out in front of me, like I have lost touch with my groundedness How to regain groundedness: go climb a tree, reconnect with nature  So to recap, my anger at my wife is really hiding sadness about my own disconnect from nature.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>