<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>phone on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/phone/</link>
    <description>Recent content in phone on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 Aug 2018 20:16:12 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/phone/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>lesson via phone</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/08/12/lesson-via-phone/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Aug 2018 20:16:12 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/08/12/lesson-via-phone/</guid>
      <description>20:16 Sunday 12 August 2018 JST Today Lin and I are at her sister&amp;rsquo;s house, but they do not have strong wifi so I cannot use Skype. At least not in this quiet room. Maybe that is why it&amp;rsquo;s quiet haha.
I do not have unlimited data on my phone, but I do have unlimited calling, so I am doing a lesson via phone instead of Skype.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>yay SOGO</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/02/18/yay-sogo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2018 14:28:42 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/02/18/yay-sogo/</guid>
      <description>14:28 Sunday 18 February 2018 JST I was late to SOGO because I was late leaving and forgot my phone so had to come back.
I was a bit late arriving, but they were late starting so it all worked out. Haha we worked out as well. My toe injury did not bleed and was basically fine, though now it&amp;rsquo;s dirty. I was puffed by the group workout at the end, running while piggybacking Naoki, but even more impressive was him running while piggybacking me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>replacement phone</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/02/05/replacement-phone/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2018 13:51:19 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/02/05/replacement-phone/</guid>
      <description>13:51 Monday 05 February 2018 JST Is it a waste to get a new phone after my phone&amp;rsquo;s screen broke to the point that I put tape on it to keep pieces of glass from falling out?
Seems like it in some ways, but maybe most of all because I didn&amp;rsquo;t keep the phone encased in case it fell, which it eventually did, and shattered the screen.
New phone arrived yesterday and was really easy to copy the bulk of data over and download apps again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>phone battery low</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/11/15/phone-battery-low/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2017 21:11:02 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/11/15/phone-battery-low/</guid>
      <description>21:11 Wednesday 15 November 2017 JST As usual, my phone battery is low after not having charged it today. I charged it at JB the past few weeks but forgot tonight.
My computer battery is charged, so I can read Michael John Grist&amp;rsquo;s rewrite of Sen&amp;rsquo;s adventures in The Saint&amp;rsquo;s Rise.
I am on page 170 or so out of 470 and had hoped to finish by 20 November. hmm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>bah my phone is slow</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/07/30/bah-my-phone-is-slow/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2017 20:08:41 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/07/30/bah-my-phone-is-slow/</guid>
      <description>20:08 Sunday 30 July 2017 JST My phone is a slow as year 2000 internet; I guess it is throttle because I went over the allotted bandwidth. bah.
If that&amp;rsquo;s true, I wonder what put me so far over the limit this month.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>wifiing</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/06/15/wifiing/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2016 14:57:26 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/06/15/wifiing/</guid>
      <description>14:57 Wednesday 15 June 2016 JST I&amp;rsquo;m not using wifi as I type this, but I plan to use my mobile wifi when I upload it in 3.. 2.. 1..
14:59 It was working, but we went through a tunnel which seems to have (temporarily) impeded progress, but it recovered without me having to do anything.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lin&#39;s possible new phone</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/11/29/lins-possible-new-phone/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Nov 2015 14:08:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/11/29/lins-possible-new-phone/</guid>
      <description>14:08 Sunday 29 November 2015 JST Lin&amp;rsquo;s like &amp;ldquo;it&amp;rsquo;s shiny and they said it works great!&amp;rdquo;
I&amp;rsquo;m like, &amp;ldquo;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;.. ummm.. maybe you&amp;rsquo;d be more likely to make the right choice if you actually use the phone (a lot more), first.&amp;rdquo;
So we&amp;rsquo;re doing that now. kinda.
15:32 Though Lin gave all her infos, and the clerk scanned both the phone and the sim card as having been selected, we didn&amp;rsquo;t buy anything.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lost my phone</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/02/lost-my-phone/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/02/lost-my-phone/</guid>
      <description>##11:37am Sunday 2 November 2014##
Got off the train, felt no cellphone in my front pocket!
Crap!
I turned around and (stupidly) started angling back toward the train door where we had gotten off, instead of straight back to the train and got on before the doors closed.
D&amp;rsquo;oh!
Went to the lost and found to report it. I was like, &amp;ldquo;so where does that train stop?&amp;rdquo; thinking they could look up that the train that left at 11:37am and know when and where it was scheduled to stop for the day (probably 大崎).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>