<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>yumi on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/yumi/</link>
    <description>Recent content in yumi on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 17:39:23 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/yumi/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>chillin with Travis and them</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/04/30/chillin-with-travis-and-them/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 17:39:23 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/04/30/chillin-with-travis-and-them/</guid>
      <description>17:39 Tuesday 30 April 2019 JST Today Lin and I drove to Travis and Yumi&amp;rsquo;s place to hang out with them and Sakura. Johan was already there and Deji came a bit later. Nice to see everyone again, though in some ways it&amp;rsquo;s like the tribe is getting smaller (and larger!)
No BBQ today due to rain, but we made 手巻き with chicken, eggs, salad, and then ice cream at the end.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apocrypha 17</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/09/22/apocrypha-17/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Sep 2018 00:51:56 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/09/22/apocrypha-17/</guid>
      <description>00:51 Saturday 22 September 2018 JST Saw Miyu briefly tonight at Apocrypha #17, a trip to remember. Met Sabrina who I thought was courageous for the story she told about her family. This was Isaac&amp;rsquo;s second event, and it went really well. Yumi told a story about a transformative experience she had, which sounded to me like it could be a mixed gender version of Mankind Project. Chelsea&amp;rsquo;s story also seemed courageous, regarding personal struggles while on vacation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>dream wearing shoes in public</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/05/28/dream-wearing-shoes-in-public/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2018 05:06:16 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/05/28/dream-wearing-shoes-in-public/</guid>
      <description>05:06 Monday 28 May 2018 JST Walking outside, I realized I was wearing hiking boots and was shocked that I was wearing them while walking around on vacation. I asked store owner if I could have a bag to put them in, but he said he could not give me one, but I could not understand the reason why. I walked further and found a place to put my boots in a locker so I did that and saw Yumi there who taking things out of her locker and she said I could put my shoes with her stuff with kinda the implication that her son would be able to wear them when he got older.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>dream scheduling conflict</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/23/dream-scheduling-conflict/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2017 04:49:53 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/23/dream-scheduling-conflict/</guid>
      <description>04:49 Saturday 23 December 2017 -03 I had a schedule conflict that I detected a few days out, but didn&#39;t try to rectify until the day of the conflict. Nate wanted to have me join a late night adventure sneaking into a dark house that only I knew the layout to find some prize close to midnight. I was more interested in joining Lin to meet Travis and Yumi for a roadtrip that started at 11pm, but planned to meet in nearly the same location, an empty field next to the building that Nate and I were going to explore in the dark.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yay Travis and Yumi are staying in Tokyo!</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/06/yay-travis-and-yumi-are-staying-in-tokyo/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/06/yay-travis-and-yumi-are-staying-in-tokyo/</guid>
      <description>##11:58 Thursday 06 November 2014 JST##
Yay! Travis and Yumi are staying in Tokyo!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>