<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>KTRU on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/ktru/</link>
    <description>Recent content in KTRU on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2013 21:49:41 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/ktru/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>KTRU doing well on soundtap.com/madness</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2013/04/10/ktru-doing-well-on-soundtap.com/madness/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2013 21:49:41 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2013/04/10/ktru-doing-well-on-soundtap.com/madness/</guid>
      <description>##21:49 Wednesday 10 April 2013
9:45pm Wednesday 10 April 2013
Well https://soundtap.com/madness isn&amp;rsquo;t responding correctly, but you can log in and listen to KTRU at https://soundtap.com/ktru and help us win. After 13 April 2013, the contest will be over so listen to whatever you want however you like.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>hey DJ</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2013/03/02/hey-dj/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2013 16:16:29 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2013/03/02/hey-dj/</guid>
      <description>##16:16 Saturday 02 March 2013
I miss DJing; that was so much fun. I just enjoyed communicating with Tom at KTRU during his Saturday midnight shift. He played a song for me, which was awesome, though I didn&amp;rsquo;t know it was for me until he mentioned it hahahaha.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KTRU to the max and 1/2</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2012/12/29/ktru-to-the-max-and-1/2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Dec 2012 16:03:05 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2012/12/29/ktru-to-the-max-and-1/2/</guid>
      <description>##16:03 Saturday 29 December 2012
OMG this is so amazing!!!
First, it&amp;rsquo;s amazing that I can listen to KTRU at all on this fancy series of tubes called the internizz. Second, Fred and I were listening to the Vinyl Frontier&amp;rsquo;s Christmas show a couple nights ago; fun times. but that&amp;rsquo;s not why I&amp;rsquo;m writing.
It&amp;rsquo;s amazing that MK Ultra show is still kickin&amp;rsquo; it. I enjoyed listening to the whole 3 hours played by Dijon, so I called him near the end just to say HI and what&amp;rsquo;s up from Tokyo, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/11/30/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/11/30/</guid>
      <description>Date: Thu, 30 Nov 2000 10:12:22 -0600 From: Lizzie Subject: too late. the door code has been changed and the stickers have all been removed from the outside door. it&#39;s over. and we&#39;ve lost. i&#39;m up at the station now and it&#39;s not a pretty picture. either we do something now or not at all, but if we do anything it must be coordinated and immediate.  9:58am 30 November 2000</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KTRU</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/06/22/ktru/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/06/22/ktru/</guid>
      <description>1:10am CDT Thursday 22 June 2000
 From: ktru Tue 16:36 Subject: Forgot to sign off To: Rob Nugen OPERATOR REPORT ERROR NOTICE This is to inform you of a problem in your entry on the operator report (log) for 6/17/00. You forgot to include the time when you signed off on the log. Please fix your entry the next time you are at the station. Thanks, If you have any questions please ask your Program Director or reply to this e-mail.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ktru</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/06/17/ktru/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/06/17/ktru/</guid>
      <description>11:48pm CDT Saturday 17 June 2000
KTRU required more than twice as much paperwork today, which made for a sub-amazing show. We always have to write down each song artist and title that we play. But today we had to also write in a different log, the artist, title, song writer/composer, and the time the song was played.
The biggest pain in the bootay about all that is figuring out who is the writer or composer!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KTRU</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/06/10/ktru/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/06/10/ktru/</guid>
      <description>7:21pm Saturday 10 june 2000
I&#39;m at KTRU as I type this on my Visor. Mood Swingaz on vinyl performing &#34;The Blessing&#34; It&#39;s been so long since I&#39;ve DJed that it seems weird. But I&#39;ve been cueing perfect segues!! 9:34 pm
Wende called during my so, so I put her on speakerphone as I cued up tracks and played stuff. After a bit I was all &amp;ldquo;okay be quiet; I&amp;rsquo;m &amp;lsquo;bout to go on air.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ktru</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/05/20/ktru/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/05/20/ktru/</guid>
      <description>KTRU 11:33pm CDT Saturday 20 May 2000
Wow! My new KTRU shift is 7 to 10 pm Saturdays during the summer. Ironically, I will not be available for my next two shifts; I&amp;rsquo;ll be at YAC retreat and OKC rally respectively.
Today I had four (4), count-em 4 DJs-in-training during my shift! I feel pretty honored to train DJs, when it seems like just a year ago that Alexis trained me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>fgnet</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/03/22/fgnet/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/03/22/fgnet/</guid>
      <description>The Feel Good Net!! 8:24am CST Wednesday 22 March 2000
Instead of going to KTRU early, I just sent out the Feel Good Net!!, a message I send out about once per week. Now I&amp;rsquo;m zipping off to KTRU!! Listen on the web every Wednesday 9-11am CST!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ktru</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/03/15/ktru/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/03/15/ktru/</guid>
      <description>12:58pm Wednesday 15 March 2000
KTRU was great fun today- had a new listener call in, &amp;ldquo;I just found this station yesterday!&amp;rdquo; I snail mailed him some bumper stickers. A few people requested various artists, and I mostly was able to find them all.
A woman named Lynn (sp) called a few times, requesting different artists - Nick Cave and the somethings, also another artist we didn&amp;rsquo;t have, and The Feelies, which we did have.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ktru</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1999/12/29/ktru/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Dec 1999 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1999/12/29/ktru/</guid>
      <description>2pm 29 December 1999
KTRU was great fun today! I recorded my show (recorded 2 hours of my 3 hour show) for Channing, a youth in Tulsa, who was really excited to expand his musical awareness! I think Side A is more musically expanding&amp;hellip;
But!! The coolest thing: A guy called in; &amp;ldquo;Will you play something by Squarepusher?&amp;rdquo; (I gave my standard non-committal answer; I didn&amp;rsquo;t know if I could find it).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ktru</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1999/12/13/ktru/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 1999 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1999/12/13/ktru/</guid>
      <description>I was on KTRU today &amp;ldquo;helping&amp;rdquo; Alexis interview a guy named Philip Gayle. At first I was anti-impressed with the interview; it seemed trite and unprepared. But that sponteneity really became great fun! So I went out there to see them.
I say &amp;ldquo;helping&amp;rdquo; because I was an unplanned uninvited guest. But Alexis was happy to have me join.
Philip Gayle is just a solo artist. He had 2 little mandolins and would make up songs: &amp;ldquo;I call this one &amp;lsquo;I have too much sugar in my chloaca&amp;rsquo;&amp;rdquo; and just scribble and scratch the strings, for a full five minutes, including licking his fingers and rubbing/squeaking the wooden surface of the mandolin&amp;hellip; crazy!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ktru</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1999/12/07/ktru/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 1999 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1999/12/07/ktru/</guid>
      <description>12:28pm Tuesday 7 December 1999
KTRU was great fun today! I didn&amp;rsquo;t have a theme, but had a few excellent segues. One was priceless! I was playing the Sounds of North American Frogs CD, which consists of hundreds of tracks. Most of them are about 17 seconds long (a few are longer) and of the following format:
 This frog, the blahblahbinous blahvine, has a trill twitter sound much like its cousin, the bluhvine bloovious.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>san antonio rally</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1999/10/29/san-antonio-rally/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Oct 1999 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1999/10/29/san-antonio-rally/</guid>
      <description>(transcribed from my diary) [except for text in brackets]
29-31 october 1999
5:31am Saturday 30 October 1999
Oh my god it&amp;rsquo;s 5:21 am. I&amp;rsquo;m at San Antonio Rally. After work I was all &amp;ldquo;Ohshit! I didn&amp;rsquo;t get the van!&amp;rdquo; [it would be a very unfortunate situation to have 12 youth ready to go to San Antonio and me have to say, &amp;ldquo;um, I forgot to pick up the van from the rental place.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>amazone</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1999/10/16/amazone/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Oct 1999 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1999/10/16/amazone/</guid>
      <description>16 oct 1999
I came in to work today for the speedy internet connection, and so I could review CDs while I&amp;rsquo;m online. At home, I use linux to be online, but I haven&amp;rsquo;t set it up to be able to listen to CDs.
Today I reviewed pro audio by neil landstrumm, and a ma zone by zap mama.
Neil CD was techno-esque with mostly two step (boom tik boom tik boom tik sound) and lots of layers of electronics on that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>laundry work</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1999/10/07/laundry-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Oct 1999 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1999/10/07/laundry-work/</guid>
      <description>7 october 1999
Today it was decidedly cold when I woke up! I&amp;rsquo;ve been sleepin&amp;rsquo; with only a sheet for the past some weeks, and my bedroom window is open so Spot can get in and out via his tree. But this morning I woke up and brrrr! It was like 60 degrees! I couldn&amp;rsquo;t find my comforter in my sleepy state, so I grabbed my sleeping bag and recuddled myself up for a bit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ktru texas</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1999/10/05/ktru-texas/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 1999 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1999/10/05/ktru-texas/</guid>
      <description>5 October 1999
This morning before KTRU, I purchased a cassette tape to record my show for Zara, who requested a Rob Mix tape. When she asked me for such a tape, I was all, &amp;ldquo;when will I ever have time to make a mix tape???&amp;rdquo; Oh yeah.. I can just record my show at KTRU! So that is what I did.
However, at KTRU I was not able to get the station turned on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ktru thre</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1999/09/27/ktru-thre/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 1999 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1999/09/27/ktru-thre/</guid>
      <description>27 September 1999
Last Tuesday I had fun at KTRU. So much fun that I still want to write about it 6 days later!!!
I had made a decision before I even started to play &amp;ldquo;Coffee&amp;rdquo; by Awol off of a certain SKA compilation we have. It&amp;rsquo;s a good wake-up song that I thought would be appropriate for 9am.
The song happened to be track 3 on the CD.
Ah, a gimmick for the day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>eric at ktru</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1999/09/17/eric-at-ktru/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 1999 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1999/09/17/eric-at-ktru/</guid>
      <description>17 September 1999
Friday night is MK Ultra night at KTRU, so I cruised out there to say HI to Tejus and Eric, who was spinning ambient techno on the air! Eric is great fun (same Eric who I DJed with about a month ago 1-4am) and I feel a certain comradery with him, since he&amp;rsquo;s just getting started a spinning and mixing vinyl. It was great to watch and talk and see him get better.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ktru new shift</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1999/09/07/ktru-new-shift/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 1999 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1999/09/07/ktru-new-shift/</guid>
      <description>7 September 1999
Today started a new semester at KTRU. My new shift is now Tuesdays from 9am to 11am.
This is my first semester with only a 2 hour shift! Holy cow it went by so quickly today!
The coolest thing is that at 9am, no one is on before me, so I get to turn on the station in the morning. So check it out each Tuesday at 9am CST (www.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ktru eric</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1999/08/21/ktru-eric/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Aug 1999 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1999/08/21/ktru-eric/</guid>
      <description>15:46 Saturday 21 August 1999
Last night (and every Friday night) KTRU broadcast MK Ultra show - 3 hours of live DJs mixing jungle or techno or breakbeat or any basic rave music. I love the show so I go to watch the DJs spin and basically just think, &amp;ldquo;wow! [I wonder if I would enjoy spending enough time to get that good?]&amp;rdquo;
Last night Chris Anderson was spinning; he&amp;rsquo;s big in the Houston rave scene and maybe way bigger than that; I know he&amp;rsquo;s spinning in Santa Fe tonight.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ktru jury conflict</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1999/08/17/ktru-jury-conflict/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Aug 1999 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1999/08/17/ktru-jury-conflict/</guid>
      <description>6:54am Tuesday 17 August 1999
Today I have jury duty. The summons came by mail to my apartment while I was in Iowa. When I saw the summons, I was like, &amp;ldquo;uh oh- I hope I didn&amp;rsquo;t miss it!&amp;rdquo;
I didn&amp;rsquo;t miss it. But I did miss the fact that I am scheduled for KTRU on the same day. Doh! I caught this too late and requested a sub only a couple days ago.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ktru jason</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1999/05/19/ktru-jason/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 May 1999 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1999/05/19/ktru-jason/</guid>
      <description>9pm Tuesday 19 May 1999
Today Jason and I worked for a few hours pulling phone cables down walls at a company where I installed about 28 cables, but hadn&amp;rsquo;t pulled them down the walls. We didn&amp;rsquo;t have exactly the right tools to use, but we had a lot of fun and got most of them done.
We could have finished them all, but at noon, we had to leave. I asked Renee, &amp;ldquo;have you ever listened to KTRU?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ktru</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1999/04/15/ktru/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 1999 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1999/04/15/ktru/</guid>
      <description>(transcribed from my diary)
Thursday 15 April 1999
Wednesday Night dinner was at Chuck E. Cheese last night. We were there until like 10pm. I played a race driving game against Jon several times in a row; he beat me about 60 percent of the time. I didn&amp;rsquo;t crawl in the ball crawl.
It was like 10pm ish by the time we left. I had to go to bed before KTRU.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ktru ultimate</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1999/04/08/ktru-ultimate/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Apr 1999 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1999/04/08/ktru-ultimate/</guid>
      <description>7:12pm Thursday 8 April 1999
Aw man, first, super duper special thanks to Wende for reminding me last night that today is Thursday and I was supposed to work at KTRU!!!! I had totally forgotten it, and she mentioned it offhandedly (whatever that is supposed to mean) and I was like, &amp;ldquo;!!!!!!!!!&amp;rdquo;
Wende and I had just eaten at Dude and Veronica&amp;rsquo;s house and it was gettin&amp;rsquo; late. We still had to go to Sterling McCall to get Scott after he had his timing belt and water pump replaced.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ktru 7</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1999/04/05/ktru-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 1999 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1999/04/05/ktru-7/</guid>
      <description>5 April 1999
On Saturday morning I was on at KTRU from 7 to 9am. On the way driving there, only static was on the station; that meant no one was there. This brings to mind one question for me: &amp;ldquo;will I be able to get into the station?&amp;rdquo;
More specifically, will I be able to get into the building in which the station is located? I&amp;rsquo;m not a student at Rice University, so I don&amp;rsquo;t have a card that will let me into the building if it&amp;rsquo;s locked.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ktru application</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/12/21/ktru-application/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Dec 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/12/21/ktru-application/</guid>
      <description>KTRU application
21 December 1998
I am sure I mentioned previously that I applied to be a DJ at KTRU. I never heard back from them until I got this letter: To: thunderrabbit@cheerful.com Subject: KTRU Application  hi, i am ellen&#39;s sister and i work at KTRU (i actually was the one who opened the door for you, although i didn&#39;t know it was you). i know your brother, fred, although he always confuses me with a girl named lee meredith, and i also know mike ossowski (he doesn&#39;t confuse me with anybody) and perhaps other YRUUers that you would know.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>