<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>today on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/today/</link>
    <description>Recent content in today on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 16:45:26 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/today/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>today</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/08/30/today/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 16:45:26 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/08/30/today/</guid>
      <description>16:45 Friday 30 August 2019 JST Several different things on my day off today. Mostly related to work, where I realized the value of having a staging server with non-live data. &amp;ldquo;Ohhh that is right; I tested saving data as well..&amp;rdquo; when AB was like, &amp;ldquo;Um, where is the Azabujuban record?&amp;rdquo; which had been renamed to &amp;ldquo;Doraemon 5e5433a38e2b035689a75c9ed11ffb0e&amp;rdquo;
Once I fixed all of those (about 8 different records) based on the old live DB which is still available at cli with mysql as root, I watched episode 3 of The Naked Director.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Friday</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/07/26/friday/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2019 10:22:29 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/07/26/friday/</guid>
      <description>10:22 Friday 26 July 2019 JST Nice meditation this morning and just finished an online group meeting for Integration Group Coordinators. It went well, though some &amp;ldquo;summaries&amp;rdquo; from small groups seemed like they may be as long as the originals.
I wanna do some work for AB, ConSwi, TEDx, and meditation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>men&#39;s group today</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/05/06/mens-group-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2019 18:11:18 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/05/06/mens-group-today/</guid>
      <description>08:40 Monday 06 May 2019 JST Right now I&amp;rsquo;m headed to Hiroo for two (2) workshops. One, for men already in the group, a Mission workshop to find or refine our life missions. Why are we here in this world, on this planet? What value do we bring to the world? How?
The next workshop is for new men, an introduction to our work. I think a couple men will attend even though I am the only person who has responded on Meetup for our second Journey of the Heart workshop.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>today</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/04/26/today/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 13:53:19 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/04/26/today/</guid>
      <description>13:53 Friday 26 April 2019 JST Today has seemed busy; my brain was spinning with what to do next for a while this morning. I ended up creating a new Part entry for Marble Track 3 (tssfobls) before attending men&amp;rsquo;s group meeting (Integration Group Council).
Now I am on the way back from Tokyo station where I met Tariq and Jon (for different reasons). Tariq about ConSwi, and Jon to give him a bag he left at our house.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>today workin</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/01/09/today-workin/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2019 20:42:35 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/01/09/today-workin/</guid>
      <description>20:42 Wednesday 09 January 2019 JST Today was a long day, starting with recording a first draft of a video for my first GoFundMe campaign, then two TY lessons, two MKP meetings, lunch with Tomoko, then an hour chillin with &amp;ldquo;a flower in each hand&amp;rdquo; behind the desk of the Sweets Party Attendants, having a non-lesson with them because they have nothing going on.
During this non-lesson, Tomoko showed me her &amp;ldquo;personal こたつ&amp;rdquo; which consisted of a heater under her desk and a blanket strategically arranged to drape down over her legs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>to do today</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/10/11/to-do-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2018 13:41:38 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/10/11/to-do-today/</guid>
      <description> 13:41 Thursday 11 October 2018 JST  contact BH about MKP local site write MT3 entry go to SCC update Redmine for AB work done recently teach at SCC go to Akihabara teach in Akihabara go home eat Japanese homework Japanese lesson check emails from TY update MT3 site to have latest video on top page  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>busy morning</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/09/20/busy-morning/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Sep 2018 13:41:47 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/09/20/busy-morning/</guid>
      <description>13:41 Thursday 20 September 2018 JST Slept late until 8 am after getting home late after long day yesterday.
Worked on Marble Track 3, where I have just linked to the main scene the scene which explains the chopstick falling from the heavens.
Great MKP men&amp;rsquo;s group today; I got to figure out (at least one of the reasons) why I was upset about people not doing what they say they would do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>plans for today and forever</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/08/12/plans-for-today-and-forever/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Aug 2018 08:25:50 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/08/12/plans-for-today-and-forever/</guid>
      <description>08:25 Sunday 12 August 2018 JST After watching &amp;ldquo;A Journey Towards Inner Beauty,&amp;rdquo; Shirley Liu being interviewed on The Happy Mindset,
  I have been thinking about my morning routine. Today I came upon a grand idea to exercise each morning by walking around my local area for perhaps 20 or 30 minutes on days that I do not have to leave at 5:45 in the morning.
Lin walked with me today, and we saw some interesting old (and not as interesting new) houses in our neighborhood on streets I had never previously used.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>today / recently</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/08/06/today-/-recently/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2018 22:27:39 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/08/06/today-/-recently/</guid>
      <description>22:27 Monday 06 August 2018 JST I contacted the organizer of TEDx Roppongi, which is scheduled for November 3rd of this year. I&amp;rsquo;m not sure if I will end up helping with that, but I&amp;rsquo;m interested, because eventually I would like to speak on stage at a TEDx event.
In other news, I&amp;rsquo;m preparing for a workshop to be held on November 23rd, which will be an introduction to the men&amp;rsquo;s group work that we do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>no SOGO</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/06/24/no-sogo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jun 2018 10:08:29 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/06/24/no-sogo/</guid>
      <description> 10:08 Sunday 24 June 2018 JST No SOGO today due to rain.
I hope Mark got the message; I met him on the train yesterday and invited him to join.
So what to do today?
Plan:
 write in Japanese work on MT3 fix https://robnugen.com/geocaching to refresh to https://new.robnugen.com/geocaching  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>(teaching) today</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/05/30/teaching-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 May 2018 23:03:40 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/05/30/teaching-today/</guid>
      <description>23:03 Wednesday 30 May 2018 JST On Wednesdays, I wake up at 5am and leave the house at 5:45am so I can get on a train that arrives in Noborito at 6:29am but leaves Noborito at 6:57am. That gives 58 minutes of sleeping time on the train including both waiting and riding to Kawasaki.
Then lesson in Solid Square with Ayano, Takato, Yohei, Ai, and I talking about reasons we (dis)like certain months or seasons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>today</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/05/06/today/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 May 2018 20:47:42 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/05/06/today/</guid>
      <description>20:47 Sunday 06 May 2018 JST Egad I got my credit card bill (yay I have a credit card) and holy shipes I should have been a bit more careful. Gotta sort out $450 by the tenth. I would think I should have this shit figured out by now.
In other news, Lin and I walked into one of the unfinished homes near our house. Did not stay too long and did not go to the second floor because there were no stairs installed yet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>today</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/22/today/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Apr 2018 00:06:34 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/22/today/</guid>
      <description>00:06 Sunday 22 April 2018 JST oops it is tomorrow already, but today Lin and I had neighbors Richard and Mai over for lunch, and then went for a walk with them and Fitz. We found a geocache.
https://coord.info/GLVJHGHK

I got a sharp flake of plastic splintered into my foot on the way home. Thankfully Lin was able to get it out relatively easily.
Today was the last day for Build Your Speaker Bio course; I will miss everyone and am really thankful for how much Soness helped with my speaker sheet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>sentence remix</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/13/sentence-remix/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Apr 2018 09:24:09 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/13/sentence-remix/</guid>
      <description>09:24 Friday 13 April 2018 JST うちの近くにアパートの建設がまだ続いています。 Apartments are still being built near my house.
今日、そこで見たけど写真を撮らなかった。 Today I looked, but did not take pictures.
猫の写真を反映しましょうか。　Why don&amp;rsquo;t I post a cat picture?

子猫の写真を反映する事ができるサイトはプレースキッテンと言います。 A site which allows posting kitten pics is called placekitten.
今日ジオキャッシュを探す時間がないので探さない。 I don&amp;rsquo;t have time to look for geocaches today, so I won&amp;rsquo;t find any.
しかし、他の人はジオキャッシュの時間があるから見つけられます。 But someone has time, so a geocache will be found.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Planet on Purpose</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/02/planet-on-purpose/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Apr 2018 22:15:35 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/02/planet-on-purpose/</guid>
      <description>22:15 Monday 02 April 2018 JST No one attended co-gender group (besides me) today. I read several pages of Planet on Purpose by Brandon Peele. Quite a good book for me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>today</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/20/today/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Mar 2018 23:37:51 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/20/today/</guid>
      <description>23:37 Tuesday 20 March 2018 JST Yesterday I studied during co-gender group; no one else came.
Today I broadcast for two hours on Youtube for Marble Track 3.
Today before the men&amp;rsquo;s group, I met Rohini in Hiroo at Aloha Today restaurant. Told her about my experiences in Portland. She bought me dinner (yay + yum) and then I went to men&amp;rsquo;s circle. 4 men (including myself) attended the men&amp;rsquo;s group.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>today</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/16/today/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 23:23:02 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/16/today/</guid>
      <description>23:23 Friday 16 March 2018 JST Kinda lazy day, but now am finally caught up after trip last weekend. Did not get as much done with Complice items as I wanted, but still got more done than I think I would have without having Complice as a reminder, or without my accountability partner on the site.
I watched the most recent two episodes of かケグルイ(sp) and had a Japanese lesson with Fumiko.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>today</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/14/today/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Mar 2018 21:12:11 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/14/today/</guid>
      <description>21:12 Wednesday 14 March 2018 JST After my morning lesson I had a big gap during which I had a big nap because dang I was tired. I seem to have gotten over the jet lag (new vocabulary word for some students today). I was roused by a security guard when I tried to nap on a grassy field on 3F of Lazona (next to Eggs N Things (or something)).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>today</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/08/today/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Mar 2018 18:16:25 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/08/today/</guid>
      <description>18:16 Thursday 08 March 2018 JST Today I spent the morning setting up a test image upload page to see why I can&amp;rsquo;t get the main page to work via https.
Frustrating: the test page is working fine.
Working, I was distracted from online integration group, and then zoned to SCC and found out the manager is leaving soon.
Now in Akihabara about to go to GG lesson.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>today</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/03/today/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Mar 2018 08:23:35 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/03/today/</guid>
      <description>08:23 Saturday 03 March 2018 JST In Complice I added 22 Intentions for today ranging from online courses to programming, to fixing the ugg boot which Bryn bought me back in the day. Also, gotta leave at 10:30am to TY today, which is two hours from now, so I am tempted to work on MT3 in this time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>today</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/02/26/today/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2018 22:57:54 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/02/26/today/</guid>
      <description>22:57 Monday 26 February 2018 JST Lesson at IL, then session with E, then lesson at UG, then chillin&amp;rsquo; until co-gender group tonight.
Four people in attendance (including myself), and great work tonight by all. So proud of everyone!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>today</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/11/16/today/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2017 13:18:54 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/11/16/today/</guid>
      <description>13:18 Thursday 16 November 2017 JST Funny talking to Scotty on Marco Polo; he kept not being able to hear me until I was like &amp;ldquo;okay bye&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;okay I hope you could hear it that time!&amp;rdquo;
I am headed to Kawasaki to support the guides in the English versions of their work. Then GG lesson in Akihabara.
Quick online I-group today; everyone checked out so it was just me and my coach near North Zulch, Texas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Headed to Nagano</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/08/18/headed-to-nagano/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2017 07:54:47 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/08/18/headed-to-nagano/</guid>
      <description>07:54 Friday 18 August 2017 JST We are leaving at 10:30, after my virtual I-group meeting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>today</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/03/23/today/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2017 15:33:02 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/03/23/today/</guid>
      <description>15:33 Thursday 23 March 2017 JST Bleary eyed wake up with Noisy at 5:30am.
Was genki and dancing around by 6am to wake up Lin.
cold cold walk to station and caught 6:?? train then in Kawasaki by 7:30 for my 7:50 lesson.
Online I-group after the lesson featured lots of disconnects by the free wifi provided by Wired Cafe. But free, for the price of lunch.
Bought a trackball mouse afterward.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>today</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/01/06/today/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2017 23:50:28 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/01/06/today/</guid>
      <description> 23:50 Friday 06 January 2017 JST  I nearly wrote two emails to ask for help with HHS presentation, but I realized I was kinda seeking permission, which I don&amp;rsquo;t need. I invited some peeps to HHS workshop I did two hours of work on Ansible, trying to get Redmine installed I did 1 hour of Japanese lesson, trying to understand おく  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>plan</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/12/18/plan/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2016 08:01:40 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/12/18/plan/</guid>
      <description>08:01 Sunday 18 December 2016 JST I plan to work for a bit to create an English version of a website and then head out to SOGO. The weather looks stunningly good.
10:04 Monday 19 December 2016 JST The weather was great. Workout was great. Some of the organizers were hung over, and others were hung over enough to not attend.
Eric invited people to Crayon House (vegan buffet) to which I had been once before; it was great this time as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>today</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/09/05/today/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2016 21:40:02 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/09/05/today/</guid>
      <description>21:40 Monday 05 September 2016 JST Great lesson this morning; we estimated the viability of a product based on its description. This process provided a review of vocab from last time so I think it was really useful.
Worked at work and updated Ghost Inspector tests to deal with new version of Datatables. Moving to version 1.10 of datatables I needed to change Ghost Inspector to find the search field as type=&amp;ldquo;search&amp;rdquo; instead of type=&amp;ldquo;text&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>today</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/02/29/today/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Feb 2016 17:37:56 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/02/29/today/</guid>
      <description>17:37 Monday 29 February 2016 JST Today I sent Gary Summer Vacation, and I sent Three Straps to Scout Seven.
I logged on to streamen (NSFW) to broadcast my feet today. Today was the first time I chatted with anyone on the site! One person seemed to really like my feet, but didn&amp;rsquo;t send any tips. But it was enough to encourage me to keep trying.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>today</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/06/13/today/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jun 2015 18:15:25 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/06/13/today/</guid>
      <description>18:15 Saturday 13 June 2015 JST Today I worked on getting Hugo to do some things I&amp;rsquo;d like it to do. I created a crappy theme and used pagination functions which spewed out 300 pages worth of entries.
Need to get prev/next working before I&amp;rsquo;ll actually have it a bit further than Middleman, but wooodoggie Hugo sure is faster than Middleman!
Worked on pong a bit. Now the AI is a bit more random about what ball it chases, but it&amp;rsquo;s definitely not smart about it!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>to do to day</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/05/22/to-do-to-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 May 2015 18:56:30 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/05/22/to-do-to-day/</guid>
      <description>12:00 Friday 22 May 2015 JST To do today:
 upload journal entries burn copy of Debian iso to DVD burn copy of SystemRescueCd to DVD work on tickets while those are running install new HD in new old PC see if I can install Debian on new computer write to Mutsumi work on Unity proofread Mt Mitake CSETI event notes temp staff Chris  18:56 Friday 22 May 2015 JST Middle of installing Debian now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Plan to do today</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/03/29/plan-to-do-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2015 10:42:31 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/03/29/plan-to-do-today/</guid>
      <description> 10:42 Sunday 29 March 2015 JST  fast all day (in progress) meditate (34 minutes woo!) upload latest journal entries (not inc. this one because Middleman is too slow) reboot my computer study Japanese post daily meditation thread to bittippers seven minute workout 80 more pushups (20 are inc. in 7 min workout) post about 80s cafe Japanese class schedule appt at Apple Store go for a bike ride with Lin begin to convert date formats of old journal entries try hugo instead of middleman for website do tetris unity tutorial meet Tariq  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do Today</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/03/05/do-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2015 07:36:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/03/05/do-today/</guid>
      <description>##07:36 Thursday 05 March 2015 JST##
 Add to Sunday prep for AB server update Check textbook (1 hour) pushups * 15 Clean kitty litter (5 mins) post daily meditation thread to bittippers Redo work on #2401 after having received new set of images (1 hour hopefully) pushups * 15 Tell Lin to check her schedule (at noon) Study Japanese (1 hour) pushups * 20  ##10:20
Well checking the textbook took nearly 3 hours, but ま, it&amp;rsquo;s a textbook and needs to be perfect.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do Today</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/03/03/do-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2015 10:43:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/03/03/do-today/</guid>
      <description>##10:43 Tuesday 03 March 2015 JST##
Slightly different than other todo lists I&amp;rsquo;ve made, I will put time limits on items today, during which I currently have 6 hours available:
 check illustrations (1 hour) get Redmine to send emails (1 hour) create invoice from Redmine (1 hour) try to fix journal entries so unadulterated Middleman can use them (1 hour)  If I had a tomato timer, I&amp;rsquo;d count off 15 minute increments with it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>