<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>blog on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in blog on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2019 11:27:31 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Simple steps for dealing with anger</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/blog/2019/06/27/simple-steps-for-dealing-with-anger/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2019 11:27:31 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/blog/2019/06/27/simple-steps-for-dealing-with-anger/</guid>
      <description>1) breathe. Focus on your breathing until the initial wave of anger has passed. It may help to focus on counting the breaths.
Allow your breathing to deepen and slow.
2) label. Say you yourself, &amp;ldquo;I feel angry.&amp;rdquo; Labeling the emotion brings your thoughtful brain back online.
This helps move beyond the Fight or Flight reaction of the reptilian brain
3) acknowledge. Recognize the steps that brought you into this situation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>evaluating several hugo themes</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/06/25/evaluating-several-hugo-themes/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2019 15:19:12 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/06/25/evaluating-several-hugo-themes/</guid>
      <description>15:19 Tuesday 25 June 2019 JST I have gone through all the themes in the repo for All Hugo&amp;rsquo;s Themes and come up with a list of several which do a lot of these things:
 content on top page list page for blog/ list page for journal/ paginate blog/ paginate journal/ show tags paginate tags show categories paginate categories nicely show Youtube videos  I don&amp;rsquo;t know if a single one does all the above things, but here is my list so far:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Save Money Through Meditation</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/blog/2019/06/22/save-money-through-meditation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2019 14:27:22 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/blog/2019/06/22/save-money-through-meditation/</guid>
      <description>My TV says if I buy this or that toothpaste / car / ______ then I will be happy. What TV doesn&amp;rsquo;t tell me is that happiness is temporary. Instead of buying my way into temporary happiness, I can sit my way into lasting happiness.
Sitting allows me to reset my brain to my center, my spirit, my essence. This is where permanent happiness resides. In this moment, sitting in what I call the Ever Present Present, I can just be, happily.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What do emotions tell us</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/blog/2019/06/18/what-do-emotions-tell-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2019 21:22:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/blog/2019/06/18/what-do-emotions-tell-us/</guid>
      <description>Sticking with the basics, we have joy and fear.
Joy is how I feel when I have what I want, or I don&amp;rsquo;t want what I don&amp;rsquo;t have. I am aligned with what is, and have no need or desire to change it.
Fear is the emotion which says I don&amp;rsquo;t have enough information. This is usually about an unknown future. I come to a proverbial fork in the road and could simply choose arbitrarily, but if there is a part of me that wants to choose the &amp;ldquo;right&amp;rdquo; option, I may feel fear about choosing the &amp;ldquo;wrong&amp;rdquo; option.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>