<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>skate on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/skate/</link>
    <description>Recent content in skate on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2000 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/skate/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>skate</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/01/13/skate/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/01/13/skate/</guid>
      <description>SKATE!! 11:07pm Thursday 13 January 2000
Started as we normally do on Thursday nights, meeting at Texas Art Supply (very close to my house) This night, only Scott and I showed up. I was quite excited to skate, and a bit glad that it was only he and I; I haven&amp;rsquo;t been out in so long that I didn&amp;rsquo;t want to hold back a big group.
We set out toward downtown, and within 2 blocks, my legs were burning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>before skate</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1999/10/14/before-skate/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 1999 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1999/10/14/before-skate/</guid>
      <description>14 october 1999
Yay!
Today was payday at my work. $823 for me for two weeks&amp;rsquo; work. Today I scoured the internet for a bulk email management program, but found only 2 possibilities for us.
We need one that will allow us to send a unique attachment to 30000 email addresses, keep track of bounces, easily resend to a few addresses, and that&amp;rsquo;s about it.
I found tons and tons of software to help spammers scour the Internet for email addresses, and how to send email &amp;ldquo;without your ISP knowing you&amp;rsquo;re sending bulk email!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>skate tired</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1999/10/08/skate-tired/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 1999 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1999/10/08/skate-tired/</guid>
      <description>8 oct 1999
I went skating last night but didn&amp;rsquo;t really have the energy to do much. I fell once while jumping over a road hump thing. The fall was not bad, but was an indication that something was amiss in my skating abilities. I had never previously fallen while jumping a road hump! (There are times when I don&amp;rsquo;t make it all the way over the hump, but that doesn&amp;rsquo;t cause a fall.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>skate 9999</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1999/09/09/skate-9999/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 1999 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1999/09/09/skate-9999/</guid>
      <description>9-9-99
Tonight, this is where we skated: follow the blue line starting from near the top right corner.
(One inch = one mile)
 click map for more info</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>skate late</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1999/08/20/skate-late/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Aug 1999 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1999/08/20/skate-late/</guid>
      <description>20 August 1999
Last night was Thursday, so I went skating. No one else was in our designated parking lot at 8pm, so I sat in Scott&amp;rsquo;s open trunk writing in my diary for a few moments. I was literally ready to leave at 8:09 when two people arrived at the same moment.
We got our skates on and we headed toward downtown. I love skating through downtown. The construction, the traffic, the unlimited space, steps, curbs; all the things that are unlike a skating rink, I love.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>sandy skate</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1999/08/17/sandy-skate/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Aug 1999 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1999/08/17/sandy-skate/</guid>
      <description>(transcribed from my diary)
11:45pm Tuesday 17 August 1999
Skated from TX art Supply down to Herrman Park around by medical center around rice University. Oh- I zipped down the hill by Miller Outdoor Theater twice and around Rice and got ice cream at Walgreens in Rice Village area. and I met Gwen and Kelly and Darwin (&amp;ldquo;Like Charles&amp;rdquo;) and Roberta and then skated back toward my house along Hazard hauling ass and BLUH LAM I hit sand and my skates stopped and I fell bang on the sandy asphalt almost into a parked car.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>new skate group</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1999/08/10/new-skate-group/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Aug 1999 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1999/08/10/new-skate-group/</guid>
      <description>10 August 1999
Last night I went skating with a group called Inline Swine. Far as I can tell, they don&amp;rsquo;t associate themselves with the name so much as associating themselves with, &amp;ldquo;we meet on Tuesdays and Thursdays at 8pm at Texas Art Supply.&amp;rdquo;
I found the group while skating alone downtown 3 weeks ago. They were about a block away so I caught up with them. I discovered they were cool and they skate regularly so I may hook up with this group regularly!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>god dance skate connect</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/12/19/god-dance-skate-connect/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Dec 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/12/19/god-dance-skate-connect/</guid>
      <description>god, Y2K, dance, skate, connect, all in one day!
1:11pm Saturday 19 December 1998 (10496)

(transcribed from my diary)
I just spent 2 hours online doing email and updating website and the SWD YRUU website. Yesterday was asesome! To kick it off, Glen called me back and was super exciting about signing up with Flashnet! yay!! Then Ben Easton and I went skating around Rice University, got kicked off (gently) by a Rice Cop and went to eat at Bibas and discussed Y2K predictions, and our philosophies of god and cosmology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>skate to uh</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/11/11/skate-to-uh/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/11/11/skate-to-uh/</guid>
      <description>Skate to UH main campus
5:45pm Wednesday 11 November 1998
Today after doing computer stuff, I decided it was high time I went skating. (Who made that term &#34;high time&#34; ?) As I shut down my computer and my left hand brain, I wondered where to skate. I wanted a challenge, and I didn&#39;t want to just skate downtown. I thought about going down Memorial Drive to the Picnic Loop in Memorial Park, but I didn&#39;t feel like messing with traffic on Memorial Drive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>skate galveston</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/10/13/skate-galveston/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/10/13/skate-galveston/</guid>
      <description>Skated at Galveston
13 October 1998
This morning I went to Galveston to skate. &#34;Galveston?&#34; you may ask. It&#39;s the city on the Gulf of Mexico 60 miles south of Houston on I-45. It&#39;s where 3 lanes each direction of I-45 melts into asphalt surface road with lights at mile marker 0. Galveston. So anyway, I drove there early this morning - like 8am and parked on Stuart Beach. I walked slowly around the beach and waded in the water, and even sat down in the shallow surf for a while, all while reading my new JavaScript book.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>skate drum corps</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/07/24/skate-drum-corps/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jul 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/07/24/skate-drum-corps/</guid>
      <description>Skate and skate
24 July 1998
Today I went skating!! I totally was all like &#34;I&#39;m going skating&#34; and I just decided to skate to Herrman Park and went basically down Montrose, a pretty heavily trafficked (sp??) 4 lane + turn lane street. The traffic was a bit heavy as it was rush hour, so I mostly stayed on the rough and tumble sidewalks. The wind was pretty amazingly blowing against me; I looked forward to having it behind me on the way back!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>skate and imax</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/07/11/skate-and-imax/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jul 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/07/11/skate-and-imax/</guid>
      <description>Skate and IMax
11 July 1998
Each day this week, I&#39;ve been working at the New Warrior Lodge. (see Men In Mission for details) The biggest thing we did this week was mail out a couple hundred directories of men who have completed the training. The coolest thing about the work is I get a hug each time I come in to the &#34;office&#34; and I don&#39;t have to wear shoes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>stream of conscious skate with blood</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/05/22/stream-of-conscious-skate-with-blood/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 May 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/05/22/stream-of-conscious-skate-with-blood/</guid>
      <description>Wild Skating Adventure
22 May 1998
I am home from work. Take this damn button down shirt off. Damn pants. Damn leather shoes but they are kinda comfortable and would make good slippers. Damn socks. Damn undershirt. Freedom. Underwear stays on because I want to go skate but first: refrigerator grab a quick something. No. close the door. I am not hungry. Okay. I&#39;m cool. Where&#39;s my skates? Um I think they&#39;re outside hafto get my keys where&#39;s my keys?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>skate with diane</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/05/14/skate-with-diane/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 May 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/05/14/skate-with-diane/</guid>
      <description>Skating
14 May 1998
I just got back from skating downtown with Diane. It was the first time we&#39;ve skated in months! And before that it was like half a year before we had skated! I excitedly described the hopes and visions I have for the cluster, and that I&#39;d like to create a position where I can actually make some dollars doing that which I love. Diane asked about the new phone number for Wende that&#39;s indicated on my answering machine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>thanksgiving day skate</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1997/11/27/thanksgiving-day-skate/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 1997 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1997/11/27/thanksgiving-day-skate/</guid>
      <description>Thursday 27 November 1997
Happy Thanksgiving!!
I just got back from skating all around the Thanksgiving Day Parade in downtown Houston. I started at a lazy 10:00 in the am, strapped on skates and skated all the way down Dallas Street toward downtown. As I approached, a small fragmented crowd of parents and kids and baby strollers dispersed away from where I knew the parade must be. Was it over already?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>third annual Thanksgiving Eve skate</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1997/11/26/third-annual-thanksgiving-eve-skate/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 1997 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1997/11/26/third-annual-thanksgiving-eve-skate/</guid>
      <description>27 November 1997
Last night Jim E and I embarked on our Third Annual Thanksgiving Eve Skate. He got to my house at like 9:30pm (after my dad and I saw Alien Resurrection with Sigourney Weaver; it wasn&#39;t that super great of a movie; see it at matinee price.) and we drove to downtown to begin our adventure.
Once on skates, we cruised down to Jones Plaza where there were many buses full of performers who had just practiced their dance routines for the parade.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>skate perfect timing</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1997/10/16/skate-perfect-timing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 1997 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1997/10/16/skate-perfect-timing/</guid>
      <description>16 October 1997
I just got back from my latest Wild Skating Adventure!
I tossed my skates and stuff into the back of Wende&#39;s truck and drove to UH Downtown as she was getting off work. She stepped out of the building as I was in the back of the truck putting my skates on. I offered to take her mail to the post office, since it wouldn&#39;t take me as long to get there, but she declined the offer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>skate with Diane at Rice Stadium</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1997/03/13/skate-with-diane-at-rice-stadium/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 1997 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1997/03/13/skate-with-diane-at-rice-stadium/</guid>
      <description>13 March 1997
I just got back from my latest Wild Skating Adventure.
Starting from my apartment, I skated over to Empire Cafe&#39; to meet Diane, one of my skater buds. We chatted for a bit while I got some water and then she got on her skates and we went. We did not really have a destination in mind except maybe to skate along Fannin street to find some lilies for Wende, who is returning tomorrow at 9am from Hawaii!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>lovely Saturday skate</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1997/03/08/lovely-saturday-skate/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 1997 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1997/03/08/lovely-saturday-skate/</guid>
      <description>8 March 1997
Today is a wonderful Saturday, and I spontaneously decided this morning to skate. Started at my apartment, through the intersection which is no longer under construction, down Taft to Allen Parkway (where the light didn&#39;t agree with me so I had to go slowly through the intersection) and toward downtown.
I skated gently to Jones Plaza, where I was surprised to find some guys digging a trench through one side of the block.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>random skating</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1997/03/01/random-skating/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 1997 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1997/03/01/random-skating/</guid>
      <description>1 March 1997
Last night I skated hard for the first time in a long time. It had been since Thanksgiving of last year, so my endurance was low. But I still had fun.
I started from my apartment, skating down the street to where it&#39;s all under construction. Watching traffic patterns carefully, calculating trajectories and the reactions of drivers, I rolled smoothly between the barrels and between the cars, then accelerated toward oncoming traffic in a blocked-off section of street.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>skating in Chicago</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1996/08/31/skating-in-chicago/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 1996 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1996/08/31/skating-in-chicago/</guid>
      <description>31 August 1996
This Labor Day weekend I am in Chicago visiting my friend Laura. Yesterday I went skating. She lives 1 block from Lake Shore Drive which curves around her section of Lake Michigan. I cruised over to the bike and skate path they have along the beachfront. It&#39;s mostly nice smooth asphalt, with a couple of steps down toward the shore, which is sand in some case, asphalt or concrete in others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>skate frisbee job search</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1996/08/02/skate-frisbee-job-search/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 1996 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1996/08/02/skate-frisbee-job-search/</guid>
      <description>2 August 1996
Last night was my most recent Wild Skating Adventure. I started at Fuzzy&#39;s at about 9pm and skated down to Jones Plaza, where a Rod Stewart impersonator was performing at Party on the Plaza. For some reason, there was not a very large crowd. ;)
I chatted with Joy and said HI to a couple of friends and tried to find someone to play frisbee with me across the street at Jones Hall.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>car surfing skate</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1996/07/19/car-surfing-skate/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 1996 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1996/07/19/car-surfing-skate/</guid>
      <description>19 July 1996
Last night when I went skating, I did some car surfing. It&#39;s similar to people surfing, but I use cars. The streets are all one way, so traffic is pretty predictable. At the top of a hill (a hill for Houston), on the left hand side of the street, I wait for the light to turn green and I start off with the cars as they go through the light.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>skated Beltway 8 overpass with Marcel</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1996/06/04/skated-beltway-8-overpass-with-marcel/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 1996 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1996/06/04/skated-beltway-8-overpass-with-marcel/</guid>
      <description>4 June 1996
Back in about mid-May I had a super awesome skating adventure. My friend Marcel had called me to say basically, &#34;Hey- they&#39;re almost done building the new Tollway down near my house. Let&#39;s go skate on it before it opens!&#34; Excellent idea.
I picked him up after work and we cruised down to his (&amp; Kayse&#39;s) apartment. We goofed around on his computer a bit (cause we&#39;re computer nerds at heart) and then we drove out to the Tollway.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Olympic skate met Kim Zmeskal and Sonja</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1996/05/21/olympic-skate-met-kim-zmeskal-and-sonja/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 1996 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1996/05/21/olympic-skate-met-kim-zmeskal-and-sonja/</guid>
      <description>21 May 1996
I have been skating lots and lots lately, and have written no stories since they&#39;re all about the same. Tonight, skating was different.
Today the Olympic Torch was paraded down Memorial Drive into downtown Houston, and we skaters were invited to skate with the parade!! I got to Memorial Park area at 6:30pm, expecting a much smaller crowd than what I found. There were tons of people on foot, skates, bikes, cops on horses, and lots of golf carts parade vehicles full of people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>dark night skate</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1996/05/07/dark-night-skate/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 1996 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1996/05/07/dark-night-skate/</guid>
      <description>7 May 1996
Last night I experienced a new cool level of skating.. I called a couple of friends until I found that Susan was home and wanted to skate. We went out west of Houston, out near Bear Creek Park. By the time we got there, it was 8:30pm or so, and vaguely dark outside. She showed me a jogging/biking/skating trail that wound its way through some trees sans lights.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Memorial Loop Easter skate</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1996/04/07/memorial-loop-easter-skate/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 1996 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1996/04/07/memorial-loop-easter-skate/</guid>
      <description>Happy Easter!! 7 April 1996
Today I joined some of my friends out at Memorial Picnic Loop to skate and have a picnic and skate some more. The place was *packed*. At first this kinda bugged me, but then I realized that the cars slowly driving through the loop made great obstacles! I carefully skated past them, around them, or between them, (not over them) at high speed. I found that essentially no matter how close the cars drove together, they would leave at least 6 inches between the mirrors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>pulling skaters is good for your legs</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1996/04/05/pulling-skaters-is-good-for-your-legs/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 1996 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1996/04/05/pulling-skaters-is-good-for-your-legs/</guid>
      <description>5 April 1996
Last night my adventure started at Fuzzies, which, actually has been closed for non-payment of taxes for a while now. We&#39;ve been meeting in the parking lot across the street.
I saw my friend Danielle, who was in her car on her way to the Jones Plaza. I was on my way there, so I had her pull me! It was pretty cool, though we &#34;only&#34; went about 20 mph, which is the speed at which the traffic lights are timed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Southside skate park bruising</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1996/04/04/southside-skate-park-bruising/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 1996 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1996/04/04/southside-skate-park-bruising/</guid>
      <description>4 April 1996 Last Friday I went to Southside Skate Park and met Ed there. That was only the second time I had gone to do vert ramps and such. The first time I went, it was inline skaters only. Friday there were skaters, skate boarders, and lots of guys on bikes. I noted that I was easily the oldest person there, including Ed, as I found out that he is like 1 month younger than I.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>random skate stories</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1996/04/01/random-skate-stories/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 1996 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1996/04/01/random-skate-stories/</guid>
      <description>1 April 1996 (no foolin!)
My two most recent skating adventures were this past Thursday and Friday. I&#39;ve skated several times since I wrote Skating Adventure Twelve, but I never typed them up. So I&#39;ll pile several adventures into one here.
Some weeks ago, we met at Fuzzies and decided somewhat arbitrarily to skate to Transco Tower, which is probably about 10 miles from Fuzzies. Soon after we began our adventure, one of my skate wheels died.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Southside Skate Park met Laura</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1995/12/23/southside-skate-park-met-laura/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 1995 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1995/12/23/southside-skate-park-met-laura/</guid>
      <description>2:45am Sunday 24 December 1995 Merry Christmas! This is actually my latest skating adventure, from which I just returned and am still feeling the effects. I went to Southside Skate Park (I think that&#39;s what it&#39;s called) and for the first time I skated some half pipes and vert ramps. This is also the first time I&#39;ve done any ramp skating since my accident over a year ago.
They opened at 11pm and a bunch of people were already waiting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>skate met Jim and Nancy</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1995/11/24/skate-met-jim-and-nancy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 1995 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1995/11/24/skate-met-jim-and-nancy/</guid>
      <description>24 November 1995 Wednesday night I went skating downtown to check out all the floats for the Thanksgiving day parade. I parked at Fuzzy&#39;s and put my skates on. Didn&#39;t see anyone out. I skated to Party on the Plaza area and there were a couple of skateboard dudes on skateboards goofing around and a couple of security guards guarding a lot of empty chairs. I talked to one of them and was like, &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>skate road rash</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1995/01/20/skate-road-rash/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 1995 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1995/01/20/skate-road-rash/</guid>
      <description>Friday 20 January 1995 Last night was my latest wild skating adventure. I skated from my house to Party on the Plaza and met Chris and about 5 of his friends there. We goofed around up there playing disc with my glow-in-the-dark Boneheadz disc. Then we went to The Texas Club, which is one of my favorite garages in the downtown area. It&#39;s like 12 or 13 stories tall, and it&#39;s *entirely* enclosed by windows, so it stays comfortable and clean in there all the time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skate with Roberta</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1995/01/13/skate-with-roberta/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 1995 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1995/01/13/skate-with-roberta/</guid>
      <description>Friday 13 January 1995 Wow. Tonight was my latest wild cool skating adventure. I skated to Kirsten &amp; Scott&#39;s apartment and Roberta and Mike were there and we all skated to downtown (about 2 miles). We skated the Blueprint Garage first. I think it should be called 777, because that address is more prominent than the name of &#34;Blueprint,&#34; a store-type thing at the bottom. The garage is 12 stories tall.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>skate accident fast recovery</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1994/12/13/skate-accident-fast-recovery/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 1994 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1994/12/13/skate-accident-fast-recovery/</guid>
      <description>13 December 1994
Since my accident, I have had an exceptional recovery. I only have a little bit of tense muscle type problem in my back. I almost have my entire sense of smell back. I am ready to skate. I went looking for a helmet, but was unable to find one that seemed quite tough enough for me. One weird thing was that when I described my accident to some guys at a bike shop, they were like, &amp;ldquo;oh, you&amp;rsquo;re the one!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>skate recovery</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1994/10/05/skate-recovery/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 1994 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1994/10/05/skate-recovery/</guid>
      <description>5 October 1994
Instead of a wild and crazy skating adventure, I will describe (briefly) the latest news on my recovery. My head has stopped hurting, my ear has stopped ringing, and I might have the tiniest bit of my sense of smell back. However, my back is still really hurt. I went to my chiropractor and she popped my back. (they call it &#34;aligning.&#34; I call it pain.) But, in fact, after the pain, my back did actually feel a little bit better.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>my skating accident</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1994/09/23/my-skating-accident/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 1994 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1994/09/23/my-skating-accident/</guid>
      <description>23 September 1994 Well, as you may have heard, my latest Amazing Skating Adventure wasn&#39;t as wonderful as some of the others I&#39;ve had. On Thursday (the 15th) I went downtown to Jone&#39;s Plaza area and found my friends watching some skaters jump 2 different ramps while *hundreds* of other skaters watched.
Wow. One of the ramps had 3 boxes stacked behind it- I&#39;m guessing about 9 feet high. Eric, who built that particular ramp, was jumping the boxes consistently, smoothly, beautifuly, capturing the attention of all the hundreds of skaters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>skate Woblong Roberta</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1994/07/01/skate-woblong-roberta/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 1994 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1994/07/01/skate-woblong-roberta/</guid>
      <description>Friday 1 July 1994 Skating last night started out lame, but ended with wild new adventures for me. I hung out at Party on the Plaza with Karen who only remembered me after I reminded her that she was the first person I talked to after I sliced my thumb and smeared blood all over my NO FEAR T-shirt. I was wearing the shirt last night, as I always like to when I skate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>skate George R Brown disc perceptions</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1994/06/14/skate-george-r-brown-disc-perceptions/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 1994 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1994/06/14/skate-george-r-brown-disc-perceptions/</guid>
      <description>14 June 1994 About a week ago was my latest crazy skating adventure. My goal for the night was to skate down the 18-wheeler access ramps at the George R. Brown Convention Center on the edge of downtown. At Party on the Plaza, I talked to a guy named Matt, I think, told him my goal, and he and I skated over there. The access ramps are about 3 stories tall and pretty darn long.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>skate ramp birraporettis wall</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1994/06/02/skate-ramp-birraporettis-wall/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 1994 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1994/06/02/skate-ramp-birraporettis-wall/</guid>
      <description>2 June 1994
(above date is an educated guess)
Dude.
Last Thursday I went skating again- my ankle was kinda messed up, but not from skating. I don&#39;t know what was wrong with it, but it *really* hurt by the end of the night.
A guy had a small ramp set up out by Party on the Plaza. This was super cool. It was designed to convert all your speed into upward momentum.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>skate pulled by truck</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1994/05/30/skate-pulled-by-truck/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 May 1994 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1994/05/30/skate-pulled-by-truck/</guid>
      <description>30 May 1994
(I am guessing at the date above. I know it was 1994; I know it was warm; there were fireworks. I&#39;m guessing it was Memorial Day.) I went skating last night all over downtown Houston. It was pretty darn fun. I played on Party on the Plaza and practiced skating up and down the steps there. One time last night I was able to jump entirely up about 9 steps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>wild skating adventure</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1993/07/04/wild-skating-adventure/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jul 1993 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1993/07/04/wild-skating-adventure/</guid>
      <description>July 1993
I went out on a Thursday night a couple of months ago and met some skater dudes, and we skated down parking garages, and through a tunnel underground that connects some underground garages. We had to haul ass through the tunnel because there was a security guard down there, and we are *not* supposed to be there. I was not great at going up or down steps, but I had to learn really quickly in the tunnel.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>