<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>tomoko on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/tomoko/</link>
    <description>Recent content in tomoko on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2019 22:07:47 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/tomoko/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>lunch with Tomoko</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/02/27/lunch-with-tomoko/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2019 22:07:47 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/02/27/lunch-with-tomoko/</guid>
      <description>22:07 Wednesday 27 February 2019 JST Actually not lunch, but after the NWTA meeting, I worked on AB and then hung out with Tomoko from 2:05pm to 2:50pm. Midori was off today, so I didn&amp;rsquo;t get to see her. We talked about badminton and Mari-chan, who is in the badmintion group and happened to be with Tomoko when she let me in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>lessons at SCC</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/02/21/lessons-at-scc/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Feb 2019 17:29:51 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/02/21/lessons-at-scc/</guid>
      <description>17:29 Thursday 21 February 2019 JST Today (and most Thursdays) I taught at SCC in Kawasaki. Naoko reviewed for her test next week. Yasu reviewed the same material for his test sometime in the future. Azusa did much better with her fluency and intonation for her presentation. Liliko asked about the brochure that has to change soon to accomodate new opening times.
After the lessons I went to say HI to Tomoko and Midori, but Midori had the day off.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>work</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/06/20/work/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jun 2018 15:14:48 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/06/20/work/</guid>
      <description>15:14 Wednesday 20 June 2018 JST Lunched with Tomoko and Yukiko (first time to meet her) at SCC, talking about movies and fears (acrophobia, claustrophobia, arachnophobia) and then lesson with Midori, talking about spot AC units which do not need ducts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>work work work</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/02/28/work-work-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2018 18:36:47 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/02/28/work-work-work/</guid>
      <description>18:36 Wednesday 28 February 2018 JST I&amp;rsquo;m on break now at JB, listening to the other class, where the teacher&amp;rsquo;s Japanesey English always kinda bugs me. But the students seem happy and have been in the class for a long time.
This morning thinking about C who apparently took my investment advice before bitcoin blew up. She quit her job and is overseas now. hahahah nice!
Then working on AB, getting three alleged issues sorted.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Great lesson in SSC after lunch</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/02/14/great-lesson-in-ssc-after-lunch/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2018 17:58:12 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/02/14/great-lesson-in-ssc-after-lunch/</guid>
      <description>17:58 Wednesday 14 February 2018 JST Tomoko did well in our lessons in the SSC. She had to give a presentation in English today. Midori does not have to present as soon so she is trying to memorize more, it seems.
Lessons were after we ate lunch together on the 4th floor. I still kinda feel like an outsider there, as if my face and Visitor badge are flashing beacons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>two hour lesson with Tomoko</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/11/two-hour-lesson-with-tomoko/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2018 17:59:27 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/11/two-hour-lesson-with-tomoko/</guid>
      <description>17:59 Thursday 11 January 2018 JST Today was the first of five 2-hour lessons this month at SCC. Today I helped Tomoko by making corrections to her written English. She plans to present the features of some of her company&amp;rsquo;s products. Pretty cool stuff like elevators and batteries, and elevators that run on batteries. We studied up in their cafeteria on the 4th floor, and then I went down the escalator to the third floor and went out the exit I had never gone out before (but had seen many times).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>