<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>silent football on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/silent-football/</link>
    <description>Recent content in silent football on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Jun 2015 07:12:00 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/silent-football/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>dream youth group</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/06/16/dream-youth-group/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jun 2015 07:12:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/06/16/dream-youth-group/</guid>
      <description>##07:12 Monday 16 June 2015 JST##
Playing silent football, with Nick and Laura D, they kept footballing to each other and then Nick sent it to me and expected me to send it to her, so I made a big show of finding a way to measure the distance to her: I searched in my pockets for a measuring device and found a short length of string and began to measure the distance to her, but it was more than 5 string lengths to get just to the next person so I dramatically tossed it over my shoulder and pulled out a pantomime string and measure one unit for each person away, and determined that Laura was in fact 4 people away from me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>halloween</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1999/10/31/halloween/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Oct 1999 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1999/10/31/halloween/</guid>
      <description>(transcribed from my diary)
31 October 1999
After dropping off youth at church, I went home, showered, picked up my friend Nancy and went to Molly&amp;rsquo;s Halloween Simpson&amp;rsquo;s party!
Marcel and Kayse were there! Big hugs to him (and dainty hug to her) Also John, Maggie, Eric, Meredith, Melanie, Steve, Nancy, my Nancy, and Kerry.
Apple bobbing contest was great fun! Boys against girls and we won barely! Steve was pretty slow and I was pretty fast to make up.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>