<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>zzzz on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/zzzz/</link>
    <description>Recent content in zzzz on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2019 17:28:17 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/zzzz/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>sleeepy</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/09/13/sleeepy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2019 17:28:17 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/09/13/sleeepy/</guid>
      <description>Crud I am falling asleep here in a mildew-stricken cafe near the cigarette-smoked Infinity Books. I&amp;rsquo;ll go upstairs and see if it is better and if I can snooze a bit.
Still not fixed my site indicies yet. blarg</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Early morning snooze before work</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/09/04/early-morning-snooze-before-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2019 07:50:24 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/09/04/early-morning-snooze-before-work/</guid>
      <description>I slept on 南武 line from 登戸 to 川崎 station today. Nice to get a 57 minute sleep on a 30 minute trip. (The train sits in Noborito for 27 minutes before departing.)
Early morning lessons on Wednesday are back after the summer break. I&amp;rsquo;ve been teaching here for some years, &amp;ldquo;wouldn&amp;rsquo;t mind&amp;rdquo; if the lessons were taken over by someone else.
&amp;ldquo;Wouldn&amp;rsquo;t mind&amp;rdquo; in quotes because that was the phrase Eriko doublechecked with me to be true regarding the lesson.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>super tired</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/07/02/super-tired/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2019 00:03:26 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/07/02/super-tired/</guid>
      <description>00:03 Tuesday 02 July 2019 JST Well, I missed the first day of the month by 3 minutes. I have been zoned out in front of my computer longer than 3 minutes so oh well.
Logged 6 hours of work and noticed how much longer it will take. At 10 minutes per line, and 400 more lines to change that&amp;rsquo;s 4000 minutes (hopefully max!), but that is just to get rid of a single singleton.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>tired after long day</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/06/18/tired-after-long-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jun 2018 22:44:31 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/06/18/tired-after-long-day/</guid>
      <description>22:44 Monday 18 June 2018 JST 5am woke up. Home just a bit ago.
Tired long day.
IL Lesson
Wendy&amp;rsquo;s Wild Rock and Happy Dad&amp;rsquo;s day with Dad and Fred and Saundra on the line.
UG Lesson
Saizeria for lunch
ooops no cash. wrote my name and number; went to the bank; came back and paid.
Hung out with cats until time for co-gender circle.
Co-gender circle. 3 people in attendance, including me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>gotta write but too tired</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/05/22/gotta-write-but-too-tired/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 May 2018 23:30:47 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/05/22/gotta-write-but-too-tired/</guid>
      <description>23:30 Tuesday 22 May 2018 JST Great Integration Group tonight after meeting a potential new man. He has been in Tokyo for 6 months and may join on the first week of June. Met another man who has already attended [New Warrior Training Adventure]() so we welcomed him into the circle tonight.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>late</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/06/late/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Apr 2018 00:54:06 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/06/late/</guid>
      <description>00:54 Friday 06 April 2018 JST Just watched a couple episodes of Rick and Morty on Netflix. From season 1, the Zigerian scammers, and then the Mr Needful half of the Pluto episode (, fast forwarding through the Pluto parts).
This was after Japanese lesson with Mel, who often gives me bonus time yay! We read a few pages of a Doraemon book with 100 four-kanji words.
All that was after eating chocolate on the way home from the station after reading Planet on Purpose after talking to Yoko after the lesson after receiving the remainder of the chocolate rabbit she brought to class after she arrived late after we had been talking about Planet on Purpose after talking about Skype after having talked about the lesson from last week after Mayumi asked me about it after not having been there then.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dirk Gently and the focused binge</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/13/dirk-gently-and-the-focused-binge/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2018 02:29:22 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/13/dirk-gently-and-the-focused-binge/</guid>
      <description>02:29 Saturday 13 January 2018 JST Heh. Well, it was pretty great. Dirk Gently&amp;rsquo;s Holistic Detective Agency was good enough that I just watched the last four (4) episodes in a row. At 40+ minutes each that&amp;rsquo;s 160+ minutes or about oh my god I have to go to bed.
https://news.newonnetflix.info/news/dirk-gentlys-holistic-detective-agency-season-2-date-for-netflix-uk/
Now it is apparently canceled, but I hope not. https://variety.com/2017/tv/news/dirk-gently-2-1202644035/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>yikes stripes limited sleep coming right up</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/08/30/yikes-stripes-limited-sleep-coming-right-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2017 01:48:11 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/08/30/yikes-stripes-limited-sleep-coming-right-up/</guid>
      <description>01:48 Wednesday 30 August 2017 JST The past few entries are dated some hours after they happened, but this one is being written in real time. I gotta wake up in 3 hours. shit shit shit.
Fortunately, I can sleep for a bit on the train. Unfortunately, I can only sleep for 50 minutes on the train and it usually leaves me groggy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>tired</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/01/12/tired/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2017 01:51:30 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/01/12/tired/</guid>
      <description>01:51 Friday 13 January 2017 JST This morning I woke up on time to arrive near Zavas at 7:45am. That lesson was fine, and then I-group online was equally fine.
Went to lunch with Kai, and talked about our respective presentations while eating at Kung Fu Panda (?) in the food court.

Had an extra hour before lesson at T, so I went to Unidy and got a hook for my wallet chain, because my previous hook broke.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>zzzzz</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/01/28/zzzzz/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/01/28/zzzzz/</guid>
      <description>##23:17 Wednesday 28 January 2015 JST##
I&amp;rsquo;m so tired, but my silly brain wants to play Minecraft instead of go to bed or take a shower. Fuck you brain, it&amp;rsquo;s showertime.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>