<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>jon on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/jon/</link>
    <description>Recent content in jon on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 21:34:24 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/jon/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>met Jon for dinner and bridge spotting</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/27/met-jon-for-dinner-and-bridge-spotting/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 21:34:24 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/27/met-jon-for-dinner-and-bridge-spotting/</guid>
      <description>21:34 Friday 27 April 2018 JST Jon and I ate burgers after we did a bit of a code review and MySQL discussion. Short answer: it&amp;rsquo;s better to loop through via code than do group+sort+filter+etc in MySQL.
After discussion, he showed me a lovely bridge across a river. It connects a building to a parking area with 15 bicycle parking spots on the far side of a river. 15 bicycle parking spots is a joke compared to the size of the building, and even the bridge itself, which features glass elevators on each side.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paola and Jon came over</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/09/23/paola-and-jon-came-over/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2017 20:20:27 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/09/23/paola-and-jon-came-over/</guid>
      <description>20:20 Saturday 23 September 2017 JST Today was the first time for Paola and Jon to come visit our house since we moved last summer. Lovely time including delicious salmon quiche, indian graham crackers (my name), plum pie, and two different salads. Oh, and we played the ball game that I do not have a name for yet, but which I got from the shop in Harajuku. Everyone played and enjoyed it!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>headed kinda toward Academy</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/01/30/headed-kinda-toward-academy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2016 15:17:34 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/01/30/headed-kinda-toward-academy/</guid>
      <description>15:17 Saturday 30 January 2016 CST Now Jon is driving me with Ma and Lin in circles toward Academy. It&amp;rsquo;s fun!
Jon said he prefers paper maps to Siri.
16:00 Yay I now have skates again! They didn&amp;rsquo;t have extra wheels, but I hope I can buy them online or in Japan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fun day at reiki and wandering around Asakusa</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/11/08/fun-day-at-reiki-and-wandering-around-asakusa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Nov 2015 19:49:42 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/11/08/fun-day-at-reiki-and-wandering-around-asakusa/</guid>
      <description>19:49 Sunday 08 November 2015 JST We attended a reiki share in Asakusa, featuring a reiki master from Kyoto. He was quite friendly and chatty, both in English and Japanese. It was the second time or Lin and I to join this particular reiki share.
Afterward, we wandered around Asakusa with Jon, had sushi at a 回転 sushi shop, went to an English book store where we bought a total of three books, and then walked to Tokyo Sky Tree where I got a bunch of gifts for Fred (in a pay-by-the-container system).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Two pix from Christmas at Jill&#39;s 2011</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2011/12/25/two-pix-from-christmas-at-jills-2011/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2011 12:46:02 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2011/12/25/two-pix-from-christmas-at-jills-2011/</guid>
      <description>25 Dec 2011 (written 12:46 Monday 10 July 2017 JST)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>pics from skype with Ma, Jon, me, and Lin</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2011/06/19/pics-from-skype-with-ma-jon-me-and-lin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2011/06/19/pics-from-skype-with-ma-jon-me-and-lin/</guid>
      <description>(written 21:40 Sunday 23 November 2014 JST)
I don&amp;rsquo;t remember the details, but I took pics!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>