<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>busy on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/busy/</link>
    <description>Recent content in busy on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2019 21:32:49 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/busy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Working today</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/09/18/working-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2019 21:32:49 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/09/18/working-today/</guid>
      <description>(written 21:32 Wednesday 18 September 2019 JST)
Headed toward home on Nambu Line now after waking up at 4:30 (after one sleep cycle) and doing my morning routine (write dreams, write gratitude, meditate, brush teeth, etc) then headed to work in Kawasaki for JB in Solid Square. Sayuri came about 15 minutes late and was the only student in attendance.
Headed to JR Kawasaki afterward to meet やなさん but he ended up having to cancel for some reason.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>today</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/08/30/today/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 16:45:26 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/08/30/today/</guid>
      <description>16:45 Friday 30 August 2019 JST Several different things on my day off today. Mostly related to work, where I realized the value of having a staging server with non-live data. &amp;ldquo;Ohhh that is right; I tested saving data as well..&amp;rdquo; when AB was like, &amp;ldquo;Um, where is the Azabujuban record?&amp;rdquo; which had been renamed to &amp;ldquo;Doraemon 5e5433a38e2b035689a75c9ed11ffb0e&amp;rdquo;
Once I fixed all of those (about 8 different records) based on the old live DB which is still available at cli with mysql as root, I watched episode 3 of The Naked Director.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>today</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/04/26/today/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 13:53:19 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/04/26/today/</guid>
      <description>13:53 Friday 26 April 2019 JST Today has seemed busy; my brain was spinning with what to do next for a while this morning. I ended up creating a new Part entry for Marble Track 3 (tssfobls) before attending men&amp;rsquo;s group meeting (Integration Group Council).
Now I am on the way back from Tokyo station where I met Tariq and Jon (for different reasons). Tariq about ConSwi, and Jon to give him a bag he left at our house.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>busy weekend</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/03/03/busy-weekend/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2019 21:45:44 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/03/03/busy-weekend/</guid>
      <description>21:45 Sunday 03 March 2019 JST Oh man I should write a SOML.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Busy prepping for MKP trip</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/01/30/busy-prepping-for-mkp-trip/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jan 2019 22:10:31 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/01/30/busy-prepping-for-mkp-trip/</guid>
      <description>22:10 Wednesday 30 January 2019 JST Just a couple days ago I got my tickets all sorted to staff two different NWTA weekends and also attend the MKP USA Face to Face weekend in Texas.
After pretty much settling on the plans, it was pointed out that attending an IGFT might give me more of the training I am looking for, but I trust this is the training / trip I need.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Too busy</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/11/14/too-busy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 21:10:01 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/11/14/too-busy/</guid>
      <description>21:10 Wednesday 14 November 2018 JST I can basically tell how busy I am by how much time I (don&amp;rsquo;t) spend writing in my journal. Inverse relationship between entries and busy. It&amp;rsquo;s not surprising, but just a thing to note.
Recently, my &amp;ldquo;journaling&amp;rdquo; has included Marble Track 3 website, and that has included revamping the website a bit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>too busy for me</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/10/11/too-busy-for-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2018 13:38:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/10/11/too-busy-for-me/</guid>
      <description>13:38 Thursday 11 October 2018 JST I did MT3 livestream today, but have not made time to add an episode.
I attended online men&amp;rsquo;s circle this morning, but was distracted with emails.
Kevin&amp;rsquo;s website is throwing memory errors, probably because old version of site needs upgrading. I contacted his provider about getting it upgraded.
I am on the train headed to SCC, but forgot to bring my tea cup so I probably have to use a paper cup (or go without tea).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lin on bicycle got hit by a car</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/04/27/lin-on-bicycle-got-hit-by-a-car/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2015 13:21:34 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/04/27/lin-on-bicycle-got-hit-by-a-car/</guid>
      <description>13:21 Monday 27 April 2015 JST On my way home yesterday there was an ambulance and police car next to traffic light near our house. Lin&amp;rsquo;s uncle was there and he goes &amp;ldquo;Lin&amp;rsquo;s in the ambulance&amp;rdquo;
!!!
Holy shit wait what?
I was so relieved to see her alert and essentially &amp;ldquo;fine&amp;rdquo; though it&amp;rsquo;s still super spooky fuck fuck fuck!
I didn&amp;rsquo;t have my computer at the time so I didn&amp;rsquo;t write about it last night.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>busy, but not too busy</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/12/05/busy-but-not-too-busy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/12/05/busy-but-not-too-busy/</guid>
      <description>##21:54 Friday 05 December 2014 JST##
(written Tuesday 9 Dec 2014)
My greatest journal reader called me today; he said he&amp;rsquo;s been crazy-busy with work and moving, but still had time to read my journal! I guess it helps that I haven&amp;rsquo;t uploaded things in a while, but I&amp;rsquo;ll probably fix that today.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>