<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>wow on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/wow/</link>
    <description>Recent content in wow on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2019 23:59:59 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/wow/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>I performed stand up comedy!</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/09/13/i-performed-stand-up-comedy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2019 23:59:59 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/09/13/i-performed-stand-up-comedy/</guid>
      <description>(adapted from my note last night to Mark)
I went to a stand-up comedy open mic tonight and ended up doing a set (my first ever!)
Several jokes went well, a couple did not; one of those is not recoverable in any way I can think of.
Soness said it was really good that I used contents of the room for several of my bits.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>kanauknot</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/07/22/kanauknot/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2019 13:53:37 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/07/22/kanauknot/</guid>
      <description>(actually written 13:53 Wednesday 24 July 2019 JST)
Though my phone conked out overnight without being charged, I was able to get one picture with these guys
 before I knew I would love them before I knew I didn&amp;rsquo;t have to wear shoes in the park  ( image coming soon )
They came out to greet the incoming guests as the park opened, and I got a picture with them because this guy was on a 2 meter tall unicycle!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>laser printer</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/05/24/laser-printer/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 23:05:51 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/05/24/laser-printer/</guid>
      <description>23:05 Friday 24 May 2019 JST Until now, we have always had inkjet printers. Our inkjet printer ran out of ink again, and I was like ef this. We are buying a laser printer.
It arrived today.
It is thrice as heavy as the inkjet and ten times as fast, a lot more crisp, and omg super great.
It scans like a champ (with its autofeeder that even worked with somewhat not-flat pages).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Misato gave me and Lin bracelets</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/02/27/misato-gave-me-and-lin-bracelets/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2019 22:11:26 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/02/27/misato-gave-me-and-lin-bracelets/</guid>
      <description>22:11 Wednesday 27 February 2019 JST So surprised when Misato gave me and Lin matching tiger eye bracelets today! I had commented on Misato&amp;rsquo;s bracelet last week (and apparently praised it too much!) cause it caught my eye, and I had never seen dark tiger eye before. Super striking!
I guess this means I should buy her something kinda special from my trip.
I probably should have gotten a picture of our matching bracelets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Go is great</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/08/31/go-is-great/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Aug 2018 21:50:51 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/08/31/go-is-great/</guid>
      <description>21:50 Friday 31 August 2018 JST Wow Go is great. The compiler doesn&amp;rsquo;t let you fuck around too much. &amp;ldquo;Hey you&amp;rsquo;re wasting variables!&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Hey those are different!&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Hey you already did that!&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Don&amp;rsquo;t include it if you don&amp;rsquo;t need it!&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Don&amp;rsquo;t use it if you didn&amp;rsquo;t include it&amp;rdquo;
I can imagine what Travis meant when he said if a Hakyll Haskell program compiles, it probably works correctly. Even with all the side effects available in Go, I am much more confident that my code works than with any PHP code.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>no bare feet</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/22/no-bare-feet/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2018 13:10:23 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/22/no-bare-feet/</guid>
      <description>13:10 Thursday 22 March 2018 JST Lazona has a new green faux grass field in the middle of the open air area, featuring firm inflatable plastic chairs, a geodesic dome tent, a sakura tree in full bloom, and a sign saying no playing ball, no music, no work(?), no events, and no bare feet.

Wait, what? No work? Maybe it doesn&amp;rsquo;t say that.
Wait, what? No bare feet? Maybe they haven&amp;rsquo;t ever tried walking barefoot on the surface.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>recreation</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/13/recreation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Mar 2018 01:46:35 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/13/recreation/</guid>
      <description>01:46 Tuesday 13 March 2018 JST 09:46 Monday 12 March 2018 Portland Recreational marijuana is legal in Oregon. I took advantage of this fact last night and had a really overall positive experience with several experiencial teachings I gained.
I am still a bit affected as I write this, sitting in the airport in Portland, waiting for my flight back to Narita.
The most interesting aspect about the experience itself was the time stretching.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Great LT1 weekend</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/11/great-lt1-weekend/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Mar 2018 16:05:39 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/11/great-lt1-weekend/</guid>
      <description>16:05 Sunday 11 March 2018 JST 23:05 Saturday 10 March 2018 JST Bunch of great guys here in Oregon for the LT1 and ST1 dual training. I attended ST1 (Staff Training 1) in Perth last year and am attending LT1 (Leadership Training 1) in Oregon this weekend. Got to meet Alan who I know from my online men&amp;rsquo;s circle, and met Mike P with dredlocks who I had met online as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>good i-group</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/10/12/good-i-group/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2017 14:09:20 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/10/12/good-i-group/</guid>
      <description>14:09 Thursday 12 October 2017 JST Great I-group today; I had chills from within when I got to yell at my dad from when I was 7 years old.
He said &amp;ldquo;if there were 100 people from your class all in a line, you would be the smartest.&amp;rdquo;
He meant it well, but it&amp;rsquo;s like hey fuck you don&amp;rsquo;t put that on a 7 year old! what is he going to do with that info?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>President Trump</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/11/09/president-trump/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2016 22:58:17 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/11/09/president-trump/</guid>
      <description> 22:58 Wednesday 09 November 2016 JST [11/9/16, 8:40:55 PM] Rob: surprised yes, but I&#39;m secretly happy [11/9/16, 8:41:15 PM] S: i knew the polls were rigged but that is an absolute routing [11/9/16, 8:41:19 PM] Rob: I can only imagine people were like &amp;quot;fuck 4 years of the same shit&amp;quot; and flipped the switch [11/9/16, 8:41:25 PM] S: yep  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>permanent resident</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/10/19/permanent-resident/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2016 22:46:45 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/10/19/permanent-resident/</guid>
      <description>22:46 Wednesday 19 October 2016 JST I now have permanent residency status in Japan.
I don&amp;rsquo;t really know how I feel about it. Good? Traitor?
After cutting my toe on the way to work, I put some tissues on it and it stopped bleeding without having to tell anyone at work. Yay. I don&amp;rsquo;t want to be pressured into wearing shoes just because of a little blood.
On the way home I asked Cine where she had been and she said a family member passed just 7 hours ago.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apparently I got permanent residency visa for Japan</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/10/13/apparently-i-got-permanent-residency-visa-for-japan/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2016 00:34:27 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/10/13/apparently-i-got-permanent-residency-visa-for-japan/</guid>
      <description>00:34 Thursday 13 October 2016 AWST I haven&amp;rsquo;t seen it, but Lin just sent me an email saying as much!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wow car was faster on the way back</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/11/22/wow-car-was-faster-on-the-way-back/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2015 12:40:01 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/11/22/wow-car-was-faster-on-the-way-back/</guid>
      <description>12:40 Sunday 22 November 2015 JST Actually I don&amp;rsquo;t know if it was faster, but it was less expensive and I got to sleeeeeeep all the way back to Fuchuhonmachi or something on the Nambu line.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New computer case made by Mutsumi</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/11/03/new-computer-case-made-by-mutsumi/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Nov 2015 19:26:32 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/11/03/new-computer-case-made-by-mutsumi/</guid>
      <description>19:26 Tuesday 03 November 2015 JST Wow wow wow so happy! Mutsumi made a new sleeping bag for my computer during my lesson with Yoshie today. I&amp;rsquo;m so blessed and lucky! When she presented it, I was like, &amp;ldquo;oh my god it&amp;rsquo;s so amazing!!&amp;rdquo; and she demurred, &amp;ldquo;it&amp;rsquo;s not amazing.&amp;rdquo;
Still super happy!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>bare feet</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/07/13/bare-feet/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2015 15:29:07 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/07/13/bare-feet/</guid>
      <description>15:29 Monday 13 July 2015 JST Amazingly, someone spoke to me about my bare feet. It was great to be addressed in Japanese, and to basically be able to handle the conversation. Just a couple words I didn&amp;rsquo;t know (maybe かど or something with こ) which she explained meant something like people talking (to me, like she, about my being barefoot).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>adaptive images</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/03/22/adaptive-images/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Mar 2015 23:52:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/03/22/adaptive-images/</guid>
      <description>##23:52 Sunday 22 March 2015 JST##
I just came across a beautiful solution to resizing images on my site. It allows me to keep my existing images&amp;rsquo; filenames, and it just works as a drop-in solution. A single PHP file (plus a few lines of .htaccess to point images through it). The resulting image URLs are unchanged, but the size of the image is adapted per the device size.
Adaptive-Images</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>super early</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/01/14/super-early/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/01/14/super-early/</guid>
      <description>##16:58 Wednesday 14 January 2015 JST##
I took an express train and arrived here a bit early.
##18:00
Chapter featured five peeps from the previous class, so it&amp;rsquo;s nice to see them again. We practiced self introductions, and I picked on Ayako a bit to help her recall the phrase I gave her. &amp;ldquo;I work at XXX as an assistant to the CEO.&amp;rdquo; She couldn&amp;rsquo;t quite articulate &amp;ldquo;administrative assistant&amp;rdquo; so I swapped out the words for her.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Just realized something about my dream</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/01/07/just-realized-something-about-my-dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/01/07/just-realized-something-about-my-dream/</guid>
      <description>##07:55 Wednesday 07 January 2015 JST##
I honestly didn&amp;rsquo;t know what the white limestone was called, but I found it with a search on Google for white stone with shells impressions
 
I was debating whether I should waste Andrew&amp;rsquo;s time telling him about my dream when I realized one of the key things I saw was the limestone steps, and the first image I found which clearly shows them is at dcfossils.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>wow amazing collection</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/12/14/wow-amazing-collection/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/12/14/wow-amazing-collection/</guid>
      <description>##02:13 Sunday 21 December 2014 JST##
Okay, this guy&amp;rsquo;s house is a bit like a museum.
He said he&amp;rsquo;s 82 years old, and has been collecting this all his adult life.
                 
It&amp;rsquo;s all just in his house. I want to get a Japanese-speaking historian to interview this guy and something something something I don&amp;rsquo;t know what.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>lunch between lessons at JBs</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/12/06/lunch-between-lessons-at-jbs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/12/06/lunch-between-lessons-at-jbs/</guid>
      <description>##13:08 Saturday 06 December 2014
(written 01:19 Sunday 21 December 2014 JST)
Wow! What a surprise!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get Sync; it loooks quite interesting!</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/14/get-sync-it-loooks-quite-interesting/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/14/get-sync-it-loooks-quite-interesting/</guid>
      <description>##11:34 Friday 14 November 2014 JST##
Wow! This Sync product by BitTorrent seems pretty interesting! I wonder where on my device it stores the data&amp;hellip; right now I&amp;rsquo;ve got it installed in my phone, but is that the only copy of my images? If not, whose data am I storing? How does it deal with spotty connectivity? Hmmmm!
Get Sync at https://www.getsync.com/.
##17:46
Oh, I think I understand! It&amp;rsquo;s basically a way for me to seed files to other devices.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>