<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>rochelle on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/rochelle/</link>
    <description>Recent content in rochelle on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Mar 2007 07:58:16 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/rochelle/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Oaxaca Report Back in Olympia</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2007/03/06/oaxaca-report-back-in-olympia/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Mar 2007 07:58:16 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2007/03/06/oaxaca-report-back-in-olympia/</guid>
      <description>##07:58 Tuesday 06 March 2007
Hello Family and Friends&amp;hellip;
I am back in the states after my 7 month trip to Southern Mexico where I spent mid July until December learning from and photographing the incredible uprising occurring in Oaxaca followed by two months in Chiapas. In Olympia this week, through photos, video clips, and stories, I hope to share the spirit and creativity of the teachers strike turned full scale popular rebellion that managed to take control of the city for multiple months demanding the resignation of the corrupt state governor, Ulises Ruiz Ortiz.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Report from the Zapatista International Encounter</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2007/02/26/report-from-the-zapatista-international-encounter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2007 23:07:56 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2007/02/26/report-from-the-zapatista-international-encounter/</guid>
      <description>##23:07 Monday 26 February 2007
hello all&amp;hellip;
It has been quite some time since I sent out a report from my time here in Chiapas. I have been working with Frayba, a human rights organization that sends internationals into Zapatista and other indigenous communities to do peace observing work, documenting any threats or actions against the communities by paramilitaries as well as any movement by the Mexican military. It has been an incredible experience and I am hoping to spend two more weeks in a community before I begin the long road home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>had to flee Oaxaca</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2006/12/15/had-to-flee-oaxaca/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2006 11:08:32 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2006/12/15/had-to-flee-oaxaca/</guid>
      <description>##11:08 Friday 15 December 2006
Hello all&amp;hellip;
So I have been experiencing some sort of writers block. I had intended to send this update last week but ended up needing some time to reflect and decompress. The repression by the Mexican government that I described on the 25th has continued. On October 29th the government leaked that they had compiled a list of 100 internationals from video footage who they alleged were committing vandalism alongside the movement and who they intended to deport.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rochelle update from oaxaca</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2006/09/18/rochelle-update-from-oaxaca/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2006 10:41:45 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2006/09/18/rochelle-update-from-oaxaca/</guid>
      <description>##10:41 Monday 18 September 2006
Hello family and friends&amp;hellip;
I am sorry it has been awhile since I sent an e-mail. I have been able to get a few pieces published and have been focusing on writing for those. I have thought about sending them out to this list but I fear they would be repetitive. There is so little information out there that each piece I write has a lot of the same background information.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oaxaca struggle persists</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2006/08/24/oaxaca-struggle-persists/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2006 11:37:33 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2006/08/24/oaxaca-struggle-persists/</guid>
      <description>##11:37 Thursday 24 August 2006
from Rochelle:
hello all! The teachers and their supporters continue to remain strong in the face of nightly acts of repression. The police and government goons shot up the transmitter for channel 9, shutting down the state tv that the the women from the movement had controlled since the 1st of August. Immediately stations all over the city were taken over. In the last two nights two teachers have been killed by government forces while protecting those stations.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>