<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>workshop on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/workshop/</link>
    <description>Recent content in workshop on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2019 12:38:22 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/workshop/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Headed to second eye gazing workshop</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/09/28/headed-to-second-eye-gazing-workshop/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2019 12:38:22 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/09/28/headed-to-second-eye-gazing-workshop/</guid>
      <description>Today is the second time for me to lead an eye gazing workshop. This will be in the same location in Dogenzaka.
It will be my first time to meet Yuna face to face! We have been doing lessons online for a while (since July 2018), so we know each other pretty well, but we have never met!
Currently 4 people are scheduled to attend, which is better than the Past Lives workshop!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Helping people see past lives?</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/blog/2019/09/07/helping-people-see-past-lives/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2019 17:26:33 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/blog/2019/09/07/helping-people-see-past-lives/</guid>
      <description>I put a question mark on the title because I cannot really prove the visions are related to past lives, but this is a fun way to guide people through a process to see what could be their past lives.
Each participant gets into a relaxed position, usually either sitting in a chair, or laying down, or otherwise sitting against something comfortable. Spend a few minutes leading the participants through a relaxation process, whereby they let their bodies relax and keep their minds awake.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Remembering Past Lives workshop today</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/09/07/remembering-past-lives-workshop-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2019 12:54:45 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/09/07/remembering-past-lives-workshop-today/</guid>
      <description>I am excited about Remembering Past Lives workshop today
(written 17:13 Thursday 12 September 2019 JST:)
Two people in attendance and had a good time! Great to hear their questions at the beginning. One was &amp;ldquo;What&amp;rsquo;s the process?&amp;rdquo;
Each participant gets into a relaxed position, usually either sitting in a chair, or laying down, or otherwise sitting against something comfortable. I will spend a few minutes leading you through a relaxation process, whereby you let your body relax and keep your mind awake.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eye Gazing Workshop - 17 August 2019</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/blog/2019/08/05/eye-gazing-workshop-17-august-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2019 09:33:44 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/blog/2019/08/05/eye-gazing-workshop-17-august-2019/</guid>
      <description>In two weeks I will be leading an Eye Gazing Workshop near Shibuya station.
To help plan my first workshop, Rin asked me to choose something that made me really excited.
I told her I would have to think about it, and a couple days later it suddenly came to me as the perfect workshop.
After determining what I wanted the final outcome to be, the workshop plan went through a few iterations, with support from Georgie, Mark Wild, Soness, Kevin Turner, and others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>workshop 17 Aug 2019: Past Lives Connections</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/08/01/workshop-17-aug-2019-past-lives-connections/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2019 08:46:09 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/08/01/workshop-17-aug-2019-past-lives-connections/</guid>
      <description>08:46 Thursday 01 August 2019 JST I plan to do a workshop on August 17th. Just need a time, place, and a writeup!
Ever been curious about past lives?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>great visionboard workshop</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/06/09/great-visionboard-workshop/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2019 21:15:08 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/06/09/great-visionboard-workshop/</guid>
      <description>21:15 Sunday 09 June 2019 JST Six people in the visionboard workshop tonight. Great teaching points for me because Rin said the day before that I was the only one who expressed interest in attending. The next day three more chose to come, so it was Hiro, Rin, me, then three others, who were perfectly balanced for each other and us. Similar backstories, blessings for me to learn, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>new workshop coming soon</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/05/30/new-workshop-coming-soon/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2019 20:31:27 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/05/30/new-workshop-coming-soon/</guid>
      <description>20:31 Thursday 30 May 2019 JST final feeling = great and inspired to move forward, connected with new accountability partner
stretch created
allow partner selection randomly
partner found
what happened at that time? How did you respond to the situation?
It&amp;rsquo;s time to allow the universe to reveal to you what you have already stated you want.
welcome to the group
take five minuts with partner you do not know and tell them things you do not want them to know about yourself.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>