<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>blog on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/categories/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in blog on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2019 17:26:33 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/categories/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Helping people see past lives?</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/blog/2019/09/07/helping-people-see-past-lives/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2019 17:26:33 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/blog/2019/09/07/helping-people-see-past-lives/</guid>
      <description>I put a question mark on the title because I cannot really prove the visions are related to past lives, but this is a fun way to guide people through a process to see what could be their past lives.
Each participant gets into a relaxed position, usually either sitting in a chair, or laying down, or otherwise sitting against something comfortable. Spend a few minutes leading the participants through a relaxation process, whereby they let their bodies relax and keep their minds awake.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Affirmations 101</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/blog/2019/08/29/affirmations-101/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 13:21:24 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/blog/2019/08/29/affirmations-101/</guid>
      <description>Growing up, we are taught various things in order to guide us toward being a fully functioning adult. Some of the messages we got as children do not serve us as adults (and some didn&amp;rsquo;t serve us a children!) so affirmations are an easy way to help retrain our brain to have positive messages rolling through.
I had heard of affirmations many times before, but my coaching sessions with Rin really helped me see the value of affirmations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Law of Attraction is real</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/blog/2019/08/25/the-law-of-attraction-is-real/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2019 19:23:58 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/blog/2019/08/25/the-law-of-attraction-is-real/</guid>
      <description>draft: true
The Law of Attraction is real, but maybe not in the way you&amp;rsquo;ve heard portrayed. &amp;ldquo;Think of something and it comes to you&amp;rdquo; brings to mind people thinking of a new fancy car, but still not see it in their driveway so assume LoA is a LoAd of Hooey.
But let&amp;rsquo;s go to a more subtle level. In the same way that my focus matters, I tend to bring experiences to myself based on my intention or attention.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to have lucid dreams</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/blog/2019/08/07/how-to-have-lucid-dreams/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2019 07:59:41 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/blog/2019/08/07/how-to-have-lucid-dreams/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever found yourself flying like a bird, only to later realize it was a dream?
Have you been chased by &amp;ldquo;bad guys&amp;rdquo; or haunted by scary situations in your dreams?
&amp;ldquo;Lucid dreaming&amp;rdquo; is a state of dreaming while being aware that you are dreaming. Lucid dreaming allows me to have more fun flying dreams and fewer scary dreams. This is how I got started:
There are a few techniques I have used at different times of my life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eye Gazing Workshop - 17 August 2019</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/blog/2019/08/05/eye-gazing-workshop-17-august-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2019 09:33:44 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/blog/2019/08/05/eye-gazing-workshop-17-august-2019/</guid>
      <description>In two weeks I will be leading an Eye Gazing Workshop near Shibuya station.
To help plan my first workshop, Rin asked me to choose something that made me really excited.
I told her I would have to think about it, and a couple days later it suddenly came to me as the perfect workshop.
After determining what I wanted the final outcome to be, the workshop plan went through a few iterations, with support from Georgie, Mark Wild, Soness, Kevin Turner, and others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>my focus matters</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/blog/2019/07/08/my-focus-matters/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2019 12:49:16 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/blog/2019/07/08/my-focus-matters/</guid>
      <description>Where I place the focus my attention makes a difference in how I experienced my life.
Have you seen the basketball video? If not, have a look:
  If I&amp;rsquo;m in a bad mood I tend to see things that are likewise bad. If I&amp;rsquo;m in a good mood I tend to see things that are likewise good.
This causes a natural feedback loop that tends to amplify itself.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>