<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>feet on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/feet/</link>
    <description>Recent content in feet on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2018 13:10:23 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/feet/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>no bare feet</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/22/no-bare-feet/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2018 13:10:23 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/22/no-bare-feet/</guid>
      <description>13:10 Thursday 22 March 2018 JST Lazona has a new green faux grass field in the middle of the open air area, featuring firm inflatable plastic chairs, a geodesic dome tent, a sakura tree in full bloom, and a sign saying no playing ball, no music, no work(?), no events, and no bare feet.

Wait, what? No work? Maybe it doesn&amp;rsquo;t say that.
Wait, what? No bare feet? Maybe they haven&amp;rsquo;t ever tried walking barefoot on the surface.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>yay SOGO</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/02/18/yay-sogo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2018 14:28:42 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/02/18/yay-sogo/</guid>
      <description>14:28 Sunday 18 February 2018 JST I was late to SOGO because I was late leaving and forgot my phone so had to come back.
I was a bit late arriving, but they were late starting so it all worked out. Haha we worked out as well. My toe injury did not bleed and was basically fine, though now it&amp;rsquo;s dirty. I was puffed by the group workout at the end, running while piggybacking Naoki, but even more impressive was him running while piggybacking me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>my bare feet and I were on TV</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/05/09/my-bare-feet-and-i-were-on-tv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2016 18:48:35 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/05/09/my-bare-feet-and-i-were-on-tv/</guid>
      <description>18:48 Monday 09 May 2016 JST My bare feet and I were on TV last Monday on YOUは何しに日本へ.
There&amp;rsquo;s a vid on Daily Motion, but I&amp;rsquo;m not sure how long it will last. Scroll forward about 9 minutes to find my part.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>barefoot in restaurant</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/04/18/barefoot-in-restaurant/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2016 05:17:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/04/18/barefoot-in-restaurant/</guid>
      <description>05:17 Monday 18 April 2016 JST</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>barefoot walking last night</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/12/30/barefoot-walking-last-night/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2015 10:31:50 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/12/30/barefoot-walking-last-night/</guid>
      <description>10:31 Wednesday 30 December 2015 JST I went from my lesson in Harajuku, walked to the toy store where I stop by every week to play with their puzzles, walked past a Japanese garden, down 竹下 shopping street with lots of people, took the train to Ebisu station, walked to my office, helped them with a problem on website, back to the train in Ebisu, went to Shinagawa, then changed to other line went to Kawasaki, then walked down the night club street and talked to a few people then walked the rest of the way home&amp;hellip; all barefoot!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>