<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>poppopchaos on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/poppopchaos/</link>
    <description>Recent content in poppopchaos on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Nov 2015 15:48:57 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/poppopchaos/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Pop Pop Chaos now has variable bubble prices</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/11/04/pop-pop-chaos-now-has-variable-bubble-prices/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Nov 2015 15:48:57 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/11/04/pop-pop-chaos-now-has-variable-bubble-prices/</guid>
      <description>15:48 Wednesday 04 November 2015 JST Pop Pop Chaos now has variable bubble prices! The price to create a bubble actually goes negative if there are fewer than 30 bubbles, and gets quite expensive if there are more than like 200.
https://www.poppopchaos.com/
18:55 Wednesday 04 November 2015 JST Chris and I played Pop Pop Chaos in the French bakery in 新杉田駅. He hadn&amp;rsquo;t seen the variable pricing on bubbles (cause I just implemented it last night or so).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pop Pop Chaos almost has a chat box!</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/09/25/pop-pop-chaos-almost-has-a-chat-box/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Sep 2015 11:48:08 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/09/25/pop-pop-chaos-almost-has-a-chat-box/</guid>
      <description>11:48 Friday 25 September 2015 JST You heard it. Coming soon, I hope!
I just need to:
 Figure out how to save users&amp;rsquo; names to a consistent var when they log in Fix the CSS for the chat box, which I&amp;rsquo;ll call &amp;ldquo;Pop Pop Chats&amp;rdquo; Add tabs to flip between chat box and leaderboard and nothing Do all the other work I should be doing instead &amp;gt;__&amp;gt;  13:04 Friday 25 September 2015 JST Goodness!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pop Pop Chaos bubbles now auto-inflate!</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/09/23/pop-pop-chaos-bubbles-now-auto-inflate/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2015 20:19:07 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/09/23/pop-pop-chaos-bubbles-now-auto-inflate/</guid>
      <description>13:09 Wednesday 23 September 2015 JST Sweet! It only works on PC for now, but mouseover the bubbles and the inflate to max capacity. Single click to pop them!
The mouseover calls touchBubble repeatedly via an Interval (repeatedly calls a function every n milliseconds). It seems that if I tell the code inside the interval to burst the bubble, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t have access to the Meteor.user() value, so the user cannot get points for bursting the bubble.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pop Pop Chaos now has rolling leaderboard</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/09/21/pop-pop-chaos-now-has-rolling-leaderboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2015 20:00:47 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/09/21/pop-pop-chaos-now-has-rolling-leaderboard/</guid>
      <description>20:00 Monday 21 September 2015 JST Yay! Pop Pop Chaos now has a 7-day leaderboard. Each user&amp;rsquo;s points accumulate by date, and the last 7 days are summed to make the leaderboard scores. This allows new players a chance to shine, and encourages all players to keep playing!
Because it&amp;rsquo;s kinda moe joe to clickclickclick so much, I might make bubbles inflate just with mouseover, and click will create new bubbles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pop Pop Chaos can be played anonymously</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/09/04/pop-pop-chaos-can-be-played-anonymously/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Sep 2015 13:54:09 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/09/04/pop-pop-chaos-can-be-played-anonymously/</guid>
      <description> 13:54 Friday 04 September 2015 JST Posted at https://forums.meteor.com/t/new-easy-silly-game-pop-pop-chaos-my-first-mmo/9295
If you have time to click click click some colorful bubbles, check out my new game https://www.poppopchaos.com/ Click bubbles to inflate them; the one who pops the bubble gets the points! Reach the leaderboard by creating bubbles with your hard earned points! Thanks to https://github.com/brettle/meteor-accounts-deluxe, you can play anonymously! Feedback welcome.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pop Pop Chaos now features color-coded pressure or something</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/08/31/pop-pop-chaos-now-features-color-coded-pressure-or-something/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Aug 2015 00:11:52 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/08/31/pop-pop-chaos-now-features-color-coded-pressure-or-something/</guid>
      <description>00:11 Monday 31 August 2015 JST Nice! Fred suggested I use color to indicate how close a bubble was to popping. I told him it was a good idea, though I already had it in mind, possibly from Travis or Johan, but just hadn&amp;rsquo;t implemented it yet.
Now it&amp;rsquo;s part of the game, and was reallly easy to do, thanks to d3:
I changed
var circleColor = function(d) { return d.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Got custom domain for Pop Pop Chaos</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/07/29/got-custom-domain-for-pop-pop-chaos/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jul 2015 10:52:53 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/07/29/got-custom-domain-for-pop-pop-chaos/</guid>
      <description>10:52 Wednesday 29 July 2015 JST www.poppopchaos.com
poppopchaos.com doesn&amp;rsquo;t refresh to www version yet, but I added a DNS entry to do so.
Also poppopchaos.meteor.com will refresh to the new domain. I didn&amp;rsquo;t worry about moving data over because it woulda taken more time than it&amp;rsquo;s worth.
Archive of the first alpha version of Pop Pop Chaos
23:07 Wednesday 29 July 2015 JST Archive of the game after adding the leaderboard</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pop Pop Chaos</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/07/28/pop-pop-chaos/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2015 21:41:01 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/07/28/pop-pop-chaos/</guid>
      <description>21:41 Tuesday 28 July 2015 JST Lin suggested the name a couple days ago. I had called it Pop Pop Pop and described the game. Everyone&amp;rsquo;s touching / clicking bubbles at the same time. She goes, &amp;ldquo;it&amp;rsquo;s pop chaos!&amp;rdquo; and I was like, &amp;ldquo;yep!&amp;rdquo; and immediately changed the title of the app to Pop Pop Chaos.
(&amp;ldquo;Pop Chaos&amp;rdquo; sounds like &amp;ldquo;Pop music&amp;rdquo; but it&amp;rsquo;s not popular chaos; it&amp;rsquo;s pop pop chaos like popping bubbles!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>