<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>time on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/time/</link>
    <description>Recent content in time on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2019 01:22:09 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/time/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>time zoned</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/03/18/time-zoned/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2019 01:22:09 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/03/18/time-zoned/</guid>
      <description>01:22 Monday 18 March 2019 PDT I vaped for the first time.
01:28 Monday 18 March 2019 PDT I think it has been 20 minutes. Let&amp;rsquo;s see:
01:51 Monday 18 March 2019 PDT yay!
02:00 Monday 18 March 2019 PDT I sometimes think I feel it more if I talk.
02:14 Monday 18 March 2019 PDT Life is Improv
02:22 Monday 18 March 2019 PDT ate a brownie
02:43 Monday 18 March 2019 PDT My dad said I am a responsible person.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4 hours to Haneda</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/01/4-hours-to-haneda/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2018 19:06:56 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/01/4-hours-to-haneda/</guid>
      <description>19:06 Monday 01 January 2018 JST Had a little nap for 3 hours or so
Distracted now watching Logan Lucky while writing and trying to remember whsat I was going to write.
While sleeping I guess I felt the plane dip a bit and it appeared in my dream
We descended and hovered down by the water down by the cruise ship. I didn&#39;t recognize any of my old friends there, but was optimistic there were some onboard.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>time</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/31/time/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2017 04:54:56 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/31/time/</guid>
      <description>04:54 Sunday 31 December 2017 -02 Ten point five hours to go in our flight. It&amp;rsquo;s 5am Sao Paulo time, and 4pm Tokyo time. I took a 3.5 hour nap in Sao Paulo and woke up around 8:45pm (and wrote a journal entry about a dream I had writing a journal entry about a dream I had) and have thereby been awake 8 hours. I plan to be awake 6 more hours, at which point I will have 4 more hours of flight time to sleep before we arrive in Dubai.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>chillin at the airport in Sao Paulo</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/30/chillin-at-the-airport-in-sao-paulo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2017 23:16:11 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/30/chillin-at-the-airport-in-sao-paulo/</guid>
      <description>23:16 Saturday 30 December 2017 -02 I think we thought the flight leaves at 00:15, in which case we would begin boarding in 20 minutes or so. But it&amp;rsquo;s at 01:15 so we have 80 minutes or so.
Lin is shopping for souvenirs though our bags are overweight, and will apparently cost $100 in Dubai because *they are very strict there&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>glass museum</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/08/19/glass-museum/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2017 17:46:50 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/08/19/glass-museum/</guid>
      <description>12:46 Saturday 19 August 2017 JST Allow more time when going to the glass museum in Azumino. Or maybe just go early. We went around 10:45 and there was a queue for blowing glass until 1pm.
I did get to talk to a couple of guys down in the glass blowing room. Was soooo happy that they did not turn me away for being barefoot. I could easily imagine a rule, but apparently there was not.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>walking slowly to station</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/10/27/walking-slowly-to-station/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2016 07:51:46 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/10/27/walking-slowly-to-station/</guid>
      <description>07:51 Thursday 27 October 2016 JST My slow walk to station time takes 25 minutes
Sub times:
 3:00 from house to first light 4:00 from light to top of valley 5:00 from top of valley to next light 4:00 from light after valley 3:30 valley light to vending and pokestop 2:00 from last traffic light to last light 3:30 from last light to platform  Given these intervals, if I&amp;rsquo;m late leaving for the station, I only need to catch up to one of these points and I know I can walk slowly again.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>