<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>gg on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/gg/</link>
    <description>Recent content in gg on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2018 13:31:04 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/gg/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>work</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/22/work/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2018 13:31:04 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/22/work/</guid>
      <description>13:31 Thursday 22 March 2018 JST Right now I am in a coffee shop in Lazona, and about to go to SCC lessons for 3 hours, and then GG lesson for 1 hour.
18:02 Thursday 22 March 2018 JST Tears were apparently shed by one of the students at SCC; she is scheduled to present tomorrow and found out today that her presentation is going to be different than what she expected/practiced for.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Akihabara for GG lesson</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/11/akihabara-for-gg-lesson/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2018 18:02:54 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/11/akihabara-for-gg-lesson/</guid>
      <description>18:02 Thursday 11 January 2018 JST Now I am in Akihabara, across the street from GG lesson which starts at 18:30.
I bought a trackball mouse to replace the one I had before which seems to just mysteriously and annoyingly not work anymore. This time I will keep the receipt because I think the old one konked out before its warranty was up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>in Akihabara for last lesson of 2017</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/14/in-akihabara-for-last-lesson-of-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2017 17:54:40 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/14/in-akihabara-for-last-lesson-of-2017/</guid>
      <description>17:54 Thursday 14 December 2017 JST After working 3 hours (5 lessons) near Lazona, I&amp;rsquo;m eating cold lunch in Akihabara across the street from GG lesson. I have Lin&amp;rsquo;s sister&amp;rsquo;s heavy-as-hell suitcase. (Now I know why gorillas cannot break them)
19:41 Lesson was great; everyone was there! Yoko, Maki, and Atusko all brought sweets! Mayumi and Toshie both did homework!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GG lesson</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/07/30/gg-lesson/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2015 20:34:37 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/07/30/gg-lesson/</guid>
      <description>20:34 Thursday 30 July 2015 JST Talking about puzzles near the end of our lesson, I remembered the word puzzles with five houses, five owners, five colors, five pets, and five jobs.
Several clues are given and then the question: &amp;ldquo;Who likes fishing?&amp;rdquo; can be solved with a little logic.
SO, I attempted to create such a puzzle for GG, but with only 3 houses because I only had 5 minutes to do it:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GG lesson</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/07/16/gg-lesson/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jul 2015 12:14:48 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/07/16/gg-lesson/</guid>
      <description>12:14 Saturday 18 July 2015 JST GG lesson that night featured a discussion of Airplane Day; they were all shocked to know three towers had fallen that day. I&amp;rsquo;m curious if they&amp;rsquo;ll do some research on their own. T told me after class she couldn&amp;rsquo;t believe it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>headed to GG class now</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/06/11/headed-to-gg-class-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2015 17:15:43 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/06/11/headed-to-gg-class-now/</guid>
      <description>17:15 Thursday 11 June 2015 JST I&amp;rsquo;m about an hour early; I&amp;rsquo;m going to look at laptops to see what I can see. I should prolly also jump on TLUG list or go to a meeting before buying anything&amp;hellip;
18:15 I wandered around a bit and couldn&amp;rsquo;t find anything good in any of the smaller shops. Even when I found things that seemed basically good, they had Japanese keyboards, which aren&amp;rsquo;t good for me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>fun GG lesson</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/06/04/fun-gg-lesson/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jun 2015 20:45:19 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/06/04/fun-gg-lesson/</guid>
      <description>20:45 Thursday 04 June 2015 JST I think we&amp;rsquo;re all caught up on checking their homework, and I&amp;rsquo;m sure they&amp;rsquo;re all greatly enjoying the class (or the best actors ever).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GG lesson</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/05/28/gg-lesson/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 May 2015 20:44:31 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/05/28/gg-lesson/</guid>
      <description>20:44 Thursday 28 May 2015 JST Today before GG lesson, T asked A (in English) if she had read M&amp;rsquo;s email. A said she had not.
I used this simple exchange as the basis for fully 45 minutes of lesson:
T: &amp;quot;Did you read M&#39;s email?&amp;quot; A: &amp;quot;No I didn&#39;t.&amp;quot; R: &amp;quot;What did you ask her?&amp;quot; T: &amp;quot;I asked her if she had read M&#39;s email.&amp;quot; R: &amp;quot;and what did she say?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GG lesson</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/05/21/gg-lesson/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 May 2015 20:38:21 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/05/21/gg-lesson/</guid>
      <description>20:38 Thursday 21 May 2015 JST Headed home from GG lesson in Akihabara. Today we ended up with 7 pages of notes. And, today was the first time they invited me to ride the train home with them. Nice! Same line so it&amp;rsquo;s convenient. I ended up telling them about KTRU and how much fun it was to DJ there back in the day. I have several tapes recorded from my shows; I wonder about the legality of putting them on soundcloud or something.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>great GG class</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/05/14/great-gg-class/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 May 2015 20:21:42 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/05/14/great-gg-class/</guid>
      <description>20:21 Thursday 14 May 2015 JST Great lesson with GG tonight; after discussing customs related to death in Japan (put money in the box so the person can cross The Styx, but don&amp;rsquo;t put coins cause they don&amp;rsquo;t burn), we primarily reviewed their homework on reported speech. I had asked them to use reported speech for a picture in their textbook, and they were great! T had the great idea of writing the original speech from which she created the reported speech.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Good GG class</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/05/07/good-gg-class/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2015 20:30:24 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/05/07/good-gg-class/</guid>
      <description>20:30 Thursday 07 May 2015 JST Nice class in Akihabara tonight; five pages of notes including a coloring page which T will color and bring back next week.
Homework was pretty focused: write a sentence for each little picture on page 49, using reported speech, &amp;ldquo;while&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;during&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;because&amp;rdquo;, and any preposition, respectively.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>lesson with GG was great</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/04/16/lesson-with-gg-was-great/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Apr 2015 07:36:41 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/04/16/lesson-with-gg-was-great/</guid>
      <description>07:36 Friday 17 April 2015 JST Lesson with GG last night was great as usual. They all did good homework, and I got good feedback that the previous homework had been too difficult.
T gave good reasoning, and I was like, &amp;ldquo;hmmm you&amp;rsquo;re right!!&amp;rdquo; and explained that in my Japanese &amp;ldquo;book&amp;rdquo; (Textfugu), the author said he has cut out all the Japanese that we don&amp;rsquo;t really need, just focusing on the 20%.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>super fun lesson with GG</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/04/02/super-fun-lesson-with-gg/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2015 20:50:47 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/04/02/super-fun-lesson-with-gg/</guid>
      <description>20:50 Thursday 02 April 2015 JST Super fun lesson today with GG; just going in to the room, just before which time I had purchase a poor-me chocolate bar, I felt all my grouchiness lift away and no need to chow chocolate!
We laughed a lot and they said they learned a lot; it&amp;rsquo;s really a great class.
This is the day I paid 100 yen each of two times that GGE translated something into Japanese unnecessarily.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Great lesson with GG tonight</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/03/26/great-lesson-with-gg-tonight/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Mar 2015 20:35:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/03/26/great-lesson-with-gg-tonight/</guid>
      <description>##20:35 Thursday 26 March 2015 JST##
Tonight&amp;rsquo;s lesson in Akihabara was great as always. The students are all eager and do lots of homework, try hard to speak and ask lots of questions. I love &amp;lsquo;em!
Speaking (indirectly) of them, I haven&amp;rsquo;t studied J in two days, even though they inspired me to start again.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>