<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>brazil on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/brazil/</link>
    <description>Recent content in brazil on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2017 14:24:19 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/brazil/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>last full day in Brazil in 2017</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/29/last-full-day-in-brazil-in-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2017 14:24:19 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/29/last-full-day-in-brazil-in-2017/</guid>
      <description>14:24 Friday 29 December 2017 -02 Actually, tomorrow is our last full day, but some of it will be spent flying to Sao Paulo. Our flight to Dubai leaves at 1am Sunday morning.
We just finished lunch after Dom and Rose taught me and Jorge(sp) to play rummy. I had never played before.
14:50 The pool has just been vacuumed and now it&amp;rsquo;s time to swim!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>11pm dinner</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/27/11pm-dinner/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2017 23:17:52 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/27/11pm-dinner/</guid>
      <description>22:17 Wednesday 27 December 2017 -02 Though I thought things would be winding down here this evening, the table is being set and everyone is having fun.
23:20 Wednesday 27 December 2017 -02 Dinner was delicious, especially the dessert consisting of condensed milk, coconut milk, and prunes as topping.
I am falling asleep here, but I wanted to attend I-group. I think most men have checked out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>leaving Fortaleza soon</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/24/leaving-fortaleza-soon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2017 06:17:54 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/24/leaving-fortaleza-soon/</guid>
      <description>06:17 Sunday 24 December 2017 -03 Leaving Fortaleza today (and my glasses, unless I happen to find them on last scan of the beach)
06:58 Sunday 24 December 2017 -03 Didn&amp;rsquo;t find my glasses during a quick walk along the beach near where I lost them. We did find breakfast buffet quite lovely, and I can make do with Lin&amp;rsquo;s glasses.
Headed to the airport now to fly to Presidente Prudente via Sao Paulo (to see our friends R&amp;amp;D).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ate churascos</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/23/ate-churascos/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2017 14:19:30 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/23/ate-churascos/</guid>
      <description>14:19 Saturday 23 December 2017 -03 Lin and I just walked along the beach from the restaurante de churrascos (sp) after pretty much gorging on all the offerings.
I saw some really neat rivulets on the beach (but forgot to take a picture) where water seems to just spring from the beach. I guess that is exactly what&amp;rsquo;s happening; water within the sand works its way out and then comes down to the ocean.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>beach day</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/21/beach-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2017 22:12:06 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/21/beach-day/</guid>
      <description>(transcribed 22:12 Monday 01 January 2018 JST)
evening 21 December 2017 Great view of semi-fragile sand dunes, but not safe to climb ざんねん. Hot girls including one with braces. OMG why do so many adults have braces here?
Finished algorithm for the app (LeSwipe / ConSwi) to deal with linking swipes to shapes while chilling in a self made hole in the beach.
(pictures coming soon?)
Quite interesting to see the waves coming in over the very-flat beach, so it came up significantly farther and farther with each passing unit of time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Relaxing on the beach in Fortaleza</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/20/relaxing-on-the-beach-in-fortaleza/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2017 14:46:04 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/20/relaxing-on-the-beach-in-fortaleza/</guid>
      <description>14:46 Wednesday 20 December 2017 -03 Relaxing on the beach, we got some delicious drinks: manga con leche (sp) for me and acerola for Lin. Mine was sweeet and muito deliciouso (sp).
A man came by with a young boy in his arms, and we ended up giving him R10 $3. Then other guys selling shirts, cashews, art, and maybe one more before we ended up just leaving instead of saying no no no no.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>headed to GRU airport</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/19/headed-to-gru-airport/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2017 10:43:05 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/19/headed-to-gru-airport/</guid>
      <description>10:43 Tuesday 19 December 2017 -02 En route to GRU via taxi from Rodrigo&amp;rsquo;s aparment. I trust we are on time; our flight is at 12:45pm and the airport is apparently 14 kilometers from here. Traffic has started moving briskly; we are traveling at 80 km/h, so we should ostensibly arrive in less than 14 minutes, so I guess we are good. It&amp;rsquo;s a domestic flight so maybe less stringent through security.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>arrived in São Paulo</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/15/arrived-in-s%C3%A3o-paulo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2017 18:55:55 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/15/arrived-in-s%C3%A3o-paulo/</guid>
      <description>18:55 Friday 15 December 2017 -03 Rodrigo got the days mixed up so was not at the airport to meet us as planned, but helped us by estimating the taxi price; it&amp;rsquo;s 75% of the cash we have handy, but we can make it!
21:22 Friday 15 December 2017 -02 Oh, São Paulo is actually an hour ahead of Fortaleza, so we are in -02.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Headed to Brazil tonight</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/14/headed-to-brazil-tonight/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2017 08:01:33 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/14/headed-to-brazil-tonight/</guid>
      <description>08:01 Thursday 14 December 2017 JST Feeling a bit rushed as I get ready for work day, directly after which I will head to the airport!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>