<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>tokyo on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/tokyo/</link>
    <description>Recent content in tokyo on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2019 18:53:52 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/tokyo/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Tokyo men&#39;s group met in Shinjuku last night</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/09/10/tokyo-mens-group-met-in-shinjuku-last-night/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2019 18:53:52 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/09/10/tokyo-mens-group-met-in-shinjuku-last-night/</guid>
      <description>(written 18:53 Wednesday 11 September 2019 JST)
Tuesday night Tokyo Mankind Project men&amp;rsquo;s circle met in Shinjuku for the first time in our hourly-rented space.
The space worked well, so I have booked it for the next three months&amp;rsquo; worth of Tuesdays. It&amp;rsquo;s clean, quiet, has cool chairs and beautiful hardwood floor. Plus it&amp;rsquo;s only about 2 minutes from Shinjuku station, so come on out!
We have not sorted out how the group will pay for it exactly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>guest magician Robert Golden</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/04/30/guest-magician-robert-golden/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 21:52:55 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/04/30/guest-magician-robert-golden/</guid>
      <description>21:52 Tuesday 30 April 2019 JST Tonight, on the last day of Heisei, Robert Golden attend our men&amp;rsquo;s circle as a guest magician. It was really great to see his facilitation, and to see how closely it meshes with what we have already been doing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>new battery and fans</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/12/03/new-battery-and-fans/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 18:30:02 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/12/03/new-battery-and-fans/</guid>
      <description>18:30 Monday 03 December 2018 JST Thanks to Lantz for replacing the battery and both fans in just 30 minutes at Loreatec. (30 minutes after waiting a week for parts to be shipped)
Machine works and is back to being quiet. yay!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>met Tariq and Dipendra</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/09/21/met-tariq-and-dipendra/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2018 09:24:08 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/09/21/met-tariq-and-dipendra/</guid>
      <description>09:24 Friday 21 September 2018 JST I met Dipendra today, a young man with design chops that far exceed my own, and even Tariq&amp;rsquo;s. He is interested in doing the images for ConSwi, our swipe game we are making in Godot.
We met in a room that used to be a car showroom, but now features a coffee shop because the car showroom was not making enough money.
I showed Dipendra how to get started with Godot and git.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>great mission workshop last night in men&#39;s group</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/08/29/great-mission-workshop-last-night-in-mens-group/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Aug 2018 05:40:32 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/08/29/great-mission-workshop-last-night-in-mens-group/</guid>
      <description>05:40 Wednesday 29 August 2018 JST The Mission Workshop was a great success last night, with 8 men in attendance. We tapped in to our Little Boys Deepest needs, then visualized an ideal world with the needs met. Where everyone has had this deepest need met. What kind of world is it? _________, ___________, ____________.
Then we went back to this ideal world and found ourselves living within it. Not only living, but interacting and behaving in new ways in this ideal world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Met Dipika</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/04/met-dipika/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Apr 2018 12:45:01 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/04/04/met-dipika/</guid>
      <description>12:45 Wednesday 04 April 2018 JST Today while I was in the cafe below Muza, a woman came up and asked if I could speak English. I drew her a map to a bank on the other side of the station, but had a slightly bad feeling about sending her on a possible wild goose chase. Her name is Dipika, and she&amp;rsquo;s been in Japan just a little bit and will be here for 2 more weeks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Created a meetup group for ManKind Project Tokyo</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/29/created-a-meetup-group-for-mankind-project-tokyo/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Mar 2018 15:50:35 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/29/created-a-meetup-group-for-mankind-project-tokyo/</guid>
      <description>15:50 Thursday 29 March 2018 JST https://www.meetup.com/ManKind-Project-Tokyo/
Thanks to Richard for giving me constructive feedback on the first version which was basically The Agreements, which include a lot of what we can&amp;rsquo;t do. He suggested putting some of the benefits on the site first.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It snowed today</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/22/it-snowed-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2018 00:34:16 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/22/it-snowed-today/</guid>
      <description>00:34 Thursday 22 March 2018 JST It snowed &amp;ldquo;today&amp;rdquo; and was 2 degrees C all day long. It&amp;rsquo;s apparently going up to 16 or 18 degrees C tomorrow.
I chatted with Delayna who I&amp;rsquo;ve known since our mutual YRUU days back in late 1980s, culminating with ConCon 1988. Looking forward to seeing her herb business grow!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>men&#39;s circle meets every Tuesday</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/17/mens-circle-meets-every-tuesday/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Mar 2018 15:49:01 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/17/mens-circle-meets-every-tuesday/</guid>
      <description>15:49 Saturday 17 March 2018 JST The men&amp;rsquo;s circle now meets every Tuesday. New men are welcome on the first Tuesday each month. Email info@ this domain to get information about the meeting location.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>back in Tokyo</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/13/back-in-tokyo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Mar 2018 16:02:27 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/03/13/back-in-tokyo/</guid>
      <description>16:02 Tuesday 13 March 2018 JST Back in Japan now, on a bus headed to Tokyo from Narita airport. This bus is cheap and does not include electrical outlets like some airport trains do, but I have a bit of charge available on my computer (74% (was 79% when I started))
Ah; I can write Japanese for my lesson on Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>great integration group tonight</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/02/06/great-integration-group-tonight/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2018 21:17:44 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/02/06/great-integration-group-tonight/</guid>
      <description>21:17 Tuesday 06 February 2018 JST Five men in attendance tonight despite three regulars being absent. Great to see men look inside to find their inner truth.
https://tokyo.mypowercircle.org/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Co-gender circle meets on Mondays</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/26/co-gender-circle-meets-on-mondays/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2018 13:21:11 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/26/co-gender-circle-meets-on-mondays/</guid>
      <description>13:21 Friday 26 January 2018 JST The co-gender circle has decided to move the meetings to Mondays so we can meet every week!
Soon the men&amp;rsquo;s circle will meet every week as well, I am fairly certain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More Meetings</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/17/more-meetings/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2018 12:22:49 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/01/17/more-meetings/</guid>
      <description>12:22 Wednesday 17 January 2018 JST We had a great meeting last night with seven men in the circle.
This month has 5 Tuesdays, so normally we would skip the 5th Tuesday.
This month we will have a meeting on the 5th Tuesday.
Soon I imagine we will meet every Tuesday and have the co-gender group meet on a different day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>typhoon coming</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/10/22/typhoon-coming/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2017 21:45:32 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/10/22/typhoon-coming/</guid>
      <description>21:45 Sunday 22 October 2017 JST We are likely to have clear skies for most of tomorrow, but a typhoon is apparently coming tonight. It will be at its busiest around 2 or 3am. I look forward to seeing the river high but not flooding.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>headed home from Osaka</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/09/16/headed-home-from-osaka/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2017 21:10:06 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/09/16/headed-home-from-osaka/</guid>
      <description>21:10 Saturday 16 September 2017 JST Simon drove me to Shin Osaka station so we could chat an hour longer. The last train for me to get home tonight leaves at 9:23pm, but I was able to get the 9:03pm train. Yay!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mypowercircle.org</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/07/20/mypowercircle.org/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2017 21:18:53 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/07/20/mypowercircle.org/</guid>
      <description>21:18 Thursday 20 July 2017 JST I put together https://tokyo.mypowercircle.org/ yesterday or so, and added its calendar this morning.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>