<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>finally on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/finally/</link>
    <description>Recent content in finally on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2019 17:37:10 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/finally/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>got AB webserver upgraded</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/09/24/got-ab-webserver-upgraded/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2019 17:37:10 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/09/24/got-ab-webserver-upgraded/</guid>
      <description>I got AB&amp;rsquo;s server upgraded from unsupported Ubuntu 12 to Ubuntu 18. Now running PHP 7 instead of unsupported 5.6 Now running RDS instead of MySQL on EC2.
Not yet running ALB, but AWS tech team is looking into why the application was sometimes throwing 502 errors when I routed requests through ALB.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yesterday included sixth walk</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/08/20/yesterday-included-sixth-walk/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Aug 2018 05:20:01 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/08/20/yesterday-included-sixth-walk/</guid>
      <description>05:20 Monday 20 August 2018 JST Lin and I walked together yesterday on a completely new route.
I chose not to go to SOGO after flipping a coin after Lin asked if I wanted to stay at home and install the vertical labyrinth game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Installed vertical labyrinth game</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/08/19/installed-vertical-labyrinth-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Aug 2018 22:20:01 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/08/19/installed-vertical-labyrinth-game/</guid>
      <description>22:20 Sunday 19 August 2018 JST A couple of years ago I received a vertical labyrinth game from the toy store I used to frequent in Harajuku on the way to my lesson with Sarumama.
In the past couple of days I decided to mount the game on our wall so we can actually play with it!
Here is the game resting on a shelf, where any decent sized earthquake could send it toppling to disaster.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Finally sent book back to Margaret</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/07/11/finally-sent-book-back-to-margaret/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2017 16:32:52 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/07/11/finally-sent-book-back-to-margaret/</guid>
      <description>16:32 Tuesday 11 July 2017 JST I finally got Margaret&amp;rsquo;s book on its way back to her. She lent it to me years ago.. like 8 years and said she would like to have it back sometime.. and then our group ended and she left the country.
Funny that after I reached her and got her address yesterday, I suddenly had the desire to read the book to my GG class.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>