<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>review on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/review/</link>
    <description>Recent content in review on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2017 23:54:40 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/review/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Alien Covenant spoilers</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/10/20/alien-covenant-spoilers/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2017 23:54:40 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/10/20/alien-covenant-spoilers/</guid>
      <description>23:54 Friday 20 October 2017 JST The human story was fine but the science included a lot of &amp;hellip; fiction. I saw the ending coming a mile away even though at the very end I second guessed my correct original guess. Holy cats they threw away a lot of equipment to kill one little monster. Why would that couple hook up after having apparently been so focused on their just deceased partners?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>review for airbnb</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/08/05/review-for-airbnb/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2017 10:27:01 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/08/05/review-for-airbnb/</guid>
      <description>10:27 Saturday 05 August 2017 JST Huge Japanese home next to parks &amp;amp; hot springs (https://www.airbnb.com/rooms/17957650) is probably ideal for couples, but not big groups.
Maybe it&amp;rsquo;s because we tried to do too much, or because Dr Wada was overbooked, and did not keep to the originally planned schedule.
It&amp;rsquo;s all very confusing, actually, but in short, I do not recommend bringing big groups to this location.
(( About a week before the weekend, my co-coordinator tried to get a group discount for having invited / brought so many (14+) people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dirk Gently&#39;s Holistic Detective Agency on Netflix</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/12/14/dirk-gentlys-holistic-detective-agency-on-netflix/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2016 09:51:45 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/12/14/dirk-gentlys-holistic-detective-agency-on-netflix/</guid>
      <description>09:51 Wednesday 14 December 2016 JST Great show! My favorite character (after 3 episodes) is Bart.
&amp;ldquo;There&amp;rsquo;s only 2 universal constants..&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>movie The Magic of Belle Isle</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/11/03/movie-the-magic-of-belle-isle/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2016 00:26:35 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/11/03/movie-the-magic-of-belle-isle/</guid>
      <description>00:26 Thursday 03 November 2016 JST Lin and I watched The Magic of Belle Isle on Netflix tonight; it was lovely and touching. I didn&amp;rsquo;t like the grouchy characters at first, but the character arcs were beautiful. Yes, it&amp;rsquo;s a simple story on the surface, but it&amp;rsquo;s got stories within stories and layers upon layers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>book review The Last</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/05/03/book-review-the-last/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 May 2015 17:45:24 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/05/03/book-review-the-last/</guid>
      <description>17:45 Sunday 03 May 2015 JST I just finished Mike&amp;rsquo;s latest book, The Last. It&amp;rsquo;s a really interesting story set in the real world, just three years from now. Quite an easy read except for the queasy parts which I almost had to put down! The story leaves some unanswered questions, and lends itself to more books, which I hope he writes soon!
I was surprised by the plot twists; it seemed so simple at first!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>