<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>movie on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/movie/</link>
    <description>Recent content in movie on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2019 17:30:28 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/movie/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Watched _Jason Bourne_ movie</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/01/11/watched-_jason-bourne_-movie/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2019 17:30:28 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2019/01/11/watched-_jason-bourne_-movie/</guid>
      <description>17:30 Friday 11 January 2019 JST I just watched the movie Jason Bourne, which I would subtitle &amp;ldquo;A Series of Events That Could Never Happen in Real Life&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Greatest Showman</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/05/05/the-greatest-showman/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 May 2018 21:26:34 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2018/05/05/the-greatest-showman/</guid>
      <description>21:26 Saturday 05 May 2018 JST The Greatest Showman starring Hugh Jackman seemed reasonably realistic for a musical. I cried twice, but not at the end. It seems Jenny Lind was portrayed more poorly than Wikipedia says, but is it supposed to make the movie better? I was like, &amp;ldquo;htfd she think he was trying to get with her?&amp;rdquo;
But like I said, it&amp;rsquo;s a musical, but apparently not as realistic as I hoped.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alien Covenant spoilers</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/10/20/alien-covenant-spoilers/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2017 23:54:40 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/10/20/alien-covenant-spoilers/</guid>
      <description>23:54 Friday 20 October 2017 JST The human story was fine but the science included a lot of &amp;hellip; fiction. I saw the ending coming a mile away even though at the very end I second guessed my correct original guess. Holy cats they threw away a lot of equipment to kill one little monster. Why would that couple hook up after having apparently been so focused on their just deceased partners?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Baywatch</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/10/09/baywatch/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2017 12:01:16 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/10/09/baywatch/</guid>
      <description>12:01 Monday 09 October 2017 JST Another comedy, chosen partially because I don&amp;rsquo;t have time to finish it before we arrive.
12:06 Monday 09 October 2017 JST Yep, five minutes of ads.
12:13 Wow I had the Easy Like Sunday Morning song in my head this morning.
14:00 Monday 09 October 2017 JST aw man just missed the end of the movie. It was kinda cute. Great videography in some places.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Dog&#39;s Purpose</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/10/09/a-dogs-purpose/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2017 11:36:16 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/10/09/a-dogs-purpose/</guid>
      <description>11:36 Monday 09 October 2017 JST Lin likes dogs, so I plan to preview this movie to see if she&amp;rsquo;d like it.
11:41 Monday 09 October 2017 JST Just for the record, there were approximately 5 minutes of ads before the movie started after I pressed play.
11:58 Monday 09 October 2017 JST I turned it off. Bailey was poorly trained.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I could not watch The Passengers</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/10/09/i-could-not-watch-the-passengers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2017 10:59:36 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/10/09/i-could-not-watch-the-passengers/</guid>
      <description>10:59 Monday 09 October 2017 JST Kinda reasonable premise, if interstellar travel were to be done through 3D space.
Synopsis: I wish I hadn&amp;rsquo;t read the synopsis.
11:34 Monday 09 October 2017 JST Actually, I turned it off after the first hour; I did not see any way it could end well and did not want to see them suffer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Captain America Civil War</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/10/06/captain-america-civil-war/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2017 12:09:53 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/10/06/captain-america-civil-war/</guid>
      <description>12:09 Friday 06 October 2017 JST Pretty good movie with reasonably understandable character-driven plot. I want more Tony Stark tech and quips but yeah good movie.
haha &amp;ldquo;Hey Manchurian Candidate, there&amp;rsquo;s a truce here, you can drop the weapon&amp;rdquo; hahaha
Why does Tony&amp;rsquo;s suit have a new voice?
Me, at the end: wait, what??</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Watching Transcendence</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/12/24/watching-transcendence/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2016 21:27:17 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/12/24/watching-transcendence/</guid>
      <description>21:27 Saturday 24 December 2016 JST 23:19 Saturday 24 December 2016 JST Hmm; I didn&amp;rsquo;t quite understand the end, but it was pretty good.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>watched Kung Fu Panda</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/12/03/watched-kung-fu-panda/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2016 23:26:20 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/12/03/watched-kung-fu-panda/</guid>
      <description>23:26 Saturday 03 December 2016 JST Lin and I watch Kung Fu Panda on Netflix, which was cuter and better than she expected. I recognized Jack Black&amp;rsquo;s voice, but didn&amp;rsquo;t recognize Angelina Jolie nor Lucy Liu&amp;rsquo;s voices. I thought I recognized Liam Neeson as Master Shifu, but it&amp;rsquo;s actually Dustin Hoffman.
Is there a voice-matching site?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jack Reacher</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/11/20/jack-reacher/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2016 22:14:34 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/11/20/jack-reacher/</guid>
      <description>22:14 Sunday 20 November 2016 JST I watched Jack Reacher today and gave it 4 of 5 stars. Good action and mystery but slight too impervious hero and a point or two that made me go wut.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stand up Guys</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/11/11/stand-up-guys/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2016 21:58:53 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/11/11/stand-up-guys/</guid>
      <description>21:58 Friday 11 November 2016 JST Watching Stand Up Guys now based on it being a comedy and having Christopher Walken in it. Al Pacino is a bonus; I don&amp;rsquo;t know the third guy. They&amp;rsquo;re driving some gangsters&amp;rsquo; car now, being chased by the police.
22:59 Good movie! Not Pulp Fiction, but still funny, though a little bit blah ending. I wanted happily ever after.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>just watched Now You See Me</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/10/25/just-watched-now-you-see-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2016 15:31:31 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2016/10/25/just-watched-now-you-see-me/</guid>
      <description>15:31 Tuesday 25 October 2016 JST Now You See Me caught my eye on Netflix and I quite enjoyed it. There were a couple of minor yeah right points (besides all of them), but generally it&amp;rsquo;s good.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Watched movie Inside Out</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/10/14/watched-movie-inside-out/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2015 18:10:11 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/10/14/watched-movie-inside-out/</guid>
      <description>18:10 Wednesday 14 October 2015 JST Inside Out is the latest Pixar film I&amp;rsquo;ve seen. It hilariously and perfectly describes how emotions seem to work in our minds. Emotions in balance lead to a normal life, while unchecked emotion of any persuasion can lead to a bit of a disaster. I love how it answers so many unasked questions! &amp;ldquo;Ohhh! This explains why that happens!!&amp;rdquo;
Anyway, go see it. I hope to see it with Lin sometime.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Starting Over (movie)</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/03/07/starting-over-movie/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2015 21:52:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/03/07/starting-over-movie/</guid>
      <description>##21:52 Saturday 07 March 2015 JST##
We watched Starting Over at Jon and Paola&amp;rsquo;s. It&amp;rsquo;s a comedy romance, but pretty good, though JP were like &amp;ldquo;it&amp;rsquo;s not going to win any Oscars..&amp;rdquo; I liked the student; he reminded me of Ferris Bueller, though I barely remember that movie.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>saw Psycho</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/01/28/saw-psycho/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2015/01/28/saw-psycho/</guid>
      <description>##23:14 Wednesday 28 January 2015 JST##
I just saw (the original) Psycho for the first time. I thought it was quite slow at first, but it started getting interesting after the second murder. The long winded explanation at the end was a bit too much. I wonder what has changed to give me less of a tolerance for such explanation as movie goers when the movie was first made.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>watching John Carpenter&#39;s The Thing</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/12/27/watching-john-carpenters-the-thing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/12/27/watching-john-carpenters-the-thing/</guid>
      <description>##00:49 Sunday 28 December 2014 JST##
I&amp;rsquo;ve wanted to see this movie ever since I was a little kid when it first came out. Tonight, we are watching it on Hulu. (and by watching, I mean I&amp;rsquo;m watching, and Lin&amp;rsquo;s taking a shower. She&amp;rsquo;ll sleep on the couch soon after she gets back.)
##2:30
Well, it wasn&amp;rsquo;t terrible, but it was definitely dated.
A review on Jinni said
It is certainly not boring, but it doesn&#39;t seem to add up to much.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>watching the interview</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/12/25/watching-the-interview/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/12/25/watching-the-interview/</guid>
      <description>This entry contains spoilers
##14:29 Thursday 25 December 2014 JST##
Spoilers ahead!!
Due to the Streisand Effect, I&amp;rsquo;m watching The Interview. It&amp;rsquo;s got some funny parts, and some racist parts.. but isn&amp;rsquo;t all that thought provoking.
Spoilers next!!
##20:09
Just finished the movie. I was optimistic that they wouldn&amp;rsquo;t kill KJU, but they did. The character played by Diana Bang was great+funny+hot!
Some of the humor was childish; some of the violence was overdone; KJU&amp;rsquo;s death was quite graphic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>watching Bourne Identity</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/12/13/watching-bourne-identity/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/12/13/watching-bourne-identity/</guid>
      <description>##00:00 Saturday 13 December 2014 JST##
Sweet! Hulu now features three of my favorite movies! We&amp;rsquo;re watching Bourne Identity now. Well, I&amp;rsquo;m watching it and Lin&amp;rsquo;s sleeping, as usual during movies hahaha</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Saw Interstellar</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/29/saw-interstellar/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/11/29/saw-interstellar/</guid>
      <description>##01:09 Sunday 30 November 2014 JST##
!!!!Spoilers ahead!!!!
I cried twice during Interstellar.
I was planning to cry a third time, but the movie ended too soon!
Overall, I wasn&amp;rsquo;t put off by the physics. Using gravity to move the second hand on the watch (but not the rest of the watch) was lame, but bearable if I replace the word &amp;ldquo;gravity&amp;rdquo; with &amp;ldquo;finger coming through 5th dimension&amp;rdquo;. The emotional parts of the movie were pretty great, though I was sad to see Matt Damon play a &amp;ldquo;bad guy&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mission Impossible 2</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/06/15/mission-impossible-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/06/15/mission-impossible-2/</guid>
      <description>6:34am CDT Thursday 15 June 2000
Last night Wende and I saw Mission: Impossible 2. It was pretty stuntful, but the plot was not astonishing, and some of the stunts did not properly conserve physical momentum.
But too be sure, the stunts were really awesome. A couple of times I could see the background on &amp;ldquo;screen&amp;rdquo; behind the actor, but not too often, and I didn&amp;rsquo;t let that ruin my movie experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>movie</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/05/07/movie/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 May 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/05/07/movie/</guid>
      <description>Gladiators 12:09am CDT Sunday 7 May 2000
Gladiators was pretty cool story, but pretty gory. I didn&amp;rsquo;t watch all the scenes. Dudes fighting each other to the death is not my favorite thing to watch.
The characters were well developed and the good guy won in the end.
How&amp;rsquo;s that for a short synopsis of a 2.5 hour movie?
- - -
After the movie, we munched at Star Pizza, where Molly relayed lots of stories of Rome and how they beat Carthage in naval battles and salted the earth and became corrupted and how the Roman Empire basically fractured and imploded.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>whole Nine Yards</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/02/27/whole-nine-yards/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2000/02/27/whole-nine-yards/</guid>
      <description>The Whole Nine Yards 4:12pm CST Sunday 27 February 2000
The Whole Nine Yards is great!! I have a new movie-actress-girlfriend, Amanda Peet.. She&amp;rsquo;s so cute!!! It&amp;rsquo;s a great comedy with great lines and visual entertainment. (Now I can see why I&amp;rsquo;m not a movie critic..) Go see the film. Good funny stuff!
Julie, Wende&amp;rsquo;s sister is here, being somewhat bored. I asked if she wants to be quoted in my journal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>blast from past</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1999/10/03/blast-from-past/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Oct 1999 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1999/10/03/blast-from-past/</guid>
      <description>3 October 1999
Wende and I watched Blast From The Past last night. It was great!
I was actually pretty surprised at how well I liked it. I thought it would just be a cheesy romance thing, but I was laughing at the situations and all the wacky funny stuff!
Given the plot, the resulting situations were believable (assuming they could in fact survive 35 years in a large hole) and quite entertaining.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>the seige</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/11/08/the-seige/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Nov 1998 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/1998/11/08/the-seige/</guid>
      <description>The Seige
8 November 1998
After church today, on a total whim, Wende and I saw The Seige, starring Denzel Washington, Annette Benning, Bruce Willis, and some other guy whose name I cannot remember. The whole idea that that could happen was really scary to me. Seeing Brooklyn under martial law made me think damn I am glad to be free. Emotion and tears ripped through me to see the concetration camp that was created.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>