<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>dinner on Barefoot Rob</title>
    <link>https://new.robnugen.com/tags/dinner/</link>
    <description>Recent content in dinner on Barefoot Rob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2017 23:17:52 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://new.robnugen.com/tags/dinner/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>11pm dinner</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/27/11pm-dinner/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2017 23:17:52 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/12/27/11pm-dinner/</guid>
      <description>22:17 Wednesday 27 December 2017 -02 Though I thought things would be winding down here this evening, the table is being set and everyone is having fun.
23:20 Wednesday 27 December 2017 -02 Dinner was delicious, especially the dessert consisting of condensed milk, coconut milk, and prunes as topping.
I am falling asleep here, but I wanted to attend I-group. I think most men have checked out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kai and Mika tonight</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/11/25/kai-and-mika-tonight/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Nov 2017 00:42:59 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/11/25/kai-and-mika-tonight/</guid>
      <description>00:42 Saturday 25 November 2017 JST Hung out with Kai and Mika near Mika&amp;rsquo;s work tonight. They gave me a stack of flyers to hand out for a show that Mika and Kai will be staffing on Monday. Thanks to Mika for sending my medium rare burger back to be recooked to well done as I had ordered! Thanks to Mama for snacks she brought back today from her trip.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>yum dinner with a-san-su-tachi</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/10/15/yum-dinner-with-a-san-su-tachi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2017 21:53:27 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/10/15/yum-dinner-with-a-san-su-tachi/</guid>
      <description>21:53 Sunday 15 October 2017 JST A-san-su treated us to dinner after we went to Machida with him and a-san-su-mei. Lin wanted to drive, which I didn&amp;rsquo;t mind until we got close to the station and tried to park. Man we coulda saved a lot of time by taking the train.
Anyway, they found no souvenirs in Machida area, but got some near our station. The we ate at our favorite buffet restaurant and talked about eating less, esp at night, and eating better, esp in the morning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>aunt and uncle in town</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/10/15/aunt-and-uncle-in-town/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2017 08:46:59 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2017/10/15/aunt-and-uncle-in-town/</guid>
      <description>08:46 Sunday 15 October 2017 JST Great to have a-san-su and a-san-su-mei staying with us for a couple of days! I met them around the time Lin and I got married, so it&amp;rsquo;s been a few years since we&amp;rsquo;ve seen them! Lin&amp;rsquo;s sisters and kids came over last night for big dinner and lots of laughter. Middle sister and I did cheers a couple times with red wine and limone, respectively.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>super dinner at Paola and Jon&#39;s</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/12/27/super-dinner-at-paola-and-jons/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/12/27/super-dinner-at-paola-and-jons/</guid>
      <description>##22:13 Saturday 27 December 2014 JST##
Lin and I went to Paola&amp;rsquo;s for dinner with some cool peeps including Jas, Rob, Rio, Ryo, and Tomoko. Ryo and Tomoko brought their rabbit, Nana; Rio brought a box of tissues. Rob works with Jon who had to work a bit during the evening.
Food, of course, was amazing, and I tried amaretto for the first time. Pretty yummy!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mama made dinner for all of us</title>
      <link>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/12/06/mama-made-dinner-for-all-of-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://new.robnugen.com/journal/2014/12/06/mama-made-dinner-for-all-of-us/</guid>
      <description>##21:36 Saturday 06 December 2014 JST##
[![杏仁豆腐](/images/2014/12/thumbs/mama made dessert 2014-12-06 17.22.05.png)](/images/2014/12/mama made dessert 2014-12-06 17.22.05.png)  Lin&amp;rsquo;s mom made about 6 different Taiwanese dishes for a dinner party featuring Jas, Jon, Paola, Lin, and me. Great delicious, though a couple were a bit spicy for me.
So funny as Jon and Jas got progressively sillier and sillier as they poured a bottle of shochu(?) for everyone.
It was hard to keep Mama seated long enough to eat much; even Lin is eating now as I type this after we walked everyone to the station.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>